<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="shrink pill" />
		<preference fetish="herms" />	
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />				
		<preference fetish="demis" />	
		<text>
		Roberta places a boot on your chest and shoves you back down when you try to stand again "You've been a troublesome squab. Plucky though." she says and slips a hand into her skirt "But you know, fight like this gets me all excited. Really only way to properly finish the fight." she says, stroking her fingers across what she's packing under that skirt..but then pausing and sniffing "mhmm, wait a minute" she says and slips her hand out of her skirt, and checks you over..soon coming up with your shrink pill "Thought i smelled one of these on you. Now where could you of gotten it.." she says and chuckles "open up, time to be a plaything" she says and shoves the pill at your lips, using her other hand to force your mouth open.
		</text>
		<choice destination="microvore0" text="*resist*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="microvore0">
		<effect type="removeitem" item="shrink pill" value="1" />
	<text>
	You try to resist, but Roberta is rather persistent "Oh no squab, you don't get to choose see.." she taunts as she finally gets the pill past your lips and chuckles pushing your jaw shut behind the pill. All you can do is avoid swallowing, but Roberta is too canny to let you spit it out and holds your jaws closed with one hand as she leans in and licks at your neck..you swallow convulsively and seconds later find yourself shrinking down. <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				you're briefly lost amidst the oversized pile of your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				that you just shrunk out of. 
				<readequipment slot="2" />
			</conditional>
		The dread pirate picking your miniaturized form up off the floor with a grin "Much better...being a plaything suits you squab."
	</text>
	<choice destination="microvore1" text="oh dear"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="microvore1">
	<text>
	Your protests fall on deaf ears as she undoes her skirt and lets it fall to the floor. Roberta's actions exposing her erect shaft before you in a way that can only bode ill. This belief is quickly realized as she lowers her hand down with you within and presses you against the side of her cock "Mhmm ah give it a hug toy, you'll be going down soon" she says and grinds you up and down her shaft moaning as she does so.
	</text>
	<choice destination="microvore2" text="*used as a toy*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="microvore2">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="herms" />	
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />				
			<preference fetish="demis" />		
		<text>
		Roberta places a boot on your chest and shoves you back down when you try to stand again "You've been a troublesome squab. Plucky though." she says and slips a hand into her skirt "But you know, fight like this gets me all excited. Really only way to properly finish the fight." she says, her stroking fingers bringing a rising and growing under that skirt that soon spills free out of the split in the front..a quite nice cock for a cute kitty, growing larger as it firms up. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="$What are you going to do with that?"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	"Oh I'm not going to screw you with it don't worry" she says and then grins "I am going to feed you to it though" she adds after a beat and reaches down while you resume squirming and struggling at that revelation. One hand grasping your head and the other shoving your arm back down. Her boot leaves your chest, but only so she can haul you upwards into a sitting position and bring your head into contact with her cocktip. Roberta letting out a delighted mrowl "Oooh, everytime's as good as the first." she exclaims, her shaft schlurping around your noggin, her tip bulging out wonderfully as she starts to devour you with her cock.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="*protests*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	Roberta lets out a giggle at your muffled noises "I can't hear you over how good you feel squabby cocksnack" she says by way of teasing and moans anew as she thrusts forwards to engulf your shoulders and chest. Her shaft truly must be swollen magnificently with you now, its no wonder she wants to revel in the sensations. Her cock ripples, taking charge of dominating you as with its powerful rippling tugs. The hunger of her member engulfing your middle all of its own accord, slurping you down and starting to feed you into the cummy depths of her sack. Roberta letting out a pleased mrowl as her balls start to bulge and she slips one hand down to fondle the shape within them "Going to make a mighty load out of ya squab, have a lot of fun me and my crew."
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="$You're going to..."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	"Oh yes, as soon as I'm done melting you into a load I'm going to invite one of my crew to have some fun. Keeps them loyal." she says as her cock engulfs your hips, only your legs left outside as she sclurps you up and at this rate they won't have long before her ravenous kittycock engulfs those as well "And besides, needy kitties love dick..and cream, they especially love cream knowing it was some squab like you who was made into it." she says as she strokes her shaft and your legs gradually slither down her cock. Your feet finally disappearing into her tip with a schlurp as Roberta lets out a satisfied and triumphant moan.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="*used to make babybatter*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, soo good...patience." she says seeming to address a nearby member of her pirate crew as she strokes her shaft and feels all of you bundled and squished up inside her sack. Her balls hanging low and heavy with her soon to be seed as she fondles herself and rubs her thighs against her hefty sack "Now..be a good squab, and become seed." says Roberta as the first burbles start around you, the kitty pirate captain purring as she strokes her shaft.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore4" text="*it's not like you have much choice now is it?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4">
	<text>
	The sack clenches around you, her hot cum churning and burbling around your body as you squirm around helplessly in the depths of her balls. The herm kitty mrowling and purring and moaning in delight as you gradually begin to soften, the steady clenching tug of her stroking off soon joined by the sensations of hands against her balls as at least one other kitty almost worshipfully rubs and kneads at your softening form in there. You can feel yourself turning pliant and creamy, yielding..hot pleasurable sensations creeping into your form..you can feel it, the desire to just..relax, let go and...melt...
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="*turn into cum*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	Roberta lets out a delighted murr as she feels your shape come apart into goopy delight in her sack. The kitty pirate before her looking up with undisguised eager anticipation from where she's kneading her captain's sack. Roberta grins "Mhmm, assume the position pirate." she says "Right away captain" says the pirate and shifts over onto all fours, Roberta giving her rump a swat as she does so before helping her tug her skirts up and expose her wet and eager nethers. Eager nethers that Roberta is all too willing to fill with her girth, thrusting balls deep in a single movement as she and her subordinate let out a delighted mrowl together.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore6" text="*used as fuel for love making*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore6">
	<text>
	Roberta seizes the kitty's hips in both hands as she begins to with her. The captain's heavy swollen balls compact and round now but heavy and large with a hefty load of cum slap against her subordinates thighs with each thrust..each rocking thrust serving to even out your consistency and bring them both ever close to the most consummate of pleasures. It won't be long now, and were you still aware you might on some level sense the impending climax with a degree of primal anticipation.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore7" text="*sploosh*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvore7">
	<text>
	The two continue their hedonistic fuck play for a dozen more strokes before Roberta's pent up lust spills out like a damn breaking. The two slapped together letting out a mingled yowl in stereo as they climax, roberta's shaft spurting hot cum deep inside of the kitty. The kitty clutching at the floor as she's filled to overflowing with your gooey remnants before collapsing into a sticky mewling mess in front of Roberta as the last few spurts are spent in her leaking nethers and over her thighs and ass. Truly Roberta has the best way to maintain crew loyalty, a loyalty to which you provided a valuable and creamy contribution. And we all know how much kitties love cream.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	
</Conversation>