<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

<page ID="start">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="special_inventory" />	
	<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="greaterthan" value="1" flag="FREEHAVEN_ROBYNN_DISPOSITION"/>
	<text>
	"Hi super valued customer. Listen, seen as you've decided to spend so much money here I've decided to be super appreciative and I'm going to let you see some of my more dangerous stock. I can't always get as much of it as I'd like. But I figure you'd like it, it's a dangerous galaxy after all."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="special_inventory" value="1" />	
	<special effect="restockshop" ID="freehaven_general" />
	<choice destination="job0" text="$Do you have any work you need doing?">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>	
	<choice destination="shop" text="$That's great, let me see what you have for sale now"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$That's super, but I'll take a look later, I wasn't looking t buy anything just now"/>
</page>

	<page ID="start">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="talked" />	
	<text>
	"Hi again valued customer, what can I do for you today?" asks the kitty bounding up to her counter at the prospect of potential sales.
	</text>
	<choice destination="shop" text="$You can show me what you have for sale"/>
	<choice destination="questions" text="$Can I ask you some questions?"/>
	<choice destination="pill0" text="$So, why do you keep these shrink pills in stock? you get many buyers?">
	<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1" item="shrink pill" />	
	<preference fetish="females" />	
	<preference fetish="demis" />	
	<preference fetish="oralvore" />		
	</choice>
	<choice destination="job0" text="$Do you have any work you need doing?">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="job4" text="$About Roberta">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="job4" text="$About Roberta">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="2"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>	
	<choice destination="job5" text="$About Roberta">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="3"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>	
	<choice destination="mainquest0" text="$I was told you knew where I could get an adaptive computation core">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="3"	flag="mainquest" />	
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="adaptive_computation" />			
	</choice>
	<choice destination="mainquestPathA0" text="$Mallory had gotten herself into a sticky situation, but i helped her out and she said she'd deliver the core">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="5"	flag="adaptive_computation" />			
	</choice>	
	<choice destination="end" text="$You've given me a smile, that's enough. I'm just saying hi."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquestPathA0">
	<text>
	"Sounds like Mallory, still if she says she's getting you the core she should come through. You told her to give it to Jehari right? why don't you check if she has it yet?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Sure, I'll go do that"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquest0">
	<text>
	"Huh, I might know. Those are pretty hard to come by these days. But I ain't about to admit nuthin' till I know what you want one for and who told ya."
	</text>
	<choice destination="mainquest1" text="$Jehari needs it to decipher something for me, she told me to say hi"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquest1">
	<text>
	"Jehari wants it?" says Robyn and brightens up "Well why didn't ya say so in the beginning, she's such a sweet thing and she has a nice big.." she blushes and composes herself "Anyway. If its for Jehari I can totally swing this. I got a friend, well..supplier, shifty type. Lives on deck 4 at the starlight apartments, goes by the name of Mallory. Go talk to her, tell her I sent you and I'm calling in a favour." says Robyn.
	</text>
	<choice destination="mainquest2" text="$You're going to expend a favour for me? thankyou."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquest2">
	<text>
	"Not doing it for you stupid. Jehari is gonna be able to use that thing for her own stuff after you're gone. Maybe even help with her condition." explains Robyn.
	</text>
	<choice destination="mainquest2A" text="$Her condition?"/>
	<choice destination="mainquest3" text="$Thanks anyway."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquest2A">
	<text>
	"You must of noticed she's a lil, distractible? absentminded? Yeah the same defect that made her the big lovable pacifist she is also made her both a genius and mentally kind of flighty. She's been trying to work on a cure for herself, when she isn't distracted."
	</text>
	<choice destination="mainquest3" text="$I see, thanks anyway though"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="mainquest3">
	<text>
	"Yeah yeah, gratitude. You're still the one hoofing it down to level 4 on an errand. Mallory, deck 4, starlight apartments got all that? and be careful down there, if you get robbed or eaten we'll all get inconvenienced." says Robyn and then with a smile shoos you away.
	</text>
		<special effect="addJournal" file="main" name="mallory" />	
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="adaptive_computation" value="1" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="$Bye Robyn"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job4">
	<text>
	"Yes? what news have you got for me? completed the mission have you?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$No not yet"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job5">
	<text>
	"Yes? what news have you got for me? completed the mission have you?"	
	</text>
	<choice destination="job6" text="$yes, Roberta has been dealt with"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job6">
	<text>
	"You have.." Robyn seems to pause for a moment, her usual perky cheerfulness seeming to faulter, but she throws herself back into the attitude once again and smiles anew even if the smile seems a bit more brittle than before "Well done, she was a dastardly pirate and you did well to dispose of her. And as I've mentioned there is the reward for it." she says and produces a stack of credit chits for you "Now is there anything else I can do for you?"
	</text>
	<special effect="removeJournal" ID="301" />
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="piratebounty0" value="4" />		
	<effect type="givecredits" value="25000" />
	<choice destination="shop" text="$I'd like to spend some of these credits right here and now actually"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$no, that's all, have a nice day robyn"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job0">
	<text>
	Robyn grins "Well I do have a few shelves that need stacking.." she says before letting her expression turn mischevious and she giggles "I'm kidding, i'm kidding. I had to see what reaction I'd get though. Let me guess? some sorta space adventurer? mercenary? whatever I suppose if you weren't you wouldn't be asking that kind of question. There actually is something you can help me with if you don't mind a little danger. You interested?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job1" text="$I'm listening kitty"/>
	<choice destination="job0A" text="$I was kind of hoping you just needed some shelves stacked actually"/>
	<choice destination="job0B" text="$Not interested I'm afraid."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job1">
	<text>
	"Oooh all serious, i like that. Only my friends get to call me kitty though. Anyway. Though I appear a humble shopkeep I have connections, people who can keep me in stock in these adverse times. Trouble is they're off station, and pirates keep on attacking the shipments..also they're eating my potential customers, which is kind of bad for business...anyway, one in particular is particularly bold. Goes by the title of the dread pirate roberta, I'll reward you generously if you get rid of her."
	</text>
	<choice destination="job2" text="$And where might I find this dread pirate?"/>
	<choice destination="job1A" text="$Why this pirate in particular?"/>
	<choice destination="job1B" text="$I think I'll pass on this one for now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job2">
	<text>
	"You can find her in the Forakis system. It's pretty much a back water, I know a few people who sell guns to the liongirls on the 1st world but otherwise there's not too much of interest to merchants like me. The system is located at 1,1 in your coordinates system. You should be able to jump fine from in system coordinates 32,0 to get there. She'll be easy to spot, she'll be in the darker coloured sloop, something about striking fear into the hearts of her prey or something. Anyway, taking the job?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job3" text="$Yes, I'll get rid of this pirate for you"/>	
	<choice destination="job2A" text="$No, I'm not interested in this job"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job3">
	<text>
	"Excellent. I look forward to hearing of your success." she says and smiles "want to do any shopping before you begin?"
	</text>
	<special effect="addJournal" file="freehaven" name="dreadpirate0"/>
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="piratebounty0" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="shop" text="$yes, let me browse a little"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$thankyou for the offer but I should get started"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job2A">
	<text>
	"Oh..well, if you change your mind you know where to find me." Robyn takes this in stride and shrugs, settling back.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I might, but for now I have other business"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job1A">
	<text>
	"Cause she's more dangerous than the others? listen, you're just going to have to trust me I have damned good reasons and go get rid of her. I'm agreeing to pay you to do this after all, thought mercenaries were supposed to be discreet about these sort of things. So you interested or not?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job2" text="$I'm interested, where will i find her?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I'm going to have to pass on this one Robynn"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job0A">
	<text>
	"Yeah?" she says and then bemusedly shakes her head "Well Like I said I was kidding about that, I do all my own stock management and I don't need that kind of help. If you're down on your luck and need credits that bad but don't like danger maybe you can find some other way to make some credits on station though?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="shop" text="$maybe, but i'm not so hard up for credits I can't do a little browsing first"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Yeah maybe I'll do that."/>
	</page>
	
	
	<page ID="pill0">
	<text>
	"Oh, well. There's you, so maybe you should tell me why you bought one. Unless it's just idle curiousity." she says and smiles playfully "I stock them purely to see who might buy something that has no other purpose than to make them tiny and easy to dominate and devour."
	</text>
	<choice destination="pill1" text="$And why are you so interested in people who, might have such an interest?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I've heard enough"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pill1">
	<text>
	"Because I'm a playful kitty..and sometimes, i want someone i can play catch and eat with." she says and licks her lips suggestively.
	</text>
	<choice destination="pill2" text="$catch and eat huh, sounds fun"/>
	<choice destination="pillExit" text="$I don't like the idea of being toyed with"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pill2">
	<text>
	"Oh joy i found another mousie!" she says with a giggle and smiles, then pats her counter meaningfully "Just hop up and take the pill and we can get started."
	</text>
	<choice destination="pill3" text="*pop up on the counter and take the pill*"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$ah, this is going a bit fast, i'm gonna pass for now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pill3">
	<text>
	Robyn grins as you scoot yourself up onto the counter, tail swishing with anticipation as you pop the pill in your mouth and then within moments begin shrinking down. <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				your clothing piling around you as you shrink down to bitesize.
	</conditional>
	Once you're nice and tiny you see Robyn loom over you, a delighted smile on her face as it's clear she really enjoys these sorts of moments "mhmm, you're so cute like this." she says, leaning up over the counter, you can feel her breath as powerful wafts and see her tail flicking eagerly back and forth when you can glimpse it past her..but soon her face is becoming all that you can see..
	</text>
	<effect type="removeitem" item="shrink pill" value="1" />
	<choice destination="playA0" text="*make a run for it*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="playA0">
	<text>
	You make a dash for it across her counter, and hear her giggle, reaching out to snatch your naked little form up off the surface "gotcha!" she says and hoists you easily into the air, dangling you in front of her smiling face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="$Thought you wanted to play mousie"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"I said I sometimes did, sometimes it's enough to gobble up a little treat and know they're helpless inside me...and it's been a while, you wouldn't take me for an impulsive person though right?" she asks, but doesn't wait for you to answer..her mouth opening up as she tilts her head back, her warm wet breath washing over you as she lowers you past her lips. Her tongue undulating against you to press you up against the roof of her mouth and sample you as she pulls her fingers away and closes her mouth. Those teeth of hers sealing you in as she rolls you around in her mouth, tasting your body and brushing your feet against the entrance of her throat.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*treated like candy*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	You try to push against her tongue only to find it overwhelming as she mashes you against the inside of her mouth, being a bit rough with you at your small and delicate size. Your squirms just making her purr, a loud hum of her pleasure thrumming around you as her tongue laps between your legs, down your front only for her to press you into one cheek and turn you around afore sampling the flavour of your other side.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*and then*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Robyn plays with you with her tongue for a few more moments, before tipping her head back.. your legs pressing against the entrance of her throat afore she swallows, closing her eyes as you plunge into her throat. The catgirl pressing a finger against her neck to feel the lump of your body vanishing down into her. That tight throat pressing around you as your tiny body is conveyed steadily and inexorably down into the depths of her belly, plunging abruptly through a sphincter and dropping into her tummy. The kitty letting out a giggle as she presses her fingers against her middle "It's roomier when you're that size isn't it.. i can feel you moving around in me." she says as you got to your feet in her stomach and tried to push out, but were unable to make even a dent in her tummy walls, not a bulge or trace of your presence inside her. You're hidden away in the kitty girl as a snack.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="*digestion*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	You try to respond to her, but she's not able to hear someone so tiny over the gurgles of her gut as her enzymes begin to flow in and ooze from her stomach walls. Robyn getting comfortable as you look at the rising level of digestive fluids. It's a bit late to have second thoughts about being her snack though, the enzymes eating away at your legs as they rise up your thighs, digesting you rapidly as you feel her drum her fingers on her tummy. Abruptly your legs give way under you sending you crash into the fluid, a submersion into her potent stomach acids that you don't emerge from. Dunked into the fluids you break down in record time, only a mass of chunky ooze rising up the surface where you'd vanished within about a minute. Robyn smacking her lips and letting out a sigh as she feels her snack dissolve, mousie really is the best game to play with people.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="pillExit">
	<text>
	"It's not for everyone, but you wouldn't of been the first to be my little mouse if you'd of said yes." says Robynn, giving a wink and a smile. She seems to take the rejection in stride.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$good thing there's no hard feelings, farewell"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	You try to get the shopkeeper's attention and pry it away from the beeping device. It takes but a moment for her to notice you and she taps a button and carelessly tosses the device to one side bounding up as she shifts gear in the span of a breath and unleashes smiling cuteness on you "Nyah welcome to Robyn's emporium of general goods and supplies. I'm Robyn the proprietor and how can I help you today?" 
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
	<choice destination="shop" text="$You can show me what you have for sale"/>
	<choice destination="job0" text="$Do you have any work you need doing?">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="piratebounty0" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="questions" text="$Can I ask you some questions?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I'm happy to make your acquaintance, but I'll see what you're selling another time"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="questions">
	<text>
	"Sure, I got time."
	</text>
	<choice destination="about" text="$Can I ask a bit about you? you seem a bit 'young' for this"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I have no questions at the moment"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="about">
	<text>
	Robyn takes the comment on her air of immaturity in stride "Yeah I get that a lot. You ever hear knowledge is power? well, I inherited a bunch of that from mom. And I came here cause the wardens'd keep folks from taking it from me."
	</text>
	<choice destination="knowledge" text="$What sort of knowledge?"/>
	<choice destination="past" text="$What did you do before settling down here?"/>
	<choice destination="shop" text="$Thanks Robyn, I'd like to see what you for sale now"/>
	<choice destination="questions" text="$Can I ask more questions?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$thanks for telling me Robyn, that's all I wanted to know"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="past">
	<text>
	"That was another life, more exciting certainly. But a lot more dangerous. Lets just say I had my fill of a mis-spent youth and running the risk of ending up padding an ass on a daily basis started to wear on me."	
	</text>
	<choice destination="shop" text="$Thanks Robyn, I'd like to see what you for sale now"/>
	<choice destination="questions" text="$Can I ask more questions?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$thanks for telling me Robyn, that's all I wanted to know"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="knowledge">
	<text>
	"Contacts. Who does what and where. You'd be amazed how hard it is to get your hands on some things if you don't know who is still producing them."
	</text>
	<choice destination="shop" text="$Thanks Robyn, I'd like to see what you for sale now"/>
	<choice destination="questions" text="$Can I ask more questions?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$thanks for telling me Robyn, that's all I wanted to know"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="shop">
	<text>
	</text>
		<special effect="shop" ID="freehaven_general" />	
	</page>
	
</Conversation>