<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1" flag="digestion" />
	<text>
	The green elfin girl packing extra looks at you approach and then doubletakes, glances down. Then back to you and takes a step back "but..."
	</text>
	<choice destination="explaination0" text="surprised? I come back"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="explaination0">
	<text>
	"YES! I turned you into cum! and now you're in front of me, of course I'm surprised." Neri says throwing her arms up to try and exaggerate her shock even further.
	</text>
	<choice destination="explaination1" text="calm down, i'm not holding any hard feelings"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="explaination1">
	<text>
	"You're not mad?..well, i suppose that's good...was it fun?" she asks with a headtilt and a smile, pondering this revelation of reforming cockfood.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="2" />	
	<choice destination="explaination2" text="yes actually, I enjoyed it a lot"/>
	<choice destination="altStart" text="Let's just put it behind us and act like everything is normal"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="explaination2">
	<text>
	"ooh, well then. anytime you want to be cum just tell me and i'll happily melt ya down again."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="sackslut" value="1" />
	<choice destination="end" text="mhmm, i'll have to take you up on that sometime."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="altStart">
	<text>
	"alright so, what do you want?" 
	</text>
	<choice destination="agree" text="I need another thorough wellcum" />
	<choice destination="end" text="nothing right now" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"
			flag="talked" />
		<text>
			The green elfin girl packing extra seems to be happy to see you as she
			greets you with a bounce and a smile "Hi I'm Neri, the official
			greeter for the village of Minyos." She says, something twitching
			under her skirt as she seems to pre-empt your next question and
			plough ahead before you can say anything "that means its my job to
			schlurp new visitors into my balls as part of the official Minyos
			welcome. You look like you need a welcoming wouldn't you agree?"
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
		<choice destination="agree" text="agree" />
		<choice destination="refuse" text="disagree" />
		<choice destination="question0" text="I don't believe you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="talked" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0" flag="insulted" />	
		<text>
			"Oh hi, it's you again. You ready to be welcomed to the village yet? I'm
			not doing very good at my job if I don't welcome every visitor the
			village has. Especially ones as delightful as you."
		</text>
		<choice destination="agree" text="yes" />
		<choice destination="end" text="no, bye" />
		<choice destination="question0" text="I dont think that's how you welcome someone"/>
	</page>


	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="2"
			flag="talked" />
		<text>
			"Oh hi again, nice to see you. Hope you've been enjoying yourself here.
			Anything I can do to help you?" asks Neri fondling herself through
			her skirt lightly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="agree" text="I need another welcome" />
		<choice destination="question0" text="I'm not sure that's the official greeting"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="well bye" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="question0">
	<text>
	"I am totally the official greeter of the village, and it is totally the official welcome to the village that I put you in my sack. you're an outsider, who are you to question our ways?" Neri huffs, getting defensive at being called on this.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore0" text="you're right, who am i to question, maybe i need another welcome to really get it"/>
	<choice destination="question2" text="Well it's not the only type of greeting right? what else can you do with that thing"/>
	<choice destination="question1" text="I think you're just trying to trick me so you can turn me into your cum"/>
	<choice destination="insult" text="I think you're just lying to get me as your cum, and i'm not falling for it"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="question1">
	<text>
	"No i'm not tricking you, i mean I'm the official greeter. and even if i was tricking ya what of it, so what if i might want to churn ya?" she says, apparently not that good at this whole deception thing as she immediately falls back to a negotiating position instead.
	</text>
	<choice destination="insult" text="I think it's deplorable of you, and I'm not falling for it."/>
	<choice destination="cockvore0Alt" text="actually, i think the idea of getting churned into cum by you is pretty hot"/>
	</page>
		
	<page ID="cockvore0Alt">
	<text>
	"...geeze if i knew you'd of been okay with it I'd of just come out and said I wanted to make you my next load." says Neri giggling and rubbing the back of her head thoughtfully as she realizes her deception had been unnecessary. She realizes quickly though that she's wasting time and instead starts rubbing her cock, hand slid inside her skirt as she strokes herself to hardness then strikes her best smile "So, want to be my next load?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1Alt" text="absolutely, schlurp me up and churn me away"/>
	<choice destination="cockvore1AltRefuse" text="actually, i'm kinda just teasing ya, so no"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1Alt">
	<!--headfirst-->
	<text>
	"You're an eager one." she says with a grin and drops her skirt, unveiling that thick greenskinned elf cock of hers. <conditional>Neri waiting patiently for her willing cockfood to undress before proceeding now you're nice and naked and ready to get creamy.<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" /></conditional> She looks at your expression for a few moments then giggles again "Ready? cause I am" she asks rhetorically as she doesn't wait for a reply before reaching out to place a hand around your head and ease you down in front of her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2Alt" text="more than ready, why aren't ya shoving me in yet"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2Alt">
	<text>
	Neri giggles a bit "alright alright, i get it, ya impatient." she says and does as you say, shoving your eager head into the tip of her voracious cock. Neri lets out a gasp as her shaft bulges and stretches around your noggin and clenches to tug and schlurp you in "mhmm, i dunno if this'd be hotter if you thought I weren't gonna melt ya but...oh who cares." she puts deeds to her words and thrusts her hips, schlorping your shoulders into her tip as well now as she sets about humping your kneeling form into her cock in earnest.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3Alt" text="*get schlurped up*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3Alt">
	<text>
	Neri moans as she works over your upper body, thrusting your head deep into her shaft with her steady hip movements. You can feel hot pre and the clenching throbbing heat of her shaft press around your form all the way down to your waist. The intoxicating heady musk flooding your nose as you get closer and closer to the base of her cock and below that her awaiting sack. The thought is enough to make you squirm and push forwards eagerly, wanting in so you can enjoy being melted and churned by the elf.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore4Alt" text="rest of the way"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4Alt">
	<text>
	Neri's balls let out a little burble as you start to slide headfirst into them and displace her cum. the thick gooey cream covering every inch of your face	<conditional>
	<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="hair" /> and matting your <macro id="hair_desc_short" /> hair </conditional> as you dunk slowly into it and start to stretch and bulge out her sack "mhmm. You feel good in me traveller." she teases with a mhmm as she strokes her hands along her girl swollen shaft and steadily pulls your legs into her shaft. More of you steadily piles into her sack, starting to curl in those wonderfully lewd confines that will soon churn you down into a wonderful load of cum for the elf. Neri watches your feet through half lidded eyes as they wave around slowly in the air and approach her tip. Her balls sagging low and swelling out massively with your shape, becoming all the more well defined and exquisite as she finishes devouring you with her cock. Neri fondling her shaft as she feels your legs slide down into her sack to join the rest of you "Mhmm, you were wise to come to me you know. You make excellent cockfood." Neri teases and grins as she slides one hand down between her thighs to rub over the huge bulge you're making in her balls. The sensation all the better for how it rubs hot cum into your already jizz coated form.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5Alt" text="yes, yes i am, now...churn me, i want to be made into..nutbutter"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5Alt">
	<text>
	Neri hears your lust addled plea and smiles "mhmm that's the plan." she says and giggles as she gets comfortable sat down with her legs spread around the bulge you make in her loins. Neri steadily rubbing over her sack as her balls begin to burble and churn to start working you down "there we go, here we go. You'll be good cum" she says and just luxuriates in the sensation, soon in a half sprawled out position as time passes. The elf apparently enjoying your moaning squirms as you marinate in a hot cumbath deep in her balls. You're inside her, and you're melting, your hands rubbing against the inside of her sack find her flesh yielding less as you weaken and soften until you find that your hands are wonderfully liquidating and melting away. Your fingers mooshing against the inside of her sack until they melt away, wonderful, imagining how her balls must look starting to round out as you relax and feel your form starting to lose definition and spread out into the surrounding cum. It feels, wonderful...
	</text>
	<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="1" />		
	<choice destination="cockvoreAltGO" text="..burble"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvoreAltGO">
	<text>
	Under her teasing hand you have your final moments, the exquisite dissolution the last sensation you experience as you entirely melt away into thick and sloshing cum in Neri's balls. Neri smiles and rubs her thighs against her sack, feeling the contents slosh and displace fluidly "We both got what we wanted traveller...mmhmm" she exclaims in delight and her hands slide to her satiated cock. She starts to jerk off, slowly at first as she enjoys the full feeling but then faster when the massive load you've made starts to assert a needy pressure. The elf jacking off all the more with a moan as the need to cum and waste your goopy remains on the ground becomes all consuming. And finally, both of you accomplished your goals. Neri letting out a shuddering moan as she climaxes, eyes rolling back in her head as she starts spurting and splattering out her load. And you get ejaculated out of her to form a hot steaming puddle of pleasure fluid in front of her.
	</text>
	
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1AltRefuse">
	<text>
	Neri facefaults, she seems to take a few moments to collect "hyah! you! ngh!" and now the spasms of incoherence in place of a retort, and finally she huffs "You have a cruel sense of humour, you know that right?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Yeah, but your reaction was comedy gold, bye"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="question2">
	<text>
	"I dunno why you think you know more than I do about our tribe and all...but what exactly are you proposing?" asks Neri, frowning but looking at you askance in an expectant fashion as she wonders where you're going with this.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF0" text="well, I'm looking to become a ,Member, in the tribe. If you catch my meaning">
	<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="think on it a bit, i'll come back another time"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF0">
	<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="ratquest" value="5" />	
	<text>
	Neri blinks "What do you...oooh" Neri gasps as you grab her crotch and suggestively stroke over her shaft, she glances in the direction of the alchemist's hut questioningly. Then meets your eyes, she clearly didn't expect you to be this perverted and submissive. She blushes all the heavier as she realizes you're serious, but then looks apologetic "I dunno where you heard we could do that, but we can only do that with some stuff the alchemist whips up, and she doesn't have any right now."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="really? damn, i was looking forward to swaying between your legs"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF0">
	<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="ratquest" value="5" />	
	<text>
	Neri blinks "What do you...oooh" Neri gasps as you grab her crotch and suggestively stroke over her shaft, she glances in the direction of the alchemist's hut questioningly. Then meets your eyes, she clearly didn't expect you to be this perverted and submissive. She blushes all the heavier as she realizes you're serious "ooh, you're...well, as the greeter I think I know the thing to make you into a very firm and dependable part of the tribe." she says and then giggles "You're such a naughty traveller, I've never actually cock'd someone before."
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF1" text="first time for everything"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF1">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, I'll be right back, don't go anywhere or you won't go under my skirt." she says and gives you a mischevious smooch afore dashing off, probably to ask the alchemist if she can have something that'll let her integrate you into the tribe. It takes a few minutes but she comes back in remarkably little time all told. Her erection bobbing and swaying visibly as she seems to have a bit of a stiffy at the thought of what's to come "Guess you didn't have any second thoughts." she says and motions you over with her as she takes a seat on a log, baring her cock with one hand then deftly flicking the cap off the jar she'd come back from the alchemist with. That done she sets about lubing her cock up with the goop from the jar "all you gotta do is plant yourself on it and...mhmm, well you can guess what happens next right."<conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
	she explained as you undressed so you can adopt your new look.		
	</conditional>	
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF2" text="*sit on her cock*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF2">
	<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
	<text>
	Neri lets out a moan as you plant yourself on her cock without hesitation. Your nethers stretching around the shaft you're wanting to become as you sheathe her within your warmth and feel her arms wrapping around you from behind. She seems entirely at ease with cocking you right here out in the open and you can't help but become rather blaise to the prospect of anyone watching. The elf smiling as she wriggles a bit underneath you, then lets out a mmhmm and patpats "it's starting." she teases, as if you don't know. A gasp coaxed from your lips as her veins start to take root in soft nethers, anchoring your pussy to her shaft and starting the process of changing you into more pipe for her to swing.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF3" text="yes, cock me Neri, make me a part of you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF2">
	<text>
	Neri lets out a moan as you plant yourself on her cock without hesitation. Your tight ass stretching around the shaft you're wanting to become as you sheathe her within your warm rear end and feel her arms wrapping around you from behind. She seems entirely at ease with cocking you right here out in the open and you can't help but become rather blaise to the prospect of anyone watching. The elf smiling as she wriggles a bit underneath you, then lets out a mmhmm and patpats "it's starting." she teases, as if you don't know. A gasp coaxed from your lips as her veins start to take root in your bowels, anchoring your rump to her shaft and starting the process of changing you into more pipe for her to swing.	
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF3" text="yes, cock me Neri, make me a part of you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF3">
	<text>
	"Mhmm yes, you'll be a wonderful cock." she agrees and strokes her hands over you. Neri feeling you get veiny and more sensitive under her palms as she cockifies you right out in the open. Your legs starting to feel warm, limp and soft as they begin to change and simplify. Your legs destined to become a nice pair of plump and virile balls for the elf. Your feet clump together and you curl your legs upwards to let them stick together then turn boneless and round. Neri lets out a gasp and giggle as she feels that, stroking approvingly over her new sack as the transitions finish "so fertile, i'm gonna fill so many holes with you."
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF4" text="something to look forward to, use me lots as your fuckstick"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF4">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, shame you won't be able to talk dirty when you're my dick." says Neri with a chuckle and smooches the nape of your neck, gasping at how that feels as the sensitivity and shared sensations of your transformation has made it that far. You start to answer but then feel hot precum pulse up your throat and drool out from your lips, silencing your witty banter. But then dicks aren't known for their witty banter, so you stop trying to talk. Instead you press your arms against your flanks helpfully to let the simplification of your upper body claim them, merging them into your flanks as your innards simplify and turn into cumtube and throbbing cockflesh. The sensations are wonderful "Won't be long now my new cock, any last words?" asks Neri teasingly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF5" text="SPLGH!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF5">
	<text>
	Neri giggles "I agree completely" she says as the changes reach your head and shoulders. Your neck puffing out into folds of foreskin as your eyes and nose shrink away. Your face simplifying into the bell of her glans while continuing to splutter and drool hot precum. Her hands energetically stroking over her new cock as the last of you transforms, your <macro id="skin_colour_desc" /> skin is utterly overtaken by her own emerald hues.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTFGO" text="*twitch, throb*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="CTFGO" noReform="true">
	<text>
	Neri groans in delight as she strokes over her new cock, admiring the heft and length you've given her. It feels wonderful though and you probably think the trade of all you were for what you are now was worth it. your new form throbbing in her hands as she masturbates, pulsating with lusty sensations as she works herself to climax. Neri gasping and spasming her hips as her newly sensitive shaft erupts, pumping hot cum out through you to stain the ground with ropes of thick jizz. The orgasm serving to make you a bit more of a manageable third leg for the naughty elf, who looks at her handiwork then down at her crotch and giggles "well, welcome to the tribe traveller. I think you fit in just perfectly." she says and watches as you soften, adding "I guess we have a place for all outsiders."
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="insult">
	<text>
	"Why you...that's mean, you're a meanie. I am too the greeter and you should totally go in my sack, but now you're not gonna cause you're mean." She says and crosses her arms afore turning away from you and stamping her foot in a tantrumish fashion...seems you struck a nerve.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="insult" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="...yeah not dealing with this"/>
	</page>
	

	<page ID="agree">
		<text>
			"Excellent, lets get you nice and thoroughly welcomed." says Neri and
			smiles, reaching down to undo her skirt and let it fall down around
			her ankles revealing her cock. That green shaft already rising to
			attention and helped along by a few eager strokes she gives it as it
			seems to grow a bit larger and then larger still "just have to get it
			ready." she comments.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				As you take the time she's getting ready to get ready yourself by
				undressing.
			</conditional>
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="time to get wellcummed" />
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="2" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			"mhmm. All ready." she remarks as she finishes stroking herself to
			firmness. Her cock now standing proud jutting out from her hips as
			she motions you onto a fallen treetrunk "lets not waste anymore time.
			give me your foot" she says, taking it when proferred and guiding it
			into her tip "you might want to hold onto something" she remarks as
			her cock schlurps around your foot, accepting it remarkably easily
			deep into her length. Hot pre soaking your calves up to the knee as
			you feel your foot pushing out the inside of her sack and she motions
			for you to give her your other foot. Neri sliding it in and letting
			out a groan of delight at feeling both of your feet pushing against
			the underside of her sack.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="slide in" />

	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			"that's it, you're being an excellent greetee so far." she remarks as she
			takes both your hands to support them, moaning as her hot cock
			ripples and schlurps up your thighs steadily. Hot pre bubbling up
			around you as she works you inside her bulging shaft, your legs
			starting to curl and soon your knees are pushing out her sack nicely
			as they're plunged into the cum within. Her cocktip rising up around
			your chest as she moans even louder "a truly excellent greetee." she
			reiterates as she engulfs your hips, her cock bulging mightily around
			your lower body as she prepares to schlurp in your upper half.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="all the way down" />

	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			Her cock slides up to your shoulders, and she grins "Welcome to the
			village of Minyos." she says as she places a hand atop your head and
			gives you a push. Your head vanishing entirely into her tip and your
			arms soon following. Hot musky pre and cum surrounding you utterly as
			you plunge down her cock, her hands tracing the bulges in her cock as
			she slides you down entirely into her balls. Your form curling up
			between her legs as she reaches down to scoop up her skirt and put it
			back on, though it does nearly nothing to hide her immense bulging
			and highly visible sack.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="settle in" />

	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			You feel her moving around, walking with a rolling gait with you trapped
			in her balls. Your confines jostling and swaying around with each
			step, sloshing the hot cum back and forth around you. You're utterly
			covered in the stuff and it occurs to you she never mentioned when
			she'd let you out of her balls. She seems to be simply going about
			her day normally despite the impediment of you in her loins.
		</text>
		<choice destination="speakup" text="ask about getting out" />
		<choice destination="staysilent" text="keep quiet" />

	</page>

	<page ID="speakup">
		<text>
			"What you want to be let out already?" Neri asks with a pout, reaching
			down to pat and stroke her sack where you bulge out her nuts"I wanted
			to keep you in there longer, I'll let you out later okay?" she
			suggests, as wonderfully hot tingles soak your flesh. Her oozing cum
			seeming to seep into your pores. It's truly a luxurious sensation,
			why not stick around a little longer.
		</text>
		<choice destination="insist" text="let me out" />
		<choice destination="hushup" text="i'll wait" />

	</page>


	<page ID="insist">
		<text>
			"Fine, but come back anytime if you change your mind that you haven't been
			properly welcomed to the village okay?" Neri says and finds a good
			spot, settling on a fallen tree and stroking herself. The hermy green
			elf vigorously working her cock with mounting moans until with a
			final moan she reaches her climax, sending you rocketing back up her
			cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="letout" text="woosh" />

	</page>

	<page ID="letout">
		<text>
			You land in a hot creamy puddle of her jizz in front of her. Neri
			pouts a little but smiles "hope you enjoyed your stay inside my
			balls, come back anytime." she says
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				and offers you your clothes so you can get dressed again
			</conditional>
			. Neri fondling her cock a little more before letting it soften and
			slip back under the concealment of her skirt.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was an experience" />
	</page>

	<page ID="hushup">
		<text> You decide to be quiet and she takes that as assent "alright
			then." Neri says and returns to going about her business. Going back
			to sloshing you back and forth in her glorping sack as she moves
			around, her thighs pressing against you rthythmically when she walks,
			rubbing her cum into your body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="hushdigest0" text="relax" />

	</page>

	<page ID="hushdigest0">
		<text>
			You find yourself utterly relaxing in her sack, going with the motion as
			she carries you around and lets you enjoy sloshing inside her. It's
			so relaxing it feels almost..like you can't move, you begin to
			realize things are going further. Your form soft, her balls once
			sharply bulged now soft and round as you burble inside her all creamy
			and white. Your attempts to bring this to Neri's attention resulting
			in only a gurgle and gasp as you begin to spread out. Your movements
			to try and push out just spreading your form out into the surrounding
			cum.
		</text>
			<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="1" />	
		<choice destination="digestGO" text="melt away" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="digestGO">
		<text>
			Inside her balls you begin to succumb entirely, the sloshing sway of her
			sack, her rubbing thighs..all working to dissolve your weakened form
			into the surrounding spunk. Neri grinning a bit as she feels that
			churning take on a more pronounced and liquid feel and patpats her
			sack "ooh, now you're nice and well cummed visitor." she says and
			grins "I can let you out now." she continues stroking herself to
			hardness and then further. The green elf masturbating as you slosh
			and flow fluidly in her sack as naught but cum now. Neri reaching her
			peak and shuddering, crying out as she sends you arcing out to
			splatter all across the ground. A thick liquid stain of her jizz
			pooling there your only remains. She surveys her handiwork and leans
			in "let me tell you a secret" she says conspiratorially to the puddle
			"there's no such thing as an official greeter for visitors in this
			village, i made it all up."
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<page ID="staysilent">
		<text>
			You decide to keep quiet, confident everything is going to plan.
			Besides, this cumbath feels..wonderful. You can really feel the thick
			goo soaking into your skin as you marinate in her seed. You can feel
			her moving around, chattering away over trivialities with other
			elves, sitting, standing, walking. She really is being quite generous
			in hauling around the burden of you as she goes about her business.
		</text>
		<choice destination="staydigest0" text="enjoy the bath" />
	</page>

	<page ID="staydigest0">
		<text>
			You feel yourself easing into your surroundings, utterly comfortable.
			The sack conforming precisely to your shape as you spread out and
			soften. You can feel yourself melting, but everything is going
			according to plan. It's not something to worry about, her sack now
			round and starting to shift into two orbs anew as your oozing form
			loses definition and conforms more and more to your surroundings.
		</text>
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="1" />		
		<choice destination="digestGO" text="melt away" />
	</page>

	<page ID="refuse">
		<text>"But it's my job. really. Fine though, I can't exactly force ya.
			come back if you change your mind though." she seems put out but has
			taken the rejection at least a little gracefully.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="sure, if that happens" />
	</page>


	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1" flag="insulted" />
		<text>
		"I don't want to talk to you anymore." ah the joys of dealing with the sulky and immature. Maybe leave her be?
		</text>
		<choice destination="apologize0" text="actually, i kinda want to apologize for what I said."/>
		<choice destination="end" text="yeah, dunno why I'm bothering you" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologize0">
	<text>
	"you want to apologize? really, well uh." Neri is taken by surprise but apparently bounces back with mercurial speed from her sulk "Does that mean you want me to wellcum you to the village now?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologize1" text="ah, yes Neri. I think that'd be a good idea"/>
	<choice destination="apologize2" text="no. i just wanted to apologize not go in you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologize1">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, thanks traveller. You won't regret this, i'll make sure you're thoroughly wellcummed don't you worry." she says brightly, bounding up to give you a hug and rub the firming bulge of her package against you before disentangling and getting ready.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="insult" value="0" />
	<choice destination="cockvore0" text="*the things you do to see a smile*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologize2">
	<text>
	"Then what kinda apology is it if you still don't want to be in my balls?" she says and crosses her arms huffily, seems she has a bit of a onetrack mind and won't be budged from it.
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologise3" text="Okay, alright, please... I'm sorry"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="stubborn girl, goodbye"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologise3">
	<!-- content by alphaShows-->
	<text>
	"Ohhh..? You reeaally want me to just let it go..?" she says slowly, taking a few steps away from you. Suddenly she turns back, uncrossing her arms and smiling mischievously
	"I'll make sure to properly forgive you, but first I want to see how you'll eeeever make it up to me Ms. meanie."
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologycv0" text="Give her the 'apology' she wants"/>
	<choice destination="helpcv0" text="I think I'll need some help with this one"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologycv0">
	<text>
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				You undress slowly giving her a little turn, showing off your body in the process.
			</conditional>
		Neri is clearly very excited, her short primitive skirt stretching to the limit and
		struggling to contain her twitching bulge. You sashay over to her, winking seductively and you can hear the individual seams snapping one by one.
		Slowly moving closer, you trace your fingers up her thighs and she gives a small shudder and suddenly her skirt can no longer
		keep up with her growing cock and bursts open with a loud rip. "Oooooouugh.." Neri moans in relief as she feels the pressure of the tight skirt suddenly gone,
		thick cock swinging up to stand at attention right in front of your eyes "You're well on your way to being forgiven, buuut I'm sure you know what you need to do next traveller.."
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologycv1" text="Give it a taste"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologycv1">
	<text>
	Neri gently grabs your head and brings you closer, but stops just short of her throbbing member, a huge dollop of precum welling from the slit 
	"Well, what are you waiting for?" she says impatiently, her smug grin widening. Face to face with the large green cock you swallow a little saliva and lick your lips.
	Although the tip gapes hungrily for your face, maybe you can get out of this without being sucked down?
	Kneeling down and fondling her balls, you lick from the base to the tip and look back up at Neri.
	She is staring directly into your eyes with an expression of lusty anticipation, green skin tinged with a deep blush.
	She pushes you softly back down and thrusts forward slightly starting to get more impatient.
	As quick as you can, you take her to the hilt and move back forth rapidly, swirling your tongue and sucking while lingering on the tip with each stroke.
	Neri eeps with surprise at the sudden assault but is soon moaning and thrusting in time with you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologycv2" text="Finish her"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologycv2">
	<text>
	Speeding up your ministrations until you feel her twitch and then slowing back down to stop her from blowing, you continue on for a few more minutes.
	Thinking it's time to end this before you're tired, you hasten your movements once more and look up to admire Neri's face, twisted in pleasure.
	Right when you're sure she is about to erupt, you feel her quickly pull backwards, yanking her shaft free. 
	Surprised, your momentum makes you lose balance and you fall forward. 
	With a grin and another loud moan, Neri thrusts forwards herself, her cock schlorping over your head and pulling you in to your chest.
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologycv3" text="Wait, this wasn't the plan!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="apologycv3">
	<text>
	"Sorry..? I didn't quite catch that!" Neri exclaims excitedly, grabbing your ass roughly and shoving you down.
	You're dunked headfirst into the hot churning cum you thought you'd be soon be swallowing, but now you're tasting it in quite a different way!
	"I diiiid tell you it wouldn't be a real apology if you didn't end up in my balls didn't I~?" Neri teases playfully, with a tone as if talking to a child.
	Quickly schlurping up the rest of you, she continues where your lips left off, stroking with her hands. 
	Feeling disoriented and curled upside down, the almost broiling spunk soaks into your skin.
	</text>
	<choice destination="apologyGO" text="B-but..."/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="apologyGO">
		<text>
		"Shhh... It's been fun traveller, but it's about to get a lot funner!" she pants out, jacking off with one hand and fondling your rapidly softening form with the other.
		Almost exactly as your consciousness fades to black, Neri screams in pleasure and unleashes a massive gout of thick steamy cream that splatters wetly against the landing pad, forming a spreading puddle on the stone work.
		Neri almost loses consciousness herself, tongue lolling out as she can think of nothing else besides the intense pleasure your untimely demise is giving her.
		Gasping for breath and wiping the sweat from her brow, cum still spurting and running down the ship,
		Neri pants out the words you wanted to hear so badly "Haa.. Haaa.. Apology... Accepted...." 
		It's quite unfortunate you were otherwise indisposed at the moment
		and you couldn't quite hear her, or maybe disposed of is more apt...?
		</text>

	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="helpcv0">
	<text>
	"Hey, c'mere a minute!" you call out to a rather tall and buxom elf girl who was mid-conversation with another elf and motion for them to come over
	"You too babe!" you say winking to her friend. As they cautiously approach, you admire the buxom elf's large top straining assests and then look over to her friend.
	Her sizeable thighs squish together as she walks over and her rear is so large you can see it's outline clearly, even from the front.
	"Sorry to interrupt your talk.." you tell them apologetically as they draw near, trying very hard to look them in the eyes "I've offended your official village greeter and would very much like your help to make it up to her."
	The two elves looks at you and then at Neri, "But we don't have an off-" starts the taller girl but Neri quickly brings her finger to her mouth shushing her and giving an impish grin
	"What I mean is uh, we don't have an official apology custom in the village..?" she says unconvincingly looking to Neri for approval who then nods, happy with her answer.
	"But uhm, sure I'll help! It'll be fun!" she says with an excited hop towards you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv1" text="What about you?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv1">
	<text>
	"O-oh me? Sure I guess if Kaia says it'll be fun.." You leer at her extra wide hips and almost bursting skirt, wondering who fits these alien clothes and wordlessly giving them a prayer of thanks
	"H-hey Ner" the timid shorter elf stammers out, clearly uncomfortable with being around her 
	"I haven't seen you since my sister had you over for dinner a few weeks ago... Uhm, Good to see you..!"
	Neri smiles widely at her before replying "And what a dinner it was~! How is she doing anyways?" you see her skirt beginning to bulge with it's expanding contents.
	"W-well we uhh.. W-we haven't seen her since then either... I was-erm-We were hoping you'd know where she was?" She stumbles out with a hopeful look.
	Neri has an expression of realisation and fondles herself through her skirt thoughtfully smiling slyly
	"Actually now that you mention it I do know where she went.. If we hurry and get this started I think I'll be able to show you right after!"
	"If you'd like I can bring over our pet doggy too? What do you think Bea?" The tall elf you know know as Kaia asks, but Neri quickly shakes her head
	"Nonono, no pets at my place! I always err.. 'lose' them and then people nag me about where they went, so I don't like having them over anymore.. 
	Anyways, let's get going!" she points you to a wooden house and skips quickly towards the door, the others following behind her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv2" text="Follow the girls!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv2">
	<text>
	As you enter the house, your nostrils are assaulted with the stench of stale cum. Looking around inside, your face scrunching up instinctively,
	 you see there are dried cumstains over almost everything in the house, especially on the far walls near the bed.
	"Welcome traveller! Neri exclaims with an exaggerated flourish, but seeing the look on your face she looks around herself before realising
	"Oh yeah.. Sorry about the clutter, my job as official village greeter has given me a lot more uh, 'mess' to clean but no time to do it! ...Well then..."
	Neri walks with a swagger over to the bed, Bea gasps as Neri strips off her skirt and shows you all how ready she is "You want to start your 'apology'?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv3-1" text="Demonstrate how it's done"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv3-1">
	<text>
	"Let me show you how we used to apologise where I came from" you say 
		<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				while slipping out of your garments,
		</conditional>
		running your hands over your naked body,
		slapping Bea on the behind as you pass her and sauntering over to embrace Neri.
		You plant a kiss firmly on Neri's lips and wedge her member between your legs,
		wiggling your hips as you push her down onto the bed. Still kissing passionately, your hands roam to her pert breasts
		and you tweak her nipples softly, Neri moaning into your mouth begins to fidget to give her schlong more friction and kisses you more intensely.
		The two elves fondle each other while watching, engrossed in the scene playing out before them.
		Breaking the kiss but still looking Neri directly in the eye, you wordlessly motion for the others to join you on the bed.
		They waste no time and strip down too, rushing over, Kaia envelops your head in her soft warm cleavage and rubs her slit against Neri's cocktip.
		Bea is slower on the draw but no less enthusastic, leaving her shyness behind on the floor with her clothes, she feels you up while making out with Kaia.
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv4-1" text="Getting hotter"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv4-1">
	<text>
	As the room is heating up, limbs entangle and saliva is crossed, moans and giggles echo out of the wooden house.
	The foreplay continuing until finally, Neri breaks away from your hold and begins to make demands. 
	"Let's get this started for real... Traveller, get over here!" She flips you around so you're lying, back on the bed and thrusts her snatch onto your face
	"Get to work down there and Kaia, you get to be first!" Grabbing ahold of her hips with a grunt,
	she roughly thrusts in as best she can without letting you move much. Kaia starts to cry out loudly but is silenced by Bea sitting on her face. 
	Working as best you can to time your tongue with her thrusting while still getting some oxygen, you hear some muffled complaints from up front but can't really see what's going on.
	After a few minutes, Neri can't keep up with all the stimulation and with a girlish yell, begins to empty her load right into Kaia and spurting liquid from her sex onto your face.
	Given some reprieve and wiping your face clean of girlcum, you raise your head to look down and can see Kaia being sucked right into Bea's crack
	"Ah, that'd be the complaining" you think just as a wad of thick cum splashes back out of Kaia and straight into your eyes.
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv5-1" text="Ackk!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv5-1">
	<text>
	Temporarily blinded, you hear moaning at such a volume you didn't think was possible from the timid elf,
	as she continues to consume who you presumed to be her only friend with her ass.
	Startled by a tongue on your face, you regain your vision and see Neri licking up the spunk from around your eyes.
	She silently mouths the word sorry and winks, before getting off you to watch the rest of Kaia's legs be sucked into that huge derrière.
	Still moaning but suddenly realising what she has done, Bea turns and looks you two with tears welling in her eyes,
	right before she has an orgasm where she stands as Kaia reaches her final destination inside her. 
	"O-ohhh Kaia..!" She cries out as her legs jellify and she falls onto the bed sobbing.
	Neri looks from her then to you, the gurgling from Bea's distended middle easily heard over her sobs.
	"That was soooo hot!" Neri yells excitedely, her cock already standing erect again "Sorry to interrupt Bea, but you did want me to take you to your sister right..?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcv6-1" text="Let's see where this goes"/>
	<choice destination="bea1" text="Give her a break Neri..."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv6-1">
	<text>
	Bea looks up at Neri from the bed, her teary face looking quite a mess, but hopeful "You really know where she is Neri?? ..I-I think I'll need her help to get over losing Kaia like this.."
	Looking down at her gut sadly, it gurgles loudly in response and she tries to hold back a burp. "Ohhh yeah Bea I can show you exactly where she is, even the exact path she took to get there!"
	Neri says with glee, stroking her shaft and walking towards her. "A-alright just let me put my clothes ba-" Bea begins but is cut off as her head is sucked in with a loud schlorp.
	"W-waiiit Neri what are you doing!!?" the muffled voice of Bea cries out "Y-you don't mean that you..."
	Rubbing the digesting body of Kaia inside Bea's belly as she leisurely sucked her down, Neri winked at you and sat down on the edge of the bed.
	"Ahaha, yep! She begged for me to end her and shoot her all over the walls in here, just like I did to your precious mummy! When she found out she couldn't stay away!"
	A despairing wail sounded out from somewhere inside Neri "Nooooo! I don't believe it! M-mum... The predators outside the village got her months ago!"
	Neri, looking rather sadistic as the wails got worse, giggled at how she had broken the poor girl. 
	"When I jizzed her out, a big heap fell into my washing bucket with her clothes and necklace and I thought it was too perfect of an opportunity to waste! I threw it outside town guilt free!"
	Still sucking Bea down steadily, she gasped as she made it to those wide hips and got stuck, grunting, she strained to fit them in.
	"Anyways just like I said, I'm showing you where your sister went and even how she got there! She got churned up in there and soon, like her, you'll go straight into the wall!"
	Gesturing for you to come over and help get her down, Neri ignored whatever Bea had left to say, too distracted by her building pleasure. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcvGO1" text="A good push will end this!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="helpcv7-1">
	<text>
	As you were struggling to push Bea the rest of the way down, suddenly with a great shudder,
	Neri's cocktip opened wide and got past the blockage smoothly sucking her in from there. 
	Unfortunately you were still pushing with both hands and they were sucked in, quickly down to your elbows.
	Falling forwards a little, unsteady in your footing you ask nervously, "H-hey Neri? You're kinda getting me too? Think you could help me out here?"
	Neri just looks down at you and raises an eyebrow, grinning widely. Her cocktip pulses around your arms, warm cum lubricating them as they slide deeper.
	Realising she is the last person on the planet who'd help you out right now, you frantically try to escape before it's too late.
	</text>
	<choice destination="helpcvGO1" text="Uh oh..."/>
	<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="1" />		
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="helpcvGO1">
		<text>
		Not having any chance to regain your footing, you slip over on some cum on the floor, practically feeding yourself the rest of the way in.
		Feeling you dumped into her bubbling sac, Neri lays back pointing her cock straight up, knowing she'd soon be making yet another mess she wouldn't clean up.
		You fall right onto the gooey Bea, sending cum splashing everywhere with a squelch, saturating you. Digestion already setting in, you lock eyes with Bea and apologise silently.
		Funny, it was apologising that got you into this mess. You laugh softly as you feel yourself spreading out and losing form, perhaps just a little rest...
		Meanwhile, Neri was doing anything but resting. Her extremely distented balls sloshing widly with the digested remains of 3 people as she pumped wildly.
		Being this full, she couldn't hold back for long and with a series of grunts, gasps and moans she let loose.
		Ropes of incredibly thick semen exploded out of Neri's cock with insane force. Shooting straight into the ceiling and busting through the flimsy construction,
		great amounts of spunk rained down on Neri and her house, her mind blank and her everything focused completely on her powerful orgasm.
		After what felt like years of continuous spurting, Neri had passed out from pleasure overload and her cock continued to gush like a fountain into the air.
		The artificial rain she created eventually stopped coming down, the house still dripping with a fresh new coat of white 'paint'. 
		With an extremely dopey smile on her face and cock still dribbling, Neri slept peacefully, completely satisfied with your apology.
		</text>

	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="bea1">
	<text>
	Turning back to you frowning, Neri crossed her arms and huffed. "It's not my fault, she ate her! Besides, I didn't even get to feel those huge tits going down my shaft!"
	Bea looked up at Neri, angrily wiping her teary eyes. Neri pointed backwards to Bea as she continued "She was supposed to be mine after I spunked this fatso and let her meet up with her dumb sister on the wall!"
	Surprising you again, Bea jumped up and grabbed Neri from behind closing the distance in an instant. "What was that you were saying Neri?"
	Still pouting and apparently feeling no danger from the upset elf, Neri points to a pile of ruined and cumsoaked rags in the corner. 
	"Right there is where your stupid sister ended up! She begged me to end her in my sac! Now let me go and hurry up and become my next load!"
	Bea doesn't let go and for a moment, no one moves or says anything, the only sound Bea's gurgling middle.
	Without warning, gripping her tightly, Bea shoves Neri's head into her mouth and swallows hurriedly before she can make any attempts to escape.
	You watch in amazement as the shorter elf gulps and slurps her down with ease, her stomach soon bulging out, outweighing even the size of her huge behind.
	Angry and out of breath, she looks over to the cumsoaked pile and tears well up once again.
	</text>
	<choice destination="bea2" text="Time to leave!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="bea2">
		<text>
		Feeling concerned about the new developments, you're thinking it might be a good time to get out of here. You slowly
		<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				grab your gear and begin to
		</conditional>
		back away towards the door, hoping she won't notice. Your foot slides a little on the slick floor and you let out a gasp of surprise.
		Bea, hearing this, suddenly turns, remembering you were there. "You... This is all because you brought us here!" She spat out, a crazed, hungry expression on her once timid face.
		Though she is probably shorter than 5ft tall, Bea is looking rather intimidating as she walks towards you.
		"I may not be able to take back what happened, but at least I can ease my conscience by getting rid of you!"
		With speed that shouldn't be possible, she lunges at you and tackles you to the floor, pinning you down with her large belly.
		She grabs your legs and brings your feet to her mouth taking them in.
		</text>
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="digestion" value="1" />		
		<special effect="removenpc" />	
		<choice destination="beaGO" text="You don't have to do this!" />
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="beaGO">
		<text>
		Ignoring you and looking at you bitterly, Bea pulls you towards her with a few gulps, wanting to waste no time getting her revenge.
		She greedily slurps down your legs and past your waist, not wanting to cause you any pleasure eats you as fast as she can.
		What little fighting you do makes no difference and within moments you are being dunked into a very crowded tight space.
		Bea moans and rubs her overfull midsection as she stands back up, sloshing and gurgling slowly back towards the bed.
		You find Neri masturbating angrily, she is even now thinking of only one thing. Figuring it's now or never, you squirm around and manoeuvre yourself onto her shaft.
		Saying nothing and pretending you don't exist, she thrusts roughly and quickly into you, trying to spurt one last time.
		As the tingling on your skin is getting painful, Neri shudders as she climaxes inside you pulling out and closing her eyes. 
		Trying to also get off before time is up, you drift off with your hand still moving up and down.
		Bea lays uncomfortably on the jizz soaked bed, not really sad about the events of the past hour anymore. Although she'll miss her friend,
		the feeling of fullness as her stomach happily digests it's contents almost makes it worth it.
		</text>

	</gameover>	
	
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			"Oh uh, nope nothing to see here." she adjusts her clothing and frowns
			"Nothing for you anyway, I can just tell you wouldn't appreciate it."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="well bye" />
	</page>
</Conversation>