<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The amphibian girl's ample chest heaves as she looks up at you, clearly
			uncertain as worried now you've beaten her. Her curvaceous form is at
			your mercy now, and quite appealing with her half sprawled before
			you. The curves of her ass and breasts on full display in all their
			emerald and cream hued glory.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="she'll make an ample meal">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="mhmm, time to be merciful this time" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			She looks sexily curvaceous sprawled out like that. But a big gal
			like this'll make an even more satisfying meal than she would
			anything else.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Though there's no way your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				will stretch over such the belly you're about to have so you undress
				before continuing.
			</conditional>
			With thoughts of your impending satisfaction in mind you situate
			yourself in front of the amphibian, uncertainly she flicks her tongue
			out to taste you. But she's not the one getting a meal today and you
			flick her tail admonishingly, which confuses her until you lunged
			forwards. The frog girl letting out a startled ribbit as she sees
			your mouth stretching wide to encompass her head. Her soft body
			squirming and jiggling about in surprise as you take your first
			swallow and swell your throat and neck out pleasingly with her skull.
			She's trying to pull back away from you already, but to no avail with
			you already past her shoulders and pinning her arms from stopping
			your hunger.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="now for those delicious tits" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			The froggy's mmhmphs and croaks of protest are muffled nicely, uttered
			into the depths of your throat as they are. And these complaints dont
			distract you from your wonderful quest to cram her frame past your
			lips, both hands going to her tits now. Those pillowy breasts soft
			and spilling out past your palms, your fingers dig in as you begin to
			squeeze her wondrous cushions past your lips. Gradually though you
			conquer these wonderfully gropable obstacles, feeling them swelling
			your neck afore they slide down to seemingly disappear behind your
			collarbone as you cram the froggy deeper. And now you have the soft
			padded expanse of her tummy to devour as you start to pack her away
			into your own. Her equally ample rump getting closer to your lips as
			her gut padding squishes past your jaws and down your throat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="and now to gobble up dat ass" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			Your gut starts to really stretch and swell out around her, the bulges
			made by her head and breasts clearly visible on your front as you
			grope her ass and prepare to swallow that part of her up as well.
			This feels just as good as you thought it would! with a mhmm from you
			and a protesting croak from your big meal you start to work her ass
			inside. Her webbed hands push out at your insides to try and stop her
			descent. But she's no match for your hunger and your throat tugs her
			down, forcing her arms against her as she's packed away and her
			thighs start to slide past your lips.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="polish her off" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			You're settled comfortably on your ass now as your gut distends out
			massively into your lap. The frog girl's weight resting on your
			thighs as you swallow up her legs steadily, curvy hips and meaty
			calves vanishing past your lips as she's forced to curl up inside of
			you. The big froggy finally vanishing entirely into you filling you
			with lip smacking satisfaction. Her unhappy croaks and pushes against
			your groaning and stretched belly serve only to increase your
			satisfaction. That satisfaction far outweighing any discomfort from
			how much you've stretched your gut to contain the frog girl..now,
			time for the final act of your enjoyment of her curvy body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4" text="digest her" />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore4">
		<text>
			You feel her squirm around inside you and let out a startled sound as
			you start to gurgle her away. That ample soft form provides little
			resistance to your enzymes, but her sheer bulk means it takes time to
			digest her. She struggles and squirms and shoves at your insides
			making your belly rock around, but despite it all she's gradually
			softening..you can feel her gurgling inside you and see it in how her
			curvy bulges weaken and get rounder. The ending was never in doubt
			and when it does it comes with a toe curlingly satisfying gurgle and
			glorp of her form being squished into slurry as the last of her
			resilience fades away. All of her fat and figure now just a soup of
			goopy nourishment in your belly. The bulge of your tummy now nice and
			round compacts and shrinks down steadily, absorbing her nutrients to
			sustain you until nothing remains but your overwhelming sense of
			satisfaction at a meal well claimed.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>