<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<assertion evaluate="hasStatus" uid="90" />
		<text>
		Without warning the frog woman's tongue snaps out across the distance towards your tiny form, how did she even catch sight of you like that. You stumble as the tongue strikes your body and sticks, but you don't even get a chance to fall over before the tongue snaps back. Your body soaring up in an arc through the air towards her as her tongue rapidly pulls back in, you can see her jaws stretching wide open ahead of you like a catchers mitt. With no way to alter your trajectory in your seconds of flight you find yourself falling right between her lips. The frog girl snapping her mouth shut behind you and mhmming as she seals you into the wet hot embrace of her mouth.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*savoured*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	Tiny and trapped in the frog girl's mouth you're helpless against her desire to savour you. That curling tongue of hers pressing you against the inside of her mouth, up against the roof of her maw and then curling around yourself to taste your form. The frog girl letting out pleased moans and ribbits as she rolls you about in her mouth and starts teasingly pressing you up against the back of her mouth and the entrance of her throat.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*swallowed*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The froggy woman seems to tire of savouring you as she tips her head back and her tongue flexes to press you into the back of her throat. She swallows and a barely noticable bulge is visible on her neck where she sends your tiny form down towards her belly. Your predator letting out a hearty ribbit and drumming her fingers on her chubby belly as her snack finishes sliding down her throat, your body emerging from the tightness into the cavern of her belly. You're nothing more significant than a morsel to her and her stomach fluids splash around you as you bath in the depths of her gut, unnoticable and soon to be reduced to an even more insignificant form within her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*and digested*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Trapped in the depths of her belly you're too small to even reach the stomach valve above you. But as enzymes start to pour in that changes, and all the while you hear her fingers drumming on her belly as the caustic fluids rise. The stomach gradually fills with enzymes, it would be possible to escape back up her throat at least in theory once full. But by the time that happens your little body has been worn down to nothing by her digestive goo, reduced to nothing but a smear of nutritious soup floating atop her stomach broth. An ignoble end for so insignificant a snack.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
</Conversation>