<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
			<preference fetish="demis" />
		<preference fetish="females" />			
		<text>
			With that final kick you're sent reeling back and then slump in a heap in
			front of your curvaceous predator. The frog girl squatting down to
			give you a look over, grinning broadly and uttering a little ribbit
			followed by a chuckle as she sizes you up as her meal. Her
			appreciation indicated doubly so when you hear the gurgle of her
			belly, seemingly not muffled by that layer of chub wrapped around her
			middle. The ample amphibian seems to be done anticipating and
			appreciating you visually though, or perhaps unwilling to wait let
			you recover. And so your predator hauls you up with smooth yet firm
			hands on your upper arms. You feel that flexible and long tongue lash
			out and run up and down your body, tasteing you, curling around your
			frame as her mouth gapes wide before you, then chomps down. The frog
			girl engulfing your head in her wide mouth in one movement. Your
			predator moaning in delight as she samples your face and neck and you
			feel her prodigious rack and groaning belly pressed softly against
			your body as she positions herself to start gobbling you down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="tasted and devoured" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			Cuddled close to her you can feel the soft warmth of her padded frame and
			the eagerness of her body to contain yours as she keeps you snug and
			under control while eating you alive. Her arms are powerful despite
			the softness of how they feel and they hold you firm as she swallows,
			a powerful loud glucking gulp pulling your chest into her mouth and
			your head into her throat. The amphibian curving you inwards easily
			as her hands shift down to your thighs and you slide easily down her
			throat towards her belly. Your struggles and protests of no import to
			her though some of the more spirited acts of defiance at least get
			her to chuckle muffledly around her ample mouthful of space
			traveller.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			As the amphibian eats you alive that tongue gets, simply everywhere,
			twining between your legs, curling around your body and intruding
			between your thighs. the voracious frog seems to be intent on
			sampling you thoroughly as she eats you alive, your legs waving
			around in the air now as she starts to work you into her belly. The
			frog's gut starting to swell out as you're packed away behind her
			chub. The insides of the voracious frog stretching easily to contain
			you, proving positively soft, roomy and accomodating compared to
			other stomachs you'd had the misfortune to experience. It seems that
			soft fleshy sack behind that padded tummy is to be your new home as
			she's working your ass past her lips and crams your upper body inside
			her belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			Over halfway past her gaping jaws now you know it won't take her long to
			chug you down. The amphibian grabbing ahold of your leg by your calf
			and ignoring the flailing of the other as she tips her head back and
			gulps and gobbles you down. The frog finally snapping her jaws shut
			and smacking her lips in satisfaction behind your feet. Your form
			sliding down and curling up inside her gut as she rubs and kneads at
			her middle with both hands. The froggy woman letting out a delighted
			ribbit and croak of pleasure then chuckles and patpats her middle as
			you push out, being able to only make indistinct handprints as you
			shove out against the thick walls of her tummy.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="try to escape her belly by force" />	
		<choice destination="submit" text="get comfortable and get digested" />
	</page>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			You're entirely curled up inside her now and as you feel her soft innards
			all around you you settle down. It's really quite comfortable in
			here, even if she is intending to break you down becoming another
			layer of fat on her already amply padded form doesn't sound that bad
			at all. You hear the predator amphibian chuckle and shift her
			position, settling slowly into the water until she's floating on her
			back. The frog stroking her gut and croaking in delight as she hears
			her belly starting to gently but unmistakeably gurgle and churn
			around you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitGO" text="let it happen" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitGO">
		<text>
			Inside the comfy depths of the frog girl's gut you feel yourself stewing
			and digesting away. The sensation is surprisingly pleasant if you're
			not bothered by your pending dissolution, the steady rocking and
			gurgling of her gut softening you down to mush over an indulgently
			long time. But in the end all that's left is that slurry of goopy
			former space traveller, your form now a soft pliant mass in her tummy
			as she kneads her hands into her chub. The frog girl letting out
			delighted ribbits at feeling beyond her fat nothing more solid than a
			soup that her form steadily absorbs. Her tummy returning from its
			former distension to something more trim but still rounded as your
			nutrients are distributed to add to her fat softness.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="struggle">
		<text>
			You feel her patting her gut and smacking her lips in satisfaction and
			renew your struggles. You're not about to sit here quietly and get
			churned into more pudge on this chubby amphibian. The patpats of the
			frog seem somewhat condescending as they patpat her gut now that you
			vigorously attempt to upset her ample gut and escape your curvaceous
			prison. One can only hope you're too unruly a meal to keep down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="must escape" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="escape" />
		<outcome destination="gurgle" />
	</check>

	<page ID="escape">
		<text>
			The frog girl is indulgent in her doting on her gut initially. But as
			you really get going in vigorously shoving and pushing at her insides
			she loses her condescending complacency and starts to urp and croak
			in distress, pressing her hands into her soft and distended belly to
			try and settle it. But even that is not enough to stop you as your
			stamina and energy proves too much for her. She lets out a sickening
			urp and doubles over in distress, retching as you take this moment to
			force your way back up her throat. You land in a heap amidst the mire
			waters, splashing into the dirty liquids as she horks you up and then
			collapses into a dismayed heap.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="*back up*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="gurgle">
		<text>
			The frog girl dotes on her gut indulgently as you become unruly and
			uppity inside her belly. As you get a bit more vigorous the soft
			ribbiting and contentment of her resting form does give way somewhat
			to her giving you a squeeze with tummy muscles and both hands. But
			nothing more than that is garnered by your spirited attempt to
			escape. Your inevitable succumbing to fatigue makes the froggy give
			you a patpat through the walls of her chubby tummy, as if to go
			'there there' about your stirling but ultimately futile effort to
			escape her innards. The gurgling digestive fluids are starting to get
			a bit more active around you as you realize there's nought you can do
			except turn into another layer of fat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleGO">
		<text>
			You can't escape, but that doesn't stop you squirming as she digests
			you. Your occasional resigned whimper and palm print pushing out
			doesn't get anything more than those condescending and doting pats
			from her though as you gurgle away. And in time nought is left inside
			her that would tell anyone that a spacetraveller had met her end
			inside the amphibian, her gut turning still softer under her hands as
			your mass turns liquid and compacts into a dense nutritious mass.
			Once that's done her gut trims out further, distributing the chub
			from your form all over to add to her thighs, ass, breasts and
			middle. What once was you is now a thin layer of well distributed
			softness covering the form of this dangerously curvaceous predator.
		</text>
	</gameover>


</Conversation>