<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	"Oh hello? you out of your pen?" asks the kitty looking up at you without fear. She starts to smile as she scrutinizes you though"myah, you're not one of ours. That's okay though." she says and glances around to check she's unobserved and then mhmms "I got a pen for you though, comeon let me show you it." she says and reaches out to stroke your head and guide your muzzle down closer to her skirt.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth0" text="*be an obedient dragon*"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="*pull away*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth0">
	<text>
	The kitty murrs in delight as she strokes both hands along the sides of your skull and coaxes you lower and lower..she glances around again and then mhmms "right here" she says and then quickly flicks her skirt up, laying her skirt down over the top of your head, hiding your head almost as far as your eyes. The warmth of her thighs rubbing up against your muzzle from either side as she mrowls in delight. The wonderful scent emanating from above you makes you arc your nose up towards her crotch, those warm wet nethers oozing a little drip of lusty fluids as you nose up more insistently. "myah, time to pen you up" she says and then wriggles downwards, your muzzle vanishing into her surprisingly stretchy lil cunny.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth1" text="*mmph!*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth1">
	<text>
	The kitty lets out a delighted mrowl as despite the size of your muzzle she easily encompasses it with the voracious snatch she was hiding up there behind her skirt. The catgirl's tail swishing as she grabs your smooth and flexible neck and helps feed you in. Her nethers also clenching to tug more of you inside, your head soon trapped up within her womb. The hot and silkenly soft walls of her insides stretching to accomodate your head and bulge out her middle as she sets about confining you into your 'pen'.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth2" text="*MMPH MMPH!*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth2">
	<text>
	You can feel the lil kitty capably handling you despite your size as she packs more of your body into her womb. Her hands guiding your neck up to disappear between her thighs as she continues to suck you in with the inexorably powerful grasp of her netherlips. Your flexible form starting to curl up within her even as you squirm. The catgirl gradually slides down to lay on her back as her middle starts to distend massively, becoming gravid with a huge amount of dragon she has no choice but to lay back and focus on dragging you in with naught but her ravenous nethers. Her fleshy channel proving more than up for the task as foot by foot of your smooth form disappears under her skirt and from there into the nicely defined series of bulges and contours in her middle that shows off your form.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth3" text="*whimper*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth3">
	<text>
	"OOh myah, right..right there..you're...squirmy..and..myah..biiig." the catgirl mewls out in delight, sprawled out pinned by the immense mass her womb is containing as she draws your rear legs and tail past her clenching netherlips. Your form schlurped up into her silken embrace with remarkable ease, practically pinning the kitty girl under the massive dragon contoured orb of curled up wombfodder she's successfully claimed for herself. You can do naught but squirm and twitch inside her tight confines now that the kitty has put you in your...pen.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth4" text="*a temporary stay*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth4">
	<text>
	You whimper, hardly able to move, as you feel her womb squeeze down over you as she lets out a yowl. The kitty gasping and squirming under your bulge "oh you're..you're gonna be hard to slosh.." she says as her naughty juices soak into your body, and gradually starting to soften you up. Her sweltering silken womb starting to work you down, your hide turning slick and then gooey and starting to yield to the constant pressure of her womb all around you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth5" text="*liquidation, naturally*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="unbirth5">
	<text>
	The catgirl mewls as she strokes over the top of her dragon filled middle. Her impossibly gravid tummy gradually starting to lose its exquisitely visible draconic contours and contract. Her womb squeezing down over you, compressing your form as you lose solidity and become pliant in both senses of the word within her. Her round middle shrinking down as your whimpers turn to burbles, your form barely holding together as you feel her rubbing her legs together and then....she yowls, your form squished apart into naught but steaming girl juices that erupt from her cunny as she climaxes. The orgasming kitty sending splattering gushes of liquidated dragon across the ground, soaking her tail and ass as she forms a puddle of your remains.. The lil kitty panting and purring amidst the lake and glancing down afore reaching out and running a hand through the gooey remnants and up to her lips for a taste "myah..so worth it..."
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	
	
</Conversation>