<?xml version="1.0"?>
<NPC>
	<sprite value="yeti.png" />
	<name>yeti</name>
	<description>A full figured feminine body well protected against the cold by ample padding and a layer of snow white fur over the chub. With her hefty breasts, chubby middle, broad rump and curvy thighs the snow bound female has the look of some ancient fertility deity to her. Though perhaps the horns and tusks would spoil the image. Looming at over seven feet tall she simultaneously projects a subtle menace of a powerful predator at home in her environment. Yet at the same time, damned if she doesn't look warm and super cuddly. And appealing in an ample and perhaps motherly sort of way. 
	</description>
	<rpg>
		<experiencevalue value="200" />
		<ability ability="STRENGTH" value="6" />
		<ability ability="AGILITY" value="5" />
		<ability ability="DEXTERITY" value="5" />
		<ability ability="ENDURANCE" value="5" />
		<ability ability="CHARM" value="5" />
		<ability ability="INTELLIGENCE" value="5" />
		<stat stat="HEALTH" value="60" />
		<stat stat="RESOLVE" value="60" />
		<attribute attribute="PARRY" value="4" />
		<combatMove name="boulder" pattern="RANGED" bonusAttribute="MELEE"
			timeCost="4" bonusToHit="4">
			<missText count="2">
				<text>yeti throws a boulder wide of TARGET</text>
				<text>yeti throws a boulder at TARGET who evades</text>
			</missText>
			<hitText count="2">
				<text>yeti pummels TARGET with a boulder for VALUE damage</text>
				<text>TARGET is hit by a boulder thrown by a yeti and suffers VALUE damage</text>
			</hitText>
			<effectDamage type="KINETIC" minValue="4" maxValue="10"
				modifier="STRENGTH" />
		<effectStatus probability="50" value="STRENGTH" >
			<applyText>TARGET has been knocked down and stunned by the impact of a boulder</applyText>
			<statusStun uid="9" duration="10">
				TARGET has recovered
			</statusStun>
		</effectStatus>
		</combatMove>
		<combatMove name="smother" pattern="MELEE" bonusAttribute="MELEE"
			timeCost="2" bonusToHit="4">
			<missText count="2">
				<text>yeti attempts to boobsmother TARGET but fails</text>
				<text>yeti tries to smother TARGET but is pushed back</text>
			</missText>
			<hitText count="2">
				<text>yeti squeezes TARGET against her huge furry tits and loses VALUE resolve</text>
				<text>TARGET finds their face pressed between yeti breasts, the flustering experience strips VALUE resolve from them</text>
			</hitText>
			<effectDamage type="TEASE" minValue="4" maxValue="10"
				modifier="CHARM" />
		</combatMove>		
	</rpg>
	<respawn delay="2000" />
	<defeated conversation="alpha_minoris_III/yeti/defeat" />
	<seduced conversation="alpha_minoris_III/yeti/defeat" />
	<victory conversation="alpha_minoris_III/yeti/victory" />
	<seducer conversation="alpha_minoris_III/yeti/seducer" />
	<controller AI="yeti" />
	<faction value="monster" />
</NPC>