<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA_MALWARE"
					operator="equals" value="1" />
		<text>
			workstation locked, please contact your systems administrator. LBREAK
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			workstation online. LBREAK
			warning data corruption detected. LBREAK
		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="access mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="mailbox">
		<text>
			partial mailbox contents recovered LBREAK
			select message LBREAK
		</text>
		<choice destination="email0" text="access 713" />
		<choice destination="email1" text="access 749" />
		<choice destination="email3" text="access 1025" />
		<choice destination="email10" text="access 1623" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email0">
		<text>
			From: mgr. Ansbel LBREAK
			To: all staff LBREAK
			subject: improper storage of synth accessories LBREAK

			To the responsible parties, LBREAK

			Please note that when not attached to the Omnico synthetic predator gynoid
			the class II genital attachment is to be stored safely in sub-level 2
			storage area B. Furthermore they're to be contained in a type-7 cargo
			box compliant with the standards for the preservation of flexible
			synth material. LBREAK

			It is not in fact appropriate to store them in an open topped plastic
			document tray perched precariously atop the door to Orrena's office.
			I should warn you that should you persist I will be forced to make
			some HR decisions. LBREAK

			I also should remind you that unlike our products I don't need an
			attachment for that, and I have space on my shelf for a 2 gallon jug.
			LBREAK

			-Ansbel. LBREAK

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>


	<page ID="email1">
		<text>
			From: Reshi LBREAK
			To: T. Velas LBREAK
			subject: dodgy units? LBREAK

			Is it just me or are the latest batch of synths from head office kinda
			off. I can't put my finger on it, but something about the way they
			talk and look at me is freaking me out. Reminds me a tad too much of
			my last girlfriend, or the boss for that matter.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email3">
		<text>
			From: Reshi LBREAK
			To: T. Velas LBREAK
			subject: why build an omnico boutique out here? LBREAK

			I don't get it. We're setup in the ass end of nowhere. I mean, I get
			that we're technically on a trade route. But how many ships have
			passed by since I came here? And how many fewer bought any synths.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email10">
	<text>
	From: cousin Buenice LBREAK
	To: T.Velas LBREAK
	subject: Read me for huge penass
	
	Do you want huge penas? you want huge penas, yu deserv huge penas open atachment for yor chance to win big
	Dont delaye only so many priz to won
	
	</text>
	<choice destination="attachment" text="open attachment"/>
	<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
	<choice destination="end" text="exit" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="attachment">
	<text>
	you open the attachment and a dozen flashing and strobing images in windows pop up all over the screen before the workstation flickers and replaces all of that with a big red warning message. LBREAK
			workstation locked, please contact your systems administrator. LBREAK	
	</text>
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="OMNICO_IIA_MALWARE" value="1" />
	<choice destination="end" text="exit" />		
	</page>
	
</Conversation>