<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			workstation online. LBREAK
			warning data corruption detected. LBREAK
		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="access mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="mailbox">
		<text>
			partial mailbox contents recovered LBREAK
			select message LBREAK
		</text>
		<choice destination="email0" text="access 713" />
		<choice destination="email2" text="access 811" />
		<choice destination="email4" text="access 1041" />
		<choice destination="email8" text="access 1127" />	
		<choice destination="email11" text="access 1611" />			
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email0">
		<text>
			From: mgr. Ansbel LBREAK
			To: all staff LBREAK
			subject: improper storage of synth accessories LBREAK

			To the responsible parties, LBREAK

			Please note that when not attached to the Omnico synthetic predator gynoid
			the class II genital attachment is to be stored safely in sub-level 2
			storage area B. Furthermore they're to be contained in a type-7 cargo
			box compliant with the standards for the preservation of flexible
			synth material. LBREAK

			It is not in fact appropriate to store them in an open topped plastic
			document tray perched precariously atop the door to Orrena's office.
			I should warn you that should you persist I will be forced to make
			some HR decisions. LBREAK

			I also should remind you that unlike our products I don't need an
			attachment for that, and I have space on my shelf for a 2 gallon jug.
			LBREAK

			-Ansbel. LBREAK

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>


	<page ID="email1">
		<text>
			From: Reshi LBREAK
			To: T. Velas LBREAK
			subject: dodgy units? LBREAK

			Is it just me or are the latest batch of synths from head office kinda
			off. I can't put my finger on it, but something about the way they
			talk and look at me is freaking me out. Reminds me a tad too much of
			my last girlfriend, or the boss for that matter.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email2">
		<text>
			From: T. Velas LBREAK
			To: Reshi LBREAK
			subject: RE dodgy units LBREAK

			It's probably just a new personality routine. Some gals like that kinda
			thing. Reset to the standard, though maybe you'd prefer some alone
			time with one if you're thinking too much of your last steady.
			Safer'n' asking the boss.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email3">
		<text>
			From: Reshi LBREAK
			To: T. Velas LBREAK
			subject: why build an omnico boutique out here? LBREAK

			I don't get it. We're setup in the ass end of nowhere. I mean, I get
			that we're technically on a trade route. But how many ships have
			passed by since I came here? And how many fewer bought any synths.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email4">
		<text>
			From: T. Velas LBREAK
			To: Reshi LBREAK
			subject: RE why build an omnico boutique out here? LBREAK

			Passing trade is down. But you're right it was never really high to begin
			with. I think the computer at head office figured this was one of the
			few unexploited market areas. I don't pretend to understand how it
			works, but it beats the old board of directors, trust me on this.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email5">
		<text>
			From: mgr. Ansbel LBREAK
			to: all LBREAK
			subject: missing ship LBREAK

			As you all know the ship from head office is now overdue. I'm keeping
			the comm open to try and flag down passing traffic to pass on a
			message of inquiry to head office but so far interstellar traffic
			appears to have taken a nose dive. It is however nothing to worry
			about, our stock and supplies will last a considerable amount of
			time. Especially with the lack of passing customers.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email6">
		<text>
			From: T. Velas LBREAK
			To: all LBREAK
			subject: help! LBREAK

			Someone locked me into testing with one and it's not stopping. I'm starting
			to get really sore..this isn't funny.

		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="email7">
		<text>
			From: mgr. Asbel LBREAK
			to: all LBREAK
			RE: preventing accidents LBREAK

			I'm going to presume the recent glitches involving the synth safeties
			are down to maintenance or defects rather than actual foul play for
			the time being. However it has become clear I need a contingency in
			place unless I want to explain to head office how I'm down half the
			staff due to the synths getting gurgle happy. As such I've pulled
			some strings to get us a reformation tube. It'll be locked in the
			back of the storage level unless the main computer detects synth's
			without their safeties. This is to stop you lot using it
			recreationally which I know you would do, and probably still will do
			despite my best efforts. Just remember I can blank patterns and I
			have a space on my shelf.
		</text>
		<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="email8">
	<text>
	From: mgr. Asbel LBREAK
	to:	all LBREAK
	RE: reprogramming synths LBREAK
	
	I'm addressing this to all rather than the specific person responsible, and yes, i know exactly who you are. No one else shares your taste in vids and the sooner you realize that the better. Nevertheless it must be stated that despite the lack of traffic here it is not permitted to attempt to modify proprietory omnico software running on the synth units as a way to pass the time. Not only is it meddling with company policy, not only are none of you properly certified, but having the synths randomly spouting lines of dialogue from that inane show is insufferable. Revert them to factory settings and do not attempt this chicanery again.
	</text>
	<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
	<choice destination="end" text="exit" />	
	</page>

	<page ID="email11">
	<text>
	From: mgr. Asbel LBREAK
	to:	all LBREAK
	RE: do not open untrusted attachments! LBREAK
	
	I should not have to go over basic IT policy but I will reiterate for those of you who must of spent the job interview under HR's desk instead of in front of it. Do not open attachments from any address other than a confirmed Omnico account. This runs the risk of allowing malware and viruses to infilitrate the network here, and I remind you that the synths have a wireless connection to the network and non omnico approved code has been known to cause them to act in an erratic or unsafe fashion.
	</text>
	<choice destination="mailbox" text="return to mailbox" />
	<choice destination="end" text="exit" />	
	</page>	
	
</Conversation>