<?xml version="1.0"?>
<journal>
	<entry name="quest0" ID="1" priority="1" title="crashlanded">
	Your escape pod has crashed on an alien world with no chance of rescue and little chance of encountering fellow humans. If you ever intend to return home to earth you will at a minimum need to get back into space. The escape pod is not going to be any help there. Even if its engines weren't burnt out they couldn't fight this world's pull. You've seen signs of alien technologies though, perhaps you can find an alternative spacecraft.
	</entry>
	<entry name="quest1" ID="1" priority="1" title="expanding horizons">
	Your new craft is servicable enough for allowing you to travel beyond the first alien world you've reached. But it's obvious that both the wreck of the heinlein and earth itself are impossibly distant unless you find a way of overcoming the light barrier. You can't build a wormhole drive like the Heinlein had, but it's clear from what you can see now that a star spanning alien civilization touched these worlds at some point. Perhaps it exists still, at any rate you will need to find a way of acquiring the FTL technology that must of made their civilization possible.
	</entry>
	<entry name="quest2" ID="1" priority="1" title="faster than lightspeed">
	You've done it. You've acquired an FTL engine capable of travelling faster than light. You should prepare for your trip but when ready you should engage the drive and see where it takes you. After that you'll need to find your way back to the Heinlein. The secret to this is inside the black box data for the escape pod. But back tracking its course from that data will require the abilities of a scientific genius.
	</entry>
	<entry name="adaptivecomputation" ID="120" priority="2" title="an adaptive computation core">
	You have met Jehari, the clever but absentminded scientist on freehaven. In order to decipher the black box data for you Jehari needs an adaptive computation core. She has told you that Robynn may know how to acquire one.
	</entry>
	<entry name="mallory" ID="120" priority="2" title="mallory should have the core">
	Robynn has directed you towards Mallory, a supplier of hers who lives on deck 4 of freehaven in the starlight apartments. You should find Mallory, Robynn says Mallory owes her a favour and should give you the core when you call it in on her behalf.
	</entry>
	<entry name="mallory_free" ID="120" priority="2" title="get mallory to give you the core">
	Mallory has been freed from a sticky situation brought about by owing a lot of money to some unsavoury people. She should be grateful, hopefully now you can get the adaptive computation core you need for Jehari.
	</entry>	
	<entry name="mallory_digested" ID="120" priority="2" title="mallory has been digested">
	Mallory, the person you were hoping to get the computation core from, has been digested by a criminal. You will probably have to go back to Robynn to ask if there's another way of getting the core.
	</entry>		
	<entry name="quest3" ID="1" priority="1" title="The wreck of the heinlein">
	You've backtracked the escape pod's course. This will let you jump to the system where the Heinlein met its end and investigate. You need the navigational data from the Heinlein in order to determine your position relative to earth and plot a course back home. The Heinlein is located at stellar coordinates -1,-1 and you will need to jump stellar north west from the original star system to reach it.
	</entry>
</journal>