<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The lil lixi pants, looking up at you from the ground after you
			have bested her. Her eyes and antenna flicker skittishly as she looks
			for an escape from you, twitching and squirming on the spot as you
			step closer.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="she'd make a good orgasm">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="it'd be so fitting to shove the bothersome critter up your ass">
					<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
	<text>
	The vicious lil bug had been a pain in your behind. So this really is only fitting, and you can only imagine all that exoskeletal chitin of hers will make her slide in niice and smooth. Her eyes widen as you <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				expose your ass and
			</conditional> twirl around to plant those cheeks right over her face. Her antenna squished and squeezed against the top of her head as you cram her face into your asscrack. The lixi finding herself squeezed between a rock and a soft voracious derriere that proves all the more apt to begin encompassing her as you start to settle down over her. The lil bug girl's hands going up to try and support your weight but unable to get the right leverage to stop your ass from schlorping down over your head. 
	</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="*shove her in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore1">
	<text>
	The lil bug girl chitters and squeels muffledly into the depths of your ass as you wriggle your hips atop her shoulders and schlorp the lixi deeper inside. The bug helpless to stop you forcing her up into your hungry behind though that's not to say she isn't putting up a commendable effort. She squirms and struggles and tries to stop your rear from encroaching over her shoulders and petite, hard shelled, breasts and her insectile wings.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore2" text="*all the way in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore2">
	<text>
	You straighten your legs, and in so doing foist the helpless bug up off the ground. Her legs flailing out from where she's embedded hips deep in your ass and then slowly being confined as you drag her inside with rthythmic clenching tugs of your inner muscles. Your hungry behind making it clear she's utterly outmatched as the cute insect demi is schlorped the rest of the way into your ass. Her writhing and squirming feet vanishing into your pucker with a final plop of your rump cheeks smacking back together. So satisfying, you can feel her still struggling about inside you as she's forced to curl up as a hefty bulge in your gut. You can only imagine how satisfying it'll be to grind down that exoskeleton and the rest of her down into nourishing mush.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore3" text="*conquer her, digest her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore3">
	<text>
	She squeels and shoves at your innards, making bulges in your gut and jostling it around. But she can't escape, doomed to digestion but unable to accept it. The lixi's body enduring your enzyme assault, her exoskeleton slowly softening and corroding under your digestive processes. It takes an exquisitely long time as you gurgle her with increasing fury before she final succumbs. But when she does succumb it's with a rolling gurgling slosh as her armour dissolves away and your enzymes permeate and dissolve every inch of her in minutes. The lixi turning soft and still, quiet except for glorps of digestion.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			Quite the lusty little thing isn't she, well you have a perfect use
			for a lusty little thing. Advancing over her and then
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				lowering your pants and underwear before
			</conditional>
			starting to rub yourself down there. The lil buggy girl becoming
			aroused at the sight of your moist nethers, but you want more than
			just that inside you. And as you lower over her her optimistic
			stroking of herself and leaning up to lick turns suddenly frantic as
			you press down over her. The bug girl's antenna pressed against the
			top of her head as it disappears up between your netherlips with a
			lewd squelch, a squeel from her and a moan from you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="deeper!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			The lixi squirms helplessly as your lustful netherlips claim
			more of
			her, sliding easily and smoothly over her slick chitinous
			exoskeleton, forcing her into your clenching softness as you lower
			yourself over her squeezing her between yourself and the floor
			beneath. The bug girl's antenna twitching deep inside your womb as
			she starts to swell you out. Your voracious netherlips sliding down
			the petite insectdemi towards her waistline as she's forced to curl
			up within you. Her exoskeleton for now unyielding against the
			clenching massage of your womb around the upper half of her body,
			trapping her little wings to wetly twitch against the grasp of your
			womb.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="all the way" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
		<text>
			Halfway in it'd be easy to take her little body in the rest of
			the way.
			Clenching, drawing her in more with your passage now than by
			squeezing her against the floor. Her feet eventually sliding up off
			of the floor and twitching and dangling about. The lixi squirming
			helplessly as you rub your middle and with a final schlurp draw those
			feet up into your pussy. You squeeze and rub over her firm chitin
			clad little form as she squirms and squeeks helplessly within you.
			She's at your mercy, and it'll be interesting to see how long it'll
			take for her chitin to soften as you set about turning her to a
			splash of cum. Or you could just enjoy holding her like this and see
			if she calms down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthEnd" text="gush her" />
		<choice destination="unbirthEndo0" text="hold her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthEndo0">
		<text>
			You get comfortable sat down with her squirming in your gravid middle.
			Her distressed squeeks and movements going on for a time as the lil
			herm tires herself out.
			You give your round tummy an almost doting pat as she slows down and
			just pants, wrapped in your overpowering heat and all tuckered out.
			Perhaps it's starting to dawn on her that you have no intention of
			liquidating her, took her long enough, silly thing. Though now she
			seems to have realized it you can feel her shifting. The bug girl
			moving around though not to try and squirm out it seems but just to
			get more comfortable. You wonder whether your fluids soaking her
			exoskeleton'll do her some good, she seems content to bask in your
			though as your soft womb walls snugly press all around her. This is
			much nicer.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthEndo1"
			text="hold her for a bit longer, then let her out" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthEndo1">
		<text>
			You fall into a sort of doze while holding the bug girl, feeling her
			squirm now and then. But after a while you decide it's probably time
			to let her out again and so you get up from where you were resting
			and rub over the bulge to rouse her. Once she's good and ready you
			squat down and part your legs, starting to birth the cute insect demi
			back into the world gradually. Her body easing out from between your
			legs inch by inch and slick and glossy with your juices, her carapace
			gleaming when it catches the light. She seems reluctant to come out
			at first but soon helps you by wriggling her way out of your snatch.
			The bug soon a sticky heap in front of you, her antenna flicking to
			dislodge the feminine juices covering them as she looks up at you and
			flushes. Seems she enjoyed that, but it looks like she'll need
			sometime to recover.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<choice destination="end" text="such a cute thing makes a good womb pet" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthEnd">
		<text>
			The bug girl's squirms as your womb begins to clench and
			rthythmically
			work her over are delightful to feel and you settle down
			to enjoy
			them. Seated on the ground one hand strays between your legs,
			to play
			over your netherlips as you feel her futile struggles. On and
			on, she
			struggles, you squeeze and her form endures allowing you to
			draw the
			pleasure out. In fact as you reach your first climax with a
			gasping
			cry you feel her movements within the crushing grip of your
			womb as
			your nethers spasm and stain the stones with sexual fluids.
			You take
			a moment to catch your breath, and again she endures as you
			orgasm a
			second time and your womb squeezes down upon her, yet feel
			her soften
			and yield slightly. The relentless squirms of your lusty
			little womb
			fodder drawing you on as you work your fingers into your
			snatch again
			and go to work for a third time, moaning..gasping,
			panting..and
			finally as your third orgasm rocks through you you feel
			something
			give, your spasming sex crushing inwards and you hear her
			squeek and
			then abruptly dissolve. Her weakened chitin now as pliant
			as butter,
			her form crushed into lusty liquids in a single rolling and
			blissful
			contraction. Lixi remnants gushing out of your sex to
			splatter over
			the floor forming a thick goopy puddle in which
			fragments of soft
			chitin can be seen floating. As you contemplate your
			handiwork you
			slide a finger along your soaked inner thighs and up to
			your lips.
			The bug girl breeder for all her sexual appetite, has been
			consumed
			utterly by a sexual appetite of your voracious snatch. An
			appetite
			far more encompassing and capable in getting what it wanted.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>