<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
		<preference fetish="demis" />
		<preference fetish="herms" />
		<text>
			Weakened by poison you've fallen before your diminutive opponent,
			ending up in an undignified sprawl on your front. The horny bug girl
			fluttering and bounding eagerly, landing in a squat over you.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				yanking off your clothing and exposing your hips to the air before
			</conditional>
			grabbing her shaft and stroking, eagerly and vigorously jerking
			herself to hardness as she uses her other hand to keep you from
			wriggling away even as she transitions into rubbing that cock of hers
			against the softness of your bare skin.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="get fucked" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		<text>
			The small herm can be felt fumbling eagerly. one hand rubbing
			and
			stroking around your hips and thighs and then grabbing one of your
			legs, angling it up and out a bit exposing your nethers afore you feel
			her middle press against your rear and her modest endowment arcing up
			to press into your snatch. the horny wee critter enacting the most
			grievous violation on your doped body. The drug of her poison meaning
			you're in no fate to resist as she begins to thrust in and out of
			your sex vigorously.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="*try to resist anyway*" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="*think of england*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			The small herm can be felt fumbling around between your legs,
			but
			swiftly she makes a confused disapointed noise not finding what
			she
			hoped for. But undeterred she changes her aim up and inwards at
			your
			exposed bottom, pressing into your ass with her modest endowment.
			The
			lixi soon going to town on your derriere's tight hole instead,
			raping
			your rear while her poison leaves you in no fit to resist her
			actions.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="*try to resist anyway*" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="*think of england*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			As she starts to thrust into you you decide that maybe it's not
			that
			bad to be used for her pleasure. She is after all very cute and
			wonderfully sexually aggressive. At your mhmming and lack of
			resistance she chitters and gives you a pat on the back. The lixi
			taking her time, making up in enthusiasm for her modest size as she
			fucks you eagerly and lustily. Her chitters and chirrs of delight
			becoming more eager as she ruts, but alas all must come to an end and
			soon you feel her cock spurt and spasm pouring sticky white cream
			deep inside your warm body. You shiver in delight at the sensation
			and feel her drive her cock deep inside you and nestle it there, not
			pulling out even as her orgasm subsides. And soon you feel the reason
			why as strange hot sensations creep out sensually from her cock
			within you, starting to anchor your hips to her crotch and spreading
			out to change you. The little bug girl clearly intent on turning you
			into a longer and girthier cock between her legs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="acceptCTF0" text="acceptance" />
		<choice destination="struggleCTF1" text="struggle" />
	</page>

	<page ID="acceptCTF0">
		<text>
			You find yourself blushing rather than struggling at the
			thought. While
			it's perhaps not a future you visualized for yourself
			before now as
			her blood begins to flow in your veins you find yourself
			looking
			forward to swaying between her legs. The lixi seems confused
			by your
			murring stretching underneath her, as you wriggle to get
			comfortable
			and stretch your toes out only to feel them curl inwards
			into fleshy
			lumps. The lixi's curiousity you allay with a stroke,
			reaching up and
			back to caress her, meeting her gaze askance and
			letting her see the
			acceptance in your eyes. The lixi's face suddenly
			breaking out into a
			delighted grin and she smooches your arm afore
			chirring and stroking
			her hands along your veiny flanks. Her hands
			joining your own just as
			your murrs and her chirrs and clicks of
			pleasure form a duet of
			delight as two become one in so naughty a
			fashion.
		</text>
		<choice destination="acceptCTF1" text="wonderful changes" />
	</page>

	<page ID="acceptCTF1">
		<text>
			Gradually you feel yourself merging into a part of her body.
			Under her eager
			hands, her excitement, pleasure and eagerness all too
			contagious and
			you find yourself urging her on in making you into her
			cock. Your
			legs gradually folding upwards and inwards, folding at the
			knees and
			then again until they form into indistinguishable masses of
			flesh
			extruding a sack around themselves. Your hands and her own
			gliding
			down in delight to feel over her new fertile balls made of
			your legs,
			churning with hot seed to spread her genes. You feel her
			tongue as
			she gives you a smooch on the back and then licks, feeling
			your upper
			body begin to change. Your torso going veiny under her
			hands, your
			spine softening and your inside organs simplifying into
			hot throbbing
			dickmeat and cumtubing with messy sounding squeelches.
			You taste her
			musky cum in your mouth and know it wont be much longer,
			before both of you
			are satisfied with the completion of your
			transformation.
		</text>
		<choice destination="acceptCTF2" text="cum through me!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="acceptCTF2">
		<text>
			The bug girl seems to take your desires even without knowing the
			words,
			and rocks her hips grinding her body against your tubular
			torso, her
			immense new shaft of veiny cockflesh. Only your arms marr
			the
			perfection of her new dick and as she strokes over your flanks you
			obligingly press your arms to your sides. You feel your hands
			sticking against your flanks, knowing you'll not need them in your
			new role you relax and murr as the change works up your arms. Soon
			those limbs are stuck to your sides entirely, sinking away as your
			head swells out and the lixi buzzes and chitters in anticipation of
			the completion of your transformation. Your form becoming a bit more
			manageable between her legs as your neck and shoulders turn to
			foreskin and your face finishes puffing out into a pre drooling bell.
			Finally you feel it as your eyes close and sink away, sealing you
			into darkness. Though with the sensations of her stroking hands and
			the sounds of her delight you find yourself not really missing the
			sensation of sight that's been taken from you. You're her new cock, a
			great big third leg for the lil hermy bug girl and her strokes over
			your form are ever so wonderful to experience.
		</text>
		<choice destination="acceptGO" text="climax and aftermath" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="acceptGO">
		<text>
			Her hands stroke vigorously and you throb with the pleasure you
			share
			with her. Such pleasures that reach crescendo, a rising climax
			that
			roils and pulses through you sending forth splatters of hot jizz
			to
			stain the stones and make the breeder bug buzz in delight. After a
			small eternity of mind smotheringly intense the climax tapers off,
			having lost count of the spurts you wonder whether all such uses will
			be as astoundingly overhwleming in future. Gradually you soften and
			turn flaccid between her legs. You're more manageable now, far larger
			than what she had before but not so large she'd have trouble moving.
			The bug girl gives her new cock a pat, happy that you willingly gave
			yourself in the end to increase her dick size she slinks off into the
			shadows. When you're next aware she's showing you off in her mating
			display to one of the large female lixi, your form hard under her
			stroking hands and swaying and bobbing with her animalistic gyrations
			and hip thrusts. The display must of been pleasing to the eye though
			as soon, you get to experience sex from the perspective of a cock.
			The breeder getting her chance to mate and thrust you into the
			willing holes of the large Lixi girl, spurting cum through you to
			pass her genes on and create the next generation of bugs. And this
			was not the first sexual conquest your body serving as her dick size
			led to, again...and again, you feel her go through the display and
			plunge you in and out of willing and tight Lixi nethers. Again and
			again you shoot her loads of cum into a succession of females. As
			fates go, one could hardly say your adventure ended badly. You are
			this pintsize cassanova's cock, and it's certainly an exciting place
			to be!
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<check ID="struggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggleCTF0" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			You are no ones rape toy, and so despite the poison weakening
			you you
			gather your resolve and try to squirm out from under her.. the
			chitin
			clad violator clicking and hissing at you angrily as you try to
			get
			away. But somehow you gain the coordination and strength to grab
			ahold her exoskeleton clad form and shove her back, her cock popping
			free from your body as she stumbles and fwumps to the ground. However
			she is quick to recover and she glares not so easily thwarted and
			attempts to re-leap atop you, luckily while most of her is hard one
			particular part is soft and delicate and vulnerable to a good kick.
			The lexi falls to the ground truly beaten back now whimpering she
			curls up into a ball of agony clutching herself and giving you time
			to get away and recover some of your strength. Though she's liable to
			recover herself from that kick before too long.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleCTF0">
		<text>
			You are no one's rape toy, and you struggle against the one
			violating
			you. Hearing her chitter and click angrily as you squirm
			around, but
			despite your efforts your body is weak and the grip of her
			poisons
			are strrong. You feel her thrust hard within you, cock sliding
			deep and
			then being held there. And then you feel her true intent
			start to be
			enacted, veins permeating out from the insectgirl's thick
			dick..merging to your hot snug insides. Your hips starting to fuse to
			her crotch as she chirrs and chitters more lustfully now and strokes
			over you..and you realize the truth, you're not going to be her rape
			toy..you're going to be her COCK.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleCTF1" text="oh no!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleCTF1">
		<text>
			You attempt to struggle at the sensation of your body fusing to
			her
			loins but the drugs make you weak and the sensations of her clawed
			hands stroking along your increasingly veiny and pale sides is
			awfully distracting. Your torso becoming more sensitive even as your
			limbs begin to weaken and turn limp and nonresponsive. Though not
			before your attempts to push yourself off of the cock you're now
			fused with sinks your hands into her crotch. The lixi chirring and
			rocking her hips as she transforms you, grinding her own sack against
			your thighs, sticking them in place..her scrotal flesh beginning to
			stretch and slide up over your legs. Her loins engulfing them,
			immersing them entirely in the lusty heat and visibly showing the
			bulges and outlines and contours of your legs pushing out the inside
			of her sack before your legs begin to devolve entirely into a fertile
			and virile pair of balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleCTF2" text="arms are next" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleCTF2">
		<text>
			the diminutive lixi herm chitters happily and wraps her arms
			around you
			as she leans back. The bug girl settling into a seated
			position, your
			upper body jutting from her hips as your lower legs
			change. the bug
			girl reaching down to caress and stroke over her sack
			containing your
			legs as they convert entirely into her balls, the heft
			of which seem
			to please her a great deal even as the changes creep up
			your torso
			now. your arms oozing into your sides, merging into a pair
			of
			throbbing veins flanking your torso as it becomes increasingly her
			throbbing breeding tool. Your mouth full of pre as the bug strokes
			her hands up towards your head, coaxing the changes up beneath her
			eager palms as she chitters gleefully and your face begins to change.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleCTF3" text="no going back now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleCTF3">
		<text>
			Your face changes, regressing, swelling out and simplifying as
			your
			features are erased. Your identity subsumed by your new purpose
			as
			the lil hermy insect girl vigorously jerks off her new dick, and
			truly that's all you are now as you're sealed into darkness by the
			removal of your eyes. You're a cock, a throbbing shaft in her hands
			as she strokes over her now much more impressive endowment. You feel
			her climax boiling, the last of your agency keeping her gushing
			orgasm at bay. But as she jerks off you feel pleasure, her pleasure,
			filling your being with every stroke of her palms and every throb of
			her heartbeat that pulses through you. Her balls tense, and you feel
			your will eroding as you realize, your body is hers, your
			purpose...is this. the lixi lets out a hissing chittering cry of
			bliss as she climaxes, her cum erupting through you, splattering the
			ground in thick jizz.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleCTFGO" text="aftermath" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleCTFGO" noReform="true">
		<text>
			The lixi's orgasm tapers off steadily, last spurts jetting forth
			from
			her new cock and you're dimly aware even as she stands up and you
			soften between her thighs. Your perceptions turning vague for a time,
			flaccid as her new hefty third leg you're unaware of her search for a
			female. The lixi breeder presenting herself to one of those tall and
			imposing female workers. The bug woman watching the herm's eager
			display, the breeder stroking herself to hardness making you engorge
			jutting and swaying and bouncing from her hips as she strokes and
			gyrates.. the female must of liked what she saw for soon that
			gyration and swaying gives way to thrusting and the sensation of hot
			wonderful nethers wrapped tightly around you as you're put to use.
			The lixi's new cock netting her breeding rights with this female, and
			many others, as you're used to shoot load after load into a
			succession of willing holes you find yourself forgetting your old
			life. Your existence as anything but her cock a distant dream, but
			you could hardly be happier than you are now as this insectherm's big
			and well used dick.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>