<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
	<!--insulted-->
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="insulted" />
	<text>
	Her highness L'aang narrows her gaze at you, she doesn't say anything..simply radiates hostility in her glare and agitated twitching.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="*back off*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
	<!--is servant meetings-->	
	<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="laang_servant" />	
	<text>
	L'aang gives you a toothsome smile of pleasure at your approach "Hello, How is my favourite servant?" she asks, motioning you closer and scrutizing you possessively. Even giving you a little sniff.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="$I'm fine mistress, but i was wondering if you were hungry">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<preference fetish="females" />
		<preference fetish="anthros" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I'm fine mistress, just popping in to say hi"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
			<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="9" />
	
	<text>
	"For you? Always my delicious servant." she says and licks her lips, leaning in to pass that tongue of hers over your chest "Lets put these gorgeous tits of yours where they belong, bulging out my belly." she says with an anticipatory murr as she rises out of her seat <conditional>"Now, strip for your mistress"
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" /></conditional>
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="$Of course mistress"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"For you? Always my delicious servant." she says and licks her lips "Lets get you where you belong shall we?" she says and smiles as she looks you over and rises from her seat <conditional>"Now, strip for your mistress"
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" /></conditional>
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="$Of course mistress"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	Soon, oh so very soon, you're standing naked before your mistress. Naked and ready for her to consume, the voracious reptilian royal standing likewise before you..her gaze drinking in your form, her snout moving closer to breath in your scent and taste your neck "Your mistress thanks you for this servant, you will be a pleasing meal." she says, placing her hands on your shoulders. She breathes in deeply of your scent for a moment longer, then her neck arches down and her jaws part to stretch over the top of your head. Her sweltering hot saliva drooling copiously down around your ears and soaking your <macro id="hair_desc_short" /> hair. L'aang moaning softly as she licks over your face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*food for your mistress*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Your mistress savours you for a few glorious seconds before starting to gulp you up into her royal throat. That long neck of hers serving to wonderfully outline your head, then shoulders as she stretches her jaws and works them down over you. Her hands holding you in place now grasping on your hips as she licks her way down over your body.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="*deeper in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
			<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="9" />
	<text>
		The jaws of the A'shani stretch to encompass your ample and copious tits. L'aang letting out a more pleased groan around your maw filling breasts as she works them fully into her mouth, licking over them before turning them into a hefty bulge in her neck. The bulge of your wondrous rack sliding on down through her as she starts to gulp down more and more of you, reaching your waist around the time your head starts to slide past her collarbone, chest and nears her belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="*oh yes, get ate*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	The A'shani works her mouth down around your chest, smoothly encompassing your assets and letting her tongue roam over them as she gobbles you up. Your head sliding deeper down her throat, leading the way to the wonderful belly of the reptilian princess. Your head continues sliding deeper as she works to gulp down more and more of you, reaching your waist around the time your head starts to slide past her collarbone, chest and nears her belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="*oh yes, get ate*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	You start to slide your way down into the welcoming embrace of mistress's belly. Your chest squeezing behind her own nicely sizable scale clad breasts and then spilling down into her gut as well. The voracious reptile groping your ass as she helps squeeze you down into her belly, bulging out and swelling your predatory mistress nicely. Soon she's straightening up her neck and powerfully hefting your legs up into the air. Your upper body bulging her neck, before those bulges are replaced by those of your thighs..then calves, then ankles and feet as you slither easily down her long throat and pile entirely into her belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore5" text="$How was your meal mistress?"/>
	</page>

	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="9" />
	<text>
	"Oh delicious..mhmm..you feel so good, stretching me out." she growls and strokes her claws over the outline of your body in her gut before pressing in and expertly squeezing you around with her stomach muscles so that you're facing forwards..your legs press out against the sides of her bellies and your magnificent tits on display as a pair of bulges framed below her own "That's it....i'm sure you don't mind your mistress showing you off." says L'aang as she gropes over the shape of your tits pressing out her thinly scaled belly and even licks and nuzzles at the bulge of one of them as she revels in having you inside herself.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore6A" text="$not at all..happy to be of service."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore6A">
	<text>
	"Good, just the right attitude..mhmm, but I can only hold off on melting such a treat as yourself for so long." says L'aang, continuing to possessively rub over the bulges of your tits as she stand and yes, poses for any onlookers to see your shape exquisitely outlined in her belly. Your voracious A'shani mistress looking incredibly proud of her tum for a few minutes before true to her word she can't hold back anymore. Her stomach beginning to gurgle and glorp, pressing and kneading all around you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore7A" text="$Ah, yes..that's it..digest me mistress"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore7A">
	<text>
	"Of course my delicious servant, become one with me..let me melt away your curves." says L'aang licking her lips and continuing to grope over her belly as you're squeezed snugly within. Her digestive enzymes soaking into your flesh, powerful stomach muscles grinding and squeezing over your form as the reptilian A'shani moans in delight, a sound you cannot help but add your own muffled voice to from within her as you feel yourself softening.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore8A" text="$yes, i can feel it..all over, digest me!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore8A">
	</text>
	L'aang continues to squeeze and rub over the bulges, and strokes over the sides of her belly as your shape begins to lose definition and round out. Your predatory mistress moaning and occasionally leaning in to nuzzle at your softening titbulges as they become more and more indistinguishable from the smooth curves of her tum.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore8A" text="$it's wonderful..it's..wonder.."/>	
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore9A">
	<text>
	Her highness princess L'aang, sighs out a long drawn out satisfied murr as she feels you glorp away. Her gut turning round and smooth as you're reduced to a nourishing liquid. That gut of hers starting to compact and shrink away "You really are a magnificent meal my servant." she says approvingly and then settles into her chair happily to enjoy the warm satisfying sensations of your nutrition coursing through her veins as her gut flattens out.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<text>
	"Oh delicious..mhmm you fit so well inside me." she growls out in pleasure, stroking her claws over the contours of her belly in which you're tightly confined and curled up. The possessive touch of her inner muscles and her stroking claws from outside reinforcing your place as a glorious meal for your mistress. L'aang letting out little delighted noises as she rubs her belly and it gurgles softly around you, soaking you with her enzymes as she leans in to nuzzle and kiss against the bulge of your head in her gut.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore6B" text="*let her stomach claim you*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore6B">
	<text>
	L'aang moans as her belly starts to gurgle more noisily around you, starting to soften you up with her relentless digestive processes. Your shape losing definition even as you squirm blissfully inside of her. Her claws continue to stroke over the curves of her gut as gradually they begin to round out under her kneading hands..it won't be long now, won't be long until you're one with her highness..nourishing and sustaining your mistress.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore9A" text="*soon...you can feel yourself going*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
	<!--subsequent meetings-->
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="talked" />
	<text>
	L'aang smiles "Greetings again. What brings you to me?" she asks, patient and magnanimous as she holds court at her table in the bar.
	</text>
	<choice destination="what" text="$So what are you doing here?"/>
	<choice destination="serve0" text="$would you be interested in taking me on as a servant your highness?">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="servant_info" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"	flag="servant_check" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Nothing, merely paying my respects in passing"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve0">
	<text>
	L'aang pauses a bit, then smiles "Well naturally, why wouldn't you. I may be willing to give you the honour of serving me. But first, I'd like to ask some questions. Purely to determine your suitability you understand. How good are you at organization? There are a great many things in a royal's life which they really must not be troubled with. Keeping Itineraries, schedules, that sort of tedium."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve0A" text="$I would say I'm a highly organized person and happy to help organize for others"/>
	<choice destination="serve0B" text="$organizing things? I have trouble putting on matching socks in the morning"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve0A">
	<text>
	"Excellent. I am pleased to hear it."
	</text>
	<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="value" value="1" />		
	<choice destination="serve1" text="*next question*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="serve0B">
	<text>
	"Well. I suppose I can't expect everything. This isn't the homeworld and it's not like you were properly trained." says L'aang.
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve1" text="*next question*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve1">
	<text>
	L'aang smiles "Now. As an A'shani I have particular needs that you might not be familiar with, and as a royal I certain deserve my pampering. So I will ask, how are you when it comes to scales and claws. Polishing, cleaning, trimming, waxing, oiling. A finely bred A'shani such as myself needs a lot of attention to be at my best dear."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve1A" text="$I know my way around caring for a creature as magnificently scale clad as yourself"/>
	<choice destination="serve1B" text="$I just need to scrub you down with a lump of pumice right? that'll sort it out"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve1A">
	<text>
	L'aang smiles with genuine pleasure and surprise "Well, you truly are an unexpected find. We'll see if your skills live up to your words. But you certainly express the right attitude."
	</text>
	<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="value" value="1" />		
	<choice destination="serve2" text="*next question*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve1B">
	<text>
	L'aang actually winces, flinching back a little forming a more severe arch with her neck before continuing on with a forced bland tone as she untenses and shifts back into a relaxed posture "Not quite, still one cannot have everything and I suppose I was expecting too much."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve2" text="*next question*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve2">
	<text>
	L'aang looks you over and then asks "And this is the final question and I believe perhaps the most pertinent one. When consumed do you know how to please your predator? I don't want a passive meal who simply sits inside me and waits to digest. Make no mistake, serving as my meal is part of serving me."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve2A" text="$I will make you feel good I promise, I know how to squirm just right and i'm looking forward to feeding you"/>
	<choice destination="serve2B" text="$I'm not overly enamoured by being food and I prefer to just get it over with if it happens"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve2A">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="9" />
	<text>
	"Oh yes, that's what I like to hear. Especially from a nicely endowed meal such as yourself." she says and glances at your chest "I look forward to feeling those bulging out my belly."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve3" text="*final decision*"/>
	</page>

	
	<page ID="serve2A">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, yes. I will enjoy you, perhaps I will even enjoy you frequently." she says and smiles in delight as she looks you over.
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve3" text="*final decision*"/>	
	</page>
	
	
	<page ID="serve2B">
	<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="9" />
	<text>
	"A pity, and you do have such magnificently tasty assets." says L'aang, making an uncharacteristically crude cupping motion with her palm at about chest level "But I suppose the proper attitude might take time to cultivate."
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve3" text="*final decision*"/>
	</page>

	
	<page ID="serve2B">
	<text>
	"A pity, but i suppose the proper attitude might take time to cultivate." says L'aang unruffled by this it seems.
	</text>
	<choice destination="serve3" text="*final decision*"/>
	</page>	

	<page ID="serve3">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="greaterthan" value="3"	flag="value" />
	<text>
	L'aang smiles "Well on balance I think I would be happy to have you as a servant. Alas my diminished means are such that I will not be able to keep you here with me. You will unfortunately have to see to your own upkeep, in gracious recognition of this I will allow you to come and go as you please. Though I do expect you will be here frequently to attend to your duties. I know this is discouraging, to serve an A'shani who cannot fulfil her obligations. But nevertheless, do you accept?"
	</text>
		<choice destination="serve4A" text="$Yes, I would still like to serve you L'aang"/>
		<choice destination="serve4B" text="$No, I must refuse your offer"/>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="servant_check" value="1" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve4A">
	<text>
	L'aang smiles at that in delight "Mhmm, yes. Then I am happy to accept and honour you with the position of my servant. You may have the privilege of calling me mistress."
	</text>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="laang_servant" value="1" />		
		<choice destination="end" text="$Thankyou, mistress."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve4B">
	<text>
	L'aang looks, disappointed..but nods "Of course, you wouldn't want to serve an A'shani who couldn't afford to keep you clothed, rested and fed. I understand." she says and then smiles weakly "I respect your decision."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Sorry, I'll be going now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="serve3">
	<text>
	"I'm afraid I've thought about it. And you really don't make the grade for a servant to an A'shani of my standing. A royal must have standards and you are I'm afraid below them. I am afraid I must refuse your desire to be my servant. Though I'm sure with training and diligence you will make another A'shani very happy some day."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="servant_check" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, Farewell then"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	The reptilian looks up from her affectation of disinterest and turns her gaze in your direction. She seems to be assessing you and doesn't seem impressed "Hmm, and who has the honour of approaching me?"
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="introduction" text="$my name is PNAME"/>
	<choice destination="honour" text="$the honour of approaching you? who the hell do you think you are?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="introduction">
	<text>
	"I suppose your name is important very well, and I am her highness princess L'aang of the A'shan people." she informs you regally "You may refer to me as your highness, or possibly mistress should you have such a privilege bestowed upon you."
	</text>
	<choice destination="bar" text="I cant help but notice your highness you appear to be holding court in a bar"/>
	<choice destination="respect" text="Then I am indeed honoured to meet you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="honour">
	<text>
	The reptilian bristles slightly "I am an A'shani royal, L'aang princess of the race and the empire. And you are neither blessed with royal title nor elevated to the race of A'shan. You will accord me due respect."
	</text>
	<choice destination="respect" text="Fine, I apologize."/>
	<choice destination="bar" text="What sort of royalty holds court in a bar?"/>
	<choice destination="disrespect" text="You must be joking, I'm not about to respect a lizard giraffe with delusions of grandeur"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="bar">
	<text>
	"I am temporarily inconvenienced by political turmoil. But my status is undiminished, nor is the respect I am to be afforded. In time I will return to my throne, to dole out favours to those who aid me and punishment to those who slighted me." says L'aang, remarkably unruffled by the question. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="respect" text="I see, forgive my inquiry then your highness."/>
	<choice destination="disrespect" text="$You're a delusional lizard playing pretend in other words"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="respect">
	<text>
	L'aang graces you with a smile "And they say non a'shani are uncultured barbarians. You are well met then Vu'loi." says her highness "What brings you in front of me?" 
	</text>
	<choice destination="word0" text="$What does Vu'loi mean?"/>
	<choice destination="curiousity" text="$Just curiousity, you are very different from the other creatures here"/>
	<choice destination="what" text="$I was more wondering what you were doing here."/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Nothing, having made your acquaintance i will take my leave"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="what">
	<text>
	"Well, I could spend my exile here cowering in my quarters. Or I could hold court at this table to see what comes of it. Perhaps I will find ones willing to aid me, do for me boons that I will return in kind when once more upon my throne. A throne i will regain all the sooner if one is willing to aid me in that. Or perhaps those who wish the privilege of being one of my." she pauses and seems to change what she was about to say "Servants." she finishes with a smile.
	</text>
	<choice destination="servant" text="$A servant?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, I wish you luck in your endeavours"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="servant">
	<text>
	"Well of course, any of you should be honoured to have the privilege of serving an A'shani of such distinguished lineage and breeding as I. Alas, many are blind to this obvious fact. Still, it has been a while." she says, looking thoughtful and maybe a little despondent for a moment as she contemplates this fact.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="servant_info" value="1" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="$thankyou for sharing but I have to go"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="word0">
	<text>
	"Ah, it's as simple as to mean non A'shani." says L'aang with an expressive neck flex and a slow blink at being asked about it. Might be a slip of hers.
	</text>
	<choice destination="word1" text="$and that's all it means?"/>
	<choice destination="what" text="$Okay, and now I'm curious what you're doing here in this bar."/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, I need to be somewhere else now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="word1">
	<text>
	L'aang's poise faulters only a moment as she hesitates "Well, it did imply something of a nature of inferiority and that your place was to serve as slaves and food. We've of course in our enlightened benevolence dropped our expectations that you serve in all cases." she says and smiles. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="what" text="$Okay, and now I'm curious what you're doing here in this bar."/>	
	<choice destination="pride" text="$kind of an arrogant position to take"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, I'll be going now."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="curiousity">
	<text>
	"Well naturally, the inner grace and outer perfection of an A'shani would draw the eye of even those most blind to the concept of beauty." says L'aang.
	</text>
	<choice destination="what" text="$Okay, and now I'm curious what you're doing here in this bar."/>
	<choice destination="pride" text="$you seem a little, prideful."/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, well I've drunk my fill of that outer perfection. I'll take my leave."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pride">
	<text>
	"Oh please, it's not my fault you weren't born A'shani. Do not take out your envy on me." says L'aang with a bemused scolding tone.
	</text>
	<choice destination="what" text="$Okay, and now I'm curious what you're doing here in this bar."/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Well if that's how you see it i'll take my envy elsewhere."/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="disrespect">
	<text>
	L'aang's head darts backwards in shock and she stares, momentarily surprised but that surprise swiftly morphs into anger and those widened eyes narrow into a glare. "You dare...there was a time when I would have you flayed for such an insult..begone from my presence. Go away and stay away. With every breath you take I grow more and more of the opinion it is wrong for your kind to run free." 
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="insulted" value="1" />		
	<choice destination="end" text="$Not a problem, staying away from you will be a pleasure"/>
	</page>
	
</Conversation>