<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="DICEROLL" value="5" />	
		<text>
		The harpy mhmms and bounds over into your personal space "Well hello stranger, welcome to our village"
		</text>
		<choice destination="prelude0" text="$ah and this is a welcome?"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="$ah, yes thanks.."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude0">
	<text>
	The avian presses up against, you encircling her wings around you and rubbing her bared breasts against you "Not yet? but it can be, I'd love to welcome you properly. Visitors to our village can be a lot of fun." she says and darts her head in to lick your ear "It's the fingers you see."
	</text>
	<choice destination="prelude1" text="$fingers..sounds fun."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude1">
	<text>
	"Mhmm lets see you use them" she coos in your ear "Tongue too" she strokes her wings over your back and flushes fluffing herself up afore nibbling your ear lightly and letting you trace your hands ways down her body, starting at those wonderful breasts..the softness of her flesh, the perkyness of her nipples. Only to trace further down as she nibbles on your ear some more, your hands reaching her hips and hooking to her skirt and easing it downwards.
	</text>
	<choice destination="prelude2" text="*keep exploring*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude2">
	<text>
	The harpies skirt flutters down beneath her claws as she plants a kiss upon your cheek "that's it." she says and mhmms "I can tell, you want to please me." she coos hotly and strokes her wings over your shoulders as your fingers slide up between her thighs. Your hand caressing from one inside thigh to another before reaching her mound, delving into her hot and sopping wet netherlips. She's already aroused by the time you get to her and you hear her gasp in delight as you finger her, then begin to slowly slip down onto your knees.
	</text>
	<choice destination="prelude3" text="*taste of honey*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude3">
	<text>
	You breathe in deep the scent of her nethers as you come to face with her intimate treasures. The scent and her delighted cooing draws you in, your tongue flicking out to lap over her netherlips. Her gasp urging your hands up to grasp and grope her rear as you delve deeper into her flavoursome and naughty parts. She rubs over the top of your head eagerly as you pleasure her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="prelude4" text="*slick endeavours*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude4">
	<text>
	You lick deeper into her nethers and hear her gasp wonderfully above you, her sexual folds yielding up more lustful fluids to coat your tongue and slather your chin. You can feel her tensing and flexing in a way that heralds her impending orgasm as you work expertly down over her crotch with your lips and tongue. Won't be long, won't be long at all now as you hear her utter "Oh yes..you're good at this...you belong there."
	</text>
	<choice destination="prelude5" text="*sticky finishes*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="prelude5">
	<text>
	The harpy's gasping coos are coming closer and closer together. And before you know it she lets out a screech of bliss, wrapping her thighs around your skull and holding you in place as her nethers erupt with gushes of pleasure. The clear sticky lovejuice coating your face and splattering down over your chest as she shudders over the top of you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="*she lets you up*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		"Greetings stranger" the harpy chirps and smiles "Welcome to our village."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="$Well met birdy"/>
	</page>

</Conversation>