<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Vala" value="0" />
		<assertnot evaluate="isCompanion" />
		<assertion evaluate="isFaction" faction="player" />
		<text>
		Vala sheathes her shortsword and stands at attention at your approach "Hello again PNAME. Do you have need of me?"
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporta" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="join" text="$I want you to travel with me again">
			<assertion evaluates="companionSlotFree" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="$Nothing at the moment" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<!--allied with elves, can recruit -->
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance"
			value="1" />
		<text>
		The stoic elven woman glares at you as you enter, sheathing her sword and standing up to greet you. "Hail outsider, I was at the ceremony. You have decided to join us in our fight against those reptilians. Although I won't pretend to understand your strange devices, it is an undeniable fact you've helped our village with it's troubles. Hence I must ask you this. Have you need of a warrior on your journey? I find myself lacking, and perhaps an adventure is what I need to continue to grow."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporta" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="recruit" text="$Sure. I could use the help.">
			<assertion evaluate="companionSlotFree" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="I don't think so. Goodbye." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<!-- not allied with elves, cannot recruit -->
		<text>
			An elven warrior sits on a bed in the corner of the room, polishing and inspecting a blade. She looks wary and alert, amber eyes flitting about restlessly. Her long ears twitch as if she listening to something far away. Looking you over, she grunts "Hmph. I'm not willing to associate with some outsider, go bother someone else."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportc" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="Rude..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<assertion evaluate="isCompanion" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" flag="Valaeat" value="0" />
		<text>
		"PNAME? What is it you need?"
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporta" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="chat" text="Can we talk for a minute?" />
		<choice destination="leave" text="I think we should part ways, for now." />
		<!--choice destination="spear" text="spear" -->
		<choice destination="heal" text="Patch yourself up with this." >
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="medicine" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Oh, nothing." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		Vala's expression is one of incredulity as she wordless watches your approach.
		Shaking, she stammers out some gasping inaudible words, before clearing her throat and speaking.
		"PNAME. Tell me this is no space or magic prank. ...I must have finally lost it."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportz" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="digested" text="$Sorry, somehow I never mentio-" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="digested">
		<text>
		"Don't speak apparation. Look."
		Vala turns around, cocking her hips towards you. Her improved booty bounces slightly, much tighter in her pants than before.
		"Proof of your digestion. ..Care to explain?"
		When she turns back, the shocked relief on her face is immediately apparent. She smiles at you, but locks eyes unblinking, seemingly worried you'll disappear if you leave her sight for even a split-second.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportm" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="digested1" text="$Let me explain.." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="digested1">
		<text>
		You take the time to explain the reformer and it's basic functionality to Vala, and more importantly, register her into the system. She still doesn't really believe it possible, but when you're done, she grabs you and squeezes you into a hug. Sniffling, she holds you for a decent amount of time, before becoming awkward. Right after breaking contact, she tugs on both ears at once. Maybe she'll be interested in offering herself up now that, in her words, she's 'One of the immortal gods'. You hope she doesn't just use it as an excuse to throw herself at the strongest beasts imaginable for training. The determined fire in her eyes says she intends to do just that. Oh boy...
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportu" height="1"/>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Valaeat" value="0" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Valaeat2" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Wait, maybe this was a mistake???" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="heal">
		<text>
		Taking the medicine, Vala looks much better afterwards. "Thanks, PNAME."
		</text>
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<effect type="removeitem" item="medicine" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="No worries." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="spear">
		<text>
		Use spear??
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="Valaspear" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="test" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="chat">
		<text>
		"Alright, I will humour you. Stay alert regardless PNAME."	
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportf" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self" text="Can you tell me about yourself?" >
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0" flag="Valaopen" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="selfopen" text="So if you're open to new things...">
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1" flag="Valaopen" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="people" text="Could you tell me about your people?" />
		<choice destination="funhub" text="Want to have some fun?" >
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="2" flag="Valaopen" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Nevermind, we don't have time for this" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="chat1">
		<text>
		"You need to know more PNAME? Let us not waste too much time."	
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportf" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self" text="Can you tell me about yourself?" >
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0" flag="Valaopen" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="people" text="Could you tell me about your people?" />
		<choice destination="end" text="You're right, let's go." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="lessthan" value="5" flag="Valascore" />
		<text>
		Looking a little surprised, Vala scratches her behind her ear and begins hesitantly. 
		"Myself? Well.. Hmm.. I was trained by my mothers in sword and spearmanship."
		She stops, shrugging exaggeratedly; you can tell she is embarrassed.
		"There is not much else to say. Not many care for other's life stories in Minyos.. Give me some time. I will think about it more carefully, so as not to disappoint you again."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportg" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="chat1" text="That's fine, can I ask something else?" />
		<choice destination="end" text="No problem, let's move on." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="lessthan" value="9" flag="Valascore" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="greaterthan" value="4" flag="Valascore" />
		<text>
		It's been some time before you asked Vala about herself, maybe she'll answer now. Her expression however, says otherwise.
		"Look PNAME, I know what I said last time. I'm just not sure I can trust you. Usually learning more about someone is to grasp their less obvious weaknesses. How about this then? Uhh, my favourite food is roasted deku nut salad. I admire strength. I dislike losing. Good enough?"
		You open your mouth to speak but Vala cuts in before you have the chance.
		"Okay. I can see you may want to know more. I'll share it with you once I know you're entirely trustworthy. Sorry."
		She nods then walks away, tugging at an ear.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportc" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="No problem, until then." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="greaterthan" value="9" flag="Valascore" />
		<text>
		Vala's eyes grow wide, looks like she hoped you had forgotten.
		"Oh, right. That. You truly want to know about me? Have we not travelled together enough?"
		She sighs loudly, "...Alright, alright."
		Vala, looking uncharacteristically sheepish, takes a deep breath and prepares to speak.
		"Look, I wasn't always like this. So stiff. Formal. So on edge." 
		She gestures to herself while continuing, 
		"I was like everyone else in Minyos. ...Hedonistic. You know, thinking more about gulping acquaintances than becoming closer friends with them. It was beaten out of me by my mother. She used to be nice once. Is this really the sort of thing you want to know? Some sob story? It's not like it's that uncommon. I'm lucky to have even known my parents!"
		You can see she doesn't want to talk. She sighs again.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporte" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self1" text="..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self1">
		<text>
		"My mother.. returned from a hunt one day. She entered our home to find her pregnant wife splattered all over the place. A ...cooling mess. Not too out of the ordinary around here, and many hunters don't even make it home to find their family gone. But.. It broke her, I think. They seemed so happy together."
		Vala looks into the distance wistfully for a moment, but shakes her head.
		"The thought that it could have been consensual was probably too much for her to take. It could have been anyone. Mother wasn't about to go out on a revenge massacre or anything, but she changed that day. She left that old house as it was and spent all she had to build a fenced off house on the outskirts of town." 	
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporti" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self2" text="$What about you?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self2">
		<text>
		Vala looked at the ground, ears drooping.
		"That day, my friends and I were fighting with our rival group, four or five girls a side. The feud had come to a head and most were eaten right there. Truthfully, I don't remember what the disagreement was even about. Returning home with a girl-filled stomach was a mistake I had no way of knowing I had made. My parents normally laughed it off, maybe teased a bit, but Mother was in no laughing mood. ...The things she said, I'm sure she regretted. But.. Being young and having the one you respect the most go so far.."
		Voice trailing off, Vala breathes deeply and evenly, calming herself.
		"From then on, I was trained extensively. No friends or freedom. Certainly no more live meals. Mother was an expert with the spear, she ruthlessly beat me down day after day. I wanted to leave, alas, not many could stand up to mother in battle. None would help me even when begged. Especially as she wouldn't hesitate to kill, and usually in brutal fashion. ..It was hard. Many times I ran, but she would drag me back and add more to the training. Looking back on it now, at least I got to spend so much time with her."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportk" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self3" text="$Did something happen to her?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self3">
		<text>
		"Without warning, she gave me a final test, to prove myself worthy of her teaching. Worried about the meaning of 'final' I was scared. Afraid of her leaving. Afraid of disappointing her.. Nevertheless, I passed. I inherited my deceased mother's sword, the only thing Mother had kept from that old house. 
		Vala spoke fondly of the memory, but you could hear anger breaking though. 
		"I thought she would be proud. But years of bitterness seemed to trump any other feelings she may have once had. Now believing me to be of sufficient strength, she kicked me out. Years of toiling, and she kicked me out. Without words of praise. Without words of abuse. Nothing."
		Vala had balled her fists tight enough to draw blood. Her nails pushed through even her firm calloused palms.  
		"Mother left on an expedition soon after, with the scholar Zhan. None returned."
		Inhaling through her nose, Vala trembled and grit her teeth.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportj" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self4" text="..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self4">
		<text>
		"I wish she had just talked to me. Told me why! Told me anything! Taken me with her!? What was it all for if she just goes off and dies?! I just...! And now look at me! Just like her! Alone and.."
		Tears welling up as she got flustered, Vala spat out words like she was removing poisonous bile from within.
		"Why train me so hard for so long!? Why scare away my friends?! Why! Nothing is even out here! Every day was the same! Torture that never ended! Torture from her. Torture from those gossiping, gluttonous, sex-addicts! I hate her.. Yet why do I still follow her words to the letter! I lived in that house alone and continued to train! I push away all advances and distance myself! Can I even change?! Tell me PNAME, what do I do!? What can I do?!"
		She grabs your arm, looking at you frantically, in plea for an answer.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportt" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self4a" text="$She isn't here Vala, what do you *want* to do?" />
		<choice destination="self4b" text="Say nothing, now that it's out, she just needs time." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self4a">
		<text>
		Vala slumps to the ground, tears slowly running down her cheeks, staring at her mother's sword. She sits silently for a minute. You've never heard her speak this much. The quiet pause breaks, she speaks softly, more to herself than you.
		"What do I want..? I've always wanted to join the others again.. Eating and fucking without much regard.. I've been taught to be ashamed of our tendancies. I still respect Mother. I don't want to betray her teachings but.. Every instinct tells me she was wrong. Can something so good, really be so bad?"
		Speaking louder now, she draws her sword, rubbing her hand over the flat of the blade.
		"Okay. I want to be useful. More than being a meal or as an orgasm.. I want to us to triumph over the lizards and let our people prosper. Make our village into something bigger. Better, more grand. If we had the resources, there'd be no fear of losing your family with every hunt. With star technology like yours, no one would be trapped like I was.."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportl" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self4a-2" text="..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self4a-2">
		<text>
		She thinks for a while, suddenly looking up and nodding.
		"PNAME, you've shown me much. I couldn't imagine anything other than this jungle. But now I have a goal. I cannot think of another way to show my gratitude other than this. I pledge myself to you. I want to help you. I've decided. I'll remember my mother, but surpass her and move on. She wouldn't want me to stay closed off and miserable any more than she wanted me to be eaten, I'm sure. She tried, in her own way, to protect me. I know now."
		Closing her eyes and murmuring some sort of prayer, she slowly sheathes the sword. Finished, she looks back to you, sniffling a little. 
		"Whatever your goal, I will stand by your side. When we are done, I will bring technology to my people and then work to improve everyone's lives. I don't want to live in regret any longer. I swear it."
		Vala stands up, saluting you, amber eyes determined. She looks around from side to side, before winking and adding,
		"And you know PNAME... It's been a while. I think it's time to.. Lift my self-imposed ban on consumption. Maybe loosen up and try some new things? It isn't too late... Hm. In any case."
		After a deep, respectful bow, Vala smiles at you.
		"Speaking this out loud, it helped me figure out my thoughts for the first time. Thank you. For listening." 
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportn" height="1"/>
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valaopen" value="1" />
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valalove" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="$Happy to help." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self4b">
		<text>
		Letting go, Vala slumps to the ground, staring at her mother's sword. She sits sobbing slightly. You've never heard her speak this much. Her prolonged silence is deafening, but you know that she has a lot to think about. She'll get through it. Vala sits, deep in thought for almost half an hour, looking between you and the ground. Tears long dried. Almost whispering, she speaks.
		"..Do you think anyone can actually change PNAME? Is there a point of no return?."
		She frowns, still debating something within herself.
		"Can I make friends again? Will they accept me anymore..? ..Am I already doomed to die alone?"
		Shaking her head, she stands, showing her mother's sword to you. She points to some foreign writing inscribed on the scabbard.
		"Overcome yourself. That's what it says. Whether it was either of my mothers or some other long dead that wrote it, I don't know. But this mantra was hammered into me. Every failure, every success. It's all I have left, besides memories. Maybe.. Mother was the one who couldn't overcome anything. That's why she became like that. I suppose... I just have to believe in it. Become greater than she ever was. No more regrets. I just have to believe she wanted me to stay strong, whatever I'm faced with, including losing her."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportk" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="self4b-2" text="..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="self4b-2">
		<text>
		Righting her posture and dusting off her clothes, Vala nods towards you.
		"PNAME. I thank you for the respect you have shown me by calmly listening to this outburst. Unexpected from a simple question I'm sure."
		Vala chuckles quietly, looking somewhat ashamed of the whole thing.
		"My journey with you is the first step of many. I'll continue to fight with you, for as long as needed. I've still got some thoughts to sort out, but I'll try to be more open from now on. Without moving forward, I really will never change. I can't be afraid of my own people, or who I am, any longer."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportm" height="1"/>
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valaopen" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Sure thing." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="people">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0" flag="Valaopen" />
		<text>
		Vala shakes her head as she replies,
		"I'm sorry. PNAME, you most likely know more than me, strange as it may sound. I don't get on too well with anyone besides Awari and she isn't much the type for history. Most knowledge is kept by Mother Shanna, our priestess. Best to give her your questions if you want reasonable answers."
		Although she also gave a reasonable answer, you get the feeling she doesn't want to talk about others of her race.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportc" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="No worries." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="people">
		<text>
		Vala groans.
		"Mmmmnnnn... I suppose I decided not to avoid it any longer, didn't I? I can't speak for any others but myself. But I'll give you the basics."
		She ponders where to begin, blushing a little.
		"Our libidos are extremely high, it takes considerable willpower to resist any base desires when we're horny. Even the most resistant can turn into a gluttonous sex-crazed beast. We can get a bit uhm.. Unreasonable. Not really think about the consequences of our actions.. A lot of the time this ends up with someone gushed or gurgled, but it's commonplace and thought nothing of within our tribe. It's certainly no crime." 
		She crosses her arms eying you up and down for a moment.
		"To be honest with you, I turned you away when first we met. Because I didn't trust myself. You looked so innocent and out of place. It would have been easy to just... You know."
		With a nervous glace, she mimes a grabbing and gulping motion.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="people1" text="$..and you're all okay with this?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="people1">
		<text>
		"Not everyone is fine with it, of course. However, by our law, words hold power. If you agree to anything, you're held accountable. This leads to everyone trying to trap or trick each other with gambles, dares, wordplay, that sort of thing. Unsavvy women don't last long, sharp wit is our greatest asset. Well second greatest, if you ask anyone else."
		Vala uses both of her arms to gesture a comically large backside over her petite one.
		"I've warned you before, but those girls are sly. Accept any offers, you'd better be sure there's no way they can twist it into something untoward. Unless that's what you expected, I suppose."
		A blush flashes across her face and it's not hard to guess what sort of thing she's imagining.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportx" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="people2" text="*Wait for her to continue*" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="people2">
		<text>
		"Luckily for us, our race is fertile and young ones reach maturity quickly or we'd have been wiped out long ago. Our lack of longevity is making it hard to develop our village and keep experienced warriors around. If you hadn't come along, even I might have offered myself up to someone like eugh.. Neri. Sooner or later. The ones that do leave from her place always look so satisfied..."
		Vala's blush deepens and her eyes glaze over somewhat, but she suddenly pulls on one of her ears and shakes her head. With a sad little laugh she continues. 
		"See what I mean? A simple thought and I was just about ready to break. Mother taught me to pull on my ear to clear my head of dirty thoughts. It works well enough. ..Anyway, we should probably get going. A good sweat is just what I need to take my mind off of stuff like churning and cumming."
		She jogs a small distance away, pulling on her ear again as she runs.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporty" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="Onward." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="selfopen">
		<text>
		A small blush spreads across Vala's face, tinting her green skin. "Yes, PNAME? What is it that you're thinking of?"
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporth" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="food" text="$Do you want to share meals?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="food">
		<text>
		"You want to watch me eat? Alright. Give me the word and I'll show you what I can do. I'd be lying if I said I haven't craved it again all these years."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporth" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="fun" text="$What about something more personal?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fun">
		<text>
		Vala blushes deeper, eying you up and down, biting her bottom lip.
		"More personal. Hmm... We have been through a lot together. And I did want to try something different. Yes, okay. When we are in a safe place, lest we're interrupted."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporto" height="1"/>
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valaopen" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Sounds good." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="funhub">
		<text>
		"What did you have in mind, PNAME?"
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<!-- choice destination="sex" text="Horny?" -->
		<choice destination="vore" text="Hungry?" >
			<preference fetish="demis" />
			<preference fetish="females" />
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="Actually, nevermind." />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex">
		<text>
		Blushing deeply, Vala replies bashfully.
		"Our people always are. I won't say no, well to you, at least."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="penetration" text="Horny?" >
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="10" flag="Valalove" />
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="oral" text="Hungry?" />
		<choice destination="hand" text="lets go" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="penetration">
		<text>
		
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="lets go" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oral">
		<text>
			
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="lets go" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="hand">
		<text>
			
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="lets go" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="vore">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" flag="Valaeat2" value="0" />
		<text>
		"You want to be eaten? Really? ..I can't guarantee your safety. I've never been able to hold back my digestion for long. I lack the practise I suppose. If you're sure, we can try.. But do tell me as soon as you want out, or if it gets too hot inside, I don't want to lose you."
		Vala takes off her armour, pulling it over her head. As it does, her shirt lifts, briefly showing off her toned abs. Her stomach rumbles loudly, startling her.
		"Ahaha, I'm already imagining tasting you.. It's been so hard to control myself for so long. You look so good I could just.."
		Planting a wet kiss upon your lips, she mashes her face into yours. As she pulls back,  large strands of saliva trailing between your lips and hers. Vala's eyes are half-lidded and she's panting hard, a wet patch slowly growing in the groin of her pants.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportw" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="vore1" text="It's what you want.." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="vore1">
		<text>
		No longer holding herself back, she looks downright animalistic. Breathing roughly and hunching slightly, she's upon you. You're bowled over and Vala grabs your arms, shoving them greedily into her mouth. You're slathered with drool as Vala's throat contracts around your forearms, her eyes shut tight as she revels in your taste. Moaning deeply, she slurps you in with relish, your world going dark as your head is pulled into that cavernous, drooling maw. Her insides are tight, warm and hostile, long forgotten reflexes returning as Vala consumes you. With every pleasured moan, her inner muscles ripple and pulse around you, hauling you closer to the broiling belly within.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporty" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="vore2" text="*down you go*" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="vore2">
		<text>
		You're hit with a wave of heat and a distinct acrid smell from further down the tight passage, you can hear the groaning of the hungry organ as it prepares to churn it's impending meal. Vala is gulping with as much vigor as she can muster, moaning uncontrollably all the while. The scarcity of such rich food obviously not having any diminished effect on her digestive processes. As she swallows past your <macro ID="breast_size_desc"/> chest, you wonder how often she partook before her 'fasting period', her skilled handling of you suggests it may have been more often than she'd admit. You also wonder if she remembers what she said merely moments ago, because when you reach the already deathly hostile stomach, you realise there isn't any way you're coming out intact, even if she immediately lets you back out.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportq" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="vore3" text="*all the way*" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="vore3">
		<text>
		You curl into the stinging prison, not really bothering to struggle much. Hopefully Vala won't be too distressed after she realises what she's done. She's currently in a trance, rubbing her stretching middle as she ingets the rest of your body, gasping with pleasure. "Auuuuh... PNAME you fuh-feeell. So good in there.."
		Vala now laying on the ground, cradles her middle in a full-body hug. Gurgling out ecstatic gibberish, she rolls around happily and wishes that the bulging gut would remain that way forever. Inside however, you're jostled around and mashed into the ground as the gurgling organ works you down. Vala is wracked with orgasm after orgasm, assaulting you  with bubbling waves of warmth. Looks like the forever she wished for won't come though. Not feeling much any more, with your last thoughts, you can't help but be pleased at how much joy you've just given out, at only the low cost of your entire body. The enraptured elven woman doesn't even notice your passing, the sloshing of her belly slowly dying down. Her movements become laboured as her repeated esctasies end, the tides of her stomach soon lulling her to a peaceful sleep.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportr" height="1"/>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Valaeat" value="1" />
		<choice destination="vore4" text="Zzzzz.." />
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="vore4" >
		<text>
		By the Vala awakens, her efficient system has long since processed it's passenger, padding her modest rear out somewhat, stretching her flimsy cloth pants to their seams. A few more meals like that and she'll be just as huge as the other girls from her village. Now in a much more lucid, if dazed state, she panics and wonders what she'll do from here on out. 
		"PNAME.. I didn't mean to, I just."
		...Vala shakes her head. No. She wanted it. You warned her. You did the right thing. Continually telling herself similar reassurances, Vala cleans up sluggishly. She feels wetness beginning to gather in the corners of her eyes. Holding back her feelings, she sets out once more, vowing once again to keep moving forward. And to make some new pants.
		</text>
	</gameover>	
	
	<page ID="vore">
		<text>
		Vala blushes, seeming to have anticipated this may happen again at some point.
		"You liked being melted down by me that much PNAME? You're abusing your technology. How do you know it will always be safe? I don't think it's a good idea to gamble if you can help it."
		Her words betray her actions, drool already forming at her lips while she silently stalks closer. She has no intention of letting you get away now it seems. Not that you want to, of course. 
		"I'll feel so much less guilty this time."
		She circles around you, pressing her enhanced buttocks into you. You take a feel. It's cushy flesh is soft and pilable. You feel the firm muscle within as your hands sink into the cheeks. "If eating you once did this much, think how big I'll be after two. Three?" 
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporty" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="voreb1" text="$How about after ten?" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="voreb1">
		<text>
		"Auhhhhhhgnnn..!"
		Vala lets out a strange noise and shudders violently, you're pretty sure she just came from imagination alone. "Tha.. That isn't fair PNAME. I told you how we can get.. Something like that, I may hold you to. I won't be much good with a sword anymore at that size though. Haaah..!" 
		Shaking against your body, the panting mess of a woman cries out once more. Practically holding all her weight against you, she nuzzles against your <macro ID="breast_size_desc"/> breasts, the fragrance of lust radiating from her body as you roam your hands over her supple body. Helping her undress,  
		<conditional> <assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />you do as well, </conditional>
		you begin to fold her clothes, purposely postponing her meal.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportp" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="voreb2" text="*Grabbed and lifted*" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="voreb2">
		<text>
		The teasing too much for the horn-gry elven woman, she lifts you up by the waist and her mouth opens wide, taking you into your shins. Vala wiggles her eyebrows in a faux-seductive way, as she swallows carefully, gradually, using only gravity to assist your descent. The combined forces of her saliva and your mass work quite well together, you slide in easily, until your hips. Frowning around you, Vala stops moaning, instead making a grumpy noise. Having to actually use some effort to pass the width of your body, powerful muscles begin peristalsis and you resume your slow motion free fall into the depths of your companion.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporty" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="voreb3" text="*Going down*" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="voreb3">
		<text>
		Recognising the willpower it must be taking Vala to eat you this slowly, you're impressed. She can't hold out for much longer though, and with a series of jerking motions, she gulps with much more strength, bringing you almost eye to eye with her in seconds. Giggling, you duck down and plant a kiss on her forehead. She raises her eyebrows in surprise, flushing deeply and finishing you off completely. You wiggle on the way down, with great effect, if the happy noises that Vala then makes are any indication. Tucking yourself away in the much less violent this time around stomach, you rub the inside linings and struggle against her gently, stimulating the organ somewhat. Acid tingles your extremities, but it looks like Vala wants to keep you as long as she possibly can this time.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportq" height="1"/>
		<choice destination="voreb4" text="Nice and calming..." />
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="voreb4" >
		<text>
		You and Vala have some mild conversation, discussing battle tactics and explaining technology, while you gradually dissolve inside the warm pit. Vala eventually falls into a food-induced coma, while you continue to stimulate her insides to give her pleasant dreams. It takes almost 2 hours before you can't think well enough to hold a thought together anymore, and not long after that, your fibers can't hold your body together anymore either. You drift off satisfied, thinking of the changes you'll make, whilst Vala, still asleep, cradles her swollen belly like a perverse body pillow. The protein rich mush you made soon filters out, to be absorbed and futher pad out the elven warrior's body.
		</text>
	</gameover>	
	
	<page ID="leave">
		<text>
		"Very well PNAME, I do hope to fight with you again soon."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportb" height="1"/>
		<special effect="removecompanion" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Vala" value="0" />
		<choice destination="end" text="$Farewell." />
	</page>

	<page ID="recruit">
		<text>
		She strides over to you, giving you what you assume is a salute, a faint smile on her lips. "Excellent. I am Vala. I look forward to fighting with you outsider. I wish to learn many things and staying in this village is driving me insane." She still seems rather jumpy, but her posture relaxes slightly, relief showing on her face. It seems to have taken a lot of courage to ask you to party up. She straightens and holds out a hand.
		"Ah, forgive me. For the pointless chatter. What is your name?"
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportb" height="1"/>
		<special effect="makecompanion" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Vala" value="1" />
		<choice destination="name" text="$PNAME." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="name">
		<text>
		At your curt reply, Vala nods. "I see. PNAME. I will not demand this of you, but let us keep this a purely business partnership. It would pain me to grow close to someone who could soon be fat or waste."
		She pauses solemnly, closing her eyes, though even still her ears continue to twitch alertly.
		"It is dangerous in the wilderness and as you may have surmised, there is greater danger within the village. Be wary, many of us are sly. They have no qualms in consuming whatever they can." As Vala walks past you towards the exit, you notice her tug quite hard on one of her ears.
		</text>
		<picture source="valaporte" height="1"/>
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valascore" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="$Thanks for the warning, let's go." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="">
		<text>
			
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="lets go" />
	</page>

	<page ID="join">
		<text>
			Vala bows her head, fire lighting in her eyes "I am grateful to accompany you once more. Let us be on our way."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportb" height="1"/>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Vala" value="1" />
		<special effect="makecompanion" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Let's go" />
	</page>

</Conversation>