<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			You can hear her suit respirator rasping loudly with her heavy breathing
			and a soft mmhmm as you approach. You wonder why she doesn't take the
			suit off, but maybe there's a reason. She's clearly too enamoured
			with you to resist though "what are you going to do with me?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="$I was thinking I'd pump you back into that suit once you'd had a stay in my balls">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="$nothing, actually, but I could of done" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You hear a gasp and her knees quaver. Seems your debauched suggestion
			hit a soft and oh so submissive spot so without wasting any more time
			you
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				whip out your shaft and
			</conditional>
			motion her down in front of your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			member "So depraved" she murmurs, but acquiesces to your demand. She
			lowers herself down onto her knees but makes no move to take off the
			suit, you frown and are about to speak on this but then feel her
			hands on your shaft. Her hands sliding distractingly up and down that
			length. She's surprisingly good at it, stimulating despite the gloves
			as she strokes expertly along your shaft. Your eyes starting to waver
			closed through the pleasure as a groan issues forth from your throat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="nice as this is though..." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You let her work your shaft for a little bit, thinking that in a few
			more moments you'll coax her to strip out of that suit. Except before
			you can say anything you hear a thunk followed quickly by the
			wondrous sensation of a head being fed willingly into your cock.
			You're robbed of a chance to look at her face, but being able to
			schlurp her out of the suit and melt her into cum is such a treat
			that not knowing her appearance is hardly a downer. You hear her mhmm
			inside your cocktip, precum soaking her face and what feels like her
			hair as she reaches up to undo the back of the sealing collar around
			her neck then leans forwards. The collar parting as she tucks her
			arms down and thrusts her shoulders up through the neckhole of her
			suit into your cocktip.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2"
			text="unexpected, but welcome, and it's not like they don't all look the same when your balls are done with them" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			You ripple your shaft around your seduced willing cockfood, schlurping
			more of her out of the suit. the gloved hands going limp as her hands
			are drawn up and out of them. You thrust your hips forcing your tip
			past the suit collar with a moan of your own that matches the muffled
			moan audible from inside your shaft as she slides deeper into the
			naughty depths of your loins. You focus on tensing your shaft to draw
			her further and feel her suit start to slump as her feet slide out of
			the boots and she's supported more by your rippling cock wrapped
			around her upper body, her head nearing the base of your enlarged and
			feasting shaft.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3"
			text="soon have the secretive alien secreted away in your balls" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			You hear her letting out a gasp and mhmm as her head plunges through the
			base of your shaft. Her evident pleasure at entering the chamber of
			her imminent churning sends a thrill running through you from head to
			toes to rippling dick and you redouble your efforts to shlurp this
			sackslut out of her spacesuit. Her face and then arms starting to
			press out your sagging sack as you draw her in, you feel her rump and
			then knees slipping past your cumslit. The weight of the girl
			settling into your sack you see catch a glimpse of her blue feed
			wiggling around beyond your tip as your shaft pops free of the now
			empty spacesuit with the last of your cockfood still to schlurp
			inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore4" text="one more 'swallow'" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore4">
		<text>
			You run both hands along your cock as you schlurp the last of the space
			traveller into your tip. Her feet disappearing easily past your
			cumslit and forming a bulge that traces down your length to join the
			rest of her piled into your balls, making them nice and lumpy as they
			sag low and massive against your thighs and you feel her getting
			comfortable inside of you. One of your hands going down to rub
			against your balls and you feel her squirm around with a lewd squelch
			of cum "My you were easy..." you comment teasingly, you can only
			imagine the blush on what you imagine her face must look like as she
			replies "It's...it's something about you I guess...so, sexy and
			uninhibited and mhmm." she said, making you chuckle "I'm the one
			whose uninhibited? you're the one who dived down my dick to get
			sloshed into cum cause you were horny" she has no response to that
			except to moan with a quiver of lust within your sack.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore5" text="churn her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore5">
		<text>
			"well, I suppose either way you're dick fodder. thanks for the load." you
			tease her a bit more as your sack begins to burble and churn around
			her. The teasing and tantalizing sensations of being melted into cum
			making her moan and squirm around all the more. You fondle yourself
			to the sensation as writhes lustfully within you, gradually softening
			her form and turning her pale, creamy and melty as your balls
			diligently convert her into gallons of wonderful nutbutter. Those
			balls softening and rounding out as you liquidate the alien woman
			within. The steady pressure of all that pent up cum providing a needy
			desire for release, luckily you already have a plan for where to put
			her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore6" text="where's that spacesuit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore6">
		<text>
			It turns out to be right where you left it and you grin thinking of
			what you're about to do as you yank the suit into a semi upright
			position, the empty open neckhole angled towards you. With all in
			readyness you begin to stroke off, cocktip aimed at the hole as you
			lustfully and unrestrainedly jerk off letting your pleasure be heard
			openly. The vigorous fapping sounds and moans audible to any
			hypothetical listener, followed by a gasp and series of splattering
			spurts as you climax. Hot cum pouring out of your dick into the
			spacesuit, filling it up steadily with hot steaming jizz made of the
			suits prior occupant. As your orgasm starts to subside the suit fills
			to the brim, the last few spurts overflowing the suit, cum oozing
			from the neck hole to make a lewd mess of it all...best thing to make
			of her really, and you're sure she'd agree if she could see what you
			made of her.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="100" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was fun" />
	</page>

</Conversation>