<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="analvore" />
		<text>
			The spacesuit clad dame looms ominously over you, her expression hidden
			behind the metal helm but her body language seems satified "You
			should of thought twice before picking a fight with the league." she
			says and then undoes the back of her spacesuit, a gap opening up over
			her rump as she positions herself over you "cause you were a
			potential customer, now you're potential fat." she says and then
			lowers her ass down over your face, soft ample blue buttcheeks
			visible to you afore everything goes dark. A lewd schlorp heard as
			her sphincter slips down around your ears.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore0"
			text="re-categorized as unprocessed padding and fed to an alien ass" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
			You couldn't see her face even if your face wasn't sliding up her ass,
			but by the sound of it she's enjoying herself. Her moans audible as
			her hungry back passage squelches and ripples around your head and
			shoulders drawing you deeper inside of her. You hear a few strain and
			stretching noises as her suit begins to accomodate the bulge of your
			body sliding into her own. A lump in her belly showing your head as
			she squats down over your defenceless body to shove you further in,
			soon you're squeezed inside her all the way down to your waist. Her
			asscheeks sliding over your rump as you're compressed in the heated
			depths of her body and pressed doubly so by the combined constraints
			of her gut and surrounding suit, you can already tell it'll be hard
			to get out of here and as if reading your mind you can hear her
			murmur "there's no escape, only place you're going is my curves." she
			says as she leans forwards, angling your helplessly scissoring legs
			into the air.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="swallowed entirely by alien ass" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			The spacesuited alien rests her hands on her knees as she clenches and
			schlorps your legs steadily into her rear end. Her moans sounding
			around you along with the schlorps and blorps of her insides pressing
			around your head as she pulls you into herself. Your feet wriggling
			around protruding from her ass for a few moments more as your legs
			disappear before they vanish inside her rump as well. Her innards
			squeezing hotly all around you as you're clenched inside her and feel
			her straighten up. You can hardly move, and what's worse you know if
			she gets a chance to do up the rump slot of her spacesuit there'll be
			nowhere for you to escape to.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvoreStruggle" text="try to escape before that happens!" />
		<choice destination="analvoreSubmit" text="...there's no escape" />
	</page>

	<check ID="analvoreStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="analvoreEscape" />
		<outcome destination="analvoreDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="analvoreEscape">
		<text>
			You immediately set about wriggling back out, working your arms up above
			you to push against the tightly confining innards around you to shove
			yourself back down out of her ass. The alien lurching and stumbling
			as your hands shove out the stretched belly of her suit "stop that
			you..." she reaches behind herself, your efforts so sudden she goes
			to cover her ass with her hands rather than seal her suit. She grabs
			ahold of your feet as they emerge but seems she lacks a good angle to
			shove you back in so lets out a frustrated litany of protests as you
			worm your way free. The spacesuited girl dropping into a heap as the
			last of your form wriggles free of her ass.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvoreDigest">
		<text>
			You immediately set about wriggling back out, working your arms up above
			you to push against the tightly confining innards around you to shove
			yourself back down out of her ass. The alien lurching and stumbling
			as your hands shove out the stretched belly of her suit "stop that
			you..." she protests and then reaches around behind herself to go
			about stopping you if you won't stop trying to get out. But your
			attempt, to escape her butt, is thwarted abruptly as you shove your
			feet back out from between her ass cheeks only to encounter an
			unyielding fabric surface. She's sealed up the suit before you could
			squirm out, and hear her giggle as you futilely push against it
			"naughty...good try, but not good enough." says the alien and
			clenches, working to pull your legs back inside. You resist for a
			time despite the futility of it all, but when you tire she has her
			way, pulling your feet back into her ass and pulling your body deeper
			into her own.
		</text>
		<special effect="healnpc" />		
		<choice destination="analvoreDigestGO" text="doomed now" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="analvoreDigestGO">
		<text>
			Helplessly you're drawn into the deepest depths of the alien, her hands
			drumming idly on her middle as her belly swells out massively with
			your curled up form. Trapped inside her you can hardly even squirm
			with how tightly her suit and belly presses about you, and it's here
			she gurgles you away. Your form softening and mooshing to conform to
			the shape you're being squished into, softening and goopifying until
			the steady relentless pressure on you reduces you to a compact and
			formless mass that's easy to absorb. It doesn't seem to take long
			after that for her belly to flatten out again, the spacesuit trim
			there despite its earlier stretching in a testament to the naughty
			ends to which their finest environment suit technology had been put.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="analvoreSubmit">
		<text>
			You can hardly move in the confines of her innards, and decide that
			compared to the immense struggle it'd be to force your way back out
			of her submitting to being digested by this alien has some appeal.
			You don't resist as you're squeezed up through her innards, working
			deeper into her as you leave her bowels and intestines behind for
			cosier confines in her belly. Your lack of even an attempt at
			struggling seems to have caught her attention and she runs a hand
			over her belly bulge "given up have we?"
		</text>
			<special effect="healnpc" />	
		<choice destination="analvoreSubmitGO" text="mhmmm!" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="analvoreSubmitGO">
		<text>
			The talharan laughs at your affirmation "Well if you're a gutslut I'm
			not gonna complain." she says and gets comfortable resting her hands
			on her belly as she starts to gurgle you away. Your form softening
			and mooshing to conform to the shape you're being squished into,
			softening and goopifying until the steady relentless pressure on you
			reduces you to a compact and formless mass that's easy to absorb. It
			doesn't seem to take long after that for her belly to flatten out
			again, the spacesuit trim there despite its earlier stretching in a
			testament to the naughty ends to which their finest environment suit
			technology had been put.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>