<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The saurian warrior sees you approach her defeated form and
			pushes
			herself up with difficulty into a seated position, growling as
			she
			sees your smile "I suppose it is too much to expect you to be
			gracious in victory." she says, clearly expecting you to do something
			to or with her now you have her at your mercy.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="$I think victory is worth celebrating with a good cockmeal">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="vala" text="*Let Vala handle it* (mild gore)" >
			<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1" flag="Vala" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="$actually, it isn't. I don't intend to do anything to you" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			The saurian glares at realizing the fate you have in store for her,
			though flushes slightly as you prepare yourself
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, by stripping off below the waist and
			</conditional>
			by stroking your shaft to hardness, feeling it grow under your palm
			from its
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			size to something more suitable for the task at hand "You will pay
			for this." she says shuddering as she breathes in your heady musk.
			Your cock oozing pre and wafting lewd scents "i will not go unavenged
			traveller." she threatens, prompting you to silence her with a cock
			to the face. One hand grabbing her hair to shove her firmly against
			your tip, mashing her face against your cockslit and starting to
			schlurp her inside in a way that muffles the lizard nicely. And her
			smooth scaley body is just going to feel so good going down you can
			already tell even as you've only reached her shoulders.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1"
			text="$you'd of done the same to me, now be a good lizard and be food for my dick" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			The warrior lizard has no answer to that, but then she's muffled
			by hot
			throbbing dick sliding down over her anyway. The lizard
			squirming and
			struggling mightily but without any success as you
			schlurp her
			steadily into your cock. Your rocking hips forcing
			thrusting her into
			your cumslit inch by inch over her chest and down
			towards h er hips,
			that partially scaled and all firm form swelling
			out your cock and
			sliding closer and closer to your awaiting balls.
			And her tail
			tantalizes as it sways and swishes around with her
			vigorous but
			futile resistance.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="she feels so good sliding in there!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The warrior lets out a gasping "you won't-" as her head slides
			into your
			sack before plunging facefirst into a pool of sticky jizz.
			The
			reptile redoubling her struggles delightfully as she's dunked into
			your cum, a substance she'll get quite acquainted with as you melt
			her into your next load. As you crest her hips and thighs that
			vigorous flailing tail starts to rub against the inside of your
			shaft. Her tail moving this way and that with great rapidity and
			making you groan in delight but gradually her tail is constrained as
			you schlurp up that and her legs as well. Only the lower portion of
			her legs and lower half of her tail left protruding from your cocktip
			as her upper body thrashes and squirms protestingly in your swollen
			balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="finish her off" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			You look at the protruding parts of her and smile, stroking both
			hands
			up and down your bulging shaft to coax the rest of her down
			where she
			belongs. Your shaft schlurping lewdly and easily along her
			calves and
			scaley tail as you jerk her down into your loins. The
			saurian warrior
			hissing and snarling as she feels the last of her
			sealed away
			disappearing past your cocktip and she squirms to push out
			against
			the inside of your sack and try to stop her descent into your
			balls.
			But she's no match for the triumphant strength of your cock as
			you
			plunged her entirely into your balls "you...release me!" she
			demands
			defiantly as she squirms around, pleasingly thrashing in the
			hot
			cummy bath you're giving her as you fondle yourself and revel in
			your
			victory.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore4" text="$you'll make a very nice load" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore4">
		<text>
			"You will pay for this!" she protests as your balls gurgle and
			you stroke
			off "you'll pay for this..." the repeating makes it sound
			like she's
			trying to convince herself as she struggles against the
			churning of
			your sack. But the saurian warrior is no match for the
			might of your
			balls as they work her over and down. The saurian's
			struggles and
			threats of far fetched retribution fade away gradually,
			being
			replaced with the sloshing sensations of cum and the churns of
			thick
			cum as she melted away. Soon enough not an ounce of the saurian
			remains unconquered by your ravenous balls. the sensation of the last
			of her churning away so toe curlingly exquisite it has you stroking
			off again. The pleasing load of your former adversary now applying a
			steady needy pressure as she swells your sack and you jerk off,
			stroking yourself steadily and then faster and more vigorously as
			your pleasure builds. A pleasure that soon erupts, former saurian
			splattering all over the ground as you pump wads and wads of hot cum
			out of your shaft, orgasming the remnants of your foe out to form a
			sticky puddle. Very satisfying all told.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="vala">
		<text>
		Vala looks down at the defeated saurian. 
		"Yes, this is the only thing you should have expected". 
		<random id="valaraid" />
		"Good riddance. Send as many as you want, it will make no difference."
		Looking over to you with a somewhat guilty expression, she her posture stiffens. 
		"We can't afford to be defeated here, PNAME. Although it seems cruel, many of our number have fallen to these beasts in the past. I will follow Mother's teaching."
		</text>
		<picture source="valaportc" height="1"/>
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="Valascore" value="1" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Savage." />
	</page>

</Conversation>