<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"
			flag="gender" />
		<text>
			You have fallen before a saurian warrior out in the wilderness, from
			your position down in the dirt you can get a good look up under the
			hem of her armoured tunic and you see...
		</text>
		<choice destination="genderF" text="a hungry snatch">
			<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="genderH" text="a girthy cock">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="gameover" text="a fate too terrible to contemplate">
			<notpreference fetish="cockvore" />
			<notpreference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="genderF">
		<text>
			A hairless snatch nestled between her legs, already moist and pliant
			as she sees where your gaze is going and reaches down to fondle
			herself, gently parting her lower lips. The hot pink of her nethers a
			dreadful invitation as she flashes them at you.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="gender" value="-1" />
		<choice destination="start" text="prepare for liquidation" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<!--female -->
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="-1"
			flag="gender" />
		<text>
			The saurian looks down at you and grins, dropping down into a squat. As
			she spreads her thighs you see her hairless snatch drooling wetly for
			you and she chuckles following your gaze "Mhmm, that's it..you're
			going in there." she says with a mhmmm and then reaches out. The
			saurian warrior grabbing your feet afore you can pull them away,
			instead they're pulled towards her and together so she can press them
			against her hot and hungry nethers "No escape" she taunts with a
			growl as she engulfs your feet with her ravenous pussy "but feel free
			to struggle, it'll feel better for me."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="helpless to resist" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			You can't help but protest your fate, but your lustful predator is
			having none of it and simply chuckles and grins as she grabs your
			legs and feeds them into her snatch. You feel the hot tightness of
			her sex squeeze down over your thighs and your feet plunge into her
			soft yet ravenous womb as she chirrs in delight and watches your
			face, takinga perverse form of glee in studying your expression as
			she draws you into herself. You can see her middle bulging and as it
			does she leans back, releasing you with her hands yet clenching all
			the more vigorously with her sex. The warrior's might such that even
			now she seems able to draw you in without a hope of escape.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="drawn inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			In, in in. With each rippling clench of her nethers and lewd schlorp
			more of your body is drawn inside her. Her hungry snatch and
			voracious womb claiming ever more of you as she chirrs in delight
			"mhmmm, you're gonna feel so good gushing down the inside of my
			thighs." she says and grins wickedly, revelling in the sensations as
			the bulge of your curling form eclipses her view of your head and
			arms sliding down between her legs. Your predator throws her head
			back and reaching down to frig her clit as you're dragged inside her.
			Her thighs are outlining your view of the outline now as you scrabble
			in vain for purchase to resist
			her voracious snatch but you both know that soon you'll end up inside of
			her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="overtaken utterly" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
		<text>
			You feel her clenching nethers ripple up around your head, your last
			view of the outside world framed by her lower lips afore being sealed
			into wet and squeezing darkness. Your arms flail and grasp uselessly
			a moment more before being drawn up inside of her as she chirrs in
			delight. The predatory warrior pressing her arms over her distended
			middle and clenching her thighs together to prevent you escaping back
			out "all roads end traveller, and this one ends with you as
			wombfodder." she says and gives her roundness a pat. Your body soon
			finishes being drawn up inside her, entombed within that hungry womb
			you know she intends only ill for you now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBStruggleCheck" text="try to get out of her" />
		<choice destination="UBPleasureCheck" text="try to pleasure her into letting you go" />
		<choice destination="UBSubmit" text="submit to being fluid" />
	</page>

	<check ID="UBStruggleCheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="UBStruggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="UBStruggleDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="UBStruggleEscape">
		<text>
		Despite her statement of finality you set yourself to attempting to squirm your way back out of her clenching womb. The intimate insides of the reptilian pressing snugly all around you and starting to rthythmically knead on your form and you shove back harshly against her inner flesh, your probing hands searching around for the way back out in a way the warrior starts to find rather disagreeable. The saurian warrior shifting around and then letting out a hiss as you find your way, flushing as she presses her legs together. But she finds herself no match for you as your hands shove first out from betwixt her netherlips then finds you shoving her legs apart forcing her to fall disagreeably backwards as you worm your way out of her. The saurian giving you a heated glare as you slip entirely free from her flushed and panting form, it won't take her long to recover and have her revenge for this.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBStruggleDigest">
		<text>
		Despite her statement of finality you set yourself to attempting to squirm your way back out of her clenching womb. The intimate insides of the reptilian pressing snugly all around you and starting to rthythmically knead on your form and you shove back harshly against her inner flesh, your probing hands searching around for the way back out in a way the warrior starts to find rather disagreeable. The saurian warrior shifting around and then letting out a hiss as you find your way, flushing as she presses her legs together. You shove your hands into her birthcanal and try to force her muscular passage apart so you can escape, worming further towards her netherlips and freedom. But her legs are together and as you worm your hands out you feel only her thighs squeezing them and making it impossible to escape. You strain and struggle, but tire as she clenches and ripples, tugging you back inside "you fought well, now...melt" the saurian says as you're sealed back inside, worn out and exhausted from your struggles you feel her tingling fluids kneading into you and know the end is coming. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBSTRUGGLEGO" text="liquidate" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="UBSTRUGGLEGO">
		<text>
		You writhe and plead weakly inside the saurian, but all you get for your troubles is the chiding scold of "Die with dignity." from your predator even as she sets about rubbing you out, which some might say is hypocritical. But you have bigger problems as you start to soften and liquidate in her, hearing her chirr and moan as she pleasures herself and you are compressed into an ever tighter mass of liquidated lust "no-" you manage to start to say only to end in a burble as you're scrunched and sloshed away by her voracious womb. The saurian letting out a cry that drowns out your final plea as she orgasms, splattering your remnants all over the ground beneath her as a wet puddle. The saurian warrior has truly bested you now, all that's left is a stain beneath her as she gets up and recovers her composure.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<check ID="UBPleasureCheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="UBPleasureEscape" />
		<outcome destination="UBPleasureDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="UBPleasureEscape">
		<text>
		You hear her definitive statement, oddly dignified for someone who has just shoved a defeated foe up her snatch. And well, that can't stand, also flustering her into submission from within MIGHT just be enough to stop you ending up her next orgasm. Not ending up an orgasm might of weighed heavier on your thinking as you start rubbing at her insides, tracing your expert hands along her the inside of her womb and probing at the entrance of her birth canal. You hear her gasp and chirr, the saurian flushing heavily and shivering "what are you? ooh, keep on...yes" she moans as her better judgement is derailed by your hands and of her own hands one traces down to finger herself vigorously. The saurian letting out a cry as she soon peaks and in her rapturous state of orgasm and afterglow barely registers your escape until you worm your way entirely out. Though she'll probably come down from that high in a bit, might be trouble in the offing when that happens.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBPleasureDigest">
		<text>
		You hear her definitive statement, oddly dignified for someone who has just shoved a defeated foe up her snatch. And well, that can't stand, also flustering her into submission from within MIGHT just be enough to stop you ending up her next orgasm. Not ending up an orgasm might of weighed heavier on your thinking as you start rubbing at her insides, tracing your hands along her the inside of her womb and probing at the entrance of her birth canal. You hear her gasp and chirr, the saurian flushing heavily and shivering "what are you? ooh, keep on...wait" she manages, keeping her wits about you despite your apparently less than magic fingers. The saurian clenching herself around you to impede your motions and chuckling "nice try, but i orgasm once you're a bit sloshier and not before."
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBPleasureGO" text="nothing to do but get sloshed" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="UBPleasureGO">
		<text>
		The saurian chuckles and mhmms as you try despite her fore-warned and thus fore-armed state to attempt to pleasure her. Your predator flushing as she feels you squirming and softening simultaneously in her voracious womb. Her hand only now going to rub her nethers now you're too soft to survive much longer, her womb steadily grinding away your solidity and resistance. "mhmm, nearly...nearly...mhmm" she utters as she feels her orgasm building in strength and your own weakening. Your last sensation that of experiencing her orgasm from within her as she climaxes with a cry and her womb squishes you down into a sopping wet expulsion of her juices, sticky glops of former space adventure splattering all over the floor under her as the saurian moans and gasps in delight. She doesn't even try to mop you up, just leaving you a mess out in the open for others to see as she rises back to her feet and adjusts the lay of her clothing. What an end.
		</text>
	</gameover>


	<page ID="UBSubmit">
		<text>
		You feel her womb pressing possessively around you as she declares your fate and settles contently. Though you surprise her as she hears your mhmm at those words "My you're an eager one? well..." she chuckles and leans back, stroking one womb over her distended middle and the other one sets to work leisurely between her legs. You find yourself following suit in masturbating as you let yourself get sloshed and juiced by her ravenous womb. The clenching snug confines rubbing her sexual fluids into you as you moan and hear her chirr around you, each clench making you feel even more wonderful and yet softer and more pliant.. you feel your orgasm nearing as things get wetter and wetter in every sense of the word. Nearly there, nearly, nearly...
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBSUBMITGO" text="*slosh*" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="UBSUBMITGO">
	<text>
	The saurian hears your final blissed cry muffled inside her and swiftly silenced with a burbling glorp as her own orgasm follows on the heels of your own and mashes your semi solid form entirely down into delightful liquids. The saurian bucking on the ground and splattering hot fluids out of her womb as she squeezes you into femmecum and discharges you out all over the ground. As her orgasm subsides the saurian gasps, but still chirrs in delight as she basks in afterglow and the erotic scents steaming off your heated remains. Always good when a defeated enemy knows how to be a satisfying orgasm, and that's all you've amounted to now.
	</gameover>
	
	</page>

	<page ID="genderH">
		<text>
			A thick tanned cock and some hefty hairless balls. The lizard sees
			where your gaze is drifting and cracks a smile, reaching down under
			her tunic to wrap one hand around that cock and stroke it as it
			twitches and a single glop of musk pre oozes forth to dribble on the
			ground beneath her and tantalize your nose with its scent.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="gender" value="1" />
		<choice destination="start" text="so gonna get shafted" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="gender" />
		<!--herm -->
		<text>
			The saurian looks down at you and grins, stroking her firm cock and
			glancing down meaningfully at your feet afore a droplet of her pre
			drops upon them "I think we both know what's coming next." she says
			and drops down into a squat, grabbing your feet even as you try to
			pull them away from her, guiding them toes first into the tip of her
			hungry cock "I hope you fight as well in my balls as you did out
			here, I love a squirmy load." she taunts as her shaft bulges out
			around your feet and she leans forwards to grasp your legs and feed
			you deeper inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="get schlurped up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You do squirm, though it does little more than make her moan as her
			voracious shaft ripples and schlurps its way up your legs. It
			certainly doesn't help you escape as your feet dip into her cum and
			she works her hands forwards up your body to help work you into her
			loins.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="helplessly drawn inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			Down you slide as she reaches your waist, her balls starting to bulge out
			as your legs are fed into their ravenous and sticky embrace. Contours
			of your feet imprinting on her sack rather nicely as she crams you in
			with a delighted moan and shuddering blissed out mannerisms. The
			lizard giving you a little smooch "good cockfood" she says and then
			forces more of a kiss out of you afore you can protest. The lizard
			violating your mouth with her long tongue as she shoves your body
			down into her cock..breaking the kiss to smile and place a hand atop
			your head "goodbye cockfood" she says and then all goes dark as she
			shoves the last of you into her cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="disappear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The saurian warrior who bested you now settles back into a seated
			position, stroking over the bulges made in her shaft from your head
			and upper body as you slide down entirely into her bloated sack
			"mhmmm, too few of my fights end this way." she says and then
			chuckles "but you were easier to get down than an elf, always hard to
			get their hips in." she says and continues stroking herself as you're
			entirely crammed into her balls. Stewing in hot cum you seem doomed
			to meet a melty fate.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVstruggle" text="struggle" />
		<choice destination="CVpleasure" text="rub" />
		<choice destination="CVsubmit" text="submit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CVsubmit">
		<!-- continue patrol, fuck another warrior with the cum -->
		<text>
			You consider your fate, and relax, settling comfortably into the cummy
			confines of her balls. The lizard looks down at her sack and pokes
			"not going to fight for your life? suit yourself" she says and
			fondles herself, getting to her feet with a grunt. The lizard's heavy
			balls swaying against her thighs, weighed down and bulging with your
			body as she goes to join the other lizards on their patrol. Your form
			swaying side to side each time she steps, rthythmically sloshing left
			and right as you soften in the gently burbling confines. Your
			compliant form in for a nice slow churning digestion in her balls,
			gradually those nuts soften and round out as you're creamed, melted
			and finally liquidated. Her balls now round and inflated, full of hot
			cream and nothing else as you're utterly digested into the reptile
			warrior's virile cum.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVsubmitGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CVsubmitGO">
		<text>
			One of our vanquisher's comrades had been giving her blushing looks for
			much of the patrol, so it was on the way back that she acted. The
			predatory lizard with balls full of your cummified remains snagging
			her friend and tugging her into the bushes earning a giggle, and
			frenzied clumsy makeouts as the two stumble and fumble till they find
			themselves laying down one atop the other. The hermier of the two
			wasting no more time with foreplay and thrusting into her horny
			partner, gasps and chirrs and moans audible from the rustling bushes
			as the pair go at it. And not a small amount of sloshing sounds.
			Whatever dim quasi awareness you have now can feel sloshing and
			tensing as the lizard ruts her comrade, and then a tightening as the
			herm climaxes. Your form gushing in thick spurts into the other
			lizard's womb, filling her up, filling her out, filling her to
			overbrimming with all the cum you've made until the jizz spills out
			to pool under their thighs. The two gasping and panting and kissing
			in the afterglow as the last of you leaks out. The pair are quiet for
			a few minutes, then finally emerge from the bushes somewhat more
			sticky for the experience.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="CVstruggle">
		<!-- kneeling/sitting and stroking off -->
		<text>
			Your only hope is to make enough of a fuss that she'll be forced to let
			you go. All you need to do is find the entrance to start sliding back
			up her cock amidst all this sticky cum, as you begin to push and
			shove around you hear the lizard gasp and chirr blissfully "oh yeah
			that's the stuff." she exclaims, apparently finding your vigorous
			movements pleasurable as she closes her eyes and begins to jerk off
			vigorously, the sack beginning to churn around you as you jostle it
			against the ground and her thighs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVstrugglecheck" text="must escape!" />
	</page>

	<check ID="CVstrugglecheck">

		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="CVstruggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="CVstruggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="CVstruggleescape">
		<text>
			You push around inside her sack, shoving at the inside of her cummy
			balls every which way with your hands and feet. Shoving and rubbing
			them against your imprisoning confines as she jerks off, then lets
			out a startled gasp and shudders in bliss "ah don't...noo stay.." she
			protests incoherently as you push your hands up through her shaft and
			shove off from the inside of her sack. The lizard overwhelmed by the
			sensation as you course up her sensitive shaft, under her stroking
			hands that do nothing to jerk you back down as you force your way out
			into the open air, hands grasping her tip them pulling yourself
			forwards and out of her loins. the lizard slumping into a heap as the
			last of you comes out "..get...get back in there.. i wasn't done
			melting you." she protests, making a grabbing motion in your
			direction as she pants and tries to recover from that experience.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CVstruggledigest">
		<text>
			You push around inside her sack, shoving at the inside of her cummy
			balls every which way with your hands and feet. Shoving and rubbing
			them against your imprisoning confines as she jerks off and
			blissfully moans and utters muffled approvals. But you can't find the
			way out of her balls, and as you shove at the inside of her sack you
			feel your hands spread out and mush away into glops of cum. It's too
			late, your body is soft and weak and creamy and starting to come
			apart. And her pleasure is becoming overwhelming as her active sack
			starts to squeeze and churn over your weakened form ever more
			strongly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVstruggleGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CVstruggleGO">
		<text>
			"yes, yes yes" the lizard chants as she strokes off and feels her balls
			burble and churn, softening and rounding out with a final loud
			blorping sound as you dissolve away entirely in her sack. Her
			chanting of delight taking on a more insistent tone, her strokes
			already as vigorous as can be as she feels all that pent up cum in
			her balls now needing to be unleashed. Your remains compacting under
			pressure it seems afore she lets out a screaming cry of bliss, cock
			erupting with hot cum blasting out of her tip to stain the ground.
			All that remains of you now a stain on the ground in front of her as
			she gasps and chirrs and feels shot after shot of your remnants
			ejaculate up her cock until she's spent. The lizard panting in bliss
			as she admires her handiwork, you were a much better cumstain than
			you were a warrior.
		</text>

	</gameover>


	<page ID="CVpleasure">
		<!-- laying on back stroking off, auto fellatio lizard? -->
		<text>
			Your only hope to get her to let you out is to pleasure her into orgasm
			from inside. Hopefully it'll let you be able to escape and so you
			start rubbing around at the inside of her sack, hearing her gasp and
			chirr in delight from your antics. You feel her slip onto her back,
			her swaying balls shifting with the motion to settle against the
			ground and her tail as she spreas her legs and jerks off. The lizard
			laying back as her balls shift with the imprints of your hands
			pushing out the inside of her nuts.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVpleasurecheck" text="need to get out of here!" />
	</page>

	<check ID="CVpleasurecheck">

		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="CVpleasureescape" />
		<outcome destination="CVpleasuredigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="CVpleasureescape">
		<text>
			You rub vigourously around the inside of the lizardwarrior's sack as she
			vigorously jerks off. Your efforts yielding increasingly empassioned
			moans and chirrs from your predator as you rub around the cummy
			confines and finally bearing fruit. The lizard shuddering, hips
			spasming up as she ejaculates and you shoot back up her dick whole
			and intact. Your hands coming through her tip and groping her tits a
			bit afore you pull yourself out of her cock entirely, the dazed
			lizard stained with her own climax and chirring is in no state to
			stop your escape but might recover once she's had a chance for a
			breather.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CVpleasuredigest">
		<text>
			You rub vigourously around the inside of the lizardwarrior's sack as she
			vigorously jerks off. Your actions are clearly giving the lizard a
			great deal of pleasure, her moans and chirrs and gasps are audible
			over the burble of her balls as they churn around you. In her passion
			she arches forwards to lick her cocktip as her balls start to lose
			their lumpy bulges, as your body starts to get churned in record time
			inside her now rather stimulated sack. The lizard shuddering in bliss
			as you lose your fight for solidity and slosh away into jizz inside
			her balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVpleasureGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CVpleasureGO">
		<text>
			The lizard warrior moans in triumphant bliss as her balls round out
			entirely and arches further forwards. She succeeds in the feat of
			getting her own engorged girl eating cock into her mouth, moaning
			around her own tip as she strokes the exposed length until it erupts.
			Her cock ejaculating wad after wad of you down her throat, the
			saurian swallowing you whole in your now liquid form, guzzling you
			down into her belly to gain a round belly paunch as her balls
			deflate. She finally lets the cock pop free when she can take no
			more, straightening out on the ground in time to get her face coated
			in the final spurt of your creamy remains. The lizard just laying
			there in debauched bliss and the aftermath of her messy use for you.
			Quite a sticky way to go.
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<gameover ID="gameover">
		<text>
			It would seem you've met a terrible fate
		</text>

	</gameover>

</Conversation>