<?xml version="1.0"?>
<NPC>
<sprite value="black_zetamorph.png"/>
<name>Black Zetamorph</name>
<description>An imposing yet sexy humanoid figure standing seven feet tall, with her secondary set of arms adding another 2-3 feet atop that. Her skin is coal or void black seeming to drink in the light. Her secondary arms are tipped in razor sharp claws while smaller but no less lethal claws adorn her fingers and toes. Behind her a segmented tail covered in gleaming black carapace shifts restlessly bearing a long blade at its tip. Her feminine curves are accentuated in places by additional segments of armoured carapace, as black as her skin but unlike that voidlike smooth softness her natural armour gleams and glints reflecting the light off its hard surfaces.</description>
<rpg>
<experiencevalue value="70"/>
<ability ability="STRENGTH" value="5" />
<ability ability="AGILITY" value="5" />
<ability ability="DEXTERITY" value="5" />
<ability ability="ENDURANCE" value="5" />
<ability ability="CHARM" value="5" />
<ability ability="INTELLIGENCE" value="5" />
<stat stat="HEALTH" value="60"/>
<stat stat="RESOLVE" value="30"/>

<attribute attribute="PARRY" value="2"/>
<attribute attribute="THERMAL" value="24"/>
<combatMove name="cuisinart" pattern="MELEE" bonusAttribute="MELEE" timeCost="2" bonusToHit="2">
<effectDamage type="KINETIC" minValue="2" maxValue="9" modifier="STRENGTH"/>
<missText count="3">
<text>the lash of the black zetamorph's tail fails to connect with TARGET</text>
<text>a chain of the black zetamorph's claw swipes with all four arms is evaded by TARGET</text>
<text>a devastating kick from the black zetamorph fails to connect with TARGET</text>
</missText>
<hitText count="5">
<text>the black zetamorph whirls and her tail slashes TARGET for VALUE damage</text>
<text>the black zetamorph slashes TARGET with her claws for VALUE damage</text>
<text>the black zetamorph kicks TARGET with a clawed foot for VALUE damage</text>
<text>the black zetamorph unleashes a devastating flurry of blows on TARGET for VALUE damage</text>
<text>the black zetamorph manages to clutch TARGET and rake them with the claws of both arms on one side for VALUE damage</text>
</hitText>
</combatMove>
<combatMove name="web" pattern="RANGED" bonusAttribute="MELEE" timeCost="2" bonusToHit="2">
<missText count="1">
<text>The black zetamorph launches webbing at TARGET but fails to hit</text>
</missText>
<hitText count="1">
<text>The black zetamorph hits TARGET with webbing </text>
</hitText>
<effectStatus probability="100">
<applyText>TARGET is now trapped by webbing.</applyText>
<statusBind uid="20" icon="4"  numModifiers="2">
<removeText> TARGET has escaped from the webbing.</removeText>
<effect attribute="RANGED" modifier="-2"/>
<effect attribute="MELEE" modifier="-2"/>
<bind strength="15" originDependent="true"/>
<struggle count="2">
<text>TARGET struggles to try and get out of the webbing
</text>
<text>TARGET tries to get out of the webbing to no avail
</text>
</struggle>
</statusBind>

</effectStatus>
</combatMove>
</rpg>
<defeated conversation="space/black_zetamorph/defeat" />
<seduced conversation="space/black_zetamorph/seduced" />
<victory conversation="space/black_zetamorph/victory" />
<seducer conversation="space/black_zetamorph/victory" />
<controller AI="black_zetamorph_AI"/>
<faction value="monster"/>
</NPC>