<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="eaten"
			value="2" />
		<!--digested once-->
		<text>

		</text>
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="eaten"
			value="1" />
		<!--eaten once-->
		<text>
		"Greetings warrior, what can I do for you today?" she says pausing her exercises to turn and face you once more.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="nothing, but I just wanted to say hi"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="talked"
			value="1" />
		<!--subsequent meeting-->
		<text>
		"Before me again are you? Very well, speak your piece." she says pausing her exercises to turn and face you once more.
		</text>
		<choice destination="tone" text="you have quite a dismissive tone">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="challenge"
			value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'll quit bothering you"/>		
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<!--first meeting-->
		<text>
		The elf warrior idly swings her staff through a series of stances then turns to you and looks you up and down as if sizing you up, it has a worrisome aspect of being as more than a potential opponent to it "You are the stranger from the stars? I am Awari, and I thought you'd be taller." she remarks somewhat ungraciously and plants the staff butt resting it against the floor mats.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
		<choice destination="tone" text="you have quite a dismissive tone"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="well, i'm sorry to disappoint, fair well"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="tone">
	<text>
	"You are a traveller, and yet I can see that you would not last against the dangers that lie in the wilderness beyond our village. It takes a warrior to brave the jungles of our world."
	</text>
	<choice destination="warrior" text="And what does it take to be a warrior in your eyes?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="I don't need validation from you, i will survive"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="warrior">
	<text>
	"It takes many things to survive in our jungles. Guile, cunning, alertness, willpower. But sooner or later you will find yourself in direst circumstances, when a lamia devours you will you have the toughness to resist her enzymes and the strength and techniques to escape her insides?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="teach0" text="Can you teach me to be a warrior?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="...Well thank you for sharing I guess"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="teach0">
	<text>
	"In a day? hardly. But we'll see if you have what it takes to survive if you are willing to prove your worth."	
	</text>
	<choice destination="teach1" text="And what do you propose?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="teach1">
	<text>
	"Simple, I will swallow you. And you will prove your worth by managing to force your way back out of my belly." says Awari with a lick of her lips, something about the way she'd looked at you had clued you in this might be coming.
	</text>
	<choice destination="teach2" text="And if I don't?"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="teach2">
	<text>
	"Then you were never warrior material to begin with. The choice of course is yours. But either way I'll have helped you meet your destiny." she says.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="challenge" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="challenge" text="I guess that's reasonable."/>	
	<choice destination="teach3" text="this...is absurd"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="teach3">
	<text>
	"Hardly, come back if you change your mind. Unless you run afoul of a hungry pred before then, in which case I guess it was nice meeting you." she says going back to her training.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="I'm not entirely sure the feeling is mutual.."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="challenge">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>
	
</Conversation>