<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry name="LF:mushroomfolk">
	<text>
		Description: LBREAK
		The more common form of mushroom-girl resembles
		a petite, gray-skinned, fungal, but fundamentally
		flesh-and-blood humanoid with a helmetlike red cap of
		spongy material in place of hair.
		LBREAK
		Biological findings: LBREAK
		The cap appears to be a complicated mass of folded and
		ridged material that manufactures a form of omni-pheremone
		capable of weakening will and increasing arousal in a wide
		variety of creatures. Analysis of pheremones samples
		reveals a spore-like structure to these airborne
		particles, as well as vestigial and inactive code
		that would imply once having been used for the purposes
		of reproduction but since then being developed into
		a means of defense. In this form, however, the spores
		are completely sterile. Coupled with the foreign
		pheromones found within in the subject's bloodstream,
		which possessed another individual's DNA,
		it is possible that a more advanced form of mushroom-folk
		exists within the same species, and perhaps develops
		when no other similar form is present in the colony,
		using its own pheromones to suppress superfluous
		metamorphoses. Of course, such a transformation
		would require a large amount of nutrients to fuel
		its development. It can be inferred that this advanced
		form, possibly a "mother" or "queen", would be capable
		of reproduction, secreting fertile spores that would,
		upon landing in a suitable location, develop into
		healthy mushroom-girls.
		LBREAK
		Tactical assessment: LBREAK
		The physical threat presented by the shroomfolk is minimal,
		between their diminutive stature, slender builds,
		and limited muscle mass. The real threat comes from their
		ability to project their spore pheremones at a target,
		in order to diminish said target's resolve and heighten
		arousal to the point where the target would willingly
		allow the mushroom-girl to devour them. Being both very
		soft and completely unarmored, they are likely vulnerable
		to all forms of physical attack, while their naive and
		immature personalities may leave them with little will to
		resist more esoteric forms of 'assault'. It should also be
		notede that, despite manufacturing an omni-pheromone,
		they do not appear to be resistant to the pheromones of other
		creatures.
	</text>
	<requirement name="mushroomfolk" count="1" />

</entry>