<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry name="LF:raijin">
	<text>
		description: At less than 4 feet including horns this form is
		notably stunted in
		comparison to the other reptilio-humanoid xenoforms.
		The blue
		colouration also seems somewhat unusual. Physically the
		creature is
		probably little direct threat with stunted claws and a less
		than
		imposing physical build. However the creature is clearly capable
		of
		projecting electrical energy without mechanical aid. LBREAK
		biological findings: The lack of physical mass and thus strength
		however can be
		explained by the nutritional requirements of assembling
		the
		crystalline network inside its body. This web of crystalline
		threads
		stretches throughout its entire body and centralizes in the
		bones of
		the fingers, horns and a specialist organ within the torso.
		This organ
		seems to be nothing more than a sack grown around a single
		large
		gemstone of clearly biological origin, the gemstone seems to be
		the
		source of the projective electroshock power of the Raijin. It's
		intricacies indicate that artificial means such as genetic engineering
		may have been used to make this a part of the species biology. However
		you lack the tools to conclusively prove this hypothesis. It should be
		noted that while the biological matrices of the crystall node break
		down within hours of removal from the living host that you can
		duplicate them now with suitable raw materials, which may allow a
		mechanical means of duplicating their electrical projection ability.
		LBREAK
		Tactical assessment: The raijin's lack of physical threat but
		projective
		abilities make it more of a danger at range, alas the raijin
		appears
		to know this as well and will seek to open up the distance if
		forced
		into melee. Use of nets or other means of immobilizing or
		impeding the
		creature may be necessary if a melee approach is to be
		successfully
		utilized against it.
		additionally the network of
		crystalline pathways throughout the creature's body is
		highly
		conductive. However this means that electrical attacks are
		significantly less effective rather than more as the crystalline
		threads will absorb the voltage and insulated channels will divert the
		flow harmlessly into its electrical organ, in effect giving the
		creature a charge up. Further notes, it hardly needs be stated but due
		to its attack metallic or highly conductive armour will prove less
		than effective against its lightning ability.
	</text>
	<requirement name="raijin" count="1" />
	<recipe_reward recipe="thunderstone" />
	<recipe_reward recipe="zapgun" />
	<recipe_reward recipe="tesla_rifle" />

</entry>