<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The icetreader pants softly, sprawled on her side after you
			bested her the hefty tauric gal watches you carefully. She tries to
			get back to her feet as you approach, but stumbles and slumps back
			down with a yelp and thump of her furry weight smacking into the snow
			and ice again. It's clear you could take advantage of her now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal0" text="lets find out if you can eat this taur">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="warm0"
			text="it's cold, she looks warm, maybe she could help you warm up?" />
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use you capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use your capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
                </choice> -->
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be for now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>


	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			There's no way you can eat something this big is there? of course there is!
			and the icetreader sees the look in your eyes and shies back away
			from you. Though much like her attempt to keep you away with a
			foreleg it amounts to nothing in the end as you get up in front of
			her and moisten your lips afore grabbing her head and shoulders. The
			feline letting out a threatening growl and trying to push you away
			with both hands even as you haul her towards you and lunge forwards,
			engulfing her head in your mouth. The first swallow unleashing a
			cascade of struggles in your ample meal as she tries to pull back
			from your lips.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1" text="plenty to go, get gulping" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			Despite her struggles and her size and the power of her body you're making
			progress, cramming her chest and upper body steadily past your jaws.
			Your hands grabbing up thick bundles of fur on her lower half to
			restrain her and haul her closer and down your throat as you feel her
			hands pushing out the inside of your belly in protest. But your
			hunger will not be denied and your ravenous hunger carries your lips
			swiftly down to her waistline. The broader taur body with its long
			and thick fur almost instantly slows your progress as you begin to
			try and encompass it. The taur squirms and shifts about trying to
			wriggle back out of your throat. Perhaps she thinks you won't be able
			to get her lower half in so she'll eventually escape, how cute.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal2" text="prove her wrong, devour her lower half" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal2">
		<text>
			Cute but futile, you swallow harshly and hear her utter a whimpering rowl
			from deep within your belly as your powerful throat starts to drag
			those broad furred tauric shoulders past your lips. The stretching is
			incredible, but the expectation of satiation from such a prodigious
			meal makes you all the more willing to endure it as you stretch your
			arms out to grasp another two bundles of fur and haul her further
			inside of yourself. Working your lips steadily over her, pinning her
			forelegs against her belly as your belly stretches with all of her
			humanoid half and you work to cram her tauric half in there with her.
			Her rear legs flail helplessly as they're lifted up off the ground
			and you settle into a seated position, feeling her paws and hands
			shoving at your insides in an attempt to force herself back out of
			your throat. But to no avail it seems, gravity and your desire to
			devour all of this tauric meal more than a match for her resistance.
			And gradually despite her struggles she finds her hindquarters going
			the way of the rest of her, down down down your throat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal3" text="finish her off" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal3">
		<text>
			The taur whimpers and shoves at your insides in protest and a wordless
			request for clemency as she feels the end approaching. Your jaws
			wrapped around her tail and the lower half of her rear legs now. But
			you've come too far to turn back now and you want her inside you, and
			so you swallow a last handful of times feeling those broadpawed
			hinglegs slide down your throat. As you see that long thick furred
			tail slip past your lips it coaxes a profound mhmm of satisfaction
			from you. Your gut stretched out and distended massively with your
			unruly meal, her paw and handprints pushing at the inside of your gut
			as she attempts to make you hork her back up. But you've worked too
			much to get this whimpering and filling meal down to let her back out
			again surely.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal4"
			text="in these cold lands you need the protein, digest her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal4">
		<text>
			The icetreader gets to feel your hands pressing and squeezing down on
			the immense bulge she makes in your belly as you savour her and set
			about making her yours. Those whimpers and pliantive pushings at your
			insides redoubling as you start to gurgle and churn her over. It
			takes a while for the ice treader to digest, that big body of hers
			taking a lot of breaking down. The whimpers fade first under the
			sound of your gurgling gut, followed after a while by her squirmings
			as her form weakens and comes apart inside you. and eventually she
			stills entirely, a hefty mass of meat forming a lump in your belly
			that slowly rounds out and softens into a sloshing fluid for your
			body to absorb. In the end naught remains of the snow cat but your
			satisfaction, your belly flattened out to nothing as the taur is
			completely and utterly digested and rendered into fuel for you. A
			satisfying meal.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="warm0">
		<text>
			The icetreader looks surprised and uneasy as you decide to settle in
			snug against its warm belly after all this. Though it does seem she
			makes a remarkably good warmer and blanket, the warmth and thick fur
			of her underside contrasting pleasingly with the snow and ice you've
			had to experience otherwise. You wriggle a bit closer to her and feel
			her shift one foreleg to curl herself over you a tad but as she does
			so you feel something nudging up against you, something that isn't
			fur or one of her legs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cock0" text="investigate the prodding">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="warm1"
			text="not interested, just snuggle in under the ice treader" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cock0">
		<text>
			You grope around behind you and feel something warm that stiffens and
			engorges under your hand. You turn around so you can get a better
			look down between the two of you you can finally get a good look at
			what she's packing down there and well, wow. She's big for her size
			even considering her tauric body and that cock is starting to arouse
			in earnest as you stroke along it with a thoughtful expression on
			your face. It's really an even warmer spot as you can tell from
			feeling that throbbing girth grow before you towards a length best
			measured in feet and fills the furry nook you're in with the musky
			scent of it. The taur bending her upper half down to look at you in
			curiousity, face flushed as you caress that organ of hers that she
			probably can't get at easily with anything but her forepaws. You give
			her a smile and she goes back to a more comfortable position
			seemingly willing to leave you to it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="it'll be an even warmer place to snuggle into" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You spend a little longer lewdly stroking along that prodigiously
			enormous cock as you make up your mind, hearing her growling a soft
			rumble of delight above you as you work her to full hardness. Finally
			though you're sure about this, plying a hand over that cocktip and
			feeling the delicious sticky pre oozing from it you smile
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				and strip down wanting to experience this against your naked skin
				despite the momentary discomfort
			</conditional>
			.
			You wriggle up further to give the taur a smile and position yourself,
			the snowcat giving you a confused and vaguely disappointed look as
			you've stopped stroking her hardness and nudges you meaningfully with
			a hand. But her expression of needyness turns to surprise as you slip
			back down yes, but do so by pressing your feet into her cocktip. That
			thick shaft of hers easily able to accept your feet and her delighted
			and startled mrowl of pleasure is as much music to your ears as the
			sticky shlurp of her pre oozing around your ankles.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="like a naughty sleeping bag" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			Feeling that wonderful sticky warmth throbbing around your feet makes you
			eager to proceed with this plan. As she rumbles in delight you start
			feeding your legs in out of the cold, that hotness snugly
			encompassing your legs and then ass as you worm your way deeper into
			her enormous schlong. That shaft seems to have no trouble accepting
			you as she shudders and shifts about, paws twitching at the pleasure
			as you slide your ass in. A confused gasp punctuating the rumble as
			you slip yourself into that enormous cock of hers and soon you're
			easing your upper body inside as well, feeling hot cum delightfully
			squishing between your toes as you work your feet all the way down
			her length and through into her sack. It's delightfully comfy nestled
			nearly neck deep in the shaft and balls of the virile taur. The snow
			cat looking down at you with a flush and purring rumbling as she sees
			you getting comfortable there with your legs half curled and your
			upper body contained in her shaft.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockhold0" text="relax and stay where you are" />
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="actually those balls feel even comfier" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockhold0">
		<text>
			You get comfortable inside her warm shaft, well shielded from the cold
			as you feel her engorged length throb around you and hear her rumble
			in moderate arousal. The taur apparently confused but rolling with it
			as you stay there encased in her loins and shift around now and then
			to keep her hard. After a bit of doze like this you feel the tauric
			snow cat doze off as well, probably to have some very naughty dreams.
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" />
		<choice destination="cockhold1" text="uneventful rest" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockhold1">
		<text>
			You rouse sometime later and feel the tauric cat still sleeping above
			you, though her dreams must be delightful for her shaft to still be
			firm around your body. You start going about slowly extricating
			yourself, worming and pulling yourself free of the feline's shaft
			inch by inch as she mumbles and shifts occasionally from the
			stimulation, paws flexing and twitching against the snows. The ice
			treader doesn't rouse though even when you pull the last of yourself
			out of her cock, it's a nice sleeping bag, but you have other things
			to do.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
				<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="ICETREADER_DEFEAT" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="good way to keep warm, bit sticky though" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			This is nice and all, but you find yourself preferring to be even
			stickier, warmer and more curled up than this. The perfect place to
			do that is inside the taur's balls, they're certainly roomy enough.
			With your mind made up you start to squirm down and the taur
			shudders, then gasps and smiles and you feel her cock clench and
			ripple tugging on you gently. The shaft giving you a wonderful
			massage as it presses around you and assists you in squirming your
			way entirely down into the balls of the taur, the tip schlurping as
			it seals shut over the top of your head. The shaft jostling and
			swaying and bulging as you pull yourself down with your legs until
			with a schlorp you pop entirely into the cummy confines of the cat's
			balls, hot cum slopping around every inch of you. Course now you're
			here..
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreChurn" text="those balls start to churn around you" />
		<choice destination="cockvoreEndo0" text="those balls contently hold you" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvoreChurn">
		<text>
			You feel the hot cum tingle pleasurably, soaking into you as her balls
			start to roil softly around you. Well, it is only fair seen as you
			were given such a wonderful warm place. You get comfortable in her
			full and dangling balls as they start slowly churning you down into
			gallons of nutbatter. The rumbling purr of the taur audible over the
			glorping sounds all around you as you soften up in there and feel
			yourself melting with exquisite slowness. All of you is being turned
			into that wonderful liquid warmth you came down here to experience.
			Your extremities are the first to melt away, rubbing your hands
			against the inside of her sack you feel your fingers moosh away, then
			limbs are next to lose form as your body becomes a soft and weak mass
			of living cockcream. Finally your body subsides into the rising cum,
			head slipping under and into wonderful sticky oblivion as all of you
			melts away contently into a huge load of cum for the taur.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreGO" text="churned into spunk" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoreGO">
		<text>
			The taur feels you melt away and growls in delight, curling her upper
			half down to tend to her still rigid erection. The icetreader's balls
			compacting your fluid remains into two nice round orbs as she starts
			to fondle and stroke over her cock, using her hands to rub the the
			tip and end of her length and a forepaw to rub further down the
			shaft. Her growl becoming more aroused and needy as she feels that
			hot churning cum you've become as an insistent bloated pressure
			wanting to be let out as she masturbates. The taur bucking her
			hindquarters to work her cock up vigorously against her stroking
			limbs until with a bellow of delight she reaches her much needed
			orgasm. Your form blasting up out of her tip voluminously,
			splattering hot cream all over the snow. The steaming hot cummy
			remnants of your body melting away the snow as you're pumped out of
			her sack. The tauric feline panting and rumbling in the aftermath as
			she surveys the sticky puddle of jizz that remains of you, that was
			certainly a fun way to get warm. Though you might end up cold again
			once her load cools.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="cockvoreEndo0">
		<text>
			Your host seems to understand your desire for a warm place to rest and so
			your confines are less churny and more simply snug. Though it
			certainly is a very sticky and gooey kind of snug, your every
			movement squelches hot jizz around your form with oozing sounds.
			Still it seems the rumbling kitty is quite happy for you to use her
			balls as a resting place, awfully accomodating of her. You rub
			against the inside of her balls appreciatively then settle in curled
			up comfortably to doze in her sack. And so you pass your time
			contently in the loins of the taur.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreEndo1" text="sometime later, time to leave" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvoreEndo1">
		<text>
			You feel you're done stewing around contently in her balls and start to
			work on wriggling and stroking the inside of her sack. You can feel
			her shaft had softened during your long stay and you know you're
			going to need to get her hard again in order to get back up it, still
			you feel her rumble and feel her shift at your stimulating motions
			inside her. The taur realizing what you're doing as she rubs a
			forepaw against her shaft and stiffens up, the way clear now as she's
			not really trying to keep you down there. So you set about worming
			your way out, the sticky tube throbbing semi hard around you as you
			work up her arousal towards the open air. The tip disgorging you with
			a schlurp as you wriggle free. You look back at the flushed taur and
			marvel at your ingenuity, that was truly an interesting way to
			protect yourself from the elements. Time to get going now.
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
			<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="ICETREADER_DEFEAT" value="1" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="she seemed to take this well, get going" />
	</page>

	<page ID="warm1">
		<text>
			You're perfectly fine where you are, and decide to wriggle to get
			companionably close and snuggly with the big furry cat taur. After a
			while it seems she becomes more agreeable to your presence and
			settles in with a pleased rumble resting atop you, and like that you
			rested for a while safe from the cold. When you parted giving the
			taur a pat on the head you even got a soft wet lick from her that
			shows she's apparently made her peace with you. For now at least
			she's not going to be hunting you down.
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<effect type="incrementglobalflag" flag="ICETREADER_DEFEAT" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end"
			text="who'd of thought a snuggle was all you needed to make friends here" />
	</page>

</Conversation>