<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="ferals" />
		<text> 
		The vicious predatory bird cocks its head to the side as it looms over you and lets out a little cluck of satisfaction. The big avian has you at its mercy right now, its assault has left you in no state to fight it off further. Soon you'll see what it desires to do with the morsel who it has before it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*it wants to eat you*">
				<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="*it wants to make cream of you*">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="gameover" text="*a fate too terrible to contemplate*">
					<notpreference fetish="cockvore" />
			<notpreference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	The avian bounds forwards and then snaps its beak out wide and encompassing your head in one motion. The points of the beak pressing against your belly and back as its tongue flicks and shifts around your face. The thick cloying scent of the birds breath washing over you as its saliva soaks your head and then GLUCK GLUCK jerks its head forwards and swallows to encompass your shoulders and then your chest. The voracious predatory bird's feathery neck bulging out, first with your head and then with your chest as the beast eats you alive. Dangling your lower half from its beak as it prepares to devour even more of you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*food for an overgrown chicken, the indignity of this galaxy*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The terror bird took a moment to shift its stance and cock its head to the side as your legs wave about, then starts glucking you down again. The bird tipping its head back and lunging forwards with its beak near simultaneously to gobble you down with gravity's help. Your form sliding down its muscular neck, bulging it out and then forming a hefty weight in its gut as you pile down inside. The short feathered belly of the bird sagging low and bulging with the contours of your form as you're packed away as a tightly curled up meal for the avian...
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreStruggle" text="*try to get back out of here*"/>
	<choice destination="oralvoreSubmit" text="*submit to being birdfood*"/>
	</page>
	
	<check ID="oralvoreStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreStruggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreStruggleDigest" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleEscape">
	<text>
	The bird may have gotten you down, but not out. And it occurs to you it can hardly avoid a good thrashing from the inside. Confined in its gut you do your best to strike out and upwards, aiming to cause as much pain and discomfort as possible. The terror bird letting out a squawk and shifting its weight from foot to foot as it gut jostles and wobbles with your motions. It tries to squish you with its belly muscles and disorientate you with jolting sudden motions. This seems to have nauseated the bird more than it deters you though, or maybe the internal soreness is getting to it as it thinks better of this whole eating you idea. The bird finding you too disagreeable meal hacks and coughs and then horks you up with a similar series of jerking head movements as when you went in. The terror bird backing up a few paces and shaking off the sensation after retching you up.
	</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleDigest">
	<text>
	The bird may have gotten you down, but not out. And it occurs to you it can hardly avoid a good thrashing from the inside. Confined in its gut you do your best to strike out and upwards, aiming to cause as much pain and discomfort as possible. The terror bird letting out a squawk and shifting its weight from foot to foot as it gut jostles and wobbles with your motions. It tries to squish you down with its belly muscles as enzymes soak your form with a gurgle. Shoving at its insides was a terrible plan! what were you thinking, all you've done is stimulated its digestive processes into overdrive. The bird lets out a few more squawks as your struggles redouble, but the stomach walls are now fully active, pressing and kneading and squishing over you as you find the birdy's digestive fluids are soaking into your flesh.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreStruggleGO" text="*gurgle*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvoreStruggleGO">
	<text>
	The birds stomach turns out to be as lethal as the rest of the beast and offers you just as little mercy. The avian's innards energetically gurgling and grinding you down into mush, melting you away utterly over the following hour as your struggles diminish into weak twitching and then smooth liquid glorping. The terror bird pausing its motions with a soft caw and then cocking its head to the side as it gut finishes compacting away.			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Then jerks its head back and forth and horks up your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				into a sodden pile that reeks of stomach enzymes.
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
			<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />	
			Then bounds off, already seeking out another prey.
			</conditional>
	</text>
	
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreSubmit">
	<text>
	You have the good sense to know a battle you can't win, and the terror bird had you utterly outmatched from the outset. How much more so now, you don't bother struggling and instead just squirm around to get as comfortable as you can as the creature begins to digest you. The avian predator's innards starting to secrete enzyme rich goop to soak your form, breaking down and melting your shape inch by inch...
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreStruggleGO" text="*gurgle*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	The terror bird pins you down against beneath it with a single clawed foot and caws softly. Then it lets out a throaty series of deep squawks as it leans in close, rubbing its feathered underside against your body. The sensation changing as something else starts to emerge, a large tapering length growing and hardening against you. Its musky lewd scent intruding on your thoughts and adding indignity to your defeat as it grinds against your backside..You feel it straighten up and for a moment the hope of being left alone rises, only to be dashed as the terror bird flips itself around. And suddenly the tip of that voracious birdschlong is pressing against your face, mooshing over your head as the bird chirps and caws in delight. Seems you're gonna be bird seed.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="*schlurped inside*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	You struggle but cannot escape from underneath the avian's claw as it keeps you pinned and humps its length flexibly over your head and shoulders. The tight tapering length bulging around your shape as the terror bird feeds you in, cramming you in past your chest afore lifting up its claw from your backside. The voracious bird schlong rippling to tug you in on its own with ease now, the bulging girth encompassing your hips and hanging low beneath the bird's belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="*schlurped up completely*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	Gradually you feel your squirming form drawn into that birdcock, the length twitching and rippling to schlurp up your legs as the birdy caws and chirps in delight from the sensations. Your body spilling into the down covered balls of the birdy as it finishes drawing you inside. Soon enough every ounce of your form has been crammed into those almost furry bird balls making them sag low and giving the bird an inconvenient but oh so satisfying impediment to its gait. The bird letting out little coos as you squirm around, its cock twitching against its belly from the sensation of your movements.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvorePleasureCheck" text="*try and make it cum you out*"/>
	<choice destination="cockvoreSubmit" text="*submit to being birdy ball batter"/>
	</page>
	
	<check ID="cockvorePleasureCheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="cockvorePleasureEscape" />
		<outcome destination="cockvorePleasureDigest" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="cockvorePleasureEscape">
	<text>
	You shouldn't find it too hard to pleasure the dumb bird to cumming you out whole. It's not like it's smart enough to figure out your intentions. You set about rubbing against the cum covered walls of the confining sack as if your life literally depends on it. The avian's coos and caws of delight becoming immediately more pronounced as you get to work, its shaft tip bobbing and drooling pre at the sensations as you writhe around. The slick confines squelching with your movements until with a shuddering squawking spasm the bird is pushed over the edge. Your form erupting out of the length amidst a burst of seed, landing in a splat as the bird dazedly stumbles and sways about a movement. It seems momentarily disorientated by the orgasm and afterglow.
	</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvorePleasureDigest">
	<text>
	You shouldn't find it too hard to pleasure the dumb bird to cumming you out whole. It's not like it's smart enough to figure out your intentions. You set about rubbing against the cum covered walls of the confining sack as if your life literally depends on it. The avian's coos and caws of delight becoming immediately more pronounced as you get to work, its shaft tip bobbing and drooling pre at the sensations as you writhe around. The hot cum you're sharing the space with glorping, gurgling and churning as you writhe around in it. The sack bobbing and contracting rthythmically as you pleasure the bird to no end..and find yourself softening as you've only succeeded in hurrying along your process of melting into bird seed. You find yourself weaker, unable to move with vigor and losing the sense of your extremities. Instead they seem to be replaced with a gooey warm sensation that somehow permeates your extremities.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvorePleasureGO" text="MMMPH! SPLSMNPH!"/>	
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvorePleasureGO">
	<text>
	Your efforts have only hastened your debauched demise in the beast's balls. The avian's sack turning still and round, only moving to slosh and sway as it walks now. Your form has been utterly melted down, a compact mass of thick seed within the terror bird's sack..ready for breeding, or for play, or perhaps to be wasted on the ground for inconsequential pleasure. What an unfortunate fate.
	</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="cockvoreSubmit">
	<text>
	The bird was nice enough to give you this lewd place to rest and something naughty to melt into. With a blush of colour in your cheeks you settle contently into the now softly churning sack. You can feel the bird's every movement, its strides sending you swaying around and sloshing cum over and around you. The sensations of your form softening and swaying are oddly, good..in fact they feel just so relaxing that you can let your pleasures just... 
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvoreSubmitGO" text="...."/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvoreSubmitGO">
	<text>
	Quietly you melt away, spreading into the beast's cum with a blissful burbling sigh. The avian's sack turning still and round, only moving to slosh and sway as it walks now. Your form has been utterly melted down, a compact mass of thick seed within the terror bird's sack..ready for breeding, or for play, or perhaps to be wasted on the ground for inconsequential pleasure. What an unfortunate fate.	
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<gameover ID="gameover">
		<text>
			It would seem you've met a terrible fate
		</text>

	</gameover>
</Conversation>