<?xml version="1.0"?>
<intro count="7">
	<text>
		Your health bar (red, topmost) is your resistance to being taken
		as
		unwilling prey or otherwise meeting a terrible fate. Healing items
		are
		useful for recovery. LBREAK
		Your resolve bar (pink, below) is your
		resistance to becoming willing
		prey. LBREAK
		your satiation bar (green)
		inversely represents your level of
		hunger, and is constantly
		depleting as you need food in order to live.
		LBREAK
		when your satiation
		is over 50% you slowly regenerate health, but this
		results in increased
		satiation consumption rate so healing items may
		be a preferable option		
		LBREAK
		when your resolve is less than total it automatically recovers
		regardless
		of your satiation level LBREAK
		when your satiation level
		reaches 0 you will begin to rapidly take
		starvation damage LBREAK
		Your action bar (orange) indicates your number of AP, AP is spent to use attacks, moves and abilities. AP recovers automatically. AP recovers faster if you're over 50% satiation or if you take no action that would spend AP. Your base rate of AP recovery scales with your maximum AP amount.
		LBREAK
		page 1
		(d or right to move to next page)
	</text>
	<text>
		To move your character around the game world use the arrowkeys,
		WASD
		keys or the numpad. to wait a little press 5, to wait a
		significant
		period of time press R. LBREAK
		To compress time hold down
		the shift key or the control key while
		performing other actions. LBREAK
		page 2 (d or right to move to next page, a or left to move to the
		prior
		page)
	</text>
	<text>
		The text window bottom can be expanded and contracted with home
		and end
		LBREAK
		and it can be scrolled with page up and page down LBREAK
		the list panels can also be manipulated with page up and page down or
		by
		grabbing the scrollbar with click and hold and moving it up and down
		LBREAK
		page 3 (d or right to move to next page, a or left to move to
		the prior
		page)
	</text>
	<text>
		To act on the world around you you can click the mouse on that
		tile.
		LBREAK
		One alternate way to attack a hostile enemy in an adjacent
		tile move into
		their space LBREAK
		An alternate way to attack enemies,
		even distant ones, without using the
		mouse is to activate the retro
		targeter with the O key. this will
		toggle on a mode which lets you
		browse through targets in a list and
		attack by pressing space or enter
		LBREAK
		page 4 (d or right to move to next page, a or left to move to
		the prior
		page)
	</text>
	<text>
		To select the way in which you interact with the world (look,
		interact,
		attack, special) you can click the button on the lower left
		side of
		the player status ui and this will bring up a dropdown. Special
		will
		contain all non standard moves like seduction, unlocked specials,
		weapon alternate fire and etc. LBREAK
		the hotkeys to do this without
		the dropdown is
		(L)ook,attac(K),(I)nteract,s(P)ecial. LBREAK
		additionally all dropdowns are amenable to the use of the number keys
		along the
		upper row of the keyboard. LBREAK
		you can set your action bar entries by pressing F2 LBREAK
		page 5 (d or right to move to next page, a or left to move to the
		prior
		page)
	</text>
	<text>
	In combat there are six damage types in total. 3 of them affect health, 3 affect seduction. 
	LBREAK
	Kinetic, thermal and shock damage affect health
	LBREAK
	tease, pheremone and psychic affect resolve
	</text>
	<text>
		In space mode you can move using similar controls to on the
		ground with WASD, arrowkeys or the numpad LBREAK
		You will need fuel to
		move LBREAK
		You can wait (for solar power collection or to charge a
		warp drive) by pressing numpad 5 or the spacebar LBREAK
		FTL travel is
		available from the system->nav panel when you're on a ship with an FTL
		score LBREAK
		FTL travel requires stored energy and your destination is
		selected based on your position around the star LBREAK
		page 6 (end of
		file, a or left to move to the prior page)
	</text>
</intro>