<?xml version="1.0"?>
<intro count="4">
<text> The 22nd century saw the launch of earth's 1st starship. The Heinlein's experimental wormhole drive would take the supposed best that earth had to offer to Tau Ceti. Amongst their number you stood as they said goodbye to earth, set forth to the stars and engaged the drive.</text>
<text> But something went wrong, the energies of the wormhole far more violent than predicted scoured and ravaged the Heinlein, flinging it far beyond its intended destination and into the deep black. It emerged from the vortex scorched and torn. As systems failed and the wormhole drive destabilized the order to abandon ship was given, you barely made it to an escape pod before secondary explosions ripped through the Heinlein. You have no idea if anyone had made it off, your last sight of the ship as the cryo pod engages and the glass frosts over another wormhole erupting from the drive core of the ship. You might be the only survivor of this disaster.</text>
<text>When your escape pod finally revived you it was unclear how much time has passed, how long it had hurtled through the void to reach this alien moon. You know from the stars that greet you through the portholes that no rescue will reach so unfamiliar a sky. You have been sundered from all you knew, a stranger in a strange land. You are without a home and those to whom you hold allegiance are far from here and unknown. You are a nomad.</text>
<text>
arrow, wasd and numpad to move. mouseclick on things to act upon them. 'look' button indicates current mouse click action, click it to change action. buttons to the right access key elements. gain exp to level up. running out of health may result in death or forced vore, running out of resolve may result in becoming willing prey. Running out of satiation may result in starving to death. LBREAK 
Page Up, Page Down, Home and end control the text window.(scroll and expand/contract) LBREAK 
(i)nteract, (l)ook, attac(k) and s(p)ecial are the shortcuts to change the mouse action. with the latter followed by number key input to select the special. LBREAK 
cntrl and shift keys compress time when held down to allow faster travel. LBREAK 
the 5 key waits 2 ticks, the r key rests for 20 ticks. LBREAK 
Q key activates the item in your quickslot. LBREAK 
If you want to find your way home you should first find a way off this moon and to the planet below. LBREAK 
</text>
</intro>