<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			You have fallen before the saurian warrior. Licking her lips she
			stands
			over you and reaches down to loosen the bindings of her
			armoured
			tunic with her free hand "Anything to say before you're
			lunch?" she
			taunts, that hand now tracing over her belly under the
			metal weighted
			jacket.
		</text>
		<choice destination="amends0" text="can't we just settle this with gold?">
			<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG"
				flag="allegiance" value="-1" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="please dont?" />
	</page>

	<page ID="amends0">
		<text>
			"you realize when you're digested I can just take your money
			right?" says
			the reptile with a smirk "But perhaps the symbolic nature
			of your
			desire to appease the crown can let us forgo the whole eating
			and
			digesting you." she looks at you expectantly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="gold250" text="*appease with 250 gold*">
			<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GOLD" value="250" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="appeasefail" text="I don't have enough gold" />
	</page>

	<page ID="gold250">
		<effect type="givegold" value="-250" />
		<effect type="manipulateDisposition" faction="saurian" value="25" />
		<text>
			You hand 250 gold to the saurian who looms over you, you can
			only hope
			its enough.
		</text>
		<choice destination="appeasebranch" text="*await judgement*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="appeasebranch">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="FACTIONSTANDING"
			value="50" />
		<text>
			"Mhmm, I believe this will go some way to appease the crown. You
			can live,
			for now."
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="whew" />
	</page>
	<page ID="appeasebranch">
		<text>
			"Is that the best you could do? This won't do at all. You're
			still gonna
			end up padding my thighs." she says apparently concluding
			the enmity
			you have garnered with her people is too much to be wiped
			away by
			these coins. Naturally she doesn't give them back.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="ohcrap" />
	</page>

	<page ID="appeasefail">
		<text>
			"Then you can pay for your crimes with your body."
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="ohcrap" />
	</page>
	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The lizard warrior advances on you with a predatory look in her
			eyes,
			lunging downwards to grasp your feet in her hands and haul them
			up to
			where her long tongue can lap over them. Upended you can do
			little to
			resist as she swiftly shoves your feet into her mouth and
			swallows,
			starting to eat you alive. The warrior leaning forwards as
			she gets
			to your knees, leaving you at an awkward angle yet still
			supported on
			the ground as she swallows you up feetfirst. You can feel
			her belly
			around your feet already, churning and eager to have all of
			you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="what a way to go" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Chugging away the reptilian warrior continued cramming you past
			her lips,
			reaching your hips she's squatted down over you now. Her
			throat
			rippling powerfully to draw you ever deeper as her belly begins
			to
			show, your legs starting to curl and push out the inside of her
			stomach making her tunic part around the bulge. It won't be long now
			and as you helplessly clutch at the ground you can do little to even
			slow your descent into her heated innards. Your head and shoulders
			are nearing her lips as she shifts back up into a standing position,
			head tipped back as she lets gravity help cram you down inside her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="eaten alive" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			The warrior pauses once she's encompassed your chest, as if
			teasing you
			with your last sight of the outside world and the
			possibility you
			could struggle to avoid being fully consumed. But
			before you can grip
			firmly against her shoulders, she swallows anew.
			Your body dragged
			down past her lips inexorably, arms forced above
			your head they frame
			your last view of the outside world through her
			jaws afore they
			slither down her throat to join the rest of you. The
			reptile warrior
			now running a hand over her distended and exposed gut
			as you're
			forced to curl up within her, trapped within that gurgling
			cauldron
			you will be rendered down into a meal if you do not escape.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="struggle" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="submit" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			The victorious lizard chirrs and rubs over her belly as she
			starts to
			digest her vanquished foe. Her gurgling gut squeezing in
			around you,
			but you're not planning on sticking around and she lets
			out an erf as
			you jostle and shove around inside her. Your hands and
			feet shoving
			at her insides, it eventually proves too much for her
			though. The
			mighty warrior grunting in dismay and then doubling over
			horking ou
			up with a blargh. Her gagging retching forcing you up and
			out in
			front of her in a heap. While you're wet and maybe a bit gooey
			at the
			edges the warrior reptile is in a far more dazed state, briefly
			wiped
			out by the energy taken to shove you back up into the open air.
			Might
			be time to run.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggledigest">
		<text>
			The victorious lizard chirrs and rubs over her belly as she
			starts to
			digest her vanquished foe. Her gurgling gut squeezing in
			around you,
			but you're not planning on sticking around and she lets
			out an erf as
			you jostle and shove around inside her. Her gut gurgling
			and grinding
			around you as you push out at her insides, but a series
			of rthythmic
			contractions shove you back into a submissive ball of
			curled up meat.
			Your struggles unable to to upset her powerful stomach
			as it works
			enzymes and digestive fluids into you, starting to process
			your flesh
			as she chirrs and smiles in triumph. It won't be long now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleGO" text="*GURGLE*" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleGO">
		<text>
			Despite your struggles your contest from inside the lizard is
			ending much
			like your contest outside. Her gut grinding over you,
			mercilessly
			gurgling you down. Her gut quietens your protests, stills
			your
			struggles and then gradually eases out the bulges and contours
			made
			by your body within her own. Her gut turning smooth and round as
			you
			turn smooth and liquid within her, reduced to nought but a
			nutritious
			meal as her gut slims and flattens you your remnants will
			go to make
			her stronger, and perhaps more importantly, sexier.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			To the victor go the spoils and as she chirrs and rubs over her
			gut you
			moan submissively within her as she gets to work on you. Her
			gut
			gurgling over your unresisting form as she smiles and gives you an
			approving pat, satisfied by a foe who knows when they are beaten. Her
			insides grinding over you, your form to find new purpose becoming one
			with and fuel for her own as she works you over.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitGO" text="*gurgle*" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitGO">
		<text>
			Gradually her gut turns round and smooth, softening the lumps
			made of you
			until you're utterly digested away inside her. The syrupy
			gloop going
			on a final adventure through her intestines as her middle
			starts to
			compact and then flatten, your remnants going to good use in
			filling
			the curves of her ass, thighs and breasts.
		</text>

	</gameover>


</Conversation>