<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
<page ID="start">
<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="dammathquest1" value="3"/>
<!--quest complete -->
<text>
Nissa gives you a delighted smile at your approach "Friend! the pump is working well, what can I do for you?"
</text>
<choice destination="reward" text="you said something about being grateful?">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="reward" value="0"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="shop" text="I would like to buy something">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="reward" value="1"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="end" text="nothing at the moment"/>
</page>

<page ID="reward">
<text>
"oh? oh oh yes! well, i'm not just the mechanic here.. the other villagers of dammath they find things sometimes, and when they do they bring them to me to make use of them...and well, I think they'd find it appropriate if I shared some of these things with you for your service right? I mean, not for free..the queen'd not like that..but..."
</text>
<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="reward" value="1"/>
<choice destination="shop" text="sure i'd like to buy something"/>
<choice destination="end" text="i see, I'm not really interested in buying from you."/>
</page>

<page ID="shop">
<text>
"Okay! now, I get all sorts of things...most of them don't work but you're real clever, I'm sure you can figure out a use for them."
</text>
<special effect="shop" ID="dammathMechanic"/>
</page>

<page ID="start">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="talked" value="1"/>
<!--talked before -->
<text>
"Hello!...say, I don't suppose..no I shouldn't ask it's embarassing but, could you give me some help? I can't fix this pump and you have the look of someone who might be good with technology."
</text>
<choice destination="pump" text="tell me about this pump"/>
<choice destination="end" text="looks can be deceiving."/>
</page>

<page ID="start">
<!--first greetings-->
<text>
The saurian takes a second or two to notice your approach as she's frowning and looking over a rather rusty looking chunk of metal with a sense of unhappyness, but she smiles as she rises to her feet to face you "Oh, uh hello...name's Nissa..last mechanic of Dammath." she says and then feels need to elaborate "it's why i'm fixing this here pump, or trying to anyway."
</text>
<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1"/>
<choice destination="pump" text="tell me about this pump"/>
<choice destination="end" text="it's good to meet you Nissa, but I feel the need to be elsewhere"/>
</page>

<page ID="pump">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="dammathquest1" value="0"/>
<text>
A chance to talk about machines and the earnest if somewhat ill tutored mechanic lights up with enthusiasm.
"This pump is the primary source of water for our village...my mentor's, mentor's mentor made it and we've kept it working since...till now anyway, now it's broken and I..I don't know how to fix it okay? I'm not fully trained and I'm not sure what's wrong with it." she says looking upset for a moment before bouncing back "but it's really quite an amazing thing isn't it? when it's running we don't even have to operate it by hand." she pauses "..listen I'm kinda in a bind here, if I dont fix the pump they'll probably replace it with a boring old crank. If you want to take a look at it.. I'd be ever so grateful if you manage to fix it."
</text>
<choice destination="swamp" text="the land to the east looks awfully wet. Cant you get water from there?">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="swamp" value="0"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="mentor" text="can't you ask your mentor for help? where is your mentor?">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="mentor" value="0"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="pumpquest" text="maybe I could take a look at it?"/>
<choice destination="end" text="fascinating, but I have things to do."/>
</page>

<page ID="pump">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="dammathquest1" value="1"/>
<text>
"The pump still isn't working. I'm not sure what's wrong, but if you could lend a hand I'd be ever so grateful." she says sincerely and fidgets "I dun want to be a mechanic without a pump."
</text>
<choice destination="swamp" text="the land to the east looks awfully wet. Cant you get water from there?">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="swamp" value="0"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="mentor" text="can't you ask your mentor for help? where is your mentor?">
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="mentor" value="0"/>
</choice>
<choice destination="end" text="I haven't figured it out yet no."/>
</page>

<page ID="pump">
<!-- fix pump, complete quest-->
<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="dammathquest1" value="2"/>
<text>
"you think you fixed it? let me check." she says and then goes to prod at the pump afore throwing the circuit breaker closed and then letting out a squee as the machine stutters and shudders to life. The pump gears grinding and squeeling makes Nissa frantic for a moment or two as she applies liberal lubrication, the noise becoming steadily more healthy. Nissa stepping back just as water starts to belch and burst up out of the pump to fill the bucket "it works! it really works you fixed it oh thankyou!" the lizard mechanic turns around and embraces you, overjoyed by the restoration of the pump and without a care for the stains on her tunic she might be exposing you to with her exuberant celebration.
</text>
<effect type="givegold" value="100"/>
<effect type="experience" value="50"/>
<effect type="setfactionflag" flag="friendship" value="1"/>
<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="dammathquest1" value="3"/>
<choice destination="end" text="you're welcome *disentangle quickly afore you get messy*"/>
<choice destination="end" text="you're welcome *give her a smooch then step back*"/>
</page>

<page ID="swamp">
<text>
"It's wet sure, but it's not exactly good to drink, like....at all." she looks concerned at you, stepping closer to examine your facial features "you didn't try to drink it did you? it can make you really sick...you look fine though." she steps back out of your personal space.
</text>
<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="swamp" value="1"/>
<choice destination="end" text="ah no i'm quite well, thanks"/>
</page>

<page ID="mentor">
<text>
"...she died, died before she could finish training me." says Nissa sadly "She was in the mines looking into a new way of mining more effectively when the great serpent appeared."<conditional><condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="dammathquest0" value="3"/> she then gives you a little smile "But i hear you killed it, thankyou."</conditional>
</text>
<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="mentor" value="1"/>
<choice destination="end" text="I'm sorry to hear that"/>
</page>

<page ID="pumpquest">
<text>
"you will? oh thankyou" she bounces on the spot and looks a moment like she's about to embrace you then lowers her hands "i'll be ever so grateful if you can get it to work."
</text>
<effect type="setglobalflag"  flag="dammathquest1" value="1"/>
<choice destination="end" text="I'll give it a look, no promises though."/>
</page>

</Conversation>