<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="disposition"
			value="2" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="DICEROLL" value="10" />
		<text>
			Slumped into a rough seated posture you're right where the harpy
			wants you. Alighting and then with a giggle twirling around to seat
			herself atop your head.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="hair" />
				Your
				<macro id="hair_desc_short" />
				hair becoming stained with her sexual juices from those perpetually
				salivating harpy netherlips.
			</conditional>
			The harpy letting out a delighted coo before her nethers begin
			stretching over your skull and she wriggles her hips to work her way
			down over you. The harpy starting to cram you into her hungry snatch
			to sate it once and for all.
		</text>
		<picture source="harpyportrait"/>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="continue" />
	</page>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="disposition"
			value="2" />

		<text>your view of the sky above is eclipsed as the harpy lands legs
			astride your head, that moist snatch dripping drops of pearlescent
			harpy lust that splatter against your face as she coos in
			anticipation and wriggles her hips before descending upon you. Her
			nethers mashing against your facial features, grinding back and forth
			before she shoves herself down with a gasp and you feel her powerful
			birth canal seize your skull and pull. The harpy clenching
			rthythmically, those powerful muscles working seemingly in reverse of
			normal but with great ability as she works you deeper inside.
		</text>
		<picture source="harpyportrait"/>		
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="continue" />
	</page>


	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>With your head wedged up inside of her she seems to find little
			difficulty working the rest of you in, cramming you head first into
			her womb as she shifts her hips up and down. a lewd and debauched act
			of gratification that works your body inch by inch deeper into the
			slit between her legs, her middle bulging with first your head and
			then your entire upper body as she crams you in. Finally only your
			legs are left, your flailing put to an end as she squeezes them
			together with her own and then shoves your feet against the ground.
			the harpy letting out a delighted cry and a splattering of her sexual
			nectar as she works you deeper in, another thrust and only those feet
			are left. the harpy clenching and pressing her thighs together as
			even those disappear and you're drawn up entirely into her womb.</text>
		<choice destination="wombed" text="wombed" />
	</page>
	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>The mere hunger of her voracious pussy it seems is enough to
			claim your shoulders and chest and from there her gasping and moaning
			shifting of her hips back and forth is enough to wedge your butt
			under her and up inside of her body. Once she's claimed your arse its
			merely a matter of time, the harpy letting out ever more delighted
			coos as you're forced to curl up inside the heat of her soft but yet
			ravenous womb. The harpy standing legs astride as your own legs slip
			up into her drooling nethers and you're sealed within her.</text>
		<choice destination="wombed" text="wombed" />
	</page>

	<page ID="wombed">
		<text>Trapped within the depths of the harpies womb you hear her coo
			in delight and feel past the syrupy nether juices and cradling
			confines her wings rub over the bulge you make in her. It would seem
			you might be at her mercy. And judging by the hot sensual tingle and
			possessive clench of her womb around your body it might not be a
			mercy that's forthcoming.</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="struggle to escape" />
		<choice destination="pleasure" text="try to please her" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="just let it happen" />
	</page>
	<page ID="struggle">
		<text> As the womb clenches you push back, struggling to try and force
			your way out before her womb succeeds in liquidating you!</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="struggle" />

	</page>
	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="strugglegush" />
	</check>
	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>The harpy lets out a gasp, and then a groan as you shove at her
			insides, worming your arms downwards to force her to dilate. your
			form unceremoniously squeezing out from between her legs as she
			shudders and whines. Her form now lies slumped behind you, sore and
			stunned from having herself stretched wide from within.. you should
			probably take advantage of this opportunity to run.</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>
	<page ID="strugglegush">
		<text>You struggle and push, but cannot find purchase. the womb is
			clenching and seemingly without exit as the harpy gasps and moans and
			rubs against her struggling middle with both wings. You put up a
			valiant but ultimately futile struggle with slickening fingers and
			softening limbs. But soon, she's able to do you in with a clench of
			her victorious womb.</text>
		<choice destination="gushedSTR" text="Not so strong now..." />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasure">
		<text>Your only choice, to pleasure her from within to try and make
			her orgasm you out whole. You rub the insides of the clenching womb
			as best you can to try and make her reach her peak before you succumb
			to the digestive caress of her womb.</text>
		<choice destination="pleasurecheck" text="get rubbing" />
	</page>
	<check ID="pleasurecheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="8" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureescape" />
		<outcome destination="pleasuregush" />
	</check>
	<page ID="pleasureescape">
		<text>The harpy moans under your deft touch, gasping until with a
			clench and unclench you take your opportunity. Sliding forth out of
			her spasming orgasming nethers covered in juices. The harpy looks
			dazed in pleasure by the unexpected experience and doesn't seem to
			hold a grudge for you cheating her out of turning you into an orgasm
			seen as you gave her one a strange but satisfying way.</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="disposition" value="2" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>
	<page ID="pleasuregush">
		<text>The harpy moans under your deft touch, gasping as you pleasure
			her from inside. But for all your efforts soon you soften
			nonetheless, soften and then slosh and finally slop as her womb melts
			you down into feminine nectar. She seems almost disappointed in a way
			that you can no longer please her that way, almost disappointed.</text>
		<choice destination="gushedPL" text="*slosh*" />
	</page>


	<page ID="submit">
		<text>The harpy probably deserves to have you as an orgasm after she
			went to the trouble of catching you and stuffing you in her womb. Why
			not let her do it, the hot womb juices soaking into and digesting
			your body feel rather arousing after all.</text>
		<choice destination="melt" text="let it happen" />
	</page>

	<page ID="melt">
		<text>The harpy spends a few enjoyable hours leisurely turning you
			into girlcum. Her body working your unresisting form over with
			kneading ripples and hot syrupy juices until finally you transition
			almost unnoticably from solid to liquid within her. Your form one
			with her orgasm.</text>
		<choice destination="gushedSUR" text="sploosh" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="disposition"
			value="2" />
		<text> The harpy has defeated you, landing in front of you she uses
			one wing to coax your face up against her wet nethers. She might not
			you as an orgasm, but she clearly wants you to pleasure her.</text>
		<choice destination="giveoral" text="get licking" />
	</page>
	<page ID="giveoral">
		<text>You lick at her downy muff, hearing her coo and moan and maybe
			giggle a little. Her sex rippling around your tongue as she urges you
			deeper and her nectar becomes more prominent. Gradually her delighted
			noises become more and more prominent and that wing grinds you more
			firmly against her snatch until with a cry she climaxes, soaking your
			face with her orgasm. She releases you but you can tell that in light
			of this domination next time you might not be so lucky and the juices
			gushing forth from her sex when she catches you..will be made OF you.</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="disposition" value="-1" />
	</page>


	<gameover ID="gushedSTR">
		<text>Your body had liquefied inside with a final clench and now she
			pleasures herself, tracing a wing between her thighs to rub back and
			forth as she shudders in pleasure. knowing that she's defeated and
			melted you utterly within her despite your struggles she lets out a
			long drawn out moan of delight, bringing herself steadily to climax
			and sending a gush of your remnants oozing out over her wing..soaking
			the ground as well in your liquefied form as you're now nothing more
			than a puddle of harpy juice splattered beneath her.</text>
	</gameover>

	<gameover ID="gushedPL">
		<text>The harpy was already close and touching herself from your
			earlier ministrations, pleasuring herself to the sensations as your
			wriggling attempts to rub her from inside become the slop and slosh
			of a womb full of girlcum ready to be splattered on the ground. Her
			hips bucking and her thighs grinding against eachother as she rocks
			in place and then lets out a cry, splattering you across the inside
			of her thighs and the forest floor. the harpy blushing and smiling as
			she takes off to dry her legs in the wind and leaves what's left of
			you a cooling puddle soaking into the dirt. For all your attempts to
			please her, you're just another orgasm.</text>
	</gameover>

	<gameover ID="gushedSUR">
		<text>She notices only gradually that all inside her is slosh, and her
			womb is leaking with the overful desire to release the remnants of
			its prey. With the help of another harpy helpfully delving down below
			her waist as she reclines she soon has you out of her, your form
			sloshing and melting until within a delighted sigh she leaves you
			painting the face and chest of her friend. Your form now nothing more
			than a layer of girly nectar staining the two harpies as they snuggle
			up together.</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>