<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The harpy lies gasping and defeated on the ground, her moist nethers
			are inviting. but perhaps you'd prefer to purely indulge in your own
			pleasure
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				or your own hunger...
			</conditional>
		</text>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="AMIIA_HARPIES" value="1" />
		<picture source="harpyportrait"/>		
		<choice destination="receiveoral" text="Force her to lick you">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="receiveblowjob" text="make her suck it">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="giveoral" text="Lick her folds" />
		<choice destination="meal0" text="she'd make a great meal">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
				<choice destination="capture" text="Use you capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="do nothing" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="giveoral">
		<text>With her legs splayed you see no reason not to sample her
			defeated folds. Getting situated to lick at her warm nethers you hear
			her gasp and feel her sex pliant against your tongue. You could
			probably force your way up inside of her from this position, if you
			wanted. Or keep this purely a matter of your tongue, her snatch and
			her increasingly empassioned coos.</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth" text="Crawl into the harpy" />
		<choice destination="giveoralfinish" text="just keep licking" />
	</page>
	<page ID="giveoralfinish">
		<text>
			You decide to keep on enjoying those moans and coos from the
			helpless
			harpy you're licking from the outside. stroking her thighs as
			you
			keep on licking, the scent of her downy sex flooding your nostrils
			as
			the sound of her gasps and moans fill your ears. Several minutes of
			helpless but hardly resistive writhing from the harpy culminates in
			her letting out a cry and staining your face with juices. the panting
			and cooing harpy you leave on the ground as you get back to your feet
			seems rather appreciative of your lewd efforts to please her.
		</text>
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="disposition" value="2" />
			<special effect="healnpc" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />

	</page>

	<page ID="receiveoral">
		<text>
			You climb over the harpy's defeated form,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				lowering your pants and underwear,
			</conditional>
			you place your crotch right over the bird-lady's face. She scrunches
			her eyes a bit, but eventually starts lapping at your folds.Maybe
			this is a typical form of dominance being asserted amongst harpy kind
			cause she seems not...inexperienced, her tongue touching such
			delightful places as you hold her in place against your snatch.
		</text>
		<choice destination="receiveoralfinish" text="Ooohh, yes!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="receiveoralfinish">
		<text>You can't help but enjoy the moment, that deft tongue lapping
			deep within as you close your eyes and rub her hair. the harpy girl
			submissively lapping at your folds as you grind on her face, spending
			many minutes simply being serviced by the harpy until finally she
			pushes you to your peak. Her licking rewarded with a gush of your
			juices staining her face, the harpy flushing in humiliation as you
			release her..but too weak to protest further she flutters away during
			your afterglow.</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="fun indeed" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="receiveblowjob">
		<text>
			You climb over the harpy's defeated form,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				whipping out your
				<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
				length,
			</conditional>
			stroking yourself to hardness and rubbing yourself against her face,
			smothering her with musk. She scrunches her eyes a bit, and flinches
			away from your tip when you try to stick it in her mouth. But she
			relents as you grab her head and make it clear that you're in charge
			here. The harpy stretching her lips around your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft. She's fairly inexperienced with this, but once you've grabbed
			her head with both hands you can help her past both her reluctance
			and her lack of skill. Starting to rthyhmically thrust into her face,
			enjoyably using her mouth as she utters muffled protests.
		</text>
		<choice destination="receiveblowjobfinish" text="Ooohh, yes!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="receiveblowjobfinish">
		<text>You can't help but revel in your use of the harpy, the feathery
			girl helpless as you fuck her face and feel your pleasure build. The
			unfamiliar use clearly putting a strain on the harpy especially with
			your actions being none too gentle. In only a short time your needs
			are satisfied, the harpy's eyes widening as you climax, holding her
			head in place to pump seed down her throat afore only slowly letting
			her up. Your last few wads of cum ending up in her mouth as you pull
			out. The harpy spitting the seed out on the ground, flushed with
			shame from the violation, she attempts to weakly buffet you with her
			wings but is in no good state to exact retribution right now. The
			harpy instead settling for flying away with the funk of your shaft
			permeating her nostrils and the taste of your seed smothering her
			tongue.</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="fun indeed" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth">
		<text>Well she's there. why not use her as a sleeping bag. thrusting
			both hands inside of her causes her to gasp in surprise and gives you
			the leverage needed to work your way inside of her. She writhes
			protesting, but not TOO much as you shove your upper body into her
			womb, curling up so you can haul your legs into her. Your body
			entirely disappearing into the snatch of your defeated foe with a
			slurp and coo from the harpy's netherlips and lips respectively. Its
			really rather comfortable inside her, snug and warm and seemingly
			safe for now.</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>The womb kneads at you, relaxing..massaging..liquidating.
			Putting yourself at the mercy of someone who you got the better of is
			not going to go down as the best plan ever. your form starts to get
			increasingly sloshy as you feel her wings rub at the bulge you make.</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="Not a good idea" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="unbirth2">
		<text>You squirm around, trying to find a way out of your willing
			tomb, but alas, it's too late for you, the womb closing in all around
			as you soften up until with a final squish she pulps your body into
			femcum in a single rolling contraction.</text>
		<choice destination="gushed" text="*Bloop*" />
	</gameover>

	<gameover ID="gushed">
		<text>The harpy lets out a little giggle and then a delighted coo as
			she feather frigs your remains out onto the ground. She can't help
			but be bemused by the way you chose to take advantage of her defeat,
			though she can hardly complain about the results. In fact the only
			downside is none of the harpies are going to believe anyone could be
			so silly as to climb inside a harpy like that!</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			You approach her, the lick of your lips something she knows well as
			you
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				take off your clothes,
			</conditional>
			pull her upright and lick over her face. But beaten she can only
			squirm and whimper as you engulf her head, starting to eat the harpy
			alive.
		</text>

		<choice destination="meal1" text="swallow her up" />
	</page>
	<page ID="meal1">
		<text> Her taste despite her standards of hygiene is delectible. Her
			feathered form starting to disappear inside you as you greedily
			swallow, groping her arse as you eat her alive. Your throat and then
			belly bulging with the outline of her head as she becomes steadily a
			filling meal for her better. As you engulf her rear end you cannot
			help but savour that snatch of hers, the perpetually moist nethers
			once a threat now a flavoursome compliment to the meal you're now
			ingesting.</text>
		<choice destination="meal2" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal2">
		<text> Down down down, with each swallow you take her deeper. Her
			squirming flailing legs starting to disappear past your lips as your
			belly swells out under your hands. The harpy curling within you as
			with a final swallow you tuck her feet past your lips and gulp her
			down. Now all she can do is is squirm within your dome of a belly,
			pleasing you as you feel the harpy fill you so deliciously.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal3" text="digest her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal3">
		<text>
			You lean back, stroking your belly as it gets to work. She puts up a
			struggle for a time, but is no match. That churning dome writhing and
			struggling then slowly settling down, weakening as she's gurgled away
			inside you. her body turning soft and mushy as its rendered down to
			feed you. Soon your gut is round and smooth and shrinking as you've
			digested her utterly. With a final burble your middle flattens out,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				putting your clothes back on
			</conditional>
			you rise back to your feet to continue your day. Well sated by the
			harpy's body.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>