<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			The slender seraph looks down at your defeated body and then sets her
			blade aside "I must devour you" she states, as if it's not her idea.
			She squats down at your feet and lifts them up, not really tasteing
			over them or lingering to savour your flavours. She shoves your feet
			into her mouth without pre-amble, slurping them into your warm mouth
			and swallowing to start working your feet into her throat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="compelled or not she's eating you whole" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			Your predator seems to take no pleasure in devouring you, perhaps
			something to take as a slight against your flavour, instead gulping
			you up in a perfunctory fashion. Her swallows working her way up your
			legs, engulfing your calves, then thighs as your feet enter the
			tightness of her famished belly. You hear her gut let out a loud and
			ominous gurgle as its exposed to food for what's probably the first
			time in a great many years. Her hands help ease your ass up off the
			floor as her lips start to work over your hips.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Your legs curl up inside her as she swallows swiftly over your upper
			body. The seraph taking no time to savour as she lifts your upper
			body up and gobbles you down, settled onto her haunches with wings
			spread behind her as a balance of sorts as more of your weight
			settles into her stretching belly. That once unhealthily slender
			middle doming out and bulging with the contours of your feet and ass
			as you're packed away within her by the Seraph, her lips coming up
			around your chest now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="devoured completely" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			Your slender predators belly continues to engorge and grow in size as
			you're packed away inside her, her lips forcing your arms over your
			head as they work over your shoulders, all going dark as your head
			plunges down her throat. Your body steadily piling into her belly as
			she brings her hands down to pat consolingly on her gut and swallows
			your hands down, utterly consuming you. "I'm sorry" she says softly,
			a simple statement that does little for your current predicament as
			either way you're trapped in her belly now. The long unused organ
			providing a tight pressure all about you as you it gurgles more
			energeticly and enzymes start to ooze in over you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreStruggle" text="try to escape" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreSubmit" text="let your body feed the famished seraph" />
	</page>

	<check ID="oralvoreStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="oralvoreEscape">
		<text>
			Her apology does nothing to make you want to submit to digestion inside
			her and you take a moment to situate your feet properly against the
			underside of her belly and push yourself onwards and upwards. Shoving
			your hands into the entrance to her throat you feel her swallow
			against your efforts, but seemingly only as a token rather than with
			all due force and coveteousness with regards to her escaping meal.
			Your hands and arms cresting out of her throat and grabbing ahold of
			her to pull the rest of yourself free of her throat. The seraph
			slumping forwards as your ass slides free of her lips and you wriggle
			entirely clear, she looks at you conflicted, seemingly fighting an
			inner conflict between resting and rejoining the fight that might
			give you the chance you need to get away.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreDigest">
		<text>
			Her apology does nothing to make you want to submit to digestion inside
			her and you take a moment to situate your feet properly against the
			underside of her belly and push yourself onwards and upwards. Shoving
			your hands into the entrance to her throat you feel her swallow
			against your efforts, but seemingly only as a token rather than with
			all due force and coveteousness with regards to her escaping meal.
			Despite that though your feet slip on her insides and her stomach
			clenches with a hungry gurgle and you lose your leverage to force
			yourself back up against her throat. Even despite her not putting in
			a full effort you find yourself sliding back down to be sealed back
			up in her belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreDigestGO" text="digestion" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreDigestGO">
		<text>
			"It was a good effort.." says the seraph as you tire yourself out trying
			to escape her and she gives her gut a consoling pat. Though now
			digestion is setting in in earnest. Her stomach might be out of
			practice in digesting meals such as you, but it's proving remarkably
			adept as your defeated and defenceless form is worked over in the
			tight confines of her belly. And gradually, you're worked down into
			mush inside of her. The gut of the seraph turning soft and round and
			then shrinking away as you're utterly digested and absorbed, going to
			nourish her deprived and slender form and perhaps going some way to
			restoring her to her former glory. Though one suspects that she will
			not appreciate your sacrifice in this.
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<page ID="oralvoreSubmit">
		<text>
			The seraph's apology makes you smile a little. It's really not her fault
			she was made to devour you. Maybe were your circumstances different
			you could of been, well..something other than predator and meal..but
			you're content with that sort of relationship, besides...she really
			does look like she could do with a good meal. She seems puzzled by
			your lack of resistance, patting over the bulge as you get wriggle
			around to get comfortable but gently so as not to seem to struggle.
			Her digestive process becoming all the more vigorous around you as
			her gut gurgles and clenches on your body, starting to process and
			grind you down into nourishment and she remains unmoving as if held
			to it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreSubmitGO" text="get digested" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreSubmitGO">
		<text>
			You feel her stomach working over you with increasing vigour, its
			gurgles loud in your ears. But over it all you hear her asking a
			simple question "why?" it's all she manages and you barely hear her,
			but it seems she had to work herself up to be able to fight the
			compulsion to just sit there and digest so it must be important..alas
			you're in no fit state to answer, your squirms and utterances sound
			like gurgles to her as your body comes apart within her. The seraph
			watching her gut round out with her question unanswered as you give
			yourself bodily to her form, in but a short time more her belly would
			shrink down and flatten out, your nourishment going to fuel her body.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>