<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!--written by sideromelane -->
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The Synth appears stunned, as if its programming was not
			designed to handle its current prediciment!
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="Hungry for Metal">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="You wonder what sounding with her would feel like...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="Unbirth0"
			text="A life-size dildo in girl shape? Yes please...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>			
		<choice destination="end" text="Leave it alone." />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="25" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>		
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			Sounding always seemed like an interesting fetish. The smooth
			synthflesh and
			curvacious body-shape tells you this could be the best
			cock-feeding
			experience you've ever had. The synth twitches its head
			slightly,
			fingers wiggling as it begins to reboot, but your hardening
			cock has
			other plans. The softly glowing eyes focus on your erection,
			not
			giving away any emotion, but the faintest hint of desire is
			kindled
			there. You reach out and press down on her shoulders, forcing
			the
			as-yet unresting machine onto its knees with a soft whirr of
			gears,
			and your cock slaps her in the face. The synthflesh is cool to
			the
			touch, but smooth and soft, and her mouth opens, a pre-programmed
			trigger telling the jaw servos to unfold. Her lips wrap around your
			cockhead, and suck it in, a vibrating massage surrounding the
			sensitive meat, heat and oily lubricant combining to imbue the
			experience with the sensation of using possibly the best sex toy ever
			made. Your balls twitch, as within moments you are climaxing in her
			mouth. As your cock, still rock hard, slides from her mouth, cum
			dribbles from her lower lip, nourishment unessesary to the hardware.
			It still seems largely inactive, just those glowing eyes and mouth
			moving as it licks your cock clean for you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="Slip her in." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You wrap a hand around your cock, and the other goes to the back
			of the
			synthetic head. Gently, with another whirr of punmished gears,
			you
			guide the helpess machine face-first to your cock-slit. Your cock
			opens slowly, stretching greedily around the emotionless face, cum
			and precum oozing onto her features. The glowing eyes vanish inwards,
			but you can still feel a warmth, and leaning to one side, you can see
			a dim glow matching the colour of her eyes in the stretched bulge her
			head makes in the underside of your shaft. With a moan, you lean
			forward, pushing your cock over and around the unresisting synth,
			slurping more of her into your shaft each buck of your hips. A cool
			hand touches your inner thigh, still too weak to fight you but
			stroking up to your cock to feel around, working out where it's own
			head is. A weak push against you restults in her gently grasping your
			balls, her soon-to-be home. Your cock engulfs her shoulders, and
			begins oozing around her artifical breasts, swallowing her chest with
			ease, and trapping her arms. Both her hands writhe now, her feet
			starting to kick, but her efforts to stand up merely result in her
			pushing herself into your cock in a huge surge! Your balls expand
			rapidly, as her upper body is slurped into them in a rush, and you
			stagger slightly, you feel like that fleshy sack is ready to burst
			but there's still much more to go!
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="Lose your toy!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			You grab the Synths feet, and lift, straining your back and
			belly to
			hoist the machine up, and down again, slithering rapidly down
			your
			stretched-out cock and entirely into your balls. Her hips get
			stuck,
			for a few moments, but in passing you give her snatch a stroke,
			and
			plunge your fist into her, fucking her with your entire arm,
			ramming
			her down your hungry cock in short order. With a protest of
			unhappy
			whirrs and repeated threats that you would void her warranty,
			she is
			deposited entirely into your balls, her feet making a soft
			*slurp* as
			they vanish into your cock-slit, the flesh returning to
			it's normal
			erect proportions as her bulk is removed from within it's
			girth.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="Break your toy." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			The Synth puts up a fight in your balls, nearly her entire
			system
			rebooted and resisting your body. But these machines were, it
			seems,
			designed for pleasure, not war, and her fight is short-lived,
			your
			balls secreting fluids that first short out her circuits,
			resulting
			in a series of pleasant, tingling shocks that send you into
			paroxysms
			of pleasure, dropping you to your knees and squashing the
			squirming
			mass in your ballsack. Eventually though, even the synthetic
			materials of her artifial body succumb to the ultimatly superior
			organic form, and her body softens, and collapses, crumbling into a
			techno-organic slurry, and that final squishing, collapse drives you
			over the edge once more, and you shoot the robo-cum all over the
			floor, and the nearest wall in a torrent of released lust and
			pleasure.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="25" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end"
			text="Short loading times, needs more replayability." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			No mercy for the machine! You take her unresisting hands, and
			guide
			them to your lips. You slip them in, and swallow, working the
			cool,
			smooth synth flesh down your throat, followed by her head. She
			remains unresisting, her program most certainly frozen in shock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Interesting Flavour" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			The Synth vibrates slightly as you swallow her shoulders and
			chest,
			adding an extra thrill to the meal, but you don't pause,
			gulping more
			and more, working your lips over the soft firm mounds of
			her
			artifical breasts, your tongue soaking up the bland, plastic
			flavour.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Finish her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			The synth wriggles it's legs as they are lifted upwards, aiding
			your
			ingestion as your lips glide over her wide hips, tongue sampling
			the
			slick, oily entrance of her sex, and finally, those thighs are
			sliding down your greedy gullet. Your lips close over her feet, and
			she's gone, a whirring, pleasantly vibrating weight in your gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="Absorb the machine" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			The Synth is made of durable plastic and light steel, and takes
			an age
			to digest, but seems resigned to her fate, allowing you all the
			time
			you need without struggling unpleasantly. How your stomach
			handled
			the artifial flesh is a mystery but eventually, she's all
			gone.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="25" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Nice, but you could go another..." />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth0">
		<text>
			You decide to treat the machine the way she had planned to treat
			you -
			to a pussy bath! You grab her shoulders, and force her to kneel.
			Perhaps sensing your intentions, she complies, and begins vibrating
			softly, tongue already darting out to run across your pussy lips,
			with electrifying sensations. You moan, and grab its head, pressing
			it tigher against your spasming body, already nearly at climax just
			from the oral sensations! As your body bucks in helpless orgasm, the
			Synth pushes her face in, sliding her head smoothly up your pussy
			with a slurp of juices and whirr of electronics.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Unbirth1" text="Pleasant sensations" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth1">
		<text>
			Her shoulders present a small barrier, but the machine does
			something,
			and you gasp in a second orgasm as her shoulders and tits
			are
			squeezed smoothly up your snatch and her head pops into your womb.
			You sink to your knees, settling over your womb-meal with a long,
			contented sigh of delight, her hips sending your thoughts tumbling
			again as they pass into you. Your buttocks hit the floor with a
			smack, and you groan, rubbing your clit with one hand while grasping
			the cool plastic feet with your other, sliding them in. She vanishes,
			leaving just a wet patch on the floor and a huge bulge in your belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Unbirth2" text="Absorb her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth2">
		<text>
			The Synth curls tightly inside your womb, still vibrating and
			making
			small rocking motions that have you crashing flat to the floor
			in
			another wracking orgasm. Your belly clenches, your juices working
			overtime on it's inorganic occupant, and the synth is reduced to a
			gushing flood of oil and female cum within a matter of moments. Or
			was it hours? You're not sure, but it felt GREAT.
		</text>

		<effect type="feed" value="25" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="What time is it...?" />
	</page>

</Conversation>