<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>



	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA" operator="equals"
			value="1" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA_SAFETY"
			operator="equals" value="1" />
		<preference fetish="unbirthing" />
		<text>
			"Ma'am, thank you for choosing liquidation as your omnico experience." the
			synth says cheerfully as she positions herself over you, legs spread
			presenting her hairless gynoid pussy in all its drooling glory in
			front of your face. Her words make you glance up at her in frank
			disbelief but she smiles "here ma'am, let me help you with that. We
			are quite able to help with your insertion" she says as she reaches
			down to seize your head with one hand and your shoulder with the
			other, bringing your face into contact with her netherlips. The
			gynoid emitting a pleased mhmm as her folds part around your face,
			mashing you into the hot sticky embrace of her birth canal.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingB0" text="shoved inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthingB0">
		<text>
			"Our liquidation option is ideal for both stress relief and supplying
			beverage ingredients. Please consider our drink mixer guide sold
			separately." the synth advertises. Though you can barely hear her
			over the sound of squeelching and slurping fluids filling your ears.
			Especially as with your head up her snatch everything is a tad
			muffled. It's hardly comforting to know you'll be brewed into juices
			though as she forces you deeper in muffling her next bit of corporate
			commentary into unintelligability. The gynoid's snatch stretching
			around your shoulders and chest. Her moist insides snugly squeezing
			tightly as your head slides into her womb and bulges out the surface
			of her midsection.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingB1" text="fed inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthingB1">
		<text>
			The synth's clenching nethers drag more of you in as she stands in a
			powerfully dominative spread stance. Your weight lifting up off the
			floor steadily as she draws you up inside her gynoid womb. Her hands
			resting on her hips as her powerful sex squeezes and tugs over your
			belly and down to your own hips. Her middle distending and doming out
			steadily as you're squeezed into confinement in her womb despite any
			efforts of yours to resist "Omnico appreciates your compliance with
			your impending liquidation valued customer." she says as your feet
			dangle between her legs and slide up steadily towards her hungry
			snatch.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingB2" text="the rest of the way" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthingB2">
		<text>
			The gynoid adjusts her stance in a slow and gravid fashion as your feet
			near her snatch. The synth's feet settling closer together as her
			sexual juices stream down the inside of her thighs and down your feet
			as you disappear inside of her. Your feet soon slipping up between
			her legs. Your toes now vanished between her netherlips as she emits
			a pleased moan. Imprisoned within her womb as she strokes and presses
			her hands possessively against the domed out roundness of her middle
			"you feel good inside me valued customer, please prepare yourself for
			liquidation. We hope you appreciate the highly tailored experience
			you are about to undergo."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingBStruggle"
			text="no, no i'm not going to appreciate it, i'm out of here" />
		<choice destination="unbirthingBSubmit" text="that sounds...fun" />
	</page>


	<check ID="unbirthingBStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="unbirthingBEscape" />
		<outcome destination="unbirthingBTrapped" />
	</check>

	<page ID="unbirthingBEscape">
		<text>
			You decide that being turned into the ingredient for a debauched
			beverage doesn't sound like a good idea. Even if it'd feel amazing.
			Not wanting to waste your blandishments on an uncaring gynoid you
			start shoving and pushing to try and force your way out "valued
			customer, the liquidation is not yet underway. I'll have a chance to
			let you out as a gush between my thighs later just be patient." the
			synth teases with a giggle as she presses her thighs together to try
			keeping you inside. But apparently to no avail as you work against
			her powerful nether muscles and force your hands out, shoving at her
			inner thighs and toppling her over. The impact jolting her enough
			that you manage to work your way out while she's 'stunned'. Though it
			won't be long before she's after you again.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthingBTrapped">
		<text>
			You decide that being turned into the ingredient for a debauched
			beverage doesn't sound like a good idea. Even if it'd feel amazing.
			Not wanting to waste your blandishments on an uncaring gynoid you
			start shoving and pushing to try and force your way out "valued
			customer, the liquidation is not yet underway. I'll have a chance to
			let you out as a gush between my thighs later just be patient." the
			synth teases with a giggle as she presses her thighs together to try
			keeping you inside. You shove your hands down through her sexual
			channel, fingers sliding into the open air only for her sex to clench
			and ripple and suck your back inside "Valued customer, be patient.."
			she chides you with a giggle as her womb starts to clench and ooze
			around you. Her soft flesh marinating you in sensual fluids that make
			you shudder in delight, distracting you further and further from your
			efforts to escape. Your strength and resolve waning as you give
			yourself over to the pleasure of being worked over.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingBTrappedGO" text="too good..can't resist" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="unbirthingBTrappedGO">
		<text>
			Her soft womb walls knead over you, rthythmically contracting as you
			writhe in helpless bliss. Your hands busy in self gratification
			rather than escape now as the pleasurable fluids overwhelm you and
			work you down. The synth remarks "we are pleased you are enjoying
			your liquidation valued customer, it will not be longer until you are
			reduced to my fluids." but you barely hear or register her words as
			you orgasm, then orgasm again..then..gush. The Synth's hand stroking
			over her nethers as she emits a moan and splatters you out in a
			gushing series of bursts of sticky fluids. When she's done reducing
			you to an orgasm she steps away, unmindful of the fluids saturating
			the inside of her legs and snatch as she returns to her activities.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="unbirthingBSubmit">
		<text>
			You decide to comply and settle in to enjoy this liquidation. You can
			hear the synth's finger messily shlick shlicking into her sex as she
			emits a murr "we hope you enjoy your conversion valued customer." the
			synth commends at your submission. Her womb kneading over you soaking
			you in blissful juices, making it harder and harder to focus on
			anything outside your little world of pleasure and lust. Your moans
			emanating from within her as you attend to your depraved kneads and,
			gradually, begin to soften..
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthingBSubmitGO" text="oh yes" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="unbirthingBSubmitGO">
		<text>
			The gynoid seems to pace herself, stimulating her sex as your pleasure
			builds as you soften into a blissful blushing mass within her. Your
			pleasure finally cresting into a series of rolling orgasms. Your body
			shuddering, spasming as you literally slosh yourself away into a mass
			of femmecum inside her. The Gynoid smiling and moaning as she strokes
			her nethers more vigorously upon feeling your liquidation. Her own
			climax sending you gushing out to splatter on the ground, a sticky
			mass of fragrant girljuice forming a puddle underneath her as she
			pleasantly discharges you. All that remains of you staining her legs
			and the ground beneath. You can say one thing for sure though, it
			really did feel amazing.

		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA" operator="equals"
			value="1" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA_SAFETY"
			operator="equals" value="0" />
		<preference fetish="unbirthing" />
		<text>
			"Prepare for containment valued customer." the synth commands as she reaches
			down to grasp your head firmly with both hands and guides it willing
			or not towards her netherlips. Those emulated sex lips realistic,
			moist and as it happens fully functional as the gynoid forces you
			facefirst into her snatch. Lewd squeelches audible as her juices soak
			your head and she wedges you in down to your neck in one movement "As
			you can tell Omnico has put a lot of work into emulating the
			experience of being taken and forced into a womb." the synth comments
			and continues handling you to feed in your shoulders, her insides are
			hot and welcoming. And she's right, that womb of hers is remarkably
			soft and accomodating, definitely realistic.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="a realistic womb domination experience" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			The synth continues cramming you inside. Her hands methodically moving
			down your flanks and each time they grasp you they haul you deeper
			inside, cramming your upper body up between her legs. Her womb
			stretching easily to accomodate you, her midriff distending as you're
			curled and crammed into that fleshy prison. Once she reaches your
			thighs though she straightens up, and draws you inside using nothing
			more than her clenching and potent pussy wrapped around your legs
			"Submit to my womb valued customer, your satisfaction is our greatest
			concern."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1"
			text="satisfied or not this customer is getting enwombed" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			You're not sure how being trapped in a womb is supposed to make you a
			satisfied customer but you doubt the Synth is paying much attention
			to your protests as she reaches one hand down to fondle her snatch
			just above where it stretches around your disappearing legs. Your
			feet kicking about as they get closer and closer to her domed out
			middle. Most of you is already confined in the snuggley warm prison
			of her womb. And soon all of you is imprisoned within the synth's
			body as your feet are slurped between her netherlips "Valued
			customer, please take the time to experience thoroughly the synthoid
			womb product before providing feedback." the synth continues, her
			voice as ever normal and untroubled even after shoving you bodily
			into her drooling snatch.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthStruggle"
			text="take time nothing, i'm getting out of here" />
		<choice destination="unbirthSubmit"
			text="well she has a point, it is rather comfortable" />
	</page>

	<check ID="unbirthStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="struggleUBescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggleUBtrapped0" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleUBescape">
		<text>
			Yeah no your customer experience has not been satisfactory and you push
			off against her insides to try and force your way back out of this
			deranged gynoid. The synth's womb proving soft, yielding and slick
			which makes your efforts a little tricky. But you're not to be
			deterred by a comfy prison and some marketspeak and persist, tipping
			yourself upside down in order to push off against the inside of the
			womb and thrust yourself back out through her nethers into the open
			air "error, customer is attempting escape before trial period is
			concluded." she utters robotically as she clenches to try and force
			you back inside, but to no avail as you're well beyond the point of
			being easily subdued. Instead of going back inside you wriggle the
			rest of the way out leaving the synth looking confused in that blank
			eyed mechanized way of any machine with no quick answer to what just
			happened. Still you should probably get clear before she resets and
			shoves you back inside, you might not be so lucky next time.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleUBtrapped0">
		<text>
			You want out of here so you can write a scathing yelp review or
			something and so you shove at the insides of the womb in search of
			the way out, it's the way you came in so it shouldn't be too hard to
			find. You press your fingers against the entrance of her synthoid
			birth canal and shove off against the inside of the womb. Only to
			find yourself slipping, tumbling unruly inside her. You don't give up
			though and continue your efforts to escape despite the difficulty.
			The synth resting a hand against the dome of her middle as you tire
			yourself out inside of her "error, customer actions do not
			complete...error" she hesitates a moment with a stutter of resetting
			relays then smiles "thankyou for selecting extended stay as your
			chosen option, we hope you have a pleasant entrapment." she
			announces, and you groan. Great you're tired and now set for a long
			stay as you somehow triggered a different protocol...
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleUBtrapped1" text="damnit, trapped" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleUBtrapped1">
		<text>
			The synth walks around unmindful of the burden she's carrying. You're
			forced to endure this prolonged stay as her prisoner, tightly
			smuggled away in her distended middle as the gynoid seems to go
			around doing nothing in particular. She'll walk around purely to walk
			around and then pat and rub now and then against where you're
			confined, but mostly she seems to be reinforcing your powerlessness
			to act by doing things. Eventually after a seemingly endless period
			of torpor inside her you feel her come to a halt and announce "we
			hope you have enjoyed this prolonged stay within the womb of an
			Omnico synthetic predator gynoid version 42." she rattles off and
			settles down into a seated position, spreading her thighs as she
			clenches down and sets about rebirthing you into the world. slick
			gynoid juices coating your form as you emerge inch by inch from
			between her legs until with a final schlorp your feet pop free and
			you lie there free once more "please fill out a customer feedback
			questionaire at the information office." she says placing a towel
			next to you afore stepping away seemingly done with you.
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="400" suppress="true" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthSubmit">
		<text>
			The synth smiles "We hope you enjoy this enwombing experience." the
			gynoid reiterates as she sets about wandering around, demonstrating
			her ability to handle the weight of your body inside her womb. Your
			form is nicely cradled by the fleshy confines of her soft womb as she
			goes about her business and dotes upon her bulge now and then with
			pats and rubs. When the time comes though your stay comes to an end
			as she settles down into a seated position and starts to ease you out
			of herself. slick gynoid juices coating your form as you emerge inch
			by inch from between her legs until with a final schlorp your feet
			pop free and you lie there free once more "please fill out a customer
			feedback questionaire at the information office." she says placing a
			towel next to you afore stepping away seemingly done with you.
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" suppress="true" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA" operator="equals"
			value="0" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA_SAFETY"
			operator="equals" value="1" />
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			"Ma'am you look delicious, please hold still and allow me to devour you"
			she commands as she comes to a halt looming over you. The synth's
			body emitting soft whirs as she leans down to grasp beneath your arms
			and lift you up with uncanny strength "Omnico believes that
			complimentary voracious teasing amplifies the arousal of a prey's
			impending digestion" she says offhandedly before her jaws stretch
			open. The air that wafts out is warm and moist, the experience
			already seems unexpectedly authentic as hot wet saliva coated mouth
			flesh stretches to encompass your head and her tongue plies over your
			face. The Synth's hit or miss vorish teasing unable to continue as
			she takes her first swallow and her throat bulges around the shape of
			your head.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreB0"
			text="Such impersonal and businesslike consumption" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreB0">
		<text>
			The synth letting out emulated moans around her mouthful of your body
			and slides her hand down to your ass as she begins feeding you down
			her throat.
			Her hands on your ass steadily feed you up and in, supporting your rump
			and pushing you past those flexing jaws and into that rippling
			throat. The synth continuing to emit moaning noises as your head
			slides deeper and deeper into her body, working down into her
			convincingly voracious and accomodating gut. The pale blue skin of
			her middle distending out around your form as you're forcefully
			curled in her gut by more of your body piling in atop you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreB1" text="packed away" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreB1">
		<text>
			The synth gropes your thighs afore they slip between her legs, adding a
			bit more to the possessive air your robotic predator has for you. The
			synth gulping heavily around your ass and tipping her head back to
			swallow more and more of you, gulping, gulping and gulping until with
			a final clack she shuts her jaws past your toes. The Synth mhmming
			and licking her lips smacking them together a little as she moves her
			hands down to rest upon the bulge of your form as you're squeezed
			snugly within her "We hope you enjoy being digested alive valued
			prospective customer and that you or your friend, acquaintance,
			relation or life partner will choose to purchase an Omnico product in
			the near future."
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreBStruggle" text="like hell i'm gonna" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreBSubmit"
			text="well i may as well settle in to see if the experience is properly authentic" />
	</page>

	<check ID="oralvoreBStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreBEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreBTrapped" />
	</check>

	<page ID="oralvoreBEscape">
		<text>
			You're not sold on this marketing gimmick and decide to not stick around as
			your skin becomes lathered in synthetic enzymes "Please remain calm
			valued customer, attempts to escape may disrupt the carefully
			tailored experience." the synth protests as you start shoving and
			jostling about in an attempt to force your way back up out the way
			you came. The synth placing both hands firmly atop its gut to try and
			keep you from getting any further up "please remain where you are,
			digestion is not yet compl-GL"her voice fades into incoherence as you
			shove your hands up her throat and crank her jaws wide open. The
			synth apparently not having a way of dealing with this problem as she
			shudders in robotic indecisiveness and you shove off the inside of
			her belly to force yourself back up and out. The synth overbalancing
			and toppling over once your ass is free, the impact discomforting but
			less so than the idea of being digested by an omnico pred doll. With
			a little more effort you pull your legs free.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreBTrapped">
		<text>
			You're not sold on this marketing gimmick and decide to not stick around as
			your skin becomes lathered in synthetic enzymes "Please remain calm
			valued customer, attempts to escape may disrupt the carefully
			tailored experience." the synth protests as you start shoving and
			jostling about in an attempt to force your way back up out the way
			you came. The synth placing both hands firmly atop its gut to try and
			keep you from getting any further up "please remain where you are,
			digestion is not yet.. complete" she says pausing to swallow you back
			down as you try to force your way back up her throat. The synth
			continuing to thwart your efforts until you tire out again "Omnico
			has invested in the finest prey suppression routines to induce a
			feeling of being helpless meat trapped in the body of a predator in
			prey facing imminent digestion." the synth explains as you realize
			there's really no getting out of her, the gurgling gut of the gynoid
			is gonna melt you down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreBTrappedGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreBTrappedGO">
		<text>
			Trapped by the gynoid you hear her emit pleased mhmms as she rubs over belly
			and you start melting away in earnest. The experience ever so
			distressingly authentic as you're helplessly digested and softened
			down into a goopy compact lump in her belly. Your fluidic form
			somehow stored about the gynoids body for later use, her breasts, ass
			and thighs inflating with reservoirs of glop as her belly flattens
			out. Were you still around to contemplate it you might consider the
			possibility that Omnico is a profoundly messed up company.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="oralvoreBSubmit">
		<text>
			You decide to settle in and see how it compares to the digestion of
			flesh and blood predators. The synth rubbing hands over its gut as it
			starts to gurgle around your unresisting form "At Omnico we strive
			for customer satisfaction." she states as a nonsequiter of sorts as
			you soften in her middle, yielding more and more under her kneading
			hands as the gynoid digests you away steadily.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreBSubmitGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreBSubmitGO">
		<text>
			Resting cosy and increasingly goopily inside her gut you find the transition
			from girl to glorp rather peaceful and pleasant. But it happens none
			the less, your form now a compact mass in her belly that shrinks and
			fades away slowly as her curves plump out. The synth adding more
			softness to her tits and ass as your mass is redistributed, Omnico
			had clearly put a lot of thought and development time into making the
			result of your digestion aesthetically pleasing. Shame you're not
			around to look really.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA" operator="equals"
			value="0" />
		<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="OMNICO_IIA_SAFETY"
			operator="equals" value="0" />
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>"now ma'am, please relax and enjoy your experience." the synth
			remarks as she jerks to a halt looming over you and smiles. She
			bends
			forwards and with unyielding hands grasps about your body and
			hauls
			you upwards. "Omnico has worked hard to make this as authentic
			and
			pleasant as possible." she explains afore her jaws ratchet open
			wide.
			Moist air wafting out as the synthetic woman shows off her gape
			afore
			setting about devouring you, engulfing your head and cramming
			it
			inside. The warm fluids oozing around you as that throat stretches
			and undulates, smoothly swelling around your head and gripping it to
			draw you inside. They really did put a lot of effort into making it
			feel like you really are being eaten alive by someone.</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="a real enough pred" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The synth holds you aloft as she devours you, her slender form
			holding
			surprising strength. Your legs squirm or flail around
			uselessly,
			hanging in the air as she chugs you down. Her tongue
			carefully
			tasting over you thoroughly, leaving you coated in
			artificial saliva
			as you slide on down. Your head plunging down past
			her esophagus, her
			gut steamy hot and wet and easily stretching as
			you're fed in. You
			hear her moan around your middle and then waistline
			as she engulfs
			more of you. Her hands stroking possessively over her
			gut as it
			swells out. Your form starting to curl inside the prison of
			her belly
			as it pushes out with your contours.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			The synth tips her head back, your legs swaying back and forth
			over her
			head as she chugs and rthythmically works you down the rest
			of the
			way. Her jaws flexing wide and narrow around your thighs, then
			calves, then finally flexing hard around your ankles as she swallows
			a final time. The synth gobbling you down and sealing her jaws up
			past your feet with a snap, mhmming appreciatively and reaching down
			to rub over her belly and utters satisfied lipsmacks "You were
			delicious customer." she says, her gut sagging down with your weight
			now you're curled up within the tightness of her belly, trapped
			inside the synth's containing gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleOV" text="try to get out of here" />
		<choice destination="submitOV" text="relax, it's cosy" />
	</page>

	<check ID="struggleOV">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="struggleOVescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggleOVtrapped0" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleOVescape">
		<text>
			You're not about to stay around being carried around as a belly
			pet by a
			walking talking sex doll. And you set about trying to shove
			your way
			back upwards, the synth uttering a staticky hork and flailing
			her
			arms afore trying to push down on the top of her belly with both
			hands firmly. The synth protesting your lack of acquiescence "please
			calm down ma'am, trying to get out prematurely will only harm your
			customer experience." she says, not deterred however you shove your
			way up, finally finding the entrance to her throat and worming your
			hands up and out. The synth stumbling as her jaws are forced apart
			and your fingers grasp at the flanks of her lips. With the grip you
			can easily pull your way out despite her protests, the gynoid
			stumbling and flailing and falling on her but as you work your upper
			body past her jaws, then flop out onto the ground and wriggle free.
			It's undignified, but you've gotten free.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleOVtrapped0">
		<text>
			You're not about to stay around being carried around as a belly
			pet by a
			walking talking sex doll. And you set about trying to shove
			your way
			back upwards, the synth uttering a staticky hork and flailing
			her
			arms afore trying to push down on the top of her belly with both
			hands firmly. The synth protesting your lack of acquiescence "please
			calm down ma'am, trying to get out prematurely will only harm your
			customer experience." and shoves down, you lose track of her the
			entrance of her belly as she sets about pushing and kneading at you
			with her hands rather firmly "customers who are unruly need time
			out." she says as you start to tire out and realize that she has you
			beat. In your weakened state you're unable to object as she sets
			about toting you around. the wandering synth jostling and swaying you
			about in her gut as she goes about the tunnels. It would seem you
			might be here for a while.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleOVtrapped1" text="in for the long haul" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleOVtrapped1">
		<text>
			After a timeless period of jostling and swaying without
			references for how
			long has passed you feel the gynoid come to a halt
			"we hope you have
			enjoyed your extended stay inside this demonstration
			model and will
			get in contact with a sales representative to make a
			purchase." she
			intones and then doubles over, gut flexing then
			pressing in around
			you. The synth starting to hork you up, forcing you
			up her throat and
			taking ahold of you as you start to emerge into the
			light, pulling
			you free and supporting you until she can set you down
			wetly and
			gently on the floor in front of her. She smiles "please take
			the time
			to fill out a customer satisfaction survey." she says and
			then looks
			around and adds "we seem to be out of towels at the moment,
			Omnico
			apologizes for the inconvenience."
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="400" suppress="true" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="submitOV">
		<text>
			"Enjoy yourself customer, we hope you find your experience to
			your liking."
			says the synth as you decide its fairly warm and
			comfortable inside
			her and to just let yourself be a burden on this
			synth for a bit. You
			feel the gynoid rub her belly now and then as she
			wanders around,
			swaying you gently from side to side inside as she
			walks.
			Occasionally she'd pause to reach down and snug her massively
			distended gut with both hands, cradling the bulges of your form
			inside her. When the time comes she remarks "we hope you have enjoyed
			your extended stay inside this demonstration model and will get in
			contact with a sales representative to make a purchase." and starts
			horking you up. Her insides efficiently pressing around you and
			pushing you up and out of her body. Emerging headfirst from her mouth
			you find her hands waiting for you, supporting you until she can
			grasp under your arms and help ease you out of her throat entirely.
			The synth setting you down on the floor with a bright smile "please
			take the time to fill out a customer satisfaction survey." she says
			and then looks around and adds "we seem to be out of towels at the
			moment, Omnico apologizes for the inconvenience."
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" suppress="true"/>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>


</Conversation>