<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>"now ma'am, please relax and enjoy your experience." the synth
			remarks as she stutters to a halt looming over you and smiles. She
			bends forwards and with unyielding hands grasps about your body and
			hauls you upwards. "Omnico has worked hard to make this as authentic
			and pleasant as possible." she explains afore her jaws ratchet open
			wide. Moist air wafting out as the synthetic woman shows off her gape
			afore setting about devouring you, engulfing your head and cramming
			it inside. The warm fluids oozing around you as that throat stretches
			and undulates, smoothly swelling around your head and gripping it to
			draw you inside. They really did put a lot of effort into making it
			feel like you really are being eaten alive by someone.</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="a real enough pred" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The synth holds you aloft as she devours you, her slender form holding
			surprising strength. Your legs squirm or flail around uselessly,
			hanging in the air as she chugs you down. Her tongue carefully
			tasting over you thoroughly, leaving you coated in artificial saliva
			as you slide on down. Your head plunging down past her esophagus, her
			gut steamy hot and wet and easily stretching as you're fed in. You
			hear her moan around your middle and then waistline as she engulfs
			more of you. Her hands stroking possessively over her gut as it
			swells out. Your form starting to curl inside the prison of her belly
			as it pushes out with your contours.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			The synth tips her head back, your legs swaying back and forth over her
			head as she chugs and rthythmically works you down the rest of the
			way. Her jaws flexing wide and narrow around your thighs, then
			calves, then finally flexing hard around your ankles as she swallows
			a final time. The synth gobbling you down and sealing her jaws up
			past your feet with a snap, mhmming appreciatively and reaching down
			to rub over her belly and utters satisfied lipsmacks "You were
			delicious customer." she says, her gut sagging down with your weight
			now you're curled up within the tightness of her belly, trapped
			inside the synth's containing gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="try to get out of here" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="relax, it's cosy" />
	</page>

	<check ID="struggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggletrapped0" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			You're not about to stay around being carried around as a belly pet by a
			walking talking sex doll. And you set about trying to shove your way
			back upwards, the synth uttering a staticky hork and flailing her
			arms afore trying to push down on the top of her belly with both
			hands firmly. The synth protesting your lack of acquiescence "please
			calm down ma'am, trying to get out prematurely will only harm your
			customer experience." she says, not deterred however you shove your
			way up, finally finding the entrance to her throat and worming your
			hands up and out. The synth stumbling as her jaws are forced apart
			and your fingers grasp at the flanks of her lips. With the grip you
			can easily pull your way out despite her protests, the gynoid
			stumbling and flailing and falling on her but as you work your upper
			body past her jaws, then flop out onto the ground and wriggle free.
			It's undignified, but you've gotten free.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggletrapped0">
		<text>
			You're not about to stay around being carried around as a belly pet by a
			walking talking sex doll. And you set about trying to shove your way
			back upwards, the synth uttering a staticky hork and flailing her
			arms afore trying to push down on the top of her belly with both
			hands firmly. The synth protesting your lack of acquiescence "please
			calm down ma'am, trying to get out prematurely will only harm your
			customer experience." and shoves down, you lose track of her the
			entrance of her belly as she sets about pushing and kneading at you
			with her hands rather firmly "customers who are unruly need time
			out." she says as you start to tire out and realize that she has you
			beat. In your weakened state you're unable to object as she sets
			about toting you around. the wandering synth jostling and swaying you
			about in her gut as she goes about the tunnels. It would seem you
			might be here for a while.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggletrapped1" text="in for the long haul" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggletrapped1">
		<text>
			After a timeless period of jostling and swaying without references for how
			long has passed you feel the gynoid come to a halt "we hope you have
			enjoyed your extended stay inside this demonstration model and will
			get in contact with a sales representative to make a purchase." she
			intones and then doubles over, gut flexing then pressing in around
			you. The synth starting to hork you up, forcing you up her throat and
			taking ahold of you as you start to emerge into the light, pulling
			you free and supporting you until she can set you down wetly and
			gently on the floor in front of her. She smiles "please take the time
			to fill out a customer satisfaction survey." she says and then looks
			around and adds "we seem to be out of towels at the moment, Omnico
			apologizes for the inconvenience."
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="400" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			"Enjoy yourself customer, we hope you find your experience to your liking."
			says the synth as you decide its fairly warm and comfortable inside
			her and to just let yourself be a burden on this synth for a bit. You
			feel the gynoid rub her belly now and then as she wanders around,
			swaying you gently from side to side inside as she walks.
			Occasionally she'd pause to reach down and snug her massively
			distended gut with both hands, cradling the bulges of your form
			inside her. When the time comes she remarks "we hope you have enjoyed
			your extended stay inside this demonstration model and will get in
			contact with a sales representative to make a purchase." and starts
			horking you up. Her insides efficiently pressing around you and
			pushing you up and out of her body. Emerging headfirst from her mouth
			you find her hands waiting for you, supporting you until she can
			grasp under your arms and help ease you out of her throat entirely.
			The synth setting you down on the floor with a bright smile "please
			take the time to fill out a customer satisfaction survey." she says
			and then looks around and adds "we seem to be out of towels at the
			moment, Omnico apologizes for the inconvenience."
		</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="100" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>


</Conversation>