<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>

<text>
Faced with a reeling saurian warrior who is trying to keep standing the elf wastes no time in lunging at her, discarding her blade momentarily in order to take care of the defeated lizard girl in a more vorish way. The Saurian stumbling back and clutching at her arms but unable to keep her from pulling her close, and the lizard's hiss of dismay is swiftly muffled as the elf wraps her lips around her face and takes her first powerful swallow.
</text>
<text>
The elf warrior starts to swallow her defeated foe down whole and alive. The lizard kicking and struggling but her partially scaled and all tastey body seems to not be giving the elf too much trouble. Self satisfied mhmms audible from the elf as she guzzles the lizard down inch by inch with rippling swallows. Her emerald skinned belly starting to stretch and bulge out as she works more and more lizard down her throat.
</text>
<text>
You see the feasting predatory green elf feeling up her prey possessively as she upends her, her gut swelling out as she swallows down more and more of those kicking legs and that smooth flailing tail. The lizard's protests are muffled and her struggles equally futile as she's not as a worthy foe but as a satisfying foe.
</text>
<text>
Each chugging gulp from the elf results in more of her saurian meal disappearing, her gut stretching and bulging out with the contours of the lizardgirl she's devouring. Her hands sliding down onto that distending, filling and growing belly of hers. 
</text>
<text>
The lizard's feet twitch in protest before being swallowed and soon only a frantically wriggling orange scaled tailtip is left protruding from hungry green lips before being schlurped down. You can hear muffled complaints from the curling bulge as the lizard is entirely packed away in the elf's gut. That greenskinned predator letting out a self satisfied burp followed by a mhmm and grin, giving her gut a smack as if to drive home her place to the lizard within.
</text>

</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
The elf's gut jostles around with the struggles of the lizardgirl filling her belly. The squirms seemingly only serving to bounce that belly momentarily.
</text>
<text>
The elf's belly gurgles loudly around the lizardgirl, digesting her alive as she squirms around and lets out muffled sounds of protest that the glorps serve nicely to drown out.
</text>
<text>
You see the lizardgirl push out her hands against the stomach walls, before being squeezed back down by the elf's clenching stomach muscles.
</text>
<text>
The elf's belly is starting to glorp louder and squirm around less now. The digestive process taking its toll upon the saurian warrior within.
</text>
<text>
The elf's belly is turning soft and round now, barely moving. The saurian warrior must be mostly liquidated by her at this point.
</text>
<text>
The elf's gut is compact and round, soft glorps audible as the thick fluid remnants of her prey are processed and absorbed.
</text>
<text>
The elf middle is shrinking back down now, not a trace of saurian left it seems but for the satisfied expression on her face and perhaps the extra layer of padding starting to accumulate on her ass.
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>