<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>
<text>
As the Pirate gets up, they’re met with the sultry and curvy Eve, her eyes looking hungrily at them and her balls growling for a meal. She saunters up to them, and presses her cock against their chest, grinding up and down their body, her seductive and lewd actions making them hesitate running. “Feel it throb and drip for you, honey~? Mm, it loves you~” She moans as her rod drools precum between them, and she hugs them close, her cock being massaged by their bodies as she leans forward to kiss her prey. “Mwah~ You’re a cute little snack, why don’t you….hop in?” She suggests, pointing her cock under their chin before deciding she’ll make their choice for them, and shove them headfirst into her gaping tip.
</text>
<text>
She groans and sighs as criminal beat against her cock, slowly submerging in her tight Fuck tube, sliding down her length. “Aww, don’t be mad cutie, you’re going to make this beautiful cock feel so good, you should feel honored.” She pats their shoulders as her cock presses forward, swallowing more and more of the raider, who’s struggles only send her deeper into Eve’s starving  serpent. The herm leisurely rubs her meat as lewd gulps and gurgles sound from her cockmeal, reduced to an unwilling snack to her sex. She giggles as her cock stands, firm and tall as legs crammed into pants two sizes too small slide down, sending them to their sweltering fate in her sack. The marauder is met with salty cum covering them and sinking against their flesh as they’re stewed into copious amounts of nut sludge.
</text>

</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
Eve kneads her ballsack, the herm stag playing with her swollen assets as her sex happily and hungrily churns her prey. Inside, sloshing spunk consumes the unfortunate pirate’s world as all they can see, smell and taste, is Eve’s overpowering musky cum converting them into a moment of pleasure for the hung herm. Eve huffs, her climax close as she graces her brewing load with one last word. “Mmm, don’t worry my delicious darling, you’ll become pure pleasure, my salty seed, there’s nothing more sexy than what you’ll be, other than myself, my orgasm~!” She closes her eyes as she can feel her nuts churn up a creamy mess, and she cries out as thick ropes of cum start draining her sack, relieving her cock of it’s meal. She drools as every drop is sent back out the fleshy tube it entered. “You know you look so much more beautiful as my nut sludge than the pathetic form you had before. Really you should thank me for this makeover, at least this way you made a girl cum once.”
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>