<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>
<text>
Eve stands before her defeated sister and licks her lips. One stroking her cock to attention, “Hmm I won fair and square, we both know what happens now.“ Eve informs the little one in a soothing yet seductive tone as she presses her soft dick’s head against Fawn’s soft face letting a glob of pre leak onto tiny nose. The demi rubs the crown of her dick all over the nubile face till her shaft grows to half mast, leaving the little doe in a daze of lust. “Go on, stick your feet on it for me sweetie, and let’s get started~.” Eve orders with a giggle. The impressionable Fawn listens to her “Big” sister’s order and lays down on her back, proceeding to wrap their feet around the head of the Stag’s shaft. The Fawn begins to rub the pulsating tip with her tiny feet, causing the meat to bulge and swell.
</text>
<text>
Pre begins to leak from Eve’s heft, soaking the little one’s feet in slick elixir. The little appendages continue to work over the Herm’s comparatively massive tip, coating all three in a clear shine. “Yes…! Such a good little sister. Now stick both your hot little gams in me, and make this nice and easy for the both of us~.” The Fawns face show’s only the hint of sadness. “Don’t you love this feeling of my cock drinking you in? I bet you’re excited to feel it across your whole body~.” The stag taunts as her girth greedily slurps at the girl pulling her in mercilessly. The little doe’s thighs and hips starting to stretch the bigger girls cock. Eve basks in every moment. She was getting what she wanted delightful voracious arrangement, and she knew the feeling was not mutual. Eve reached down and pulled her member up, hugging it to her torso letting gravity and the squirms of her sister help her fill her balls. “Give your big sis your first kiss~.” She demands before forcing her her lips to Fawn’s as she slides down further and further. Eve’s face was within her own member by the time she broke it off, a string of saliva connecting the herm with the doomed girl trapped inside her cruel member, “Goodbye sweetie~.” Eve said with a wink, and a smirk before the gaping maw of her cock closed completely.
</text>

</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
The fawns arms were pinned to her sides as she slid down that hot musky cum-tube, the last thing to pop into the hungry waiting sack was her head. Eve’s balls were unusually taught the visage of the little fawn was perfectly clear through the Stag’s skin. Like a thin layer of latex gripping at every inch of the small girl. She stayed swaying and wiggling between Eve’s legs for a full day before the cruel herm got to work on her… the sounds of the churns and gurgles audible from a distance, as too were the squeals from within her sack… “I can never decide what my favorite part is…” Eve ponders to her slef, “Is it the part where the loose? Is it when they break and realize it’s over? Is it the part when I finish? Or is it the part when they gurgle?” She divulged in a low ominous tone, as she begins to dote on her cock cock, Moaning in pleasure before the release. As she splattered the little Fawn all over the floor, it occurred to Eve that size of the load generated by the little one was not to her appetite. She could make a bigger one on her own. The many individuals who had vanished in her balls had given her a bit of a distended preference. Maybe next time she’d need several imoutos.
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>