<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>
<text>
Eve stares down the defeated Talharan with a smirk, “My my… lost the will to fight… and what’s that, you want to be stuffed down my cock~?” Eve almost chuckles comically putting a hand to her ear. To her surprise the space trader shuffles closer to the tree trunk swinging between her legs. Eve licks her lips, “Well get it hard, I’m waiting~.” Eve proposes. Unsure of how far the gypsy was really willing to go. Then suddenly to her shock and delight, girl grabs and strokes her member, Raising her helmet up so she can get at that cock properly. Licking it, lavishing it with her mouth, worshiping it, exulting all manner of devour unto Eve’s lower member. Eve’s shaft plumps with a vigor, “Oh my, you are quiet the slut… Well then, feed yourself to my hungry “little” girl… you know you are desperate to~.” The demi smirks and waggles her cock a bit before reaching full length for the foolish whore to force herself down, “Well if you are SO ready for it why don’t you get started~?”
</text>
<text>
Driven by Eve’s the taunting voice the Trader, dives into her cock, hands going in first stretching her meat out before her elbows slip past. Eve’s breath turned ragged, “S-slow down~ This is for me not you.” Eve’s teases which seem to only make the girl go in fervor, shoving her head down and taking that plunge even faster, sending shivers up Eve’s spine. Eve was almost struggling to keep the frantic girl out of her cock. The trip to her balls couldn’t be this fast, Eve needed more build up to enjoy herself. The merchant thrust her body into Eve’s throbbing girth with such tremendous force she knocked the stag flat on her ample ass. “Such an eager cock snack~! I’m going to have to make this harder on you.” Eve stammers, trying to sound confident as she holds what little of the Talharan that was yet in her cock at bay. Clamping down her with all her strength on her meaty shaft to halt the advances of the crazed girl. Only thighs and legs protruded from the tip of Eve’s Masculinity. Still this proved little effect as the space dealer strained against her. Driving forward with unsure footing.
</text>

</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
The spark of an idea forms in the both willing and unwilling pred’s mind. In a split second Eve rolls backward, using the VERY willing prey’s momentum against her, hoisting the pushy prey up in the air. “There. Now we do this at my pace…” Eve slaps her engorged phallus right where the helmet bulge resides with a sour look on her face. It takes her a while to start to work the rest of the eager prey down into here nuts. She feels her balls clench and squeeze on the stupid obnoxious bitch. Despite Eve’s annoyance, the Talharan was enjoying this to the fullest extent, waiting to be nothing but nut butter inside of Eve’s balls. After several short moments, she stopped moving, and rapidly smoothed out into a uniform shape. Eve tries holding back her orgasm, but she seemed just as eager to get out as she did in, and in in an underwhelming show she gushed onto the floor… Eve pouted, “Well that wasn’t worth it. Won’t be feeding any more of them to my delicate member…” Eve’s resolve lasted for four whole seconds before she proclaimed, “The next of these stupid space Gypsies better make a good load.”
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>