<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>

<text>
The warden reels after that last blow and topples back, feet going up as she goes down to land heavily on her back with a squeel. But the ruffian doesn't waste any time at this golden opportunity and discards her bat to nab those feet as she swing up in front of her. Yanking the bunny peacekeeper's boots off to get a startled protest from the warden which turns into a squeek and widened eyes as the wolfy shoves the bunny's feet into her mouth and swallows, starting to engulf her legs and eat her alive.
</text>
<text>
The wolfy ruffian lets out a growl as the warden struggles to resist her appetites, but for all her protests and resistance her weapons are just out of reach. And getting even more so as she's tugged backwards by the wolf demi's hungry throat wrapped around her thighs.
</text>
<text>
The bunny goes from trying to grab for her gun to trying to grab at the ruffian's encroaching lips only to find that was perhaps the wrong idea. Her hands seized and guided into the wolfy's mouth, the warden truly helpless now as her predator works up towards her shoulders.
</text>
<text>
Only the bunny's head is protruding from the mouth of the wolfy as the ruffian shifts back into a seating position, there's a last sight of the bunny's fearful eyes and her cries of 'nooo it can-' before she's sealed inside of the wolfy. The voracious criminal slurping those long bunny ears past her lips and swallowing, settling the bulk of the bunny down into her belly which spills out nicely in front of her.
</text>
</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
The wolfy's gut is nicely exposed, her shirt ridden up and jacket opened to make room for that massive belly. The bunny inside noisily protesting and squirming about, making the ruffian's belly jostle and sway and making her pat and rub over the bulge "Soon have you gurgled up bunny"
</text>
<text>
The ruffian's belly lets out a noisy glorp around her meal, the warden inside letting out a squeel as it seems enzymes and digestive processes are beginning to take a toll on her.
</text>
<text>
You can see the ruffian's meal starting to tire and soften, the bulges in her belly looking less defined now and the squeeks are quieter.
</text>
<text>
The ruffian's gut is still now, rounding out and compacting "Mhmm, that didn't take long..you wardens digest EASY" says the wolfy with a chuckle and gives her gut a pat, hearing the soupy remnants glorp as a result.
</text>
<text>
You see the wolfy's belly shrinking down, absorbing the remains of the bunny. Maybe for all their pretense to law and order the wardens here can't really escape the natural order of predator and prey.
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>