<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Script>
<insertion>
<text>
The warden reaches down and grabs the ruffian by her jacket and hoists her up licking her lips "Now don't be getting any silly ideas bunny.." the wolf begins, but doesn't get a chance to finish as the warden shoves her headfirst into her mouth and takes a swallow, muffling her frantic yelps and growls with her throat as she starts eating the criminal alive.
</text>
<text>
The wolfy ruffian finds herself divested of her jacket as the warden pulls it off her even while devouring her struggling form. The bunny proving quite adept as a predator despite her appearance as she swallows over the ruffian, dragging her down her throat inch by inch and steadily drawing her shoulders and chest past her lips.
</text>
<text>
The warden strips her meal of pants and boots in an almost businesslike fashion as she works the wolfy in as far as her waist. The warden's gut starting to bulge out with the outlines of the criminal's head and hands shoving out her stomach walls and growling out a "Stop it you, you can't eat me..this is stupid." to which the warden seems to pay little heed except to chuckle muffledly around the wolfgirl's waist.
</text>
<text>
Stripped of her more indigestible items of attire the wolf finds herself steadily plunging down and being forced to curl within the depths of the warden's hungry gut. The security bunny mhmming as she works her jaws down along the criminal's thighs, then calves, then finally snaps her teeth shut past her toes and swallows.
</text>
<text>
The wolf yelps and whines but cannot resist the bunny's predatory desires as she's swallowed entirely, plunging down into the steamy depths of the warden's gut to form a delightfully swollen out and rounded belly for the bunny to sport. The warden giving her gut a pat "I eat punks like you for breakfast, literally...have fun becoming bunny pudge."
</text>

</insertion>
<digestion>

<text>
The bunny spares a pat for her belly, the wolf putting up a storm of struggles as she tries to escape her insides. But she seems unable to overcome the bunny tummy for all her strength, which must be embarassing..especially as the warden's pats are more patronizing and belittling for her meal than anything else.
</text>
<text>
The warden's gut gurgles loudly, contracting and grinding on the wolfgirl within making the criminal yelp and squirm as well as making her outline and contours rather visible against the taut tummy skin.
</text>
<text>
You see the bunny's belly start to round out as the squirming movements of her prey weaken and tire out under the relentless assault of her digestive enzymes.
</text>
<text>
The wolfy girl's bravado and belligerence has been worn down now, only whimpering pleas remain. The bunny licking her lips and patting her gut "Hush up and digest wrongdoer, the long arm of the law has a hungry belly for girls like you for a reason" she says and then giggles and squishes down on her belly with both hands.
</text>
<text>
The bunny's gut has turned round and soft, glorping smoothly and no longer emanating any whimpers or pleas for mercy. Seems the ruffian has met a gurgly fate inside of the warden.
</text>
<text>
The warden's gut is compacting, shrinking down as she absorbs and soaks up the ruffian's remains.
</text>
<text>
The warden's belly flattens out with a final gurgle, leaving nothing but her satisfied smirk as she does her uniform back up to indicate the wolf was ever there.
</text>

</digestion>
</Script>