<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!--written by Sideremelane -->
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The great Serpent is a coiled heap of black hide and fur, its
			eyes closed in confusion and hurt.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="Eyes bigger than your belly.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="Show it a REAL 'Great Serpent'">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="Unbirth0" text="Oh GOD no, its massive...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="You defeated it, let it be." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You stroke your cock, bringing it to quick arousal, the shaft pointing
			slightly upwards, proud of your body, balls dangling freely, shifting
			themselves within thier fleshy skin sack as they prepare for the...
			No, you cannot possibly believe you can get the Great Serpent in
			there?
			You grab the limp tailtip of the defeated serpent, even the end of its
			tail giving you some difficulty as you hoist it to the already
			drooling cocktip awaiting it. With a sigh of pleasure, you slip the
			point of its tail in, and you groan, your cockslit gliding smoothly
			around the steadily widening girth of the serpents tail. After a few
			blissful moments, you pause to take stock, your balls already
			sloshing with the tail curled around your testicles. You've barely
			started on this, and already you are straining to support the weight
			between your legs! You cannot stop now though, despite it all, this
			feels amazing, and you want more!
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1"
			text="Tail first, then more tail first, then more..." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			Your cock is taut around your prey now, stretched to the point of barely
			containing the massive girth now crammed inside your urethra, the
			furry ridge down its spine sending a shiver of tickling delight
			through your loins with every added inch. Your ballsack is now
			heavily spread on the ground, your legs forced to straddle the mass
			as you feed ever more of the defeated serpent into your engorged
			shaft.
			A brief twinge of pain spasms through you, and you gasp, but then a
			fresh flood of pleasure washes over you, and you desperatly grab more
			of the coils and pull, cramming more and more down your cock, the
			serpent curling into tight coils within. It has begun to stir, its
			head shifting slightly as it becomes aware of its prediciment. Tiny
			limbs flail as you stuff them in, your stretched skin shifting with
			the bulges they make as they glide down your length.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="Too much" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			It's too much, surely you cannot stretch ANY further?! The serpents head
			turns towards you, eyes rolling as it prepares to turn the tables. In
			desperation, you grunt, and pull, and you feel something tear, but
			the serpent is slurped rapidly from view, slithering helpessly into
			your instaiable cock and almost transluscent ballsack. Its head is
			pulled out of sight last, jaws agape as it sucks in a helpless
			lungful of air to sustain it inside you. Your cock tightens behind
			it, sealing it within, but you notice, even in your lust-clouded
			state, that it seems to have stretched a bit as a result of this
			abuse.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="Can't move" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			And now you've got your prey, not tucked away, but stuffed, crammed into
			your ballsack, struggling to escape the over-stretched confines, much
			to your delight, and slight discomfort. But even the pain is muted,
			transfigured into pleasure by the sensations of squirming FULLNESS.
			You stroke your cock rapidly, as your sack starts to churn, melting
			the trapped serpent into cum. After an age, you climax, spurting
			gallons of melted serpent across the floor, walls, ceiling... You
			pant in release, the afterglow so intense, it almost feels like it's
			still fighting in there...
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore4" text="Still can't move" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore4">
		<text>
			Its still alive! You've melted half of it into cum and spunked it all
			over everything but it's still struggling to escape from your now
			half filled sack. You hesitantly stroke your flaccid cock, painfully
			teasing it into hardness again, your body shuddering in forced
			pleasure over and over, and it huuuurrrts, until it doesn't, and you
			shake and scream in release, the last of the serpent exploding from
			your cock in a slithering spurt, its semi-liquid form writhing on the
			floor, until it flops, and collapses into a huge, gooey puddle with a
			few scattered bones.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="85" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="So much mess" />
	</page>
	Was going to have a +whatever size to penis to reflect the level of
	abuse it just took here but clearly was not using the right code.

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The Great Serpent lies defeated in front of you, coil upon coil of flesh
			and bone and hide. Your belly rumbles, reminding you it's been, oh,
			at least a few minutes since you last ate. No, it's not possible,
			this thing is HUGE and you are only... well, you ARE hungry. Your
			lips part slightly as you think about it, and a flood of saliva
			gushes from your mouth, you can actually FEEL the contractions under
			your tongue as your saliva glands work overtime, pumping slick,
			lubricating drool into your mouth. Maybe just some of it? Hesitantly
			you approach, and pick up the heavy tailtip. Just the TAIL is almost
			more than you can hoist, and you think you can get this into your
			mouth? Well, yeah, of course you do. You raise the tailtip to your
			lips, and slip it in. You suckle for a moment, then swallow, working
			your voracious gullet around the rapidly growing girth of the giant
			serpent.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Looks like a plateful" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			You gulp, over and over, swallowing more and more of the snakelike form
			down into your gurgling gut, which already has you leaning, then
			falling to your knees with the added weight. You try to clench your
			jaw after you feel completely full, in some instinctive effort to
			bite off the excess, but your jaw muscles aren't strong enough, and
			your gullet is still working, peristalsis now claiming the serpent on
			its own with no more active involvement from you. The snakelike form
			stir, as it becomes aware of its prediciment, weakly struggling to
			attempt to free itself, or even turn the tables, but you have other
			ideas. You reach out, grabbing the rough hide, and cram it in, more
			pulling yourself over it than swallowing, but the effect works,
			filling your guts with writhing serpent.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Sore belly" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			You feel like you are getting the worst bellyache, and you still have a
			ways to go. You work up the serpents torso, its chest sinking into
			your straining mouth, its head swaying to and fro, as it desperatly
			attempts to slither free, but its still weak, unable to overcome the
			power of your gullet, and it lets out a cry of despair as your lips
			work over its head, teeth closing around its snout with a final,
			glad, slurp and *GLP* as your gullet fully claims the defeated
			serpent. Finally your lips part again, and you let out a gasp of
			relief, and a sudden wet *BELCH* that shakes dust loost from the
			ceiling.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="Digest" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			You are comically perched on top of your own gut, the shape of the
			coiled serpent clearly visible under your skin, your stomach gurgling
			and sloshing lewdly as it begins working to break down the huge mass
			of meat you just ingested. Said mas of meat doesn't want to go
			quietly however, and you let out several more echoing belches over
			the course of the next several hours as you digest your prey. Until
			it's almost gone however, you are essentially trapped in place, held
			by the weight in your gut. By the time you can move, the serpent is
			almost gone, you can merely feel a few fragmented bones and mushy
			meat beneath your stretchmarked skin. You slowly begin making your
			way back out of the cave, still sloshing.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="450" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Urp, indeed." />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth0">
		<text>
			You step forward confidently, the black tailtip looks inviting anf firm,
			your drooling nether lips hot and slick between your legs just at the
			thought of all that girth and length. You crouch, and stroke your
			slit against the rough hide, slicking it with your juices, and
			sending fresh waves of arousal through you. You reach down between
			your thighs, and lift the tailtip, guiding it expertly between your
			legs, and in, pressing your pussy lips open with ease. You moan, and
			press harder, easing more in, and then out again. You masturbate with
			the tail, working it deeper with every thrust, until you feel the
			point poke your cervix... You gasp, and in a moment of wild abandon,
			decide, what the hell.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Unbirth1" text="The tailtip does fit... You want more!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth1">
		<text>
			You grasp the girth of the serpent, and pull, rocking forward on your
			heels to slide more and more of the vast form into your hungry pussy,
			your womb swallowing the tail greedily. You pause only to gasp air,
			and shudder from a slowly building, ongoing climax. You ease forward,
			working more of the serpent in, and push harder, your belly swelling
			with the weight filling it, and you are forced to drop to all fours.
			You turn, lifting a leg over the serpent to straddle it in reverse,
			and you shove backwards, forcing more into yourself than you ever
			thought possible. You soon reach your limit, not of your womb, but of
			your strength, simply unable to lift your belly any further back,
			almost a third of the beast now within you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Unbirth2"
			text="Feels so good, but maybe you should stop and let the beast go..." />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth2">
		<text>
			The serpent slowly awakens, and finds itself partially inserted into
			your cunt! Its dim reptilian brain responds with a conflicting panic,
			both trying to escape, but also deeply aroused by the scent of your
			juices and enticed by the warmth of your swollen womb. As a result,
			instead of struggling to escape by heading away from you, it responds
			by trying to slither BACKWARDS. You had been half asleep, lost in the
			ongoing orgasm wracking you with shuddering bliss, when suddenly you
			are rammed from behind and you feel your pussy stretched even further
			as the serpents body enters yours in a rushing, slithering motion tha
			you can neither escape from nor control!
		</text>
		<choice destination="Unbirth3" text="All the way in." />
	</page>

	<page ID="Unbirth3">
		<text>
			You manage to get onto your side, shaking and crying out in shock and
			pleasure as you are invaded by the confused reptile, your belly
			swollen beyond its limits, filling the corridor with your taut skin.
			With a remarkable surge of final motion, the serpent, having
			seemingly decided your snatch was a safe place to hide, tucks itself
			into your pussy, only its face still visible, you can reach around
			under the huge swollen mass of your belly to feel its nose, peeking
			between your drooling nether lips... At your touch though, it pulls
			itself in, and you finally climax, your body wracking and shaking
			over and over, your womb clenching and squeezing the trapped serpent,
			which too late realizes its mistake, and what emerges from your
			snatch as it tries to escape, is just an unending flood of feminine
			cum that sends a small tidal wave across the floor of the passageway.
		</text>



		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="You finished the whole thing!" />
	</page>

</Conversation>