<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="analvore" />
		<preference fetish="demis" />
		<preference fetish="females" />		
		<text>
			The warrior smirks down at you as you fall before her, then
			reaches
			down, lifting up her skirt as she steps astride your head and
			shoulders, squatting down she smothers your face with her rear end.
			Those ample soft buttcheeks covering your face, squishing down to
			either side of your ears. Her sphincter pressed against your nose as
			she mhmms, shifts her hips and then pushing down further over you.
			Your head squeezing up between those cheeks with a plop and chuckle
			from the voracious green elf as you start to slip inside her ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="into the depths" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
			The elven warrior moans and shimmies her hips, clenching and
			dragging
			your shoulders into her bowels as well. Her hungry emerald
			rump
			stretching around your chest as she shifts from her squat and
			leans
			back with hands back behind herself. The elven warrior assuming
			a
			posture so you're better aligned with her sphincter as she continues
			ravenously drawing you up and into her debauched arse. Her derriere
			working down towards your waist, her belly stretching out as you
			slide further through her bowels, through her guts and towards her
			stomach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="deeper" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			The hot stifling pressure of her insides pushes against your
			upper body
			from all sides as she claims your ass with the hungry
			sphincter of
			her own. The elf groaning in delight and leaning back
			even further,
			nearly on her back as she starts to claim your legs.
			Soon you'll be
			utterly gone within that victorious green elf ass. Your
			legs unable
			to squirm or struggle now as they're pushed together by
			the tight
			anal ring of her pucker sliding down over your thighs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
			The elf is finally on her back entirely now as she finishes you
			off, her
			ass rippling down around your calves. Her buttcheeks sliding
			closer
			and closer together as she nears your feet and her belly bulges
			and
			stretches out. Your body curling trapped inside her as she
			finishes
			you off, dragging your feet past their sphincter and they
			disappear
			into her ass with a plop as your toes vanish into her ass.
			The elf
			mhmming as she rubs her middle, feeling you trapped inside her
			as a
			meal "Mmmm, don't worry my meal. You'll soon be part of a better
			warrior than you could ever be." she says and then chuckles "You'll
			probably go to my ass, most do." she remarks as gurgling gets ready
			to work you over.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="*try to escape her ass*" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="escape" />
		<outcome destination="gurgle" />
	</check>

	<page ID="escape">
		<text>
			Bested though you might of been in combat, you're not going to
			go quietly
			to your supposed fate in assfat purgatory. And so you set
			about
			trying to force your way back the way you came, struggling and
			shoving around to find the exit and stretch it as you start worming
			your way back out of her. The elf frowning "Now now, stop being a
			sore loser, losers get turned into assfat now...get back in there!"
			she remarks as you make progress, she squirms on the ground and
			clenches as your hands shove back out of her ass. But it seems she's
			not strong enough to stop you from escaping her, groaning and gasping
			and protesting as she writhes on the ground and you squirm out of her
			rump leaving her dazed on the ground as you stagger to your feet.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="*back up*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="gurgle">
		<text>
			Bested though you might of been in combat, you're not going to
			go quietly
			to your supposed fate in assfat purgatory. And so you set
			about
			trying to force your way back the way you came, struggling and
			shoving around to try and find the exit so you can start worming your
			way out of her. The elf smiles and squeezes on her gut as she smugly
			chides you "Now now, stop being a sore loser, losers get turned into
			assfat and that's exactly what you're going to be" she says and moans
			as her insides get to work on you in earnest, your form starting to
			digest in the depths of her body as it seems you cannot muster a
			successful escape from her insides.
		</text>
		<choice destination="gameover" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="gameover">
		<text>
			Eaten by her ass and imprisoned in her belly your struggles do
			naught but
			please the elf who has so utterly bested you. The green
			warrior
			feeling you weaken gets back to her feet, content to continue
			her
			patrol as gradually her lumpy bulgy middle turns round and soft.
			And
			your whimpers and squirms give way to gurgles and churns as she
			digests you away into a slurry of nutrients, much going to fuel her
			activities in the war against the perfidious reptiles. Though
			admittedly a good proportion of you goes to increase the roundness of
			her ass, improving that already luscious pear into an even more ample
			set of alluring curves. Soon enough her belly is flat and the only
			evidence of your existence is an extra layer of rump fat on the elf
			who devoured you.
		</text>
	</gameover>


</Conversation>