<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			In defeat the draconian is incredulous, glaring at you but the heat of
			her gaze is augmented and dampened by the stunned disbelief that
			still warrs with it on her face. The proud creature tries to stand at
			your approach, but stumbles back down as her form is too weakened by
			the conflict to manage the movement. The draconian laid low once
			again in a way that makes her snarl and hiss "This is intolerable, I
			cannot lose to one such as you."
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0"
			text="$But you have, and now, now I want a celebratory feast">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="$Oh your indignity won't stop with that">
		<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore"/>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="$And yet it happened, think on that for a while" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	The draconian appears confused by what you mean, at least until <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				you shuck your pants and 
			</conditional> fondle your firming <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> shaft meaningfully.
	The draconian growls "if you think I'm about to submit to your impudent lusts and let you rut me worm" 
	she says defiantly. Glaring, all sound and fury despite how little she could resist in her beaten state.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="$Good thing I'm going to feed you to it and waste you on the ground then"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	"You wouldn't dare. I am too magnificent a creature to suffer such a fate." she says, though a note of uncertainty is just beginning to creep into her proud bluster. She growls as you approach and snag her foot with one hand and guide your tip towards it with the other as your cock grows larger and hungrier "I won't let you" she threatens as she tries to tug her feet away, then snarls as despite that you manage to shove her foot into your tip and snag the other. The draconian squirming to try and tug free as one foot sinks deeper into the musky grasp of your tip and you feed the other inside.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="$Feel free to try and stop me, your struggles will make it feel better for me"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	"You!" she seems momentarily speechless in shock as you taunt her that way. But then she redoubles her struggles, but all she does is force you to restrain her thrashing tail and feed it in as you schlurp her calves into your shaft.Her smooth limb scales providing extra stimulation as they slide slickly against the inside of your shaft "un-unhand me" she demands as you draw her deeper, her feet pushing through the base of your shaft and into the cummy depths of your balls. Her knees disappearing past your cumslit. After that you make quick work over her thighs, squeezing her hips into your tip and forcing her knees to bend as she starts to get stuffed into your sack.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="$not my hand you should be worried about cockfood"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	"don't call me that" she protests, seemingly still in denial about what's happening to her as you schlurp her draconian form up with your cock. But her disbelief won't stop her from ending up your next load. And you intend to make that point by pulling her deeper into your shaft. Her upper body steadily disappearing into your loins despite her struggles.Her arms forced above her head as her wings are uncomfortably pinned as you reach her chest, engulfing her breasts and squeezing her shapely orbs along with most of the rest of her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore4" text="$why not? draconians do make the best cockfood"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4">
	<text>
	"no we're not cockfood! i'm not cockf-SMPH!" she protests, cut off as your tip schlorps over the top of her head leaving only her squirming arms protruding from your cock. The draconian futilely attempting to stop her plunge the rest of her way into your balls. But her hands cannot get a grip on your slick cumslit as they disappear down into it. The sensation of the once proud and mighty draconian being reduced to a bulge in your shaft and sack making you moan out and drawing your hands irresistably to fondle the shape of her protesting form as she sinks deeper. The draconian attempting to push out the inside of your sack as she's forced to curl up as a massive and satisfying weight sagging out your balls now.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="$not so mighty now are we dragon? somehow I think you'll melt into cum same as anyone else"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	"no, no please it can't end this way. I can't end this way." she exclaims, still protesting this fate even now as your balls begin to blorp and burble around her. The draconian struggling around making your sack jostle and sway around. But her protests and squirming avail her little as you work her over inside your balls. She's softening despite all the bluster about her supremacy and might, like any other cockfood she's going to melt away into cum. You can feel her shape yielding to your hands as you reach down to fondle and rub over your sack.
	</text>
	<choic destination="cockvore6" text="$nearly there..nearly..cum"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore6">
	<text>
	"no-gahslph-" the draconian's final protest fades into splattering gushing gurgling noises as she comes apart in your balls at long last. The draconian's mighty form now sloshing fluidly in your sack, naught but gallons of thick glorping cum for you to waste on the ground. And you set about inflicting the final indignity on that once proud creature. Your hands both going to your cock as you feels your smoothly rounded sack churn. The pent up cum as an insistent pressure at the base of your shaft stirring you on in your decadent masturbation. Your pleasure rising as you hear her remnants glorp around under your moans and fapping. Rising and then finally cresting, your cock erupting to splatter the ground with former draconian. The mighty dragon now naught but a mighty load, pooling on the ground in front of you as you pour her out in spurting bursts until you're spent. The final indignity, the draconian's much vaunted superiority amounting to a forgotten and transitory orgasm for your own pleasure.
	</text>
	<effect type="feed" value="130" />
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			"Surely you jest, it cannot end this way." the draconian scoffs, apparently
			unwilling to believe your intentions even as you loom over her and
			prepare yourself mentally and physically to put this oh so superior
			draconian in her place. She's still incredulous even as you squat
			down to more easily meet her eye level and grab her shoulders "unhand
			me you inferio-MMPH!" and with that her belittling prattle is
			silenced by your encroaching mouth as you wrap it around her face and
			engulf her head. A last look at her shocked expression afore you work
			over those horns and hair and all the way to her neck. The draconian
			shoving at your chest in protest as you savour her flavour, and take
			your first swallow. The draconian letting out a muffled protest and
			squirming anew as somehow the being she'd thought herself the better
			to was actually eating her alive.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="victory makes her taste all the sweeter" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Her shock seems to wear off quickly as you work down over her shoulders
			and towards the round delightfullness of her breasts and she realizes
			you're truly eating her. The draconian's indignant growls and
			protestations remain muffled by the tightness of your throat as
			despite her efforts she begins to slide on down through it. The
			draconian's flexing wings spread wide to stop you getting past her
			shoulders, the splayed wings resisting your efforts for a time
			forcing you to reach up and shove and press them down. The effort of
			overcoming her powerful body by main force only possible in her
			weakened state and even then it takes a time for her flight muscles
			to tire and her strength to be once again exhausted. With a mhmm you
			lap at her collar and force her wings down against her back, pinning
			them swiftly as you engulf her chest at long last with your mouth.
			Her breasts are heavenly as they press against your tongue, all the
			more delicious for the challenge in earning this sumptous feast. You
			feel her trying to shove at you with her part pinned arms and reward
			her for her efforts with a trip deeper inside you, cramming her head
			deeper in and starting to work towards her tastey tail augmented ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			The draconian struggles and squirms and protests but to no avail as you
			cram her middle past your lips. And in turn you're starting to cram
			her into your belly "unha-undevour me you impertinent..gah!" she
			snarls, alas the price of forcing her into your belly is she gets to
			talk again without her face being squeezed and muffled by your
			throat. You swallow hard to mash her face against the inside of your
			belly and groan as your middle swells out, forcing the draconian to
			curl in submission as you work your lips over her ass and swallow
			that down as well. Now you only have her tail and legs left to devour
			and the sight of the finish line for your meal stirrs you on "Give up
			this foolishness at once, you cannot devour one as superior as
			I!"..also shutting up the draconian and proving her wrong stirs you
			on, that as well. And so you swallow hard and vigorously, a mix of
			skin and scale sliding over your tongue as you polish her off
			steadily. The final frantically twitching tip of her tail protruding
			from your lips before you gulp that down as well, sealing the
			arrogant dragongirl into your body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="delicious, but she may not keep quiet." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			"You'll pay for this indignity! When I get out of here." she exclaims in
			outrage and shoves at your insides, attempting to force her way back
			out within moment's of being tightly squeezed and packed away in your
			belly. Your middle jostling and swaying and bobbing with contours of
			her wings, tail and other limbs pushing out at your tummy flesh in a
			somewhat disagreeable way. Still, you have her right where you want
			her, and where her continued defiance of the TRUE superior predator
			here can be easily rectified.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4"
			text="$somehow i doubt you'll get much revenge when I've digested you" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore4">
		<text>
			"digest me?! you wouldn't!" she protests but despite her continued disbelief
			that you could treat her that way your stomach makes it quite clear
			that to you she's now just another meal. The churning and grinding of
			your gurgling belly starts to press down on her from all sides "I am
			a dragon, a mighty and superior-" she protests and then for the first
			time whimpers as your enzymes begin to take their toll "I cannot end
			in the belly of some lowly-" she protests again later as her
			struggles weaken and slow "Dragons should not..." she manages, but
			this one sounds more like a plea as her ongoing digestion begins to
			break down her cast iron pride as it does her body. Her final words
			are weak, almost pitiable "please-don't" she begs afore finally being
			gurgled away. The draconian now more soup than girl now as your gut
			smooths out and her remains are converted into nothing but fuel for
			you, for all her arrogance and so called superior in the end she's
			just a satisfying meal conquered by your belly like any other.
			Gradually even the round softness of your belly fades and shrinks
			down to nothing as she's absorbed into your form.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>