<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			In defeat the draconian is incredulous, glaring at you but the heat of
			her gaze is augmented and dampened by the stunned disbelief that
			still warrs with it on her face. The proud creature tries to stand at
			your approach, but stumbles back down as her form is too weakened by
			the conflict to manage the movement. The draconian laid low once
			again in a way that makes her snarl and hiss "This is intolerable, I
			cannot lose to one such as you."
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0"
			text="$But you have, and now, now I want a celebratory feast">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="$And yet it happened, think on that for a while" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			"Surely you jest, it cannot end this way." the draconian scoffs, apparently
			unwilling to believe your intentions even as you loom over her and
			prepare yourself mentally and physically to put this oh so superior
			draconian in her place. She's still incredulous even as you squat
			down to more easily meet her eye level and grab her shoulders "unhand
			me you inferio-MMPH!" and with that her belittling prattle is
			silenced by your encroaching mouth as you wrap it around her face and
			engulf her head. A last look at her shocked expression afore you work
			over those horns and hair and all the way to her neck. The draconian
			shoving at your chest in protest as you savour her flavour, and take
			your first swallow. The draconian letting out a muffled protest and
			squirming anew as somehow the being she'd thought herself the better
			to was actually eating her alive.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="victory makes her taste all the sweeter" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Her shock seems to wear off quickly as you work down over her shoulders
			and towards the round delightfullness of her breasts and she realizes
			you're truly eating her. The draconian's indignant growls and
			protestations remain muffled by the tightness of your throat as
			despite her efforts she begins to slide on down through it. The
			draconian's flexing wings spread wide to stop you getting past her
			shoulders, the splayed wings resisting your efforts for a time
			forcing you to reach up and shove and press them down. The effort of
			overcoming her powerful body by main force only possible in her
			weakened state and even then it takes a time for her flight muscles
			to tire and her strength to be once again exhausted. With a mhmm you
			lap at her collar and force her wings down against her back, pinning
			them swiftly as you engulf her chest at long last with your mouth.
			Her breasts are heavenly as they press against your tongue, all the
			more delicious for the challenge in earning this sumptous feast. You
			feel her trying to shove at you with her part pinned arms and reward
			her for her efforts with a trip deeper inside you, cramming her head
			deeper in and starting to work towards her tastey tail augmented ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			The draconian struggles and squirms and protests but to no avail as you
			cram her middle past your lips. And in turn you're starting to cram
			her into your belly "unha-undevour me you impertinent..gah!" she
			snarls, alas the price of forcing her into your belly is she gets to
			talk again without her face being squeezed and muffled by your
			throat. You swallow hard to mash her face against the inside of your
			belly and groan as your middle swells out, forcing the draconian to
			curl in submission as you work your lips over her ass and swallow
			that down as well. Now you only have her tail and legs left to devour
			and the sight of the finish line for your meal stirrs you on "Give up
			this foolishness at once, you cannot devour one as superior as
			I!"..also shutting up the draconian and proving her wrong stirs you
			on, that as well. And so you swallow hard and vigorously, a mix of
			skin and scale sliding over your tongue as you polish her off
			steadily. The final frantically twitching tip of her tail protruding
			from your lips before you gulp that down as well, sealing the
			arrogant dragongirl into your body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="delicious, but she may not keep quiet." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			"You'll pay for this indignity! When I get out of here." she exclaims in
			outrage and shoves at your insides, attempting to force her way back
			out within moment's of being tightly squeezed and packed away in your
			belly. Your middle jostling and swaying and bobbing with contours of
			her wings, tail and other limbs pushing out at your tummy flesh in a
			somewhat disagreeable way. Still, you have her right where you want
			her, and where her continued defiance of the TRUE superior predator
			here can be easily rectified.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4"
			text="$somehow i doubt you'll get much revenge when I've digested you" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore4">
		<text>
			"digest me?! you wouldn't!" she protests but despite her continued disbelief
			that you could treat her that way your stomach makes it quite clear
			that to you she's now just another meal. The churning and grinding of
			your gurgling belly starts to press down on her from all sides "I am
			a dragon, a mighty and superior-" she protests and then for the first
			time whimpers as your enzymes begin to take their toll "I cannot end
			in the belly of some lowly-" she protests again later as her
			struggles weaken and slow "Dragons should not..." she manages, but
			this one sounds more like a plea as her ongoing digestion begins to
			break down her cast iron pride as it does her body. Her final words
			are weak, almost pitiable "please-don't" she begs afore finally being
			gurgled away. The draconian now more soup than girl now as your gut
			smooths out and her remains are converted into nothing but fuel for
			you, for all her arrogance and so called superior in the end she's
			just a satisfying meal conquered by your belly like any other.
			Gradually even the round softness of your belly fades and shrinks
			down to nothing as she's absorbed into your form.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>