<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		The draconian looms over you, flushed, breathing heavily as she lets out a low growl "You, I've never felt this way before." she says and then a little shiver runs through her afore she declares...what it is she wants.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="#..i want to be your food, i want to feed myself to you">
		<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="#..I want to mate with you">
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey0" text="# I want to cockvore you, i need you as my cum">
		<preference fetish="cockvore"/>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="*whatever it is you beat a hasty retreat*"/>	
		</page>

		<page ID="cockvoreprey0">
		<text>
		The draconian states her desire to melt you as she strokes her shaft, looking at you in need and running her hand up and down her large and erect shaft. Her pre stained cocktip and hefty balls look equally inviting to you.
		Her desire thrills you, and you cannot help but shiver with a matching desire to be the cum she needs you to be. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey1" text="$thought you'd never ask, I'd love to be cockfood"/>
		</page>
		
		<page ID="cockvoreprey1">
		<text>
		The draconian doesn't remark on how she didn't really ask. But just moans "Then..then get in me cockfood, my balls crave to churn you down.. i need to feel you melt in them." she declares with a growl and a thrust of her hips. The thrust splatting your cheek with pre and making you weak in the knees. You answer not with words but deeds and a thrust of your own, of your hands right into her dick. The hot pre letting out a lewd squelch that mingles with your moan and her growl to act as a delicious signifier of your deeds. Her cock bulging out around your hands and rippling hungrily as she thrusts her hips to engulf your forearms, working her shaft up towards your head with a moan. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey2" text="*yes! duck your head down, thrust in, be cockfood!*"/>
		</page>
		
		<page ID="cockvoreprey2">
		<text>
		The draconian growls in bliss "Yes, get in me..get in me cockfood." she demands lustfully as she takes in your head. All sounds except her throbbing cock and squelching pre are muffled as your head slides deeper into her rippling length. That wonderfully hungry dick of hers now bulging out gloriously as your chest slips in and you wriggle your hips to work your belly past her feasting cumslit. Her cock is wrapped around your waist now and soon she'll slurp you up entirely like the cocksnack you are. You're perhaps even more impatient for that to happen than she is, you feel her grasping her cock and lifting you upwards with ease. Your legs angle upwards and brush against her breasts and you know it won't be long now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey3" text="*can't wait...just can't wait*"/>
		</page>
		
		<page ID="cockvoreprey3">
		<text>
		Your predator's nuts welcome you with hot burbles and squelches as her cum oozes around you and you sink into the welcoming embrace of her loins. The draconian stroking her hands up and down her shaft, over the bulge you make in her dick as you slide on down. Her sack hanging low as your ass slides on down and you curl in the blissful cumbath of her sack. Soon after your legs vanish into her cumslit with a schlurp, her hands jerking you down her bulging shaft and fully feeding you down into her sack. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey4" text="*can't wait to melt*"/>
		</page>
		
		<page ID="cockvoreprey4">
		<text>
		"Mhmm, yes. I've wanted this so badly, and now..i have you right where I want you. You really are perfect cockfood." she says with a growl as she strokes her cock and feels you curled up and squirming around in her balls. Her sack bulging and bloated with your shape and starting to burble and churn as she tail sways and moans in deeper pleasure. Your form starting to soften and round out as you revel in the exquisite sensations of becoming her seed "You melt so easily..like you were made for it." she exclaims blissfully, you're only able to burble in response..not even moan as more and more of you is rendered down into creamy goo.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreprey5" text="*burble*"/>
		</page>
		
		<gameover ID="cockvoreprey5">
		<text>
		The draconian moans and chuckles "you're..you're all gone aren't you..nothing but cum." she says and then licks her lips "My cum" she reiterates with possessive satisfaction and strokes off faster, more vigorously. The draconian moaning in bliss knowing that you've been rendered down into gooey jizz sloshing about in her bloated balls as she strokes off harder and faster and then harder and faster still. The mighty predator finally closing her eyes and letting out a roar as she reaches her peak and sends your remnants gushing and splattering out to form a sticky puddle in front of her. Your body sacrificed to be a glorious orgasm for her to enjoy as she pumps wad after wad of cum out. Thick jizz mounding atop itself into a gooey puddling mound like softened wax or melting butter. The lewd and prideful draconian's orgasm finally subsiding two minutes later and she strokes a little bit more of your goopy remnants out before flying off, well satisfied by the experience it seems. 
		</text>
		</gameover>
		
			<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
	<text>
	Well a tumble with a sexy draconian sounds like a good idea to you. Question is who is going to be on the receiving end...
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexF0" text="$Good, cause I want to feel that dick of yours in me">
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		<preference fetish="herms" />		
	</choice>
	<choice destination="sexH0" text="$Good, cause I had a hankering to fuck a draconic slut">
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
	</choice>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexH0">
	<text>
	The draconian blushes deeper at that, and a soft growl rises in her throat. But yet her reaction may surprise you as your belittling taunt is answered with "Yes, your draconic slut, use me." she agrees, seemingly aroused by debasing herself as such a thing but committed to the role she's chosen and needy for your touch. The mighty dragongirl turning around, bending forwards and lifting her tail as she presents her moist nethers to you needily.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexH1" text="*use your slut*"/>
	</page>
		
	<page ID="sexH1">
	<text>
	You watch the draconian presenting herself needily to you, and her tail flicks in impatience "hurry up!...use me.." she growls and it's all you can do to tease her and not just dive in, taking time moving up behind her. The dragongirl grinding back against your length but you keep your hands on her ass to control her, and let her know that she's your slut and you'll fuck her on your terms.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexH2" text="*finally put it in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexH2">
	<text>
	You grind your tip up against her nethers, and she tries to press herself down over your length without effect as you grip her hips and pull back. She lets out a growl, but looking back at you realizes you're serious and she shivers...afore submissively lowering her gaze. And only then do you thrust into her. Filling the mighty dragongirl with your shaft as you drive your cock deep into her soaking wet and amazingly hot nethers.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexH3" text="$You're a good slut"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexH3">
	<text>
	The draconian growls at the belittling compliment "stop taunting me and fuck me!" she demands. And whether you finally gave into the puissant woman or were going to start thrusting regardless she lets out a delighted moan as you begin to pound her pussy, digging your fingers deep into the flanks of her meaty ass as you plough her cauldron like nethers with your shaft.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexH4" text="*fuck her hard*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexH4">
	<text>
	The draconian seems not to care that she's no longer in control as you fuck her like the submissive slut she's chosen to be. The mighty dragongirl moaning and growling as you use her nethers and squeeze her ass possessively. Your vigorous fucking of the dragongirl finally reaching crescendo as you slam your shaft into her a final time and paint her innards with your seed, marking her womb as yours. The sensation seeming if anything even more overwhelming for the dragongirl as she shudders and slumps down as you fill her up, the draconian spasming in orgasm until you spend yourself in her and pull out. The draconian looking up and blushing, licking at your sticky dick as you stand over her.
	</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was fun" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexF0">
	<text>
	You express your agreement to be screwed and step in close to her, leaning up to plant a kiss on her lips while groping and caressing her length. Your hand running up and down that hard and eager shaft as she growls in delight. Her hands cupping around your ass firmly, lifting your feet up of the floor and carrying you down onto your back under the lusty draconian. Her tail curling as she looks down at you dominantly and shifts her hips "Yes, you deserve my cock" she pronounces as you feel her tip lining up with your nethers.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexF1" text="$I NEED your cock"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexF1">
	<text>
	"yes" the draconian agrees simply, as she thrusts inside of you. Her thick length parting your folds, stretching your intimate insides. The dragon herm grasping ahold of your legs as she sheathes her length inside you with a growl of delight. And then she began to work her length in and out, picking up a vigorous pace she's soon pounding her cock in and out of your sex with all the animalistic lust you feel you can handle. The sensations making you shudder as her balls slap against your ass repeatedly.
	</text>.
	<choice destination="sexF2" text="$yes that's it, fuck me!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexF2">
	<text>
	The draconian's power and lust make you moan under her and make to lift and wrap your legs around her hips, but she grips your legs tighter and growls as she thrusts more firmly into you. Your fuck buddy keeping you from taking an control of the pace she's rutting you. You're helplessly, but delightfully, dominated as her pace quickens and her growls of pleasure mingle with your moans of the same. You can feel her orgasm approaching through the shuddering molten waves of your own and it makes you tingle with anticipation.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sexF3" text="$fill me up"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sexF3">
	<text>
	The draconian hears your words and growls "Yes!" she declares, hilting her cock inside of you as it spurts and paints your innermost intimates with hot seed. Her hips twitching slightly and her tail thrashing around in broad sweeps as she pumps spurt after spurt of hot cum into you "Mhmm..you're a good one" she finally compliments as she looks down at your dazed form, rumbling with pleasure as her spurts trail off and she pulls out of you. Her last cumshots splatting on your belly as she stands up, apparently done..her desires satiated and her equilibrium restored.
	</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was fun" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />	
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	The draconian seems aroused and yet shameful at the urges you've instilled in her. With a flush on her face and yet she doesn't hesitate on unfamiliar ground "so do it, what are you waiting for, eat me" she declares with a growl. Not waiting as she thrusts a hand at your lips, pressing her fingers past your lips and down your throat. You're forced to swallow or choke and as her hand bulges out your neck she blushes heavier "why are you so sexy" she mumbles accusingly as if you're really forcing her hand as she shoves her other hand into your mouth and down your throat. The draconian tucking her wings down against her back and lowering her head as you take another swallow, and then another. The draconian's newfound preyish desires are still a bit unexpected, but managable like those of everyone else who wants inside of you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*accomodate the draconian*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The draconian mumbles and moans as she thrusts her head down your throat, your hands sliding up to grasp her ample and powerful frame as she leans into your mouth. She's being such a good prey in feeding herself to you, your tongue lashing over her bared large breasts and then you're squishing them down your throat. Gradually you take over from her powerful body pushing herself into your mouth and help feed her in, squeezing her ass and feeling her tail swaying around against the back of your hands as you gobble her up "gonna be just food" the draconian moans out, aroused..but ashamed as she admits what she's gonna be..what she wants to be, for you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*swallow her the rest of the way*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	You feel your gut stretching and filling out with her body as you tip her legs into the air, feeling her grinding her hips against the inside of your throat as you swallow her down steadily. The draconian turning into a filling bulge stretching out your gut with your powerful yet preyish meal. The draconian's legs and tail the last to disappear as you polish her off and look down at your middle, she was delicious, both in attitude and flavour.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="$Well satisfied now food? you're all held in a belly, ready to be digested"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	The draconian lets out a growl but it turns swiftly into a moan as you tease her and she squirms "...yes, ready to be digested.." she really doesn't second guess her decision now, she's going all the way and so you feel happy to fulfil her goals. Your stomach starting to gurgle and glorp around her, pressing around her as she groans and squirms around and her mighty form is bathed and marinated in your enzymes.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="*treat her like the food she is*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	The draconian groans and squirms and churns inside you for a seeming age. The sensations of her form stretching and pushing against your insides toe curlingly exquisite at containing and claiming so mighty a predator as your willing meal. Gradually her form is conquered by your digestive powers, ground down into mush inside your belly. The draconian a deliciously satisfying meal for you, and one you're happy to accomodate. Once she's liquidated its not that long to absorb her entirely, her body putting up no more resistance and soon your gut shrinks down to nothing.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
</Conversation>