<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The draconian looms over you in all her sexy yet intimidating glory
			and looks down upon you with a smirk
			<random id="draconian_insults" />
			she scorns, rubbing in her victory. Though as she regards you and
			assesses you can tell she intends to make her victory total and her
			domination over you complete. You can see in her eyes the moment she
			makes her decision and says that
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="#all you're good for is to sate my lust">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="#you deserve to die without dignity">
			<preference fetish="analvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="gameover" text="a fate too terrible to contemplate">
			<notpreference fetish="cockvore" />
			<notpreference fetish="analvore" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			The draconian loomed over you and reached down, stroking herself as she
			does so. That thick shaft of hers rising to attention, she watches
			your gaze then smirks "As if you deserve the privilege of having it
			inside of you." she says and then squats down, grabbing your feet and
			then feeding them in with a schlorp "no, all you deserve is to be
			wasted on the ground." she says and chuckles, starting to drag your
			legs into her cock with her hands and the rippling of her erection.
			The voracious demi dragon moaning as her shaft bulges out, swollen
			around your calves as you plunge into the sticky heat of her cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="food for her lust" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			"Does it scare you weakling? that your inferior self will amount to just a
			burst of pleasure as i stroke you out?" she asks as she looms close
			over you, leant forwards to help feed you in and eclipse you in the
			shadow of her wings. She lets out a moan as you squirm against the
			pull of her cock, her rippling shaft schlurping up around your
			thighs. Your body pressed tightly in the squeezing musky tube of her
			cock as she oozes pre around you, lubing you up so she can swallow
			you deeper into her hungering loins. "Or maybe it excites you knowing
			that you will serve your better in such a way?" she says thoughtfully
			and smiles as she reaches your hips and shudders in bliss at feeling
			your feet pushing into her balls. The hot cum oozing around your feet
			and welcoming you inside as your feet slide down to push against the
			inside of her balls, pushing against her inner thighs but too slippy
			to stop you disappearing deeper into her as her member feasts on you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The draconian growls in delight as she feels your middle begin to slide
			past her cocktip, reaching down to forcefully press your arms to your
			sides preventing them escaping her lusty appetites. As your chest and
			then shoulders slide in the last thing you see of the outside world
			is her smirking face afore you take your final plunge "all mine, in
			you go weakling." she taunts afore placing a hand atop your head and
			shoving you in. Entirely encased in her lust and the dominative
			squeezing and pressing of her loins now you feel her stroke over her
			shaft as she coaxes you down, down on past the hot tight base of her
			shaft as she steadily settles your entire body down into her balls.
			"mmhmm, they sound pleased to meet you." she remarks with a chuckle
			as her balls make a gooey burble around your body as you settle in
			and displace their contents. The draconian smiling in delight and
			fondling herself as your form sags down her now lumpy and distended
			sack.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasureCV"
			text="attempt to pleasure her into letting you go" />
		<choice destination="submitCV" text="submit to being draconian pleasure fluid" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasureCV">
		<text>
			Your only way out is to try and pleasure her into jerking you out whole,
			and so you set to it "mhmm you're a feisty one aren't you" she
			remarks with a growl of pleasure as you start to stroke and rub
			against the inside of her sack. Your hands getting busy stimulating
			your confines, feeling them start to churn but knowing the greater
			risk of melting is the price you pay for trying to make her climax.
			As you feel the steady rthyhmic tensing of the sack that indicates
			her hand stroking her cock you can only hope your efforts will make
			her cum before you end up as cum.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVPleasureCheck" text="try to get her off" />
	</page>

	<check ID="CVPleasureCheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureEscapeCV" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureDigestCV" />
	</check>

	<page ID="pleasureEscapeCV">
		<text>
			"mhmm, is this your way of...serving your betters?" the draconian asks with
			a groan as she strokes off and feels you rubbing her sack pleasurably
			from within. Her balls jostling and shifting with your handprints
			pushing out as she slides her hand up and down her shaft, steadily
			getting more and more into it. All going according to your plan as
			your sticky hands rub up against sensitive spots inside her, the
			churning balls clenching and shuddering around you as she gasps and
			growls bucking her hips. Until with a final shuddering groan she
			climaxes, cock spasming to blast hot seed out onto the ground. But
			more importantly she also cums you out, your body rocketing up her
			cock to land with a sticky splat amidst the gooey puddle she's made.
			The draconian panting and gasping in afterglow as she opens her eyes,
			then sees you out and intact and realizes what you did. She glares,
			and starts to rise to her feet, a bit wobbly but clearly quite
			willing to put you back in your place once she gets a chance.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasureDigestCV">
		<text>
			You squirm about to try and rub at the insides of the draconian's balls
			as the superior creature masturbates the sensations "Mhmm, yes,
			please your better in your final moments..." she encourages you as
			she jerks off, feeling as you rub at the insides of her balls. Your
			hands making prints pushing out the inside of her sack as groans and
			growls in pleasure, stroking herself. Your time in the sack difficult
			to keep track of, all is clenching and rippling and hot sticky cum as
			you run your hands along the insides of that sensual churning
			chamber...hands feeling hot and tingly then numb as you rub them
			against her insides, until you realize your body is weakening,
			softening, and your hands are now no more than smears of thick cum as
			your efforts have been rewarded with a more vigorous cumgestion than
			you'd of received otherwise. There's no escape now, you're ball
			fodder.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVpleasureGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CVpleasureGO">
		<text>
			"mhmm, ooh i can feel you melt..you've got my balls boiling." she remarks
			with a moan as she strokes off, your form starting to fade away as
			you're helplessly sloshed away into draconian jizz. Your efforts to
			stroke her to pleasure having only given yourself a swift and sticky
			demise as her balls round out and she strokes off all the faster to
			the sensation. Soon all that remains in her balls is gallons of sack
			fattening spunk where once an inferior to her lay imprisoned. The
			draconian closing her eyes at that final sloppy burble sounding from
			her sack and redoubling her stroking yet again until with a growl she
			climaxes and lets you loose. Your form splattering up from her tip in
			hefty arcing blasts of draconian cum to stain the ground in front of
			her. The triumphant draconian who'd conquered you so opening her eyes
			slowly and smiling as she feels her orgasm tapering off, the last few
			wads of former explorer splatting into the heaping puddle of thick
			white goo "you know, i think i prefer you this way." she says and
			then laughs "draconian cum is a good look for you." she taunts your
			departing memory and then takes to the air, a few sweeps of her wings
			and she's gone.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submitCV">
		<text>
			Sometimes, its best to acknowledge you're beaten..and that perhaps all you'll
			amount to is a good time for a powerful predator. And besides, the
			gentle churnings of her hot cum around you are somewhat relaxing, you
			get comfortable inside her balls knowing there's no escape from her
			superior sack. The draconian feels you get comfortable and chuckles
			"that's it, no your place cockfood..." she remarks and gives her sack
			a pat before gently settling down into a seated position. Her thighs
			spread wide around the bulge made by her bloated balls as she fondles
			herself and leisurely melts you down. The slow simmering churn of her
			balls around you making hot gooey sensations seep into your flesh as
			you feel her pat and rub now and then but otherwise feel her just
			enjoy your submission and your slow melting inside her balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CVsubmitGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CVsubmitGO">
		<text>
			The digestion is long, drawn out, but after a while when the draconian
			reaches down and presses she feels you squish and yield under her
			palm "mhmm, nearly done." she remarks and then starts to masturbate
			with a bit more earnestness. The draconian starting to stroke off as
			she feels your form entirely soft and gooey in her balls, barely
			holding together as a semi solid and semi aware mass of thick goo.
			The draconian's stroking hands causing rthythmic tugs and tensings of
			her sack around you, steadily squishing away the contours and lumps
			your form makes pushing out her sack. The draconian hearing a series
			of burbles from her balls and exclaiming her rising delight as the
			last of you melts away, sloshed into oblivion by her hungry balls you
			spread out to be indistinguishable from her cum moments before she
			wastes you on the ground. the Draconian's climax sending gushes of
			you out to form a jizzy pile of gooey nutbatter as she cries out in
			pleasure. When her orgasm is over only a pile of cum and her still
			slightly fattened balls remain to mark your existence "white looks
			good on you." she remarks with a chuckle and then gets to her feet,
			spreading her wings and taking flight well satisfied with this
			excursion.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
			"An ignoble fate is fitting for a small thing such as you." she says
			with a smirk and grabs your shoulder, roughly hauling you up into a
			seated position, she looks down at you over her shoulder as she turns
			around, her magnificent ass filling your vision as you feel the
			strength of her tail curling around your body "mhmm, yes..." she says
			seeing the look of comprehension in your eyes, then dismissively
			turns her gaze away "in there." she says and then leans backwards,
			your defeated form no match for her domination as she holds you in
			place and begins to encompass you. Those soft curvaceous asscheeks
			parting around your head. The hot smothering heat of her bowels
			starting to engulf you as she slides your head up into her ass with a
			moan.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="dominated and devoured" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			"mhmm yes...you belong there, sliding into me in shame." she groans in
			delight, wriggling her hips as she starts to squat down over you.
			Your upper body beginning to slide up her ass as she forces you into
			her clenching hole. The sweltering heat of her innards squeezing over
			your shoulders, then chest as you plunge into the pungent ridged grip
			of her rippling bowels. Her tail no longer around you as your arms
			are forced firmly against your sides by her cheeks "can you feel it
			weakling? this is strength, and it has you now" she says and slides a
			hand along her hip and flank, giving her feasting rear a pat and
			clenching to drag you deeper inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2" text="forced in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
			The draconian seems to delight in her power over you as she draws you
			deeper and deeper into herself, engulfing your body down to your
			waist. The draconian then straightens her legs and leaning forwards
			as you clutch at the rim of her rear end, your feet dangling in the
			air as your legs protrude from her ass. The draconian smirks for a
			moment as you try and pull back out, letting you think yourself to be
			resisting her before a rolling schlorp drags your hands past her
			rumpcheeks. no resistance possible now as the draconian clenches
			rthythmically, each time drawing more of your legs into her. Your
			legs steadily disappearing until your feet vanish entirely into her
			ass "another inferior finds their proper and fitting place...resist
			or accept the inevitable weakling, there's no escape from me now."
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleAV" text="defiance!" />
		<choice destination="submitAV" text="acceptance" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleAV">
		<text>
			You attempt to shove your way back out of her bowels before she can draw
			you up into her belly, an effort that seems initially to just amuse
			your predatory captor as she stretches wings spread, and gives you an
			indulgently condescending pat on the bulge you're making in her with
			your form "mhmm squirm all you like, you're not getting back out.
			don't worry though, it is the aspiration of all lesser beings to
			become something greater than they are." she says with a moan as you
			begin your escape attempt.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheckAV" text="attempt to escape" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheckAV">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="struggleEscapeAV" />
		<outcome destination="struggleDigestAV" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleEscapeAV">
		<text>
			Despite her taunts and smug decrees you set to struggling out of her with a
			will, attempting to worm backwards you shove your hands out against
			the insides of her guts to try and get the leverage to force yourself
			out against the flow of the ripples drawing you deeper inside. And
			despite all odds you seem to make headway, the draconian's smug
			complacency serving your purposes as she doesn't clench to squeeze
			and drag you back deeper inside. Making progress the draconian moans
			softly from the sensations but doesn't realize you're worming out
			until your feet are shoving back out through her sphincter. The
			sensation of you starting to wriggle free despite her power surprises
			her "oh you impertinent, get back in there." she exclaims and
			squeezes, but a moment too late as your hands slide out to grasp the
			inside of her ring and this time hold firm allowing you to resist her
			efforts and finally pull free and gasping onto the ground. The
			draconian seems momentarily too incensed to respond to this
			occurence, but her reaction won't last long and you best get clear
			unless you fancy her shoving you back up into her ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>


	<page ID="struggleDigestAV">
		<text>
			Despite her taunts and smug decrees you set to struggling out of her with a
			will, attempting to worm backwards you shove your hands out against
			the insides of her guts to try and get the leverage to force yourself
			out against the flow of the ripples drawing you deeper inside. And
			despite all odds you seem to make headway, the draconian's smug
			complacency serving your purposes as she doesn't clench to squeeze
			and drag you back deeper inside. Making progress the draconian moans
			softly from the sensations but doesn't realize you're worming out
			until your feet are shoving back out through her sphincter. The
			sensation of you starting to wriggle free despite her power surprises
			her "oh you impertinent, get back in there." she exclaims and
			squeezes, overwhelming you easily with a rippling rolling schlorp of
			her anal passage. your feet sliding back inside her as she clenches
			her cheeks and lowers her tail, straightening up and smirking "I'll
			punish you for that, i think a good digestive stay in my belly will
			do you good." she says as she squeezes you up through her innards,
			rubbing her belly as your helpless form is fed up into her stomach
			"of course, i was going to do that anyway." she says with a lopsided
			grin and chuckles, settling down on the ground, no way out for you
			now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleDigestAVGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleDigestAVGO">
		<text>
			The draconian mhmms softly as she rubs over her belly, indulgently
			stroking the bulge you make as you start to succumb. Despite your
			struggles there seems to be no way of forcing your way out of her
			gurgling belly, that steaming fleshy cauldron pressing all over you
			and steadily grinding you down into mush. The relentless power of her
			innards working you over until your struggles still and fade to
			whimper, and then to fluid glorps, and finally to stillness as you're
			entirely liquidated. The draconian contently dozing, smug in her
			belief none would dare disturb her, and soon even the bulge you make
			in her fades away. The draconian smirking softly as her tummy
			flattens and her booty fattens with the last of you "Mhmm, assfat is
			the best use for weaklings such as you." she says and chuckles before
			taking to the air, the draconian undefeated and supreme.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submitAV">
		<text>
			You consider struggling as you slide slowly up through her innards
			towards the digestive doom that awaits you in her gut. But then
			realize, you are truly an inferior as she sees you to be, and the
			best you can accomplish is to add to the curves of your better. The
			draconian headtilts as she feels your movements slow, as you writhe
			and rub at her insides and wormyourself into her "what are you
			doing?" she seems puzzled, but then mhmms and her face breaks out
			into a delighted grin "mhmm, submitting to me at last are we
			weakling? good...good." she says and gets comfortable "become one
			with me." she murmurs as she half lids her eyes and feels you
			gradually ease up into her belly, where your inferior form will break
			down in order to feed that of your superior and devourer.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitAVGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitAVGO">
		<text>
			The draconian mhmms and patpats the bulge you make as you submit to her
			body. Your form entirely contained within her belly now as it gurgles
			and sloshes slowly, your rubbing out against her hands helping her
			work you down and making her chuckle indulgently. Gradually your
			surrender to the draconian becomes more than will and a matter of
			physicality as she breaks you down. Your form softening and
			diminishing, your movements weakening and going still as you become a
			part of the voracious and magnificent draconian. Soon enough nought
			remains of you except a slight pudge around her middle, her round gut
			having turned smooth and shrunk down. All that you are and were now
			going on to fuel the draconian, her smile as she gets up all the more
			satisfied "If only all inferiors would accept their place like you,
			you look good on me weakling." she says with a glance down at her
			curves, then takes to the skies.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<gameover ID="gameover">
		<text>
			It would seem you've met a terrible fate
		</text>

	</gameover>

</Conversation>