<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The zetamorph is sprawled out on her back after her defeat at your
			hands. Staring up at you but too weak from the drubbing to put up
			much resistance, she's not entirely displeased by being at your mercy
			though if that thick length of blue cock at halfmast between her legs
			is any indication.
		</text>

		<choice destination="blowjob0" text="that's a tastey cock" />
		<choice destination="sex0" text="I could go for a fuck">

		</choice>
		<choice destination="Pcockvore0" text="cockvore her">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="meal0" text="actually, all of her looks tastey">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="she should submit to my loins">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/zetamorph.xml" />	
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="zetamorph" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="not interested right now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Pcockvore0">
		<text>
			The zeta desired to use you to feed her lust, it's only fitting now
			you are the victor that you do the same to her. The Zeta's eyes
			follow your hands as you get yourself ready
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				by baring your organ
			</conditional>
			and stroke yourself to hardness. Your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			growing before her eyes and swiftly growing past anything usual and
			her eyes widen. The Zeta squirming about on the floor weakly to try
			and wiggle away as you smirk and drop into a squat and grab ahold of
			her feet, shoving them into your tip. The pleasure of this mighty
			alien monster's calves sliding into your shaft, rubbing and
			stretching out the inside of your length makes you shiver and makes
			the flushing zeta squirm all the more. But she can't escape, not now,
			you've beaten her and now..now she's gonna end up a batch of lusty
			fluid and there isn't anything she can do about it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Pcockvore1" text="feed her in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Pcockvore1">
		<text>
			The zeta starts to struggle even as her cock twitches and her skin
			flushes with arousal at the fate you have in store for her. Your
			ravenous cock starting to gobble up the mighty alien's body inch by
			inch, schlurping up her legs and towards her hips. The sensations
			coaxing you on to stroke over your cock, feeling it bulging out
			around the zeta's legs and hearing her hiss and squirm as you
			encompass her own mighty erection with the voracious tip of your
			hungry shaft. The zeta makes an effort to grab ahold of the surface
			beneath her and pull away, claws digging in to tug her a few inches
			out of your voracious cock. The defiant alien gasping and looking at
			you, but then shuddering as you smirk and pull her back in, rubbing
			her shaft against the inside of your own in a way that makes her
			spasm and hiss and almost blow. You watch her reaction, and despite
			it all she makes the same attempt again..and as you pull her hips
			back into your cock the sensation is too much for her, the Zeta
			shuddering and gasping and hissing as she spasms and stains her belly
			and breasts with jizz. The zeta's erupting cock soon disappearing
			into your tip as you swallow her up with your shaft, drawing her in
			as she's too dazed from her orgasm to resist you at the moment.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Pcockvore2" text="finish her!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Pcockvore2">
		<text>
			Only a bit of her left to go when she recovers from her afterglow enough
			to struggle. But your swift unopposed schlurping has left her with
			your cock around her chest, her big alien tits squeezing and pressing
			into your tip as she squirms about wonderfully. that muscular body
			pressing and rubbing against the inside of your shaft as you finish
			claiming her breasts, bulging your tip out with them, then work up
			over her shoulders and head. Only her clawed fighting arms are left
			protruding up over her head now as you schlurp her down into your
			balls. Those claws briefly clutching at your cocktip afore being
			schlurped in as well, her form struggling about wonderfully as she's
			squeezed and crammed down your shaft and into your balls. Your
			stroking hands feeling over her contained form every inch of the way
			until she's naught but a massive set of lumpy bulges and contours
			making your balls sag and sway and shift about. The zeta uttering
			muffled hisses of dismay as she's drenched in your sticky cum and
			squirms to try and escape this oh so gooey fate.
		</text>
		<choice destination="Pcockvore3" text="grand finale" />
	</page>

	<page ID="Pcockvore3">
		<text>
			You feel over your sack for a few moments, possessively rubbing hot
			cum into the squirming zeta and letting her know just how much you're
			enjoying this. And how thoroughly yours she is as ballfodder. The
			zeta letting out a muffled gasping hiss followed by a moaning sound
			as your balls get to work on burbling and churning her down. The zeta
			struggling against the sloshy cumbath she's marinating inside and
			inevitably starting to succumb. Your hands shifting to your cock,
			jerking off your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft as your massively bloated and swollen balls jostle and sway.
			But gradually, with exquisite slowness and commendable dedication on
			the part of your zeta cockmeal the mighty alien starts liquidating.
			Your balls slowly settling, the struggling motions weakening and
			going still, the lumpy bumps and outlines of the zeta losing sharp
			definition and turning soft and round. In the end only a round plump
			bloated sack remains, your hefty balls swollen with gallons of thick
			and gooey seed..a sensation that's so toe curlingly wonderful it sets
			you onto the edge along with that insistent pressure of all that
			eager spooge inside your nuts wanting to get out. From such a
			position its little wonder you spill over the edge entirely, gasping
			out as you in turn spill sloshy creamy white liquid zeta all over the
			floor. Hot gushes of thick gooey cum blasting up out of your dick to
			hit the floor in gloopy splats, each one piling up on the puddle
			forming a low heap of gloopy thick cum out of the zetamorph. You find
			this new form of zeta rather more agreeable as your cock trails off
			with a final dribble splat of cum that gushes onto the pile afore the
			remainder oozes out to form a dribbling splat at your feet...much,
			much better. And there's a certain thrill to overpowering and
			dominating these mighty zetamorphs that only amplifies the pleasures
			of what you've just experienced.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>


	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			you study the zetamorph extensively, your scans collecting a large
			amount of data. When you're done you're left with a large amount of
			data on zetamorphs to try and further refine and no zetamorph. But
			such is the price one must pay for SCIENCE.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="zetamorph" group="liforms0"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob0">
		<text>
			The Zeta looks curious as you kneel down between her thighs, taking her
			cock in one hand and stroking it to hardness. She lets out a
			delighted gasp as you lean in to lick at her tip, lapping at the
			flesh of her shaft as it grows thick and rather impressively large in
			front of you. Her erection soon at full mast under your stroking
			hands, her tip oozing a bit of precum as you admire it from its dark
			blue tip to the pale blue of her heavy balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="blowjob1" text="start sucking" />
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="this cock looks hungry">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>

	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob1">
		<text>
			You lower your head and the zeta lowers her lids, feeling as you
			encompass her cock with the warmth of your mouth and start to bob.
			The musky flavour of her pre spilling into your mouth making you
			massage her sack needily, your other hand stroking up and down her
			thick cock as you suck her off. Her hissing moans of delight serving
			to encourage you, until soon the cocktip is pushing through the
			entrance of your throat letting you take more and more of her thick
			length with each bob. Until with each thrust her cock is massaged by
			the tightness of your throat and your nose is nestled against her
			crotch, you can feel her pleasure building, her balls tensing as that
			cock throbs in your mouth..
		</text>
		<choice destination="blowjob2swallow" text="swallow" />
		<choice destination="blowjob2spray" text="dont swallow" />
	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob2swallow">
		<text>
			As you feel her tense and hear her gasps getting more lustful you sense
			what's cumming and inhale that length. squeezing her sack with one
			hand as you feel her push over the edge and erupt, pulsing her first
			shot down your throat. You pull up and off slowly, easing the cock
			into your mouth so you can taste her delicious cum, letting the tip
			pop free just before the final spurt to stain your cheek with her
			seed. Giving you something to wipe off and lick off the back of your
			hand as you look down at the softening cock of the gasping and
			panting zetamorph.
		</text>
			<special effect="healnpc" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="tastey" />

	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob2spray">
		<text>
			As you feel her tense and hear her gasps getting more lustful you
			pull back. Both hands vigorously stroking that cock as it pops free
			of your lips. Her shuddering hip spasm and cry heralding her climax
			as she jets hot cum over your face and chest.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				staining your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				with hot and sticky jizz.
			</conditional>
			The cock subsiding in unsteady gouts of cum until spent, her orgasm
			now staining your front as she looks down in lustful satisfaction at
			your state.
		</text>
			<special effect="healnpc" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="the mess was worth it" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			This cock seems hungry, so why not feed it? and what better food is
			to hand than yourself?
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				you get up in order to strip down taking off your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				and setting it aside before continuing, suitably naked and easy to
				schlurp down.
			</conditional>
			your caressing hands slide up to tease at her tip. And the zeta's
			eyes widen before with a smile you thrust your hand into her tip,
			feeling the hot precum ooze up around your wrist as it sinks in. The
			Zeta looking surprised at your actions..but as you wriggle around
			your hand you feel her cock clench and ripple, sucking on your hand
			and take that as more than permission to continue.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="time to feed this cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You raise your other hand, striking a dive pose as you insert it as well
			into her cock. The zeta letting out a gasp, and bucking her hips
			upwards schlurping your forearms in. as her arse settles back to the
			floor you find her cock snugly grips your arms such that you're
			pulled down with them, not an inch of you being relinquished by her
			dick..which suits you just fine, a duck of your head and a thrust
			forwards helps feed more of you, plunging into her cock and having
			the wonderful scents and throb of that hungry alien erection ooze and
			pulse around your head. The Zeta writhing in bliss as her cock bulges
			out around you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The zeta moans, overwhelmed by the surprising pleasure as you feed
			yourself to her cock. That shaft rippling around your upper body,
			schlurping, rippling and easily accepting as you push off the ground
			and lean forwards to feed more of yourself into that bulging dick.
			The zeta hardly having to work for her cockfood as you cram your
			chest and then hips past the squeelching stretched tip of her dick.
			You're piling into her balls now, pushing into them and swelling them
			out as you feed yourself to her balls and sate them with your body.
			Gradually your legs disappear into her tip, her cock upending and
			throbbing, bulging around your thighs and calves as you tug them
			inside. With a final tug you're all the way in, your legs sliding
			down to join you in her balls..bathing in her hot seed and ready to
			experience what comes next.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="time to get melted" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			The zeta reaches a hand down to fondle her sack, another stroking her
			cock as you get comfortable inside her balls. She mhmms feeling your
			own hands stroking from within, but now comes the time for all good
			cockfood to be melted into nutbatter. The zeta's bulging balls
			starting to burble and churn around you, your form weakening and
			liquefying blissfully in her hot balls. Your ability to rub and
			massage her sack from the inside steadily being curtailed as you melt
			away and take your place as her cum. Her balls rounding out as your
			solid form diminishes down to nothing, rendered down into nothing but
			gallons of nutbatter churning in her sack as she masturbates.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreGO" text="churn" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoreGO">
		<text>
			The Zeta perhaps did not expect her defeat at your hands to end with her
			balls nicely full of your liquidated form. But she cannot fault the
			result, moaning as she bucks her hips upwards and jerks off, feeling
			her pleasure grow. Her need to cum a steady pressure from her bloated
			sack until finally with a cry she erupts. Your remains arcing up only
			to rain down upon her, painting her blue form with sticky white goo.
			The zeta's cum coating her belly, her breasts, her chest, your form
			getting up close and personal with her own one final time. Alas all
			good things come to an end and even a willing cockmeal like yourself
			can only give the zeta so much jizz to spurt out, the final blast of
			cum landing in her open mouth before she lets out a sigh and slumps
			back, sprawling amidst what once was you in a dazed afterglow.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				After swiftly stripping out of your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
			</conditional>
			you kneel down to caress her cock, stroking the zeta's length to
			hardness as she hisses softly in delight before you clamber atop her.
			Some might see this as rape, but with so magnificent a cock as part
			of the spoils of your victory is it really so wrong. The Zeta lets
			out a shuddering moan as you grind against her thick blue cock,
			marking it with the stain of your moist nethers, teasing her as you
			place both hands on her alien tits and prepare to enjoy your ride.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="time to ride" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			Your hips slide up and forwards, then down and back and your pleasure is
			uttered in stereo with the sounds of the zeta as you sheathe her cock
			deep within your nethers. That thickness stretching you out as you
			push down to feel her balls against your mound. From there it's a
			simple thing to start riding that cock in earnest, the alien gasping
			and moaning even as she's being taken and used for your pleasure like
			this. Her hands kept restrained as you bounce to enjoy that thickness
			within your snatch sliding in and out and clench on it periodically
			to remind her whose boss.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="cum inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			Truly its a wonderful feeling cock, and why not have it cum inside. One
			does want the whole experience of taking and claiming that alien dick
			after all. With your passions running so high you let the zeta grasp
			your rear and grope your body as you ride her cock ever faster,
			feeling her cock throbbing within you with impending climax making
			you ride for a few more strokes and then shove your hips down,
			clenching around her cock as she climaxes. Your own pleasure not long
			to peak after, her hot jizz jetting up into you from her spurting
			cock as she lets out a cry that brings a smile to your face. Well
			satisfied in having put her to good use.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockTF0" text="she has a really comfy lap">
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="much better now" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockTF0">
		<text>
			Her lap is comfy enough to let you linger in afterglow. Feeling that
			cock still nestled deep inside you as a spreading wonderful heat as
			the tingles of your pleasure die down and the Zeta smiles, perhaps
			accepting your place in relation to her now. Though as you smile
			dreamily back and she smiles a bit more you sense something amiss,
			wriggling your hips to find them..constrained, joined to her crotch
			as the first hints of blue appear on your skin. You look back to the
			alien and see her grin all the more, and all you can do in response
			as you realize you've been trapped is spit out the precum that's
			suddenly welled up into your mouth.
		</text>
		<choice destination="embraceTF1" text="accept the changes" />
		<choice destination="resistTF1" text="no, i don't want to be a cock!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="embraceTF1">
		<text> Her goal is clear. She's getting her own back for you taking
			advantage of her by making you her magnificent cock...what a
			wonderful gift. The zeta seems surprised as you lean in and kiss her
			full on the lips, not expecting you to take it this way. She reaches
			up to stroke one hand along your back, her moan mingling with your
			own as blue veiny flesh overtakes your body making it more and more
			sensitive to her caress. Your own hands sliding down to your legs,
			reaching behind yourself to feel them curling up underneath you,
			going boneless..round, becoming the alien's balls to better make her
			seed. Sensing the change needily flowing up your arms though you
			oblige in putting them against your sides. Her hands caressing over
			your arms until they sink into your flanks as if moulding you into
			your new form.
		</text>
		<choice destination="embraceTF2" text="turn into her cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="embraceTF2">
		<text>
			You're turning more and more into her cock now. almost entirely your body
			has been overtaken by the blue hued veiny appearance of her alien
			erection. you're an armless torso with your legs now just her fertile
			sack it wont be long and such makes you moan in anticipation, the
			last sound you can manage as your lungs devolve and join the rest of
			your torso in being reshaped into her cockflesh. Her hands stroking
			over you possessively, and are you not all hers? well soon you will
			be, your neck flows out and upwards, rolls of foreskin sliding up
			over your face as you feel all four of her hands now working up and
			down your body. The last vestiges of your independence vanishing as
			your expression is subsumed under her foreskin and then subsumed into
			the flesh of her cocktip.
		</text>
		<choice destination="acceptTFGO" text="your new life as an alien cock" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="acceptTFGO" noReform="true">
		<text>
			The zetamorph moans and gasps as she peels the foreskin of her new cock
			back to reveal the dark purple of her glans. Shuddering in bliss as
			she revels in claiming you as her shaft and prepares to consummate
			her new relationship with said dick. Her hands stroking vigorously,
			masturbating that thickness. Your own self consumed by the pleasure,
			twitching as it floods through you and erupts. Her orgasm spurting
			out of your sideways lips, bliss becoming all of your being. As the
			zeta comes down from her orgasm and recovers she gets to her feet,
			looking at her heavy cock and running a hand along her new addition
			as it softens. While she might of intended to punish you for taking
			advantage of her, it seems rewarding you has worked out just as well!
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="resistTF1">
		<text>
			No, you're not going to end up a mere body part. You're not going to end
			up a mere organ dangling between her legs! you resolve to resist,
			shoving your hands down at her hips and pushing away, attempting to
			pull off her cock before it can remake you in its own image. The tug
			making you wince and the zeta hiss as you pull against her and try to
			yank the join apart. But to no avail and as you shift this way and
			that trying to unanchor yourself you find you can't pull your hands
			from her hips, they're sinking into her flesh and shifting closer to
			your arse before your horrified eyes. The Zeta grinning all the more
			as you look back up to her, there's no escape. She's going to make
			you into cockmeat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="resistTF2" text="struggle against the inevitable" />
	</page>

	<page ID="resistTF2">
		<text>
			Even now you struggle, as your legs clump up uselessly beneath
			your...your base. You try to squirm away from where you're fusing to
			her crotch as if it would mean something. But all it seems to do is
			making the Zeta moan and lean back, watching as blue veiny flesh
			overtakes you in a steadily rising flow. In its wake your body is
			becoming less motile, muscles and bones alike turning into dick meat
			held firm only by the pulse of the alien who is claiming all of you
			for her own benefit. A nice bit of turnabout for your earlier deeds
			that she's clearly enjoying a great deal, your arms sink into your
			sides and your legs burble round and testicular and full of seed. It
			won't be long now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="resistTF3" text="struggle to the end" />
	</page>

	<page ID="resistTF3">
		<text>
			You're nearly unrecognizable now, only your head left. And as you try to
			resist the change pulsing through you and shift your head this way
			and that you find your view steadily constrained, the last you see of
			the Zeta her delighted smirk before you feel her hands on you and
			your gaze is forced upwards. Your head and shoulders transforming
			now, simplifying into the sensitive bell of her glans as all you can
			taste is her pre and all you can see is the gloom of the ceiling.
			Even that sight is worth cherishing, resisting as the change flows up
			over your eyes, keeping them open until finally the urge to blink is
			overwhelming..and your eyes are no more, lids stuck together
			subsuming as the last vestiges of your former appearance is wiped
			away. In darkness all you can do is hear and feel, feel as she uses
			your sensitive flesh for her own pleasure..rubbing her hands over
			your body, her cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="resistTFGO" text="claimed as cock" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="resistTFGO" noReform="true">
		<text>
			You feel her get to her feet and put her hands on you, treating you just
			like what you are now as her pleasure builds making you shudder and
			twitch under her stroking palms. Her cock, all hers, claimed,
			reshaped...forever. The Zeta lets out a cry and you feel yourself
			erupt, her cum pumping through your helpless form, a mere conduit for
			her delight. Her climax rolling through you, making it hard to think,
			hard not to just give in. You're a mere tool of her pleasure now, and
			she makes that clear by making sure to stroke the last drops of cum
			out of you as her orgasm subsides and she smirks down at her length,
			all that you are now. Your form unable to resist as you soften and
			turn flaccid between her thighs like a good cock. It's clear the zeta
			has more than gotten even for how you took advantage of her, you used
			her dick, now she's using you AS her dick.
		</text>
	</gameover>


	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			All of her looks tastey and you want all of her inside you.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				but first you undress so as not to strain your attire with the
				bulges that this alien is soon to be.
			</conditional>
			Not to be satisfied with merely her cock you seize her feet, she
			looks down past her cock at you in perplexity. But your intent
			rapidly becomes clear as you place those feet together and squeeze
			them past your lips, making it clear you plan to turn this dangerous
			and powerful alien monster girl into nothing more than your meal. Her
			eyes widening as you swallow, tugging her feet into your mouth and
			starting to encroach up her legs. She tries to struggle, but her
			blows are easily fended off, slow and weak in her defeated state
			she's truly just the spoils of victory..to be savoured, claimed, and
			digested. She lets out distressed hisses and instead tries to grab
			ahold of the floor, even as you engulf her legs almost entirely and
			settle into a seated position to make room for the growing bulge in
			your belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1" text="gobble her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			You swallow, weakly at first but then with increasing insistence. Her
			claws gripping the floor steadily weakening, and then
			yielding..loosing her grip her middle is swiftly claimed in one
			hungry gulp, her arms forced above her head as you work her chest
			inside. Tongue savouring the blueskinned alien meal as you eat her
			alive, her head following soon after leaving those four arms to be
			schlurped up. Your belly growing massive and jostling about, her form
			struggling within you, well defined and moving in a way that's just
			delightful in its futility as you gulp in her arms and seal her away
			entirely. All yours, claimed by your triumph and then by your hunger
			she cannot escape from your innards despite the power of her
			formidable form. And she's providing the satisfying fullness of a big
			meal all while putting up her resistance to boot.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal2" text="digest her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal2">
		<text>
			She struggles, but you have her right where you want her as your
			belly gurgles and groans. That alien form thrashing about but
			steadily being squeezed and pressed down on, forced to submit to your
			stomach muscles and enzymes. It seems to take a while to really and
			truly show her who the superior being is, but eventually her muscles
			are tired and digesting and she can no longer struggle. And indeed, a
			while after that she succumbs completely, your belly losing its tight
			definition and rounding out as the gurgles it makes become more
			pronounced. Her form steadily liquidating until that dome is
			perfectly round and shrinking under your hands. The mighty zetamorph,
			now merely a mighty big meal as all that she was becomes nourishment
			to keep you going.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				as your gut shrinks down sufficiently you start to redress and
			</conditional>
			soon your gut only has a trace of bulge leftover from your meal.
			Certainly not enough to impair your adventures.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			Yes, its time to show this alien whose nethers are the superior here.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Pausing only to undress
			</conditional>
			you bestride her shoulders and reach down, hauling her face up to
			meet your netherlips. She seems uncertain as you mash her nose
			against your slit but soon gets what she thinks is the idea,
			inexpertly servicing you with her tongue. It's a good thing you want
			more than just her tongue really, you let her carry on for just a
			little bit..then curl your hand behind her head and push her in. The
			Zeta letting out a startled hiss that's swiftly muffled as her face
			slides in with a schlorp from your sex and a moan from you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="show her whose boss" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			You feel her begin to struggle, though she's still weakened by her
			defeat you don't waste time in forcing your sex down over her
			shoulders. Her primary and secondary arms pinned against her sides
			and back, restraining her as you force her up into your loins.
			Rendered unable to meaningfully resist she's forced to submit to your
			loins, to the heat and clenching tightness of your sex around her
			formidable body. A glance down gives you ample evidence of the zeta's
			arousal, despite the ignoble fate forced upon her her body is rising
			to the occasion and primal groans are heard amidst the protests of
			the squirming Zeta.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="force her inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
		<text>
			She struggles, but she's no match for the supremacy of your loins as you
			draw her up and in. Her breasts squezing past your snatch as you
			squat down over her, then straighten up hauling her own ass in line
			beneath your hips so you can force more of her inside. Her squirming
			form now starting to bulge out your middle as she's packed into your
			womb, its soft and yielding snugness holding her dangerous form
			rather easily. Another squat down forces her in down to her ass, her
			arousal next to squeeze in as you straighten up and clench schlurping
			her thighs in. Only her legs and tail left now and those are soon to
			disappear as you run a hand over your middle, feeling the vast
			distension growing as all of her is packed away steadily inside you.
			Within a few moments more her tailtip and toeclaws are packed away
			between your legs up and up into your depths. Her body squirming
			around as she hisses in protest at this debauched domination, and
			perhaps in fear of what's to come.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth3" text="liquidate her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth3">
		<text>
			A little thrill goes through you feeling her pushing out against the
			inside of your womb. And you let your eyes slip half lid as you
			stroke one hand over a middle and the other down between your legs.
			Stroking your victorious nethers to the sensation of her helplessly
			dominated and contained within you, the mighty and lusty zeta...now
			just pleasurefuel for your use. Her hissing and snarling protests
			gain a desperate tone and her struggles redouble as your womb presses
			around her and she feels your lust starting to claim and overtake her
			body..</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth4" text="keep going" />
	</page>
	<page ID="unbirth4">
		<text>
			Helplessly the zeta is stewing her away her hisses and snarls turn to gasps,
			moans and whimpers and then finally sloshes and glorps as you melt
			her down and masturbate to the sensation. The Zeta mass turning from
			lumpy and bulgey to smooth and compact..and finally you reach
			completion, the Zeta emerging as you cry out, a gush of fluid
			splattering the floor beneath you. That mighty body now much reduced
			but still ample in her volume, both of the sound of gushing and
			splattering and the sheer amount of femmecum forming a puddle now
			beneath you. Finally you fade into panting, shuddering in afterglow
			and eyeing your handiwork. Claws and plates and all the zeta was no
			match for being melted in your womb, not a trace remains but for a
			blueish tinge to your fluids.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

</Conversation>