<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The zetamorph mhmms and strokes her already hard cock at your approach,
			flushed a slightly purple hue with arousal as her tail sways and she
			eyes you lustfully. Her libido is yours to command now you've gotten
			her horny.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF0" text="get screwed">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<!-- <choice destination="sexH0" text="bend her over"> <assertion evaluate="haspart" 
			part="penis"/> </choice> -->
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="cockvore her">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="CTF0" text="get cocked">
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
			<assertion evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/zetamorph.xml" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cocker0" text="cock her">
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockmerging" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/zetamorph.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="zetamorph" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="not interested right now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			you
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				disrobe swiftly before
			</conditional>
			grasping your firming cock in one hand and the head of the zeta in
			the other, mashing her against your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft as it grows to full hardness. You continue grinding her face
			against your length as it grows still larger in a way she well knows
			the meaning of, the zeta shuddering as you shift to grind the pliant
			cummy tip of your cock against her face..a hissing croon heard afore
			she pulls back and looks up at you..flushed and panting, some small
			part of her resisting as you look down at her...and part your tip.
			You show her the inside of your cock, the dark tunnel down to your
			waiting balls.. letting her drink in the invitation, the demand, that
			she submit to your seductive wiles and be what you wish her to
			be...and slowly, with a growling groan, she leans forwards..lips
			mashing wetly against your cocktip afore she starts to press inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="take her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You groan in pleasure as the alien submits to your cock. Her foursome of
			arms tucking and curling against herself as she succumbs to your
			wiles, your allure, and the ravenous hunger of your loins. The
			thought makes you shudder, thrusting your hips forwards. Your cock
			schlurping and squeezing around her shoulders, pinning her arms
			against her. Your tip butting against the ample curves of her breasts
			making her muffledly croon from inside your shaft, hot precum
			flooding around her as she reaches down to desperately stroke herself
			off. The zeta trying to wriggle forwards, clearly so enthralled by
			your dick as she tries to squirm deeper inside. You ripple your shaft
			to help her with that, squeezing around her head and shoulders. Then
			you find that's not enough to satisfy either of you and start
			thrusting your hips again, bucking against the curves of those
			breasts and trying to squeeze them inside your tip.. and you can feel
			those bountiful round pillows begin to squeeze in, nearly,
			nearly..then with a schlurp you cram them entirely into your cock.
			The sensation is wonderful, the squeezed orbs forming a nice bulge on
			the underside of your swollen shaft as you start to work more of her
			in, working towards her hips and her own rock hard cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="take her the rest of the way" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			You can feel her head pressing against the entrance of your sack. The
			zeta writhing in your big ravenous cock as she jerks off desperately,
			lost to lust and self destructive desires. Her body spasming in a
			delightful way as her hips buck and her cock erupts, splattering the
			floor beneath her with cum. Her spasms serve though also to stimulate
			your hungry shaft and with a groan you feel it ripple and flex,
			dragging that spurting cock into your tip and squeezing it inside
			your shaft. Your balls swelling out as the blissfully orgasmic zeta
			is steadily fed down into them, tail and clawed feet swaying up in
			front of you as your cock lifts upwards and the Zeta slides down. A
			final schlurping pop audible as your cumslit seals shut behind that
			tail and your stroking hands guide the bulges of her legs down to
			join the rest of her in curling up between your legs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="churning alien nutbutter" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			The lusty yet mighty zetamorph now squirms entirely within your balls
			and while the sensation is one to savour it's possible if you linger
			too long you might be interrupted. With one hand on your sack and the
			other on your shaft you feel her writhing and crooning in your balls
			and your cock throbbing well sated in your hand. And now having
			savoured its time to move on and as you close your eyes you feel your
			balls start to churn and burble around the alien. Your other hand
			starting to stroke up and down your cock, slowly, leisurely at first,
			but steadily with more vigor as the dangerous alien in your balls
			begins to soften and melt. The zetamorph gasping, squirming and
			writhing around in your balls as she feels them press all around her.
			Then gradually her movements still and are replaced by more liquid
			sloshing and churnings as your balls round out and the zetamorph, so
			dangerous and vicious a combatant, succumbs fully to you and your
			seductive charms as she turns into sack fattening spunk. The
			sensations, the thoughts, both exquisite as your conquest compacts
			into a sticky load for you to use before erupting up and out as your
			orgasm, splattering onto the floor in a sticky gushing series of
			blasts of thick jizz. the alien's now much goopier form serving to to
			stain the floor with a testament to the superiority and supremacy of
			your shaft over her and perhaps over her entire kind.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF0">
		<text>
			It's a good looking cock, and you find yourself wanting to feel that
			big blue shaft inside yourself.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				First undressing, baring yourself entirely before her which only
				heightens her arousal.
			</conditional>
			Then taking her cock in one hand and sliding your arm around her,
			leaning up to kiss her and feel her unfamiliarly long tongue probing
			your mouth briefly. Stroking her a few moments more you start to
			guide her down with you, seating yourself, then leaning back, guiding
			her cock to your nethers as you spread your legs for her and she
			mhmms in clear consent to your desires.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF1" text="xenophilia" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF1">
		<text>
			The alien settled down over you, her true arms groping over your body as
			her claw arms come down above your head to hold her up. Your hand on
			her cock guiding that thick blue girth inside yourself, stretching
			you out as she moans atop you...sliding that thick cock inside until
			her hefty blue balls are pressing against your thighs and all of her
			is sheathed in your sex. Your legs rising up to wrap around her hips
			as she begins to thrust, working her cock in and out of your greedy
			nethers.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF2" text="harder, faster" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF2">
		<text>
			The zeta ruts you, hips thrusting vigorously back and forth between the
			embrace of your legs that stir her onto ever greater lustful feats of
			virility. Her moans issuing forth with ever greater volume as her
			pace redoubles and then redoubles again displaying remarkable amounts
			of stamina. This alien giving you the fucking you definitely needed
			as its thrusting increases in tempo and you feel your pleasure waxing
			ever stronger from the ploughing.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF3" text="climax" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF3">
		<text>
			You hear the alien screech in pleasure as she reaches her peak, pushing
			you over the edge as she thrusts hard into you and pumps hot seed
			into your body. Her thick cock spasming repeatedly, gushing spurt
			after spurt into you until she rests spent and warm atop you. Her cum
			a hot mass roiling in your womb as lays atop you, her soft breasts
			against your head for a few minutes. Only then does it seem she
			recovers and after having half smothered you under her ample rack she
			gets to her feet, pulling out of you and pushing herself up with a
			true and claw hand she looks down at you and smiles licking her lips.
			Her cock softening and carelessly dribbling cum and your sexual
			fluids down on you, you've clearly had your fun, and she's had hers.
		</text>

		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexH0">
		<text>

		</text>


	</page>

	<page ID="cocker0">
		<text>
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				quickly stripping off,
			</conditional>
			you bear your own cock before the alien, stroking your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			length to arousal as she settle down into a seated position under her
			watching gaze. Once hard you glance between her and your cock
			meaningfully and then pat your lap for emphasis.
			<conditional>
				<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="penis" partvalue="length" value="18" />
				And though she smirks naughtily at your inferior size and strokes
				her own cock to emphasize that she
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
					bodypart="penis" partvalue="length" value="18" />
				and after admiring your girth for a moment she
			</conditional>
			accepts your invitation. The large alien stepping astride your thighs
			and turning around, ample ass dominating your view as she positions
			herself. One hand on her cock and stroking it, another reaching down
			to stroke yours and guide it up under her balls and into her sex as
			she sits down atop your shaft. The alien letting out a little mhmm of
			delight and clenching around your length.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cocker1" text="show her how comfy that lap is" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cocker1">
		<text>
			The zetamorph starts to slide herself up and down in your lap, doing
			the work by riding your dick. But is startled by just how intimate
			she's about to get with you as her sex sticks against your shaft, her
			hips coming down and then unable to pull away. She lets out a
			startled cry and flushes faintly purple, glancing over her shoulder
			at you in realization. She knows how this goes, knows that you're
			going to take her body and remould it into part of your length. You
			can see the wheels turning in her head, that she can't pull away,
			she's already caught..and all she can choose is whether to struggle,
			or accept she's going to be dickmeat.. And with a moan and a lick
			over your face she does the latter, the alien grinding her ass down
			on your crotch as
			<macro id="skin_colour_desc" />
			and veiny skin begins to spread out over her dark blue rear.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cocker2" text="she'll be a great cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cocker2">
		<text>
			You run your hands over the zeta moaning in delight as she does the
			same with both her true hands and the blunt edges of her claw hands.
			More of your
			<macro id="skin_colour_desc" />
			skin overtaking her flanks and leaving her sides sensitive as a
			result, her moans suddenly interrupted with a gasping splutter as
			precum oozes up into her mouth and dribbles from her lips. Her
			insides simplifying into cockflesh as your body assimilates and
			rewrites her own. You slide you hand around to her own cock, stroking
			that raging hard erection and feeling her cum after merely a handful
			of strokes, so turned on is she at being overtaken and turned into so
			lewd a part of you. Her cock spurting cum on her breasts and face
			afore you stroke it into the erectile tissue of what was once her
			belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cocker3" text="give her what she wants" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cocker3">
		<text>
			One by one the Zetas limbs start to be overtaken by the transformation
			into your private parts. Her legs flopping and folding inwards
			towards your sack, making burbling noises as their insides convert
			and merge into your newly expanded balls. Her deadly tail starts to
			bind against her hips, merging into her segment by segment until it's
			just a prominent vein along the flanks of your new cock. The zeta
			finding herself shrinking down slightly as one by one her arms and
			claw arms stroking her sides sink into her body. As she finds herself
			unable to pleasure herself she utters a gasping moan looking up at
			you from her diminished position, desperate for you to stroke over
			her and you oblige. Your hands stroking her arms down into her flanks
			as she becomes more easily jerked off.
		</text>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="penis" variable="length" modifier="6">
			</mutation>
		</special>
		<choice destination="cocker4" text="finish it" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cocker4">
		<text>
			You feel the last changes working over her as her spluttering moans
			fade away. Her face swelling out into a cockhead for you as her eyes
			lid over and she throbs, so sensitive, so needy and lustful. She's
			everything a cock should be and as you feel her lips turn vertical
			you reach your climax, moaning as you cum through your new dick.
			Spurt after spurt gushing up through what was once a dangerous alien,
			and is now just more inches on your cock. As your orgasm subsides and
			your spurts trail off you pause to admire your length, almost
			reluctantly it starts to turn flaccid and soften between your thighs.
			Your now
			<measurement part="penis" variable="length" />
			inch cock much improved by the addition of the zetamorph, though
			perhaps if you're unsatisfied you could always claim more of them as
			inches on your dick. Thinking of that you stand, the extra weight
			down there feeling odd but oh so satisfying.
		</text>

		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get used to the new weight" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CTF0">
		<text>
			You know what she can really do with that thing, and you want her to
			do it with you. Hesitation lasts but an instant before resolve sets
			in, you want to be a part of her. You want to be her cock, grow hard
			and throbbing when she's horny and sway between her legs when she's
			not.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Eagerly you undress, not wanting anything to interfere with the
				process.
			</conditional>
			Now you just had to convince her of your desires, without
			words...grasping her cock with one hand and getting a murr from her
			before you raise your own hand to your body to trace over it. She
			watches you curious, but uncomprehending, as you trace over her tip
			and caress your face, then trace beneath the glans touching your
			neck, and steadily trace down your body and her cock as well until
			you're touching your thigh and her balls. You can see the moment when
			something clicks, her eyes widening in surprise as she reaches out to
			grope over you and cup your ass, sliding behind you even as you bend
			over and slip your hands forwards to brace against the wall.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CTF1" text="let her do it" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CTF1">
		<text>
			Her hands give either side of your rear a squeeze as she lines herself
			up. Her cocktip brushing against your sex, then pushing inside. Her
			thrust slow yet powerful, easing up forwards up against the wall as
			she groans. She starts to pump her cock in and out, and perhaps you
			worry that she didn't really understand your desires. Not just to
			feel that cock, but to become it, not receive her cum but spurt it.
			But as she thrusts in and out hot tingles spread through you, and her
			thrusts slow down again. Your sex sticking to her shaft, clamping
			down around her length, merging into her crotch as she lets out a
			long groan of pleasure. It's really happening, she's starting to
			change you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CTF2" text="changes" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CTF2">
		<text>
			You feel her veins entwining with yours, your skin turning oh so
			sensitive as she strokes her true hands over your form. Her groan and
			your moans mingling together as you start to both feel the pleasure
			of her new cock. It's enough to make you shift your hands down to
			stroke over your body as well as veins creep out from where your ass
			forms into cockbase. The zetamorph you're willingly giving yourself
			to reaching fowards to place her claw hands against the wall in place
			of your own. As you change she strokes over your arms and growls in
			pleasure as your hands stick in place against your flanks. Your legs
			also starting to feel all numb and mushy as your feet leave the floor
			leaving you entirely supported by the soon to be extra endowed
			Zetamorph.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CTF3" text="didn't need limbs anyway" />
	</page>

	<page ID="CTF3">
		<text>
			Your insides transition gradually into cockmeat, bones dissolving and
			organs simplifying to be replaced with cumtube and throbbing glory as
			your
			<macro id="skin_colour_desc" />
			skin is overtaken by the dark blue colour of the alien shaft that you
			are becoming. Her hands continue to stroke over you in increasing
			delight as your upper body becomes a throbbing cylindrical shaft and
			your legs curl up to burble as heavy balls and manufacture her seed.
			it won't be long now before you're just the dick between her legs and
			your impending loss of independence makes your head feel warm and
			fuzzy. Though that might just be the fact your skull is softening as
			the changes reach that far. Pre starting to dribble copiously from
			your lips as your face swells out, turning the dark purple of the
			zeta's glans as gradually your facial features are washed away.
		</text>
		<choice destination="CTFGO" text="cocked" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="CTFGO" noReform="true">
		<text>
			The last features that distinguish you as anything but a fat alien cock
			fade away as the zeta groans and masturbates with her new Dick. Your
			own moans trailing into a splutter and then nothing as your sideways
			lip are now to issue nothing so elevated as speech or sound. You feel
			her hands wrapped around you, stroking back and forwards in time with
			her bucking hips. Your mind awash in pleasure even as it simplifies,
			motor skills? language? you don't need those. Gradually you're
			simplified into a primal psuedo being, your needs and desires fitting
			your new role as a cock. No longer to crave independence or
			amusement, content to be soft and flaccid resting against her balls
			and thighs but ever ready for naughty play. As the last of your
			unnecessarily elevated faculties fade away you feel her reach climax,
			spurting hot cum out through you..the apex of your being, the reason
			for your existence being consummated and revealed to you as you spurt
			her seed to stain the ground then soften snugly against her warm soft
			sack. You are an alien cock, and could not imagine being any other
			way.
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			you study the zetamorph extensively, your scans collecting a large
			amount of data. When you're done you're left with a large amount of
			data on zetamorphs to try and further refine and no zetamorph. But
			such is the price one must pay for SCIENCE.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="zetamorph" group="liforms0" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>


</Conversation>