<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>




	<page ID="start">
		<!--unwilling captive -->
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="seduced"
			value="0" />
		<text>
			The mushroom mother glares at you from inside the opened containment chamber
			for a moment as she recognizes you.  Then, in what seems like the blink of an eye,
			the baleful expression vanishes, becoming an seductive smirk.  The ships computer
			blare out a biohazard warning, and you can hear the distinct sound of the ventilation
			system overclocking to filter out what is undoubtedly a surge of pheromones meant to
			seduce you.
			
			Someone's a sore loser.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0A" text="scarf her down">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="pleasure0A" text="sample her milkjugs" />
		<choice destination="loving0" text="make love to her">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="fuck0" text="fuck her tits">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<!--willing captive -->
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="seduced"
			value="1" />
		<text>
			The voluptious mushroom woman blinks tiredly as the containment chamber opens.
			Recongizing you, she smiles fondly, and began humming a gentle, happy tune.
			A soft, creamy scent fills the air.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0B" text="swallow her up">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="have sex with her">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore0A">
		<!--unwilling vore -->
		<text>
			The captive shroomgirl doesn't have a chance to overcome your
			apparent resistance to her pheromones as you open your mouth wide
			open and firmly shove her capped head inside.  She weakly struggles
			against you, her large form built for embracing a victim enthralled by
			her spores, not overpowering an apex predator fully intent on eating her!
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1A" text="eat her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1A">
		<text>
			With your hold on her solidified, you take your time to enjoy her lucious form.
			You take hold of her milk-heavy breasts, squeezing them even as you began to swallow 
			them.  The plentiful mounds slide right in, your tight throat squeezing them.  The 
			mushroom mother's hands weakly bat at you, trying in vain to fend you off.  Soon enough,
			she's unable to do even that as you finish off her breasts and began taking in her 
			soft belly.
			
			As you began to take in her hips, you tease her surprisingly moist pussy with your tongue.
			Seems your tight innards are doing their job well!  She struggles intensify as you tease her,
			but she starts to moan despite herself.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2A" text="polish her off" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2A">
		<text>
			As much as fun as teasing her is, you're here to fill your stomach, not tease the helpless
			shroom woman!  You began to take in her legs, eager groans coming from your throat.  Soon 
			enough, the last of her lucious form disappears down your throat.  Your hapless prey curls up
			in your stomach, squirming meekly.  The mushroom mother shifts tactics, whimpering slightly and
			starting to gently rub the inside of your stomach, hoping to earn mercy by pleasuring you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3A" text="Not good enough" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreEndo3A" text="Keep her as a belly pet" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3A">
		<text>
			As enthusiastic as the attempt to please you is, you're hungry, and she's food.  Simple.
			Your stomach gurgles and groans, quickly going to work on your hard earned meal.  Her squirming
			intensifies, although at this point, you can't tell if she's struggling to escape, or doubling
			down on trying to please you.

			It feels like hours, but her struggles die down in the end, and your stomach shrinks down to it's normal
			size, no trace of the former milk mother remaining.
		</text>
		<special effect="removeCaptive" />
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<choice destination="end" text="delicious, just what you needed" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreEndo3A">
		<text>
			You decide to enjoy the Mushroom Mother's attentions.  You start to softly rub
			your stomach with one hand, groping at the mushroom woman inside.  Encouraged
			by the distinct lack of digestion going on, her rubbing picks up, and her
			frightened whimpers turn into affectionate coos.

			Her movements become less eratic, more deliberate.  She nuzzles into your rubs,
			doing her best to earn your favor.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreEndo4A" text="hold her for a bit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreEndo4A">
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="nice" value="1" />
		<text>
			Time goes on, and the mushroom mother starts to prod at the entrance
			to your stomach.  She keeps up her rubbing, but her attempts to get out
			grow more persistant.  Having better things to do anyways, it's time to let
			her out.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreEndo5A" text="regurgitation" />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvoreEndo5A">
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			The Mushroom mother finds herself forced upwards and out of her tight
			confinement.  She looks at you with a confused expression for a moment,
			but quickly molds it into a mask of endearment.  If you peer closely,
			you can still see the wariness in her eyes.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreEndo5A">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			The Mushroom mother finds herself forced upwards and out of her tight
			confinement.  She looks back at you with a light blush, with a hesitant
			expression you haven't seen before.  Shyly, she reaches a hand out to
			touch your belly.  Then, she gently pulls you into a hug, rubbing her cheek
			against you.

			She withdraws, smiling and giggling happily at you.  Seems like you've finally
			won her over.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="return your new fan to containment" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0B">
		<!--willing vore,head first -->
		<text>
			The mushroom mother giggles happily as she recognizes the hunger in your
			eyes, and she offers her head willingly.  You teasingly lick her face,
			and place a kiss on her massive chest.  She moans softly, gropping your
			rear and humming softly.
			
			Then, you open your mouth wide open and wrap your lips around her head.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1B" text="swallow" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1B">
		<text>
			Your pet shroom mother moans eagerly as you take in her head, pushing herself
			further down your throat.  Her breasts leak her sweet cream.  You waste no time
			taking in her breasts, enjoying the warm milk dripping out into your mouth.

			You can see her fingering herself lightly as you take in her belly.  Her hips follow
			soon after, you gulp them down, licking at her every inch of the way.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2B" text="gulp down the eager woman" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2B">
		<text>
			Her lovely, motherly hips secured in your throat, you hurry up and take in her
			legs.  She groans loudly, bringing herself to climax as your tight innards rub
			her curvy body.  The mushroom mother began to curl inside your tight stomach, making
			you swell up more and more as she fills you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3B" text="polish her off" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3B">
		<text>
			You swallow down the last of her with a heary belch, tucking her away where she
			so clearly wants to be.  She coos happily as she settles in, quickly getting to
			work rubbing your innards.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4B" text="time to digest her" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreEndo4B"
			text="she's too sweet to digest, hold her inside you" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore4B">
		<text>
			It's been fun, but you're hungry.  The Mushroom mother stops abruptly
			as your stomach began to gurgle and churn.  She prods at your walls
			questioningly.  As your acids began to go to work, she cries out
			with alarm, pushing against the walls constraining you and cooing
			desperately at you.

			Despite her attempts, she falls quiet before long, and your stomach
			began shrinking down.  By the end of the day, there's no trace was
			ever there.
		</text>
		<special effect="removeCaptive" />
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreEndo4B">
		<text>
			You lean against the wall, settling in and enjoying the affections
			of your loyal belly pet.  She happily rubs at the inside of your
			stomach.  She kisses your loving walls, humming a soothing tune to you.

			A warmth fills your stomach, the mushroom mother milking herself and
			spilling her creamy nectar straight into your innards.  Definitely 
			a mushroom mother!
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="10" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreEndo5B" text="time to let her out" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreEndo5B">
		<text>
			As pleasant as this is, you can't sit around all day with a belly
			full of curvy belly mushrooms.  Well, maybe you could, but not more
			than a day!

			You heave her back up.  She offers you an adoring smile, yanking you
			into a chesty hug and smothering you in her cleavage for a moment.
			She lets you go with a playful wink, and settles back into her
			containment.  
		</text>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="She's back in containment, in the system not your belly" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasure0A">
		<!--unwilling receive oralsex -->
		<text>
			Those massive breasts look so inviting, and you wrap your arms around
			her chest, burying your face in her cleavage.  She taken aback
			for a moment, but quickly settles back into her mask and returns the hug.

			Naturally, this is hardly enough, and you latch onto one of her breasts,
			suckling eagerly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasure1A" text="sample her thoroughly" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasure1A">
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="nice" value="1" />
		<text>
			She gasps out with pleasure, almost unwillingly so, but made no
			moves to refuse you.  She hesitantly massages your back with her
			hands, letting you kiss and suckle her breasts.

			You slide a hand down her side, and start to tease her pussy with one
			hand.  Her moans intensify, and she grinds her hips against you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasure2A" text="drink her milk" />
	</page>
	<page ID="pleasure2A">
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			The mushroom mother tries to return the favor, but you push her hand
			back.  This is about her and just how wonderful her curves are!
			She seems flustered, but doesn't put up a fuss.  You continue
			suckling her breasts, and she reluctantly gives up some of her
			creamy milk.

			The scent of her pheromones starts to fill the air.  Looks
			like the air filters couldn't handle any more.  Sadly,
			you have to put her back in containment before it really
			stars affecting you.  As the doors close, you catch a glimpse
			of a thoughtful expression.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
		<effect type="feed" value="5" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasure2A">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			The milky mushroom maiden starts to finally relax under
			your attention, laying on her back and laying you on top of her.
			She lets you do all the work, hugging you close as you pleasure her.

			She closes her eyes, the ship's biohazard warnings cease abruptly.
			You've finally won her over.  Creamy milk flows readily into your mouth as
			you suckle her.  She moans softly as you reward her, your hands softly teasing
			her pussy.

			Before long, she climaxes, crying out with pleasure and hugging you tight.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<effect type="feed" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>

	<page ID="loving0">
		<!--tender sex -->
		<text>
			The mushroom mother watches with careful interest as your cock
			hardens, revealing your interest in her vuluptious body.  She starts to
			lean forward and offer your member a kiss, but you push her back instead.

			She hesitates, unsure what to do now that you've rejected the obvious.
			Taking the lead, you kiss her on the lips softly, and gently massage her
			heavy breasts.
		</text>
		<choice destination="loving1" text="moving on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="loving1">
		<text>
			She hesitates before returning the kiss.  She starts to massage
			your shaft with one hand, gently stroking your hardening cock.

			You lay the mushroom mother on her back, pressing your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			cock up against her netherlips.  She shudders slightly at the sensation,
			and closes her eyes, waiting.
		</text>
		<choice destination="loving2" text="penetrate" />
	</page>

	<page ID="loving2">
		<text>
			Your reluctant lover gasps as your cock slides in.  She moans out as
			you hilt your member in her nether lips.  She tightens her arms around you
			tense with anticipation.
		</text>
		<choice destination="loving3" text="love her good" />
	</page>

	<page ID="loving3">
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="nice" value="1" />
		<text>
			You start slowly, moving your hips back and forth at a steady pace.
			She starts to moan louder, obviously enjoying your attentions despite
			herself.  You take her chest in your hands, softly massaging them and
			suckling her breasts.  She arches her back lightly, bucking against you.

			You can feel her start to tense.  Almost there.
		</text>
		<choice destination="loving4" text="climax" />
	</page>

	<page ID="loving4">
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			You keep the pace, thrusting yourself in and out at a sedate pace.
			The shroom mother groans as your cock plows her nethers, and she finally
			climaxed.  She spills her sweet necter onto your crotch, and she pants heavily.

			You lay on top of her for a few minutes, resting and enjoying her warmth against 
			yours. You start to smell the scent of her pheromones, the constant release finally
			overwhelming the ship's air filters, and decide to leave.

			You catch a glimpse of her obedient mask cracking, a confused expresion on her face.
			You'll win her over eventually.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>


	<page ID="loving4">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="nice"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			You keep the pace, drawing out the moments as the mushroom mother moans and bucks
			to thrust herself against your cock when you thrust it up into her.
			Her pleasure cresting moments before your own due to your considerate
			expertise, a squeal emerging from her lips as she clenches down on
			you and shudders. The spasms of pleasure rolling through her coming
			even as you climax inside her and fill the fawn with sticky seed.
			With it all over you slowly pull out of her. The mushroom mother is looking up at
			you with a flushed panting look of satisfaction and wonder on her
			face.  She pulls your head into her cleavage, cooing affectionately.  The ship's
			computer stops blaring it's warnings.
			
			You've won her over with the power of dickings!
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>

	<page ID="fuck0">
		<!--rough sex -->
		<text>
			Time to enjoy what's yours!  You pin her down on the floor, squeezing
 			her massive breasts with one hand, and stroking your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft with the other. Her mask of affection and obedience solidifies, and
			she cooes "lovingly" at you.  You slide your cock between her breasts,
			and she presses them together with her hands, rubbing your cock with
			her breasts of her own accord.
		</text>
		<choice destination="fuck1" text="pound the titty mother" />
	</page>

	<page ID="fuck1">
		<text>
			You start to thrust your hips back and forth, and she squeals out with
			"delight."  Her ample breasts prove the perfect sleave for your shaft,
			and you quickly find yourself on the edge!
		</text>
		<choice destination="fuck2" text="fill her with cream" />
	</page>

	<page ID="fuck2">
		<text>
			Your cock twitches and throbs, and you pull back abruptly.  Then, you 
			climax, aiming down and spraying your load all over her breasts, face, and
			mushroom cap.  She catches some in her mouth, making a show of swallowing.

			Your distraction finished, you leave, almost missing the look of resentment behind you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="return her to containment, until next time you need to bust a nut" />
		<effect type="incrementlocalflag" flag="nice" value="-1" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<!--willing sex -->
		<text>
			You wave your hardening shaft, and your shroom lover coos.

			She leans over, taking your cock and one hand and kissing the tip
			softly.  Then, she wraps her breasts around your shaft, happily
			pleasuring you.  Up and down her breasts go, the mushroom mother making...
			you'd say doe eyes, but having met actual fawn girls, you're not sure it's
			a valid expression anymore.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="down onto the floor" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			You find yourself suddenly pushed onto the ground, the mushroom mother
			pinning you down with her body.  You can feel her grinding her moist
			pussy against your cock.  It seems she's a lot more assertive now
			that she trusts you!

			She wraps her breasts around your heads, smothering you in her ample
			assets.  She slides your cock into her nethers, starting to ride you eagerly.
			Up and down her hips go, bouncing on your crotch with happy cries.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="and now, screw her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			As enjoyable as this is, you can't let her have all the fun!
			You roll the both of you over, getting yourself back on top.  The mushroom
			mother smiles up at you, humming lovingly.  You began to thrust your cock into
			her, moaning softly.

			You latch onto her breasts with your mouth, suckling her milk-heavy breasts eagerly.
			She just as eagerly gives you her creamy milk.  She climaxes, her nethers clenching around your
			cock as she spells her nectar onto your crotch and the floor.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex3" text="Revenge of the shroom!" />
					<effect type="feed" value="10" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex3">
		<text>
			She's not out of the running yet!  As you slow down to give her a break, she
			grabs your hips and pulls them up to her head!  You find your cock disappearing into
			her mouth.  She keeps you seated on her breasts as she starts sucking you off, bobbing
			her head up and down.  You can just barely make out her mischevious eyes under the brim of
			the shroom cap on her head.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex4" text="pump it in" />
	</page>


	<page ID="sex4">
		<text>
			Already worked up by the titty fuck and pounding her nethers, you don't last long
			against her skilled tongue and tight throat.  You climax, hard, spilling your load
			down her throat.  She keeps her lips wrapped tightly around your cock, swallowing each
			and every last drop.

			You collapse, and the mushroom mother pulls you into a soft embrace.  You find yourself falling
			asleep soon after in her arms.

			When you awake, you find yourself waking up with a face full of breasts.  You look up to see your
			lover smiling down at you, petting your hair.  You close your eyes again, enjoying the soft
			embrace of the mushroom mother, leaning into her breasts.  Unfortunately, you still have things to
			do today.  Time to go.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="return her to containment" />
	</page>

</Conversation>