<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<!--written by andrea_crawford -->
		<preference fetish="breastvore" />
		<text> The mushroom mother opens her arms to you cooing, letting you
			step into her embrace, pressing you against the over abundance of her
			breasts as she half lids her eyes. Her arms cozily wrap around your
			addled form, one hand guiding you with seeming compassion so that you
			come face to teat with her nipple.
		</text>
		<choice destination="suckle" text="Cuddle up to those tits" />
	</page>

	<page ID="suckle">
		<text>
			Rich and sweet the white liquid rolls over your tongue,
			spreading warmth
			from your tummy as it fills with milk. Deep, female
			humms and quiet
			moans encourage you to continue, as soft, grey hands
			stroke over your
			back. Eventually though, while you are still suckling
			on the
			supersized bosom, one of her hands moves up to your head,
			running her
			fingers through your hair, playing with it. "Do you like
			what I have
			to offer?" she asks. "Come, I can give you even more."
			Without haste
			she begins to push your head against the soft orb of her
			breast which
			drank from so eagerly, and the large nipple opens
			willingly to let
			you in.
		</text>
		<choice destination="suckled on" text="Hungry boobs" />
	</page>

	<page ID="suckled on">
		<text>
			You do not resist. With the pheromones clouding your mind, the
			warm,
			plentiful milk sloshing about in your tummy and the comforting
			voice
			of the mushroom mother humming in your ears, you are way too
			relaxed
			to protest. Just like you suckled on her breast before, the
			large,
			grey nipple starts to suck on your body, drawing you inwards
			with
			slurping noises. It must be an impressive sight, you think to
			yourself, to see you stand in front of her, with your head, neck and
			now shoulders stuck in the mushroom mother's breast. When your own
			bosom follows into the warmth of her tit and a moan escapes your
			lips, you feel her hands cup your rump, kneading it gently and
			heaving you upwards. Moisture spreads between your legs as your feet
			leave the ground.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sucked in" text="Into the teat" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sucked in">
		<text>
			Her already massive tit expands even further as it continues to
			consume you, filling with your body as the mushroom mother feeds you
			into her chest. Another groan of pleasure sounds from your mouth as
			her nipple massages its way over your milk-filled belly, and you
			clutch your hands between your legs, rubbing their palms against your
			crotch.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				If she had only taken your pants off first.
			</conditional>
			It is too late for that now though, as your hips and rump wiggle
			their way inside the large breast, gently pushed onwards by the
			female's soft hands. For a moment your legs hang free from her
			nipple, but soon they are consumed as well. First the thighs, then
			your shapely calves and -with a last, satisfied sounding slurp- your
			feet are drawn into the teat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="inbreast" text="All the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="inbreast">
		<text>
			Finally all the way in, you shift about to get into a more
			comfortable
			position and curl up inside her breast - and judging by
			the sounds,
			your movement seems to cause great pleasure to the
			mushroom mother.
			Just like your belly is filled with her milk, you are
			now filling out
			her bosom in return. It seems only fair - or is it?
		</text>
		<choice destination="escapecheck" text="Snap out of it" />
		<choice destination="digest" text="Bath in her milk" />
	</page>

	<check ID="escapecheck">

		<test what="WILLPOWER" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="escape" />
		<outcome destination="noescape" />
	</check>

	<page ID="escape">
		<text>
			With yourself sealed inside the fleshy orb of the mushroom
			mother's
			breast, her pheromones are quick to lose their effect on you.
			Realizing the situation you are in, you begin to struggle against
			your fleshy prison - much to the pleasure of the mushroom mother. You
			can hear her moan as you push and shove against the slippery walls
			around you, turning and shifting about until you finally find the
			soft spot of your entrance. Pressing your hands against the nipple
			from the inside, you find it surprisingly easy to force it open and
			your arms through. It seems like the mother of the mushroom girls
			relies mostly on her pheromones to capture her prey, and not on brute
			force.
		</text>
		<choice destination="escape1" text="get out" />
	</page>

	<page ID="escape1">
		<text>
			For a moment your arms wave around in the air, but then your
			head pops
			free as well and with blinking eyes you take in your
			surroundings.
			Your vision is still a bit blurred, as if you woke up
			after a deep
			dream, but soon you realize that you are not that far
			above the
			ground. The matronly creature has lowered herself onto her
			knees, and
			while one hand supports her supersized breast, the other
			has
			travelled further south to scratch a certain itch, caused by your
			struggles. Deciding to keep her busy you push onwards, shifting and
			squirming your way out of her breast.
			By the time you pull the last of
			your legs from her tit, the mushroom
			mother is openly masturbating,
			fingering herself with closed eyes.
			But without the added pleasure
			from your movement she seems unable to
			reach the peak, and so she
			eventually stops with a sigh. "Aww, why
			did you have to leave so
			early, darling?" she coos, getting back to
			her feet. "Aren't you
			hungry anymore? Come, I have more to offer to
			you." she teases,
			heaving up her other breast invitingly.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="noescape">
		<text>
			It was fun while it lasted, but it has lasted long enough.
			Without
			being exposed to the intoxicating effects of her spores, you
			decide
			that it is better to get out of this rather sooner than later.
			Rubbing your hands against the soft walls of the inside of the
			breast, much to your captors pleasure, you feel around for the
			opening of the nipple. Where is the darn... there! As soon as you
			find it, you push your arms against the entrance with all your might,
			but it is sealed shut. You shift about to find a better angle, maybe
			push your back against the fleshy wall and force your way through,
			but all your movement causes is milk to leak from tiny, well hidden
			glands and pool up at the bottom of the teat. The nipple itself stays
			closed.
		</text>
		<choice destination="noescape1" text="a milky demise" />
	</page>

	<page ID="noescape1">
		<text>
			With a worried expression you watch the milky fluid gather in
			the shallow
			pool at the bottom, and start to fill your chamber in a
			slow, but
			steady pace. You call out to the mushroom mother, try to
			convince her
			to reconsider her plans, but her only reactions are moans
			of pleasure
			as she rocks back and forth, kneading your frame through
			the thick
			flesh of her breast. It does not take much imagination to
			assume what
			her other hand might be working on, as her groans are
			quick to
			increase in volume - and her breast further fills with her
			milk.
			You begin to struggle again, to fight against the unavoidable,
			but there
			is no chance. You have not much room to move in the tight
			place you
			are stuck in, and the fleshy walls surrounding you knead and
			squeeze
			you from all sides. Your hands slide off the slippery,
			milk-covered
			walls again and again in your futile efforts to get out,
			and soon
			enough you take another mouthful of milk as your head is
			briefly
			submerged in the warm liquid. Sputtering you manage to squirm
			around,
			filling your lungs with air once more, before you vanish below
			the
			surface again. This is not going to end well.
		</text>
		<choice destination="milk" text="Nothing but breast milk" />
	</page>

	<page ID="digest">
		<text>
			This is the best. Adrenaline pumps through your veins as you rub
			yourself against the moist walls of your surroundings, and your
			clouded, lust-driven mind guides one of your hands unerringly
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				into your pants. It takes a while to sneak it under the clothing in
				this confined space, but eventually you manage to work it out - and
				your
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				between your leg and slide your fingers
			</conditional>
			fingers into your dripping snatch. A groan escapes your lips, and you
			turn your head sideways to lap at the inner wall of the mother's
			breast, and lick up the sweet milk which begins to ooze out of it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="digest1" text="sexy demise" />
	</page>

	<page ID="digest1">
		<text>
			You can still hear her voice, calming, alluring, inviting you to
			give in
			to your pleasure, and you press back into her hand when you
			notice
			her feeling you up through the thick flesh of her bosom. You
			cannnot
			understand what she is saying to you, but you do not mind. All
			you
			can think of is the feeling of her breast pulsing and kneading
			around
			you, and the sweet, sweet milk you begin to bathe in. Your
			clothes
			are soaked within moments and your hair is a mess, but who
			cares? It
			is so warm, so soft, so...
			With a free hand, you pinch your
			left nipple. Fuck yes. More! Your
			fingers work themselves into a fast
			rhythm, digging deep into your
			sex, curving upwards inside your body
			to rub against that very
			special point. Ahhh, more! Your chest heaves
			with your heavy breath
			as you scoop up some of the milky liquid you
			are bathing in now, to
			rub it into your clothes, into your skin, over
			your face. You need
			more, more! Holding your breath, you finally let
			yourself sink,
			submerging completely in the warm pool of milk.
		</text>
		<choice destination="milk" text="Nothing but breast milk" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="milk">
		<text>
			As little waves of milk close above your head, your mind begins to
			fade. Your body goes numb in certain places, tingling in others,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				while pieces of your clothing float past yourself, upwards to the
				surface, dissolving furher along the way.
			</conditional>
			But you do not care. Nothing is of importance anymore, as you close
			your eyes and give in to the liquid surrounding you.
			It does not take
			long for the mushroom mother to begin the digestion
			properly, and loud
			glorps and gurgles can be heard from her enlarged
			breast as your
			contours begin to fade. At the beginning your outlines
			are vaguely
			visible through the stretched flesh of her bosom, but the
			longer it
			goes, the longer she kneads and massages her large,
			malleable orb, the
			more it turns back to the soft, oh so tempting
			shape it had beforehand
			- just a fair bit larger.
			But even though you are gone too far by now
			to really experience this
			anymore, the progress is attentively watched
			by many eyes. Attracted
			by her moans and the sounds of digestion,
			several mushroom girls have
			gathered around their mother, licking
			their lips and following the
			events with hungry eyes, as they observe
			you melting into milk. They
			sure are in for a very special treat
			tonight.
		</text>
	</gameover>
</Conversation>