<?xml version="1.0"?>

<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		The mother of these mushrooms lies on her back, overwhelmed
		by your own seductive retaliation. She thought she'd be the seducer here.
		</text>
		<choice destination="drink1" text="Drink from the tap." />		
		<choice destination="breast1" text="If anyone's getting their tits sucked here, it's me.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="breastvore" />
		</choice>		
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>			
		<choice destination="sample" text="Take a sample for research purposes." >
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/mushroommother.xml"/>
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="mushroommother"/>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use your capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="end" text="Leave her be." />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>	
	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>	
	
	<page ID="sample">
		<text>
		Holding an emptied can of space soda to the mother's nipple, you quickly fill
		the can and then some. Lord, it just doesn't stop coming out, does it?
		</text>
		<special effect="research" data="mushroommother" DC="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Time to do some research." />
	</page>

	<page ID="drink1">
		<text>
		Those orbs look so heavy on her. You think you oughtta lighten the load,
		so, ignoring or not suffering of lactose intolerance (if her milk even has lactose in it),
		you get down on your knees beside her pudgy, pacified form and wrap
		your arms around the breast closest to you, taking a second to really
		appreciate how soft they are. They're like water balloons you could fit
		a person inside! Then, licking you lips, you lean forward and fit the
		nozzle of her bottlecap nipple in your mouth. And man, is the elixir
		ever delightful. Warm, sweet, a little earthy. It's... intoxicating.
		Not literally, but you know. And it sounds like the mother's getting
		some enjoyment out of this, too.
		</text>
		<choice destination="drink2" text="Keep drinking." />
		<choice destination="sated1" text="That's enough for now." />
	</page>

	<page ID="sated1">
		<text>
		Alright, let's not get carried away. You've still got plenty of stuff
		on your schedule. Your lips make a popping sound when you pry them from
		her nipple. The mother isn't the happiest that you gotta bounce, but
		that's her issue.
		</text>
		<effect value="20" type="givefood"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="Get moving." />
	</page>

	<page ID="drink2">
		<text>
		You didn't need to tell you twice. You aren't stepping away from this
		teat until you're damn ready to. You're not even nearly full. And the
		mother hasn't gotten her fill of enjoyment out of this either, her cooing
		getting louder and louder. The taste doesn't get old-- hell, you might
		say it's getting better with every drop. It's... it's heavenly. It beats
		out all the swill you used to call booze, or soda, or juice, or water...
		What's it even made of? Your head feels too funny to think about that.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitA" text="Climb in. You need more." />
		<choice destination="stopcheck" text="Maybe you should stop..." />
		<choice destination="controlcheck" text="Clear your head and keep going." />
	</page>

	<page ID="submitA">
		<text>
		You can't help it. You can't have enough. Not while you're still outside.
		You pop your mouth from her nipple and jam your fingers through the opening,
		prying it wide open for your head to fit through. Soon, you've wormed your
		shoulders, your collar, and your breasts through the opening, but you got stuck
		at the waist as your feet left the ground. The fungal mother is happy to help you
		the rest of the way through, though, sweetie, with a hand on your ass to
		finish the job, nipple slapping wetly shut behind you. And so you're left to
		drink and drink and drink 
		<conditional>
			<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			as milk seeps into your clothes
		</conditional>.
		Soon, though, that funny feeling in your head spreads to the
		rest of your body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="milkA" text="You're melting." />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="milkA">
		<text>
		You're turning into milk and it's the most wonderful thing you can imagine.
		To become this heavenly elixir! To shed your much less nourishing body and
		become the purest of drinks! It suits you. The girls upstairs are going to
		love what you add to the mix.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<check ID="stopcheck">
		<test what="WILLPOWER" DC="8" />
		<outcome destination="sated2" />
		<outcome destination="submitB" />
	</check>

	<page ID="sated2">
		<text>
		Suddenly your brow furrows in realization: you're getting hit by pheromones.
		They're all around you like a curtain of smoke. You must not have noticed
		while you were busy engorging yourself on her milk. Immediately, you push
		yourself off of her, gulp down the rest of what's in your mouth, cover your
		lower face, and put some distance between the two of you, much to the mother's
		disappointment. Well, at least you filled your belly.
		</text>
		<effect value="40" type="givefood"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="Get going." />
	</page>

	<page ID="submitB">
		<text>
		You... you were thinking about doing something just now, but you forgot what
		it was. Whatever. It probably wasn't as important as this. You don't think
		anything's been as good for you as this has been. But you can only get so
		much in you with your mouth...
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitA" text="Climb in." />
	</page>

	<check ID="controlcheck">
		<test what="WILLPOWER" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="drink3" />
		<outcome destination="submitB" />
	</check>

	<page ID="drink3">
		<text>
		Focus. It's good, but not worth losing your mind over. And you've had plenty
		of good drinks before. You're sure they could be improved with her milk, but
		it's not worth forsaking them over. Like, what was that dumb shit you thought
		about water being swill? It's fucking water. There's like a cosmic rule out
		there that drinking-water cannot be swill. In any sense. Anyways, you've had...
		maybe too much of her milk. Your belly's bulging
		<conditional>
			<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			against your clothes like you've stuffed a pillow or two in there
		</conditional>
		<conditional>
			<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			out like you're pregnant
		</conditional>
		and sloshing wildly with every movement.
		</text>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="breasts" modifier="1" variable="size"> </mutation>
		</special>
		<choice destination="sated3" text="Finish up." />
	</page>

	<page ID="sated3">
		<text>
		You give her teat one last gulp
		(or two. or three) before popping her nipple from your mouth and stepping
		away. The mother tries to pull you back in with a swipe of the arm but she's
		too weak to succeed, saying, "Come back! Don't you want more?~" It falls on
		deaf ears. Then, after a loud, prolonged burp, you wipe your mouth
		with your
		<conditional>
			<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			sleeve
		</conditional>
		<conditional>
			<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			wrist
		</conditional>
		and look at your belly. Already, you're digesting her milk, belly visibly
		shrinking every minute. What's more, you seem to be growing. Or, at least, your tits
		are. When your belly returns to normal, you've grown a size. You're now a nice
		<measurement part="breasts" variable="size"/>
		.
		</text>
		<effect value="80" type="givefood"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="Get going with your new assets." />
	</page>

	<page ID="breast1">
		<text>You walk over to the mother mushroom and proudly place your
				<macro ID="breast_size_desc" />
				breasts in front of her face. She gives you a puzzled look, she's used to being on the giving end
				of these types of situations. Nevertheless she begins to suckel on your left nipple, which fills you
				with a sense of accomlishment and sexual pleasure. The large mushroom woman begins to lactate, spilling milk all over the
				cave floor. She then presses the tip of her mushrrom cap head agianst your left nipple. It's time to take her in.
				
		</text>
		<choice destination="breast2" text="Things are about to get really milky." />
	</page>


	<page ID="breast2">
		<text>
			You let out a sensual moan as your left nipple opens up to swallow the mushroom mother. Her mushroom cap tip is not unlike the tip of a cock,
			but you want more than just the tip. Through the combined efforts of your pulling and her pushing, you take the mushroom mother deeper into your mammary. All the while
			a waterfall of milk continues to flow out of her own tits. The unreal amounts of stimulation cause you to orgasm and your senses become clouded. You use you
			right hand to fondle your right breast and your left one continues to devour the mushroom woman.You lay down on the cave floor to let gravity do the rest of the heavy lifting.
		</text>
		<choice destination="breastend1" text="Become the new milk mama." />
		<choice destination="capture2" text="Keep the old milk mama."> 
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>

	</page>
	<page ID="capture2">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>
			Gravity pushes the rest of the mushroom mother's heavy body into your left tit. Having her sealed away inside your mammary has caused it to swell size so much
			that it is bigger than the rest of your body.  Despite the massive burden, you began to struggle to your feet.  You went through a lot of trouble to catch
			the milky maid, and you wanted the prize!  Somehow, you struggle back to your ship, and spill the mushroom mother into the containment cell.  Not your usual 
			way of doing things, but hey!  It worked.  For some inexplicable reason, you wander back to the cave where you found her.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Mine!" />
	</page>
	<page ID="breastend1">
		<text>
			Gravity pushes the rest of the mushroom mother's heavy body into your left tit. Having her sealed away inside your mammary has caused it to swell size so much
			that it is bigger than the rest of your body. The weight of your breasts proves too troublesome to overcome, so you decide to look up at the cave ceiling as your body
			melts the mushroom mother into mik. In about what feels like an hour, her figure can no longer been seen in your tit and much of its weight has been worn down too.
			You sit up and decide to sample your own milk. The processed mushroom is very rich in taste. And the taste is addictive too! You quickly suck out the milk
			the was once the the busty mother mushroom. You give your right tit a quick squeeze and to your surprize, a little squirt of milk comes out.
			By absorbing the mushroom mother into your tits, youve gained her ability to rapidly produce milk!
			
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="giveperk" perk="Lactation" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Get going with your newly acquired ability." />
	</page>

</Conversation>