<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<!-- content by tirat -->
		<text>
			The doggy girl doesn't react when you greet her verbally except
			to cock
			her head to one side and grin. The shameless canine pet shifts
			position and her delightful rack wobbles slightly drawing your eye.
			And you can't help but wonder what she's hiding behind that
			loincloth. you could probably have fun with this one it's not like
			anyone would mind right.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pet0" text="pet the doggy" />
		<choice destination="peek0" text="peek under her loincloth">
		<preference fetish="herms" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave the doggy alone" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pet0">
		<text>
			Her ears perk up as she smiles broadly and quickly leans her
			head into
			your hand. She rumbles happily and pants like a real dog.
			And her
			tail starts wagging as she clearly enjoys your attention.
			Looks like
			she’s actually sort of a local pet. Such a cute, friendly
			and rather
			curvy doggie.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pet1" text="pet more" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pet1">
		<text>
			Who’s a good girl? You pet more and even rub at her soft ears.
			The girl
			reacts with more rumbles and happy barks, her tail is wagging
			rapidly
			now. After a good minute of such fun she wiggles and quickly
			rolls
			onto her back. Time for the bellyrubs? Though not only her belly
			is
			in your reach now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="grope0" text="grope her breasts" />
		<choice destination="pet2" text="bellyrub" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pet2">
		<text>
			You give the doggy a belly rub, she seems to enjoy it, tongue
			lolling
			and panting. But once you're done making her good and doted on
			you
			leave off and she arfs rolling back to her feet with a dopey grin
			on
			her face.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave the good doggy be" />
	</page>

	<page ID="grope0">
		<text>
			Her boobies are nicely exposed and open, so why not give them
			some
			little attention too? Your hands touch and pet at her warm, round
			boobies, making the girl shiver with pleasure. Her pink tongue
			quickly rolls from her panting mouth as she presses more into your
			hands, clearly asking for more. Oh well, her chest feels so very good
			against your palms, lovely curve and so smooth and bouncy. Nice!
		</text>
		<choice destination="grope1" text="More touches" />
	</page>

	<page ID="grope1">
		<text>
			With a silly smile you rub more, now really kneading and groping
			at her
			boobies. They feel so very nice to touch! You even close your
			eyes
			and relax, focusing on the girl’s breasts. You can feel her
			rumbles
			vibrating under the skin and new warmth leaking from her body.
			After a couple of moments you open one eye and suddenly discover your
			hands being buried really deep into the girls warm cleavage as you.
			Maybe you dozed off for a minute? Anyway, the rumbling doggie moves
			closer and even gently drags you closer to herself, forcing more of
			your arms into the warm, soft depths of her cleavage
		</text>
		<choice destination="boobsorbEscape" text="pull back" />
		<choice destination="boobsorb" text="relax">
		<preference fetish="absorption" />
		<preference fetish="demis" />			
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="boobsorbEscape">
		<text>
			After a quick realization you stand up and pull your arms back
			from the
			strangely deep cleavage. The girl whines softly as your hands
			slip
			free and escape, making her boobies jiggle softly. Maybe that was
			just an accident? You reach and give her head some more soft pets
			before stepping away
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="boobsorb">
		<text>
			Curiously you wiggle your fingers and rub deeper within the
			girl’s cleavage.
			And she moans happily and pushes forward, quickly
			forcing even more
			of your arms in between of her boobies. Before you
			realize what’s
			going on, she rolls on top of you, trying to hug you
			close into
			herself. The warmth of her chest spreads quickly,
			enveloping your
			head and shoulders, rolling down around your chest.
			The playful
			doggie humps into you and pushes more, happily feeding
			your body into
			her cleavage. Well, at least this part of her body
			feels so very
			comfy and good!
		</text>
		<choice destination="boobsorbGO" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="boobsorbGO">
		<text>
			The darkness and softness of her cleavage envelops you gently,
			making
			you feel very relaxed and comfy. Her deep rumbles are so very
			soothing and nice to hear along with her heartbeat. You don’t even
			care as your body starts actually melting into her cute, round
			boobies, making them grow bigger. The doggie helps your feet slide
			into her chest and disappear without a trail, easily absorbed and
			added into her soft curves. Minutes later all of your former body
			will be gone, used to improve her chest. Well, from now on you’ll
			jiggle as lovely DD cups on the cute, playful dog girl.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="peek0">
		<text>
			You smile at the cute, relaxed doggie and curiously lean in
			between of
			her soft thighs. Barely she’ll protest right now, so you
			pull at her
			loincloth and… reveal her actual gender! Her girlcock is
			dangling
			against her thigh, semi-erect already. It looks rather big,
			considering her size. And inches below you spot her pink, glistering
			pussy fold. Looks like the cute doggie is actually a herm!
			You
			suddenly notice how she watches you and whines softly, wiggles
			playfully, shaking her booty and cock at you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="try her cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			With a chuckle you reach and wrap your hands around her cock.
			The girl
			grins broadly and starts tailwagging even faster. And her
			arousal
			twitches playfully in your hands and quickly swells to the
			full size.
			Oh, she got solid ten inches of the hot, veiny rod to play
			with. She
			rumbles and humps into your hand, soaking it in her warm,
			sticky
			precum.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			You smirk more and turn around
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, taking off your pants and
			</conditional>
			revealing your curvy butt. And before you can react the doggie
			pounces at your rear, quickly wrapping her arms around your waist and
			tugging you into a tight, hot hug. Her shaft grinds against your
			buttocks and in between of them, smearing more viscous lube all over
			your sensitive hole. The dog girl rumbles playfully and humps again,
			this time pressing her hot cocktip against your pucker. She acts
			rather harsh, but also skillful, so little pain quickly turns into
			pleasure.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			For a moment you realize, what elven girls probably trained that
			girl to
			do such tricks. And the doggie follows the training well and
			humps
			more, smoothly sliding even more of her shaft deep into your
			tight
			rear entrance. After just two more pushes you can feel how her
			crotch
			smacks into your butt. She playfully sways left and right,
			forcing
			her member to gently grinding into the sensitive flesh deep
			within
			your pucker. And with that she pushes you down onto all four,
			only to
			press herself into your back and keep fucking your lovely
			tush. One
			of her hands wraps around your breast and gropes it gently,
			kneading
			at the softness, while her crotch smacks rapidly into your
			buttocks.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex3" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex3">
		<text>
			The girl rumbles louder every second, working hard to please
			you. You
			can feel her shaft dripping more gooey precum deep inside
			and… oh, is
			that a knot? All of sudden you can feel a nice, bonus
			stretch just
			behind your tight pucker. The base of her seemingly human
			cock swells
			bigger, forming a hot, thick bulge. And it tugs so nicely
			at your
			exit valve.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex4" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex4">
		<text>
			AWrooo! She grinds against your back and thrusts, hilts all the
			way into
			your butt, groaning out and cumming hard. You can feel river
			of the
			rich, sticky juice flooding your bowels as she humps more and
			quickly
			pumps your rear full of her seed.
			But after so much fun the
			cute girl quickly turns limp and relaxed. She
			smiles happily and
			cuddles you more, going to flop onto one side and
			simply pet and lick
			you. Her cock stays deep in your butt and… seems
			like it’ll stay
			inside for a while, thanks to her swollen knot. But
			at least you feel
			comfy and protected in her gentle hands.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex5" text="You got stuff to do" />
		<choice destination="ctf0" text="get comfortable">
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
		<preference fetish="herms" />
		<preference fetish="demis" />					
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="sex5">
		<text>
			You try to relax in the girl’s hands, but you can’t just sit
			there for
			long. Slowly you gyrate and move your hips, tugging at her
			swollen
			knot. This thing is large and sitting tight in your pucker,
			but
			slowly you can try and let it go. You only need to tug a bit more,
			slowly lean to the right and then left. Nnngh, it stretches your
			tight, little hole by a lot! And the girl whines softly too. She even
			tries to cuddle you more and hold close to herself. But still you tug
			more and… POP! Her knot suddenly slips free, quickly followed by her
			cock and a gush of the musky juice.
			Finally you are able to stand up,
			even as your booty still aches softly.
			Well, you got stuff to do!
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="ctf0">
		<text>
			The girl rumbles happily behind you, enveloping you in the
			warmth and
			softness of her body. Staying in her embrace feels so very
			good and
			natural. You simply put your head against her warm boobies
			and yawn,
			close your eyes for a little nap.
			The dog girl holds you
			close to herself, seemingly enjoying your company
			as well. But as her
			thick knot and warm cock stay in your booty for
			so long, they start
			slowly spreading new warmth and even tingles into
			your rear. The new
			sensations are pleasant and kinda nice to feel,
			especially as the girl
			presses her crotch closer to your booty. Your
			dreams quickly turn hot
			and really moist, full of the naughty dog
			girls licking and caressing
			your naked body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="ctf1" text="but in reality" />
	</page>

	<page ID="ctf1">
		<text>
			In reality though your body slowly fuses with the girl’s cock,
			getting
			glued and attached to her crotch. Your form changes slowly,
			turning
			much more warm and sensitive, but also losing your former
			features.
			First your legs curl and melt away into the great addition
			to the
			girl’s sack. And then your arms fuse into your sides, forming
			pair of
			the thick, pulsating veins right under the soft skin.
		</text>
		<choice destination="ctf2A" text="wake up" />
		<choice destination="ctf2B" text="sleep more" />
	</page>

	<page ID="ctf2A">
		<text>
			You struggle and slowly force yourself to escape from the sweet
			dream.
			It was so good and nice! And even waking up you can still feel
			pleasant warmth pulsating through your body. Oh, that cute doggie is
			still cuddling you close! But strangely you feel smaller and somewhat
			stuck, not able to move your legs or arms.
			New struggles make the girl
			slowly yawn and stretch out, casually rub at
			your side. Why she’s
			ignoring you? You try calling out for her, but
			instead girl simply
			drops on all four and starts walking somewhere.
			And you drop and
			bounce in between of her thighs! Oh, that’s bad!
			Your whole body is
			now attached to her crotch, stuck and only able to
			heavily sway
			around. Her loincloth can’t really cover your head, but
			still no one
			is playing attention. Even elf girls you notice only
			peek down and
			giggle quietly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="ctf3A" text="time passes" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="ctf3A" noReform="true">
		<text>
			The day passes rather quickly as you are forced to stay as a new
			bodypart of the cute girl. She’s been running around the village a
			lot, sometimes barking at the lizard girls to shoo them away. Elves
			actually feed the girl and give her pets and earrubs too. But they
			are not helping with your ‘problem’ like at all. And by the evening
			even after all the struggles and attempts to fight back, your body
			completely melts away into the bonus mass for her cock. Now nicely
			hidden under her loincloth, warm and comfy against her curvy thighs.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="ctf2B">
		<text>
			You sink deeper into the sweet slumber. Oh, the dream is so very
			nice
			and lewd, a couple of hot, curvy girls tries to cuddle you close.
			Their warm, round boobies rub into your naked skin, making you
			shudder with pleasure. Slowly they start hugging you more, gently
			squeezing your body and even making you drool with the new
			sensations.
		</text>
		<choice destination="ctf3B" text="and then" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="ctf3B" noReform="true">
		<text>
			You try to groan out, but instead your open mouth leaks a new
			amount of
			the warm, viscous goo. The strange feeling makes you wake up
			more,
			only to find the girl’s hand rubbing your body in quick,
			pleasant
			motions. You try to squirm away, but instead your form turns
			really
			stiff and hard, throbbing with the new sensations. Oh, you are
			acting
			just like a good cock!
			The dog girl gives you another grope and
			rub, finally going to groan out
			and rumble as wave of the hot, rich
			cum gushes out through your body.
			She pants heavily and tailwags,
			still rubbing and helping you erupt
			all of the fresh juice. The pure
			bliss washes over you quickly,
			removing last chances to escape your
			new fate as a cock.
			And after a little moist fun she simply licks her
			hands clean and hides
			your warm, limp form under her loincloth. Nope,
			no adventurers here,
			just a thick, veiny shaft pulsating in between of
			her thighs.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>