<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The black grief lays on the ground, no longer having the strength to
			hold itself up. It swipes at you, but then goes limp soon enough. It
			should be out for a while at least, even if you just leave it here,
			yet there is no doubt in your mind that it would still be dangerous
			to get close if you weren't careful.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal0" text="Well... it would be filling...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave it be for now" />
	</page>
	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			After some hesitation you quickly reach down and grab its arms, doing
			your best to pin its claws before it can do any damage to you. Then you
			lift the thing up as best you can, before shoving it head and arms first 
			into your mouth in a rush. The taste is unpleasant, and the carapace feels
			weird in your mouth, but you forge on anyway, this is going to be a real
			challenge.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1" text="meet the challenge head on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			Its long legs twitch as you awkwardly begin to shove the enormous bug down
			your gullet. It's strange really, it was far more active just moments
			ago. Oh well, just makes it easier for you to force the whole thing in.
			You feel the creatures head and arms reach your gut, and then realize why,
			it was waiting, far less constricted in your rather elastic stomach, it
			moves one of its claws to press outwards, hard.
		</text>
		<choice destination="holdinthere" text="ignore the pain, swallow harder" />
	</page>
	<check ID="holdinthere">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="16" />
		<outcome destination="meal2" />
		<outcome destination="justafleshwound" />
	</check>
	<page ID="meal2">
		<text>
			You do your best to push through the pain, instead trying to swallow hard
			and squeeze the strength out of the grief. You hear a faint crunch as your
			throat contracts hard around the creatures torso, and the pressure stops.
			it continues wriggling as you force more of its body into your mouth, but
			it seems to no longer have the strength to properly fight back. The first
			pair of legs is forced most of the way down, and your belly is already
			rather large from the size of your "meal".
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal3" text="finish it off" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="justafleshwound">
		<text>
			You do your best to push through the pain, instead trying to swallow hard
			and squeeze the strength out of the grief. The insect stops pushing on
			your stomach wall, but only for a moment, then the pressure comes back
			even harder, your attempt to exhaust the thing only motivating it more.
			Then, there's a sharp pain in your chest, you feel something warm running 
			down your body, and everything goes black...

			The monstrous arthropod crawls out of its fleshy prison easily now that all
			effort to stop it has been ceased. Your attempt at consuming the black grief
			has only proven why it is at the top of this lands food chain. To be an apex
			predator is not just to eat all others, but to not be eaten yourself.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="meal3">
		<text>
			Onward you forge, swallowing more and more of the smooth shelled creature.
			Finally, you reach the tip of its tail, and will soon be able to wash this
			taste from your mouth. You reach out to tug at the stinger, popping it from
			the tail easily, and drop it to the ground. You have every bet that thing
			would have still done serious damage if you'd swallowed it. Then you gulp the
			thing down along with the rest of the back legs, you've done it, you didn't
			enjoy it, but you've eaten the creature.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal4"
			text="well, no moving until this is gone." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal4">
		<text>
			It takes quite some time and gives you indigestion, but eventually the black 
			grief is gone. Lost to the power of your now flattened belly. Does this mean 
			you're an apex predator? You might have already been one by this point.
			Either way, you stand up.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>