<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The creature seems to shudder for a moment, before going mostly still.
			It still twitches around in that normal insectoid manner, but it 
			doesn't seem to be trying to kill you anymore at least. You faintly
			notice a clear liquid dripping from the end of its tail.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1"
			text="Maybe you can eat it?">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="UBtail0" text="What is that stuff?">
						<preference fetish="ferals" />
					<preference fetish="unbirth" />
				<preference fetish="tailvore" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="leave" text="Well, at least it's calmed down." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			Its long legs twitch as you awkwardly begin to shove the enormous bug down
			your gullet. The creature now oddly passive, even though you're eating it
			alive. Oh well, just makes it easier for you to force the whole thing in.
			You feel the creatures head and arms reach your gut, and then whatever sort
			of effect you had on it wears off. The grief is now fully awake and aware,
			and it's still at full strength. You feel it press a claw out against your
			stomach wall, hard.
		</text>
		<choice destination="holdinthere" text="ignore the pain, swallow harder" />
	</page>

	<check ID="holdinthere">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="17" />
		<outcome destination="meal2" />
		<outcome destination="justafleshwound" />
	</check>

	<page ID="meal2">
		<text>
			You do your best to push through the pain, instead trying to swallow hard
			and squeeze the strength out of the grief. You hear a faint crunch as your
			throat contracts hard around the creatures torso, and the pressure stops.
			it continues wriggling as you force more of its body into your mouth, but
			it seems to no longer have the strength to properly fight back. The first
			pair of legs is forced most of the way down, and your belly is already
			rather large from the size of your "meal".
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal3" text="finish it off" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="justafleshwound">
		<text>
			You do your best to push through the pain, instead trying to swallow hard
			and squeeze the strength out of the grief. The insect stops pushing on
			your stomach wall, but only for a moment, then the pressure comes back
			even harder, your attempt to exhaust the thing only motivating it more.
			Then, there's a sharp pain in your chest, you feel something warm running 
			down your body, and everything goes black...

			The monstrous arthropod crawls out of its fleshy prison easily now that all
			effort to stop it has been ceased. Your attempt at consuming the black grief
			has only proven why it is at the top of this lands food chain. To be an apex
			predator is not just to eat all others, but to not be eaten yourself.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="meal3">
		<text>
			Onward you forge, swallowing more and more of the smooth shelled creature.
			Finally, you reach the tip of its tail, and will soon be able to wash this
			taste from your mouth. You reach out to tug at the stinger, popping it from
			the tail easily, and drop it to the ground. You have every bet that thing
			would have still done serious damage if you'd swallowed it. Then you gulp the
			thing down along with the rest of the back legs, you've done it, you didn't
			enjoy it, but you've eaten the creature.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal4"
			text="well, no moving until this is gone." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal4">
		<text>
			It takes quite some time and gives you indigestion, but eventually the black 
			grief is gone. Lost to the power of your now flattened belly. Does this mean 
			you're an apex predator? You might have already been one by this point.
			Either way, you stand up.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="130" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBtail0">
		<text>
			Curious of the nature of the strange fluids dripping from the insects
			tail, you circle around it to see what it is. Approaching its tip, you
			see something that you didn't quite notice while it was trying to impale
			you on it. There's a thin slit just under the stinger, made all the more
			visible by the moisture dripping from it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBtail1" text="is, is that its...?" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBtail1">
		<text>
			Yes, yes it is. That is apparently the alien bug monster equivalent of a
			vagina as you soon realize when you go to poke it and the whole creature 
			shudders as your hand slips inside. It's moist and warm from your wrist
			up. You aren't sure you wanted to know this...
		</text>
		<choice destination="leave" text="you pull your hand back out" />
		<choice destination="UBtail2" text="push further in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBtail2">
		<text>
			Oddly interested in this whole thing, you push on further into the giant 
			bugs nethers, inserting your other hand and pressing both of your arms
			in up to the elbows. It gets tigher as you do so, and you quickly find
			yourself hitting something further in. The alien vagina clenched around
			you in such a way that you aren't sure you can pull back anymore, so
			instead you choose to go further.
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBtail3" text="into the unknown" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBtail3">
		<text>
			You continue pushing, shoving yourself all the way in up to your shoulders,
			the creature, for its part, pushes back, thrusting its tail backwards, its
			cervix opens in front of you, and you find yourself forced through, stuck
			in up to your waist. Its tail lifts up, taking you with it, holding your legs
			in the air. It seems the rest is up to it now, the creatures womb pulls you
			forward, and you are forced to curl up inside of it, creating a large bulge
			at the base of the griefs tail.
		</text>
		<choice destination="UBtail4" text="relax" />
	</page>

	<page ID="UBtail4">
		<text>
			After wiggling about for a few moments to find a better position, you start
			to relax. In stark contrast to the creature you are contained within, the
			womb itself seem remarkably safe. The insect starts moving again, and you
			feel your confines shift noticeably a few times as it does so, seemingly
			from the grief moving over large rocks in its path. Eventually, you feel it
			come to a stop, and it lowers towards the ground in what is presumably a
			safe area, at which point it immediately goes still. Taking a note from the
			bug, you let yourself drift off to sleep. When you wake up, you find that
			the creature is still sleeping, and you work your way out.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="100" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="best be off now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="leave">
		<text>
			You seem to have definitely calmed the raging insect down, but you aren't
			sure you want to stick around to see how long that really lasts, and you
			aren't comfortable being close to those claws for any longer than you
			have to be.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="back away slowly... no wait, quickly is better" />
	</page>
</Conversation>