<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	The sune gives you a well practiced smile "Howdy stranger, you looking for a little loving? or maybe a lot?" she strokes a hand down her side, starting at her breast and down to her hip "If you got the creds, i got the time."
	</text>
	<choice destination="services" text="I'm interested in what you have to offer"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="not right now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="services">
	<text>
	The sune licks her lips "Sure thing hun, what can I do for ya?" she asks, stepping closer to let you smell her perfume and feel her warmth as she lays a hand against your thigh.
	</text>
	<choice destination="blowjob0" text="I'd like my dick sucked">
	<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="oralsex0" text="I'd like my pussy licked">
	<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />	
	</choice>	
	<choice destination="unbirthEndo0" text="I want to curl up in your womb">
		<preference fetish="females" />	
	<preference fetish="demis" />	
	<preference fetish="unbirthing" />
	</choice>
	<!-- 	<choice destination="unbirth0" text="I want you to juice me">
		<preference fetish="females" />	
	<preference fetish="demis" />	
	<preference fetish="unbirthing" />
	</choice> -->
	<choice destination="end" text="on second thoughts, I'll be on my way"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEndo0">
	<text>
	"Want to feel all cuddled up and safe mhmm? Well, it kinda keeps me from other custom so 300 credits and the room's yours." she says with a wink and a suggestive cock of her hips, one hand tracing down her front.
	</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthEndo1" text="$Sounds good, here's the money">
			<condition evaluate="CREDITS" operator="greaterthan" value="300"/>	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$That seems overpriced. No thanks."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEndo1">
	<text>
	The foxgirl takes your money and mhmms, slipping one hand into her pocket to disappear the money and her other hand under her skirt to delve into her nethers "You want to take a look first?" she asks with a mhmm and raises her skirt slowly. You can't help but take her up on her offer, dropping down onto your knees in order to look up at her shaved and soaking wet netherlips as she smiles and looks down at you. She moistens her lips and then uses her fingers to part her netherlips and show off her hungry pink folds "slip yourself in...just as soon as you're ready.."
	</text>
	<effect type="givecredits" value="-300" />	
	<choice destination="unbirthEndo2" text="*slip yourself in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEndo2">
	<text>
	The foxy harlot murrs softly as you reach up with your fingers to almost reverently feel around her wet folds. Your fingers tracing her inner lips before pressing together to delve deeper into her "That's it, nice and..warm, for you." she says and smiles, shifting but not moving to coax you in any faster as your wrists slide towards her netherlips and then up into her depths. Her birth canal tight, but yet pliant and stretching to welcome you as you wriggle your hands around and ease them further up into her. As you work more of your arms up into her and probe into her womb you close your eyes, ducking your head down as it nears her netherlips.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthEndo3" text="*wonderful warmth*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEndo3">
	<text>
	Gradually you ease your way into the foxgirl as she moans and gradually takes charge of your passage into her. She goes from passively letting you feed yourself up into her to leaning forwards and then pressing down over your body. The harlot showing a practiced ease with which she crams you up between her legs more and more. Your body starting to curl up in the embrace of her womb. That full body silken snuggle pressing tight yet yielding around your form as your legs begin to disappear up inside of her. Your feet dangling above the floor as she lets out a grunt and clenches, tugging you in with powerful muscles as her middle takes on an intensely gravid and bulging appearance. Soon now every inch of you is cradled within her, your feet having been tucked away with the rest of you "All warm and safe and loved on my lovely, least as much love as credits can buy..hope you enjoy your time in me."
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthEndo4" text="*enjoy your time*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEndo4">
	<text>
	The foxgirl hums to herself as she leans against the wall and her hot insides cosily snuggle and contain you. Time passes as you fall into a sort of doze, you're not sure but the foxy harlot might of done a few tricks with you inside. Though clearly nothing that involved her nethers, all you know is her muffled words and her moving around and shifting posture. In time though she drums her fingers on her belly "Okay time to come out lovely, that's as much time as your credits are good for." she warns you before squatting down and casually starts squeezing you back out into the open air of the station concourse. Your body emerging swiftly until you're sprawled slick with her juices on the deck before her "MHmm, do come again lovely. You were a good womb guest. Not like some I get." says the foxgirl as she wipes her nethers with a towel and then adjusts her skirt to properly seat over her thighs.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="I might do that..you had a nice womb"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth0">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, you want to go sploosh after a trip up between my thighs do ya? you're my kind of customer, mhmm.. still have to charge ya though, 150 credits and i'll leave you a wonderful puddle." she says with a delighted smile and a little wriggle of her hips as if already excited by the prospect.
	</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="$sure, here's the money I don't want to keep you waiting">
			<condition evaluate="CREDITS" operator="greaterthan" value="300"/>	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$You get to have that much fun and you charge as well? forget it."/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth1">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	<effect type="givecredits" value="-150" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex0">
	<text>
	"Need some tender loving? Ya came to the right place hun, 100 credits and I'll make you SING" she says with a mischevious gleam in her eyes as she smiles and slides her hand down to rest on your thigh. 
	</text>
		<choice destination="oralsex1" text="$Sounds good, here's the money">
			<condition evaluate="CREDITS" operator="greaterthan" value="100"/>	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$a hundred for a little tongue action? yeah no thanks."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex1">
	<text>
	The sune mhmms "you won't regret it, now lets see what i have to work with." she says and slides down, tails swaying back and forth in a slow and hypnotic fashion. Her hands tracing down your thighs, then sliding back up the inside to trace around the outline of your nethers without touching them. She murrs and seemingly just admires your sacred parts for a few seconds "Wonderful" she compliments before bringing her face in close to your crotch and darting her tongue out to lick over the length of your slit. Her tongue working up and then down your netherlips repeatedly before flicking out to press against your clit.
	</text>
	<effect type="givecredits" value="-100" />	
	<choice destination="oralsex2" text="*not...bad*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex2">
	<text>
	Her licks turn more naughty and works deeper into your folds, her hands spreading your lower lips so she can better seek out your most sensitive inner spots. Her mhmms at your hot fluids and flavours vibrating your sensitive parts as she nuzzles against your nethers and delves deeper and deeper into you with relentless enthusiasm and consummate skill. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralsex3" text="*getting...close*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex3">
	<text>
	She grips your thighs now, nestled deep in she licks repeatedly over your most pleasurable intimates and nuzzles her nose up against your hooded clit. Your body shuddering with impending orgasm as she squeezes your legs and then with a final lick works you over the edge. Your shudder turning into a full body spasm and a cry of bliss as your nethers clench and spurt to coat her face with lusty juices. The Sune waiting a dozen seconds supporting you with her hands before starting to clean you off. Her tongue working methodically over and around your nethers until you're clean of your juices and glistening with her saliva. The harlot letting go and getting up, wiping her lip and smiling "Told ya. Come back anytime."
	</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="$Will do slut, till next time"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="blowjob0">
	<text>
	The Sune chuckles and reaches down to stroke seductively over the part in question "Sure, got 100 credits?" she says and then smiles "You won't regret it I promise, I got a degree on gettin' on my knees." she says and licks her lips before doing something, interesting, with her tongue.
	</text>
	<choice destination="blowjob1" text="$Sounds good, here's the money">
			<condition evaluate="CREDITS" operator="greaterthan" value="100"/>	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$a hundred for a blowjob? yeah no thanks."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="blowjob1">
	<text>
	The harlot chuckles and takes the money "mhmm now what am I working with" she says and drops to her knees right then and there to service you in the street, her tails aswishing back and forth as she admires and fondles your <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> shaft. Her hands stroking along your length as she leans in and licks over your tip, playing her tongue expertly around your glans and teasing the corona around the edge of your cock delightfully. Your tip slick now with her saliva as she strokes and massages over your balls with one hand, then forms her lips into an O and brings her mouth down around your shaft. 
	</text>
	<effect type="givecredits" value="-100" />
	<choice destination="blowjob2" text="*let her do her job*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="blowjob2">
	<text>
	She lets out a mhmmpth as she encompasses your cock entirely, throat flexing as she inhales your shaft and nuzzles her nose into your crotch. Her throat massaging around your girth now as she nuzzles in and lets out pleased muffled mhmms as she squeezes your rear urging you on, her gaze looking up at you. In her eyes you can read her assent, and you reach your hand down behind her head to knot your fingers through her hair...who are you to refuse an invitation from a foxy who might like a bit of the rough stuff.
	</text>
	<choice destination="blowjob3" text="*take charge*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="blowjob3">
	<text>
	You grip her head firmly and start to thrust into her mouth, hearing her glucking around your dick each time you bottom out with your balls slapping against her chin. Her head bobbing obediently to follow your guiding hand as you start to use her mouth in earnest, your shaft plunging repeatedly into the mouth of this whore as you feel your pleasure build and your needed relief fast approaching.
	</text>
	<choice destination="blowjob4" text="*finish in her mouth*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="blowjob4">
	<text>
	The foxy harlot seems to sense your impending climax and bobs her head all the faster, alternating with powerful suction around your dick while nuzzled into your crotch. The expertise of her timing driving you up and over the crest of the mountain that is your pleasure. Your cock erupting down her throat as she swallows every gooey drop. The sune closing her eyes until she's felt the last spurt and throb of your cock before opening her eyes and pulling up off of it. She wipes her lips as your cock pops free of her mouth "Mhmm, come back anytime Hun. Ya know how to treat a girl right." she says giving your shaft a fondle as she gets back up onto her feet.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$Will do slut, till next time"/>
	</page>
	
</Conversation>