<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The little rodent looks up at you. Defeated she lets out a pliantive
			squeek and clutches her tail for comfort as you loom over her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal0" text="she's snack sized">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="she'd make a good toy">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
			<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be" />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			The weakened ratgirl squeaks and tries to wiggle away as you pick her up
			by the nape. She’s not really big, but will count as a free snack. So
			not waiting for long you open your mouth and shove almost half of the
			ratgirl inside. Another squeak echoes into your throat, quickly
			followed by a loud gulp. The snack tries to squirm still, pushing her
			lil hands into the throat walls and rubbing your neck from inside,
			but one more swallow sends most of her torso past your jaws.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1" text="gobble her up" />

	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			You can feel her soft booty shaking around close enough to let you lick
			at and tease the short meal before gulping her down. Her legs and the
			long, thin tail slide in soon after as the whole ratgirl lands into
			your stomach and curls up, making just a lil visible lump. And your
			belly will start gurgling soon, easily breaking down a squirmy
			appetizer. Well, after all the ratgirl works better than some
			not-squirmy fruits.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="50" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			The ratgirl squirms in your grip, weakly trying to break free and
			escape. She’s pretty short and will work great as a pleasure source
			for you. With a chuckle your spread your thighs wide apart and press
			the smaller girl into the sensitive folds. Her little hands rub into
			the pussy lips and then further into the moist tunnel, caressing it
			in a really pleasant way as more of the ratgirl slides inside. Feels
			like you got an extra warm, squirmy dildo sliding into your pussy,
			and then even deeper as you push at the soft booty.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="shove her in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			Another squeak vibrates into your womb as first of the ratgirl starts
			sliding inside. Her body fits easily within the tight, hot chamber in
			your abdomen, able to curl without any effort. And she’ll make just a
			cute, small lump outside. The long tail smoothly slides in as the
			pussy muscles tug last bits of the new ‘guest’. You can feel the
			ratgirl moving around still and rubbing into the sensitive walls as
			your womb starts working and melting the rat into a warm puddle for
			your pussy to leak later.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="50" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>