<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="analvore" />
				<preference fetish="demis" />
		<preference fetish="females" />		
		<text>
			You fall and sprawl out in front of the grinning rat girl. She
			happily
			squeaks and right away flops on top of your head. You can feel
			her
			soft, warm buttocks wiggle and rub against you, slowly spreading
			wider apart. The ratgirl is smaller than you, so attempts to stuff
			you inside will be just silly, but that doesn't stop her and you can
			feel how the tight pucker slowly stretches wider and wider, until
			suddenly it rolls all over your head. The greedy girl squeaks out and
			moans with pleasure, now sitting on your shoulders.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="impossible voyage" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
			Her insides are hot and really tight for you, especially as the
			girl
			leads your hands in between of her buttocks. Barely she’ll fit
			more,
			but still you can feel new pressure forcing your shoulders to
			slide
			in. Your face is easily visible on her tummy as the rat girl
			continues squirming around and tugging at the large prey. Her slimy
			bowels slowly stretch to fit more of your body, forcing you to curl
			through the fleshy tunnels.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="drawn deeper" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			You can only move your legs as the greedy rodent packs all of
			your torso
			inside, going to slow down and relax. After all bigger part
			of her
			prey is already tucked in tight and not going to leave any time
			soon.
			You can feel her tail poke and tickle at your feet, making you
			struggle more as she teasingly slow pushes your legs into herself.
			The thick, long outline of your body continues moving in her abdomen,
			filling more and more of the bowels, until finally the rat manages to
			shove even your toes into herself.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="struggle" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="submit" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="8" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			The ratgirl squeeks in distress as sooner after disappearing
			inside you
			recover your second wind and shove your way back out. She
			squirms
			helplessly on the ground as you extricate yourself, worming
			back out
			until you finally pop free a bit smellier and a whole lot
			less
			dignified.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggledigest">
		<text>
			Impossibly, you can't escape her rear. Clenched inside the
			rodentgirl's tight
			innards you cannot escape her little body, barely
			able to move you're
			forced to suffer the indignities of digestions as
			her body gets to
			work on making you hers. Enzymic slime coating your
			skin as she rolls
			forwards onto her massive belly, your shape well
			defined and outlined
			in her globular gut as you stretch it so greatly
			with your larger
			form. And she settles in to digest.
		</text>
		<choice destination="digestGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="digestGO">
		<text>
			The ratgirl can't move, but doesn't let that bother her. Dozing
			off
			resting atop her gut as the hours begin to tick by, that mass
			turning
			rounder underneath her as she digests away your body. Still
			more time
			passes and her pillow belly full of softening glop is now
			shrinking
			down. Some twelve hours later her middle shrinks down to
			nothing but
			a lingering layer of pudge as she rests now on the ground
			again. The
			chubbier ratgirl waking up and letting out a delighted
			squeek as she
			feels over herself, your profound indignity has been a
			profound gain
			for the rodent.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			You can barely move in the tight innards of the rodent and can
			hear her
			enzymes gurgle around you. The rat letting out pleased
			squeeks and
			murs as she shes over the only parts of her massive belly
			she can
			reach, she must be adorable. and it's too much bother to try
			and
			escape, you settle in to be food for the little rodent..closing
			your
			eyes as her insides start to ooze more digestive slime over your
			body
			and starts to break you down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="digestGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>


</Conversation>