<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="unbirth" />	
		<text>
		Amorously your lips meet with those of the serpent. The lamia clutching you close to her soft upper body as she seems to return your lust addled affections. Your faces mashed together in the kiss and her tongue probes and explores your mouth in a welcome intrusion. Her coils shift under you, lifting you up on a muscular loop of scaled flesh as she continues making out with you and all you can think about is the sexy serpent who has you in her arms.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="her naughty desires, revealed"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth0">
	<text>
	The sensation of the lamia's ample breasts pressed against your chest and the feel of her wonderful lips against yours is enthralling. So enthralling in fact that you barely notice her hitching your lower body up with her tail until you feel something hot and wet squeezing around your feet. You pull your lips from hers to take a look and hear her mhmm as her lips are freed, looking down you find your feet sliding into her hitherto unseen nethers. The scales having parted to let her feed you feetfirst into her bright pink sex.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth1" text="a welcoming snake pussy isn't that bad right?"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
	<text>
	The lamia clutches you against her chest and rocks her hips, rthythmic schlurping and schlicking noises audible and with each one more of your legs disappear into her steaming clef. Her birthcanal and womb seeming to extend deep into her tail as you feel your calves and then thighs plunge straight into her warmth without needing to bend your knees. Like entering an intimate sleeping bags you're steadily fed down and into the lamia's womb as she moans in delight.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth2" text="...mhmmm so good"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
	<text>
	Sinking ever lower you see the lamia look down at you with a lustful smile afore your view is eclipsed by her breasts. The lamia working your hips down into her netherlips and moaning all the while as you slip into her wonderful warmth. That hungry sex schlurping you deeper as you feel her hold on you shift up to grasp you lightly around your shoulders, the scent of her sex wafts up all around you as your head gets closer to disappearing into her loins.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth3" text="soon to be enwombed, so exciting"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth3">
	<text>
	The lamia groans in pleasure and you feel her nethers clenching around your upper body as she shifts her hands over to your head. Finally she places both hands firmly on the top of your head and gives it a shove, forcing you down into her sex with a delighted gasp. You don't hear that of course, as the lewd schlurk of her nethers around your ears swiftly becomes all you can hear as you vanish into her loins. Engulfed entirely in her warmth you can't help but shiver in bliss, stretched out in her seemingly bottomless womb. Your form serving as a bulge within her tail as you squirm to pleasure yourself within her. The hot juices soaking every inch of you as you hear her moan and fondle herself.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthSubmit" text="let her have her way with you"/>
	<choice destination="unbirthPleasureCheck" text="try to make 'friends' with her with your magic hands"/>
	</page>

		<check ID="unbirthPleasureCheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureEndo" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureDigest" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="pleasureEndo">
	<text>
		You try to give back and amplify all the pleasure you're feeling and set to work with your hands, after all you're inside this lamia and it might be a good idea to make her want to keep you around. You search the elongated womb with every inch of your body looking for pleasure points, hearing the lamia almost immediately responding with moans to your magic hands. The lamia masturbating to your motions within her as you squirm and rub around in her squelching depths. As your fingers play over her insides like a pianist through a master piece you hear the lamia's pleasured noises becoming all the more delighted. The lamia masturbating and shifting her hips as you pleasure her from within.
	</text>
	<choice destination="pleasureEndo0" text="climactic mercy"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pleasureEndo0">
	<text>
	The lamia shudders and you feel her body spasm all around you, squeezing blissfully over your body in a way that's quite overwhelming...for a moment all is bliss in the liquid, heat and soft pressure of her depths. When you finally come to your senses you're almost surprised to find you're whole, unliquidated within the murring lamia. Your predator resting her hands on the tailbulge you make as she lays sprawled and coiled in afterglow, she feels you stir and gives the shape in her tail a pat but takes no other action.
	</text>
	<choice destination="pleasureEndo2" text="rest here..."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pleasureEndo2">
	<text>
	With your safety and the good will of the lamia secured you relax, basking in the hot depths of her womb. Lamia wombs make the best sleeping bags anyway and though you wriggle occasionally for the most part you get a wonderful rest deep inside of her. Time passes, you're not sure how long or whether you fell asleep or not, but now you begin to feel that maybe just maybe you should resume your adventure rather than press further on the lamia's hospitality. Wriggling you start to worm your way out into the open air, pushing your hands up above you through her nethers and hearing her gasping as she shifts around. But she makes no effort to stuff you back down inside of herself, letting your hands into the open followed by the rest of you as you pull yourself out of her. The lamia looking at you with a blush, seems a lot less aggressive. But you should get clear lest you get lust addled by her again.
	</text>
		<effect type="imprison" value="400" />
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="pleasureDigest">
	<text>
		You try to give back and amplify all the pleasure you're feeling and set to work with your hands, after all you're inside this lamia and it might be a good idea to make her want to keep you around. You search the elongated womb with every inch of your body looking for pleasure points, hearing the lamia almost immediately responding with moans to your magic hands. The lamia masturbating to your motions within her as you squirm and rub around in her squelching depths. You can feel hear her moaning and thrusting her hand in and out of her nethers as you stimulate her from within, the fleshy walls rippling and kneading over you. You become one with the motion, rubbing and grinding yourself against the flesh around you with countless moans.
	</text>
	<choice destination="pleasureDigestGO" text="one with the motions"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="pleasureDigestGO">
	<text>
	You move with the movements of her pleasure, feeling and hearing her orgasm approaching as she's stimulated and stimulates herself. As you hear her gasping and feel her spasm though you realize you're moving with the rthythm of her insides, but not moving of your own volition...all you've done is make her orgasm you quicker. The lamia's womb has turned you into a soft weak and mostly sloshy form and as you comprehend this you hear the last thing you hear, the sound of her pleasured cry beginning afore her womb squeezes in on you. Your form sloshing apart under the pressure and turning into a gush of pleasure, erupting out as an orgasm to splatter her front and form a raunchy puddle of sexual juices staining the ground. You failed to convince her to keep you around it seems, but you did manage to make an oh so satisfying orgasm for her.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="unbirthSubmit">
	<text>
	You moan in delight as you soak in her juices, hearing the lamia delving one hand wetly into her sex above you and fondling her breast with the other. As she shifts her tail rthythmically you find her womb walls rubbing against you wonderfully each time she rocks back and forth. It feels amazing, the pleasurable sex fluids soaking into your flesh, marinading you in lusty liquid. All is motion and warmth, pleasure and liquids, and you of course. You rock with her motions, pleasuring yourself, letting all that wondrousness wash over you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthSubmitGO" text="all there is is liquid and pleasure"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="unbirthSubmitGO">
	<text>
	Lust shivered through you as it did through the serpent, blinding you with pleasure to what transpires as her womb converts you steadily into the lustful fluids you're bathing in. As her pleasure rises yours ends up consuming you, vanishing in utmost bliss within her your last moments are exquisite and then you are no more. The lamia shuddering and then climaxing, spasming as she thrusts her arm into her snatch and feels her nethers erupt with fluids, splattering hot girl fluids out onto her scales and surroundings. Every ounce of you renderd down for her pleasure and now, forming a sticky stain on the ground beneath her panting and lustful form.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
</Conversation>