<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			This database stores hundreds of thousands of bytes on the finest in magnetic reel to reel data storage technologies. You might be able to access the databank and 
		</text>
		<choice destination="databank" text="access databanks" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="databank">
	<text>
	DIRECTORY: LBREAK
	SOLAR POWER PLANT LBREAK
	SPECIMEN CONTAINMENT SYSTEM LBREAK
	CAPTURE DEVICE LBREAK
	SELECT FILE
	</text>
	<choice destination="solar" text="access file, solar power plant"/>
	<choice destination="containment" text="access file, specimen containment system"/>
	<choice destination="capture" text="access file, capture device"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="logout" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="solar">
	<text>
	The data flashes up screen by screen as you analyze it. The solar plant seems to use a series of mirrors to focus sunlight on a central element, heating it up to a formidable temperature in order to create electrical energy. It's an unconventional but effective way of generating power so long as you can deploy the mirror.
	</text>
	<special effect="blueprint" ID="solar plant" />
	<choice destination="databank" text="back"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="logout"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="containment">
	<text>
	The data scrolls by steadily. Blueprints for a device that's perhaps euphemistically named specimen containment. It uses a form of suspended animation to sustain and contain alien lifeforms inside a suspension capsule. It also comes with a form of teleportation relay link that may be utilized to transfer a lifeform to the capsule without inconvenience.
	</text>
	<special effect="blueprint" ID="specimen containment" />	
	<choice destination="databank" text="back"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="logout"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="capture">
	<text>
	The images linked to this design seem to briefly make you worried you've found the death star plans. But no this device is much smaller, handheld, and apparently a teleportation device used to teleport the target to a linked teleportation relay. It probably takes quite a while to lock on so you wouldn't be able to use it as a weapon in combat. It's also useless without a teleportation relay to act as its target, but with it you can probably get some good use out of this.
	</text>
	<special effect="blueprint" ID="capture device" />	
	<choice destination="databank" text="back"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="logout"/>	
	</page>
</Conversation>