<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>


	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="talked" />		
		<text>
		"Greetings again <conditional>
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance" value="1" />
				ser knight
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance" value="0" />
				traveller
			</conditional> what do you seek with me today?" she asks with a smile.	
		</text>
		<choice destination="training0" text="I am interested in having my first lesson">
			<preference fetish="herms" />	
			<preference fetish="demis" />		
			
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="7" />	
		</choice>
			<choice destination="training1" text="I am interested in having another lesson">
			<preference fetish="herms" />	
			<preference fetish="demis" />		
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="training" value="1" />				
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="5" />	
		</choice>	
	<!-- 		<choice destination="training2" text="I am interested in having the last lesson">
			<preference fetish="herms" />	
			<preference fetish="demis" />		
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />	
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="training" value="2" />				
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="3" />	
		</choice>	 -->
		<choice destination="job5" text="About the dragon woman">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="1" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="3" />		
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="job3" text="About those monsters">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="1" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="5" />		
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="job1" text="About those gators">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="1" />
		<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="7" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="aboutTraining" text="Do you train all your soldiers the same way?">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="trainingKnown" value="1" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="job0" text="I was curious if you had any work for me?">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="0" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="job2" text="I was curious if you had any more work for me?">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="7" />		
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="0" />		
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="job4" text="I was curious if you had another challenge for me?">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="5" />		
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="0" />		
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="Nothing, at the moment..but perhaps later"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training2A">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training2ARefuse">
	<text>
	"I can see that we'll need to work on your obedience my little soldier." she says and then smirks "But do you really believe that after all that has come before you won't eventually up inside me?" she chuckles "Run along, come back when you realize that some things are inevitable."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="You are a crazy lizard, farewell."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job4">
	<text>
	"You have come a long way. I think you are ready for this. Draconians have returned in recent times to bring suffering to our people. Perhaps their coming is tied to the clearing of the path to our ancient enemy? But no matter, draconians are prideful and with their power they have much to be prideful over. But I believe you have the potential to lay them low. There is no hidden meaning, humiliate one of these arrogant winged reptiles and then return."
	</text>
	<choice destination="job4Accept" text="Very well I will do this thing"/>
	<choice destination="job4Refuse" text="you expect me to a be a dragon slayer? I refuse."/>		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job4Accept">
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="1" />			
	<text>
	Varliss smiles and replies with a profound intensity "Yes, take these arrogant dragons. Humiliate them with their defeat, reduce them and degrade them as you force them to submit to you and show them for the lesser."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="With pleasure"/>
	</page> 
	
	<page ID="job4Refuse">
	<text>
	"As is your right. You surely know yourself now. You know whether you are truly ready better than I. Very well, return when you find yourself worthy."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Maybe, until then farewell"/>
	</page>		
	
	
<page ID="job5">
	<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="3" />	
	<text>
	"Did I not tell you to strip one of these haughty dragons of their pride? Go, defeat one. Show her that her arrogance is no match for your worthyness. Then return, I will reward you most well though the task alone should be reward in and of itself."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Right, humbling a draconian, got it"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="job5">
	<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="3" />	
	<text>
	"Have you done as I asked? yes, I can see it in your eyes. Was her humiliation exquisite? did you heap depredations on her once she was in your power? No matter. Surely with this you have felt the joy of raising yourself up by bringing one low. And when the one brought low falls from high station born of accomplishment and ability, so much the better no?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job5Reward" text="yes, but you also promised gold"/>
	</page>	
	
	<page ID="job5Reward">
	<text>
	"Yes I suppose you have earned it, that draconian will plague us no more. Here, take it." she says and then smiles "And perhaps, when you are ready. I will give you the final bit of training, you will find it a complimentary experience to your last challenge I feel."
	</text>
		<effect type="givegold" value="2000" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt2" value="3" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="yet more training? well, i'm sure that will be interesting"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'm only interested in gold Varliss, gold and nothing else."/>
	</page>		
	
	<page ID="aboutTraining">
	<text>
	"Maybe I do. Or maybe, maybe you're special and I've singled out to be trained like this. And maybe it'd spoil the fun if you knew which was which, just pick whichever answer you find more pleasant."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="That is no kind of answer, but i suspect its all i'm going to get"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, excellent. I think you know how this needs to go." she says <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />and indeed you do, Varliss likes to give her training to naked trainees. So you undress in preparation to begin.
			</conditional> "Today we'll work on your stance, after all, a soldier should know how to handle a sword." she says with a smile "now, keep your gaze straight ahead of you. arm out in front of you like so. One foot behind you, other forwards, now..lean forwards..no not like that, let me help you" she says as you obey her instructions and assume the position as she slips up behind you. Varliss reaching one hand out to your arm to adjust your position, but as she does..
	</text>
	<choice destination="training1A" text="*you feel something prodding against your behind*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1A">
	<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />	
	<text>
	You feel her tip lining up with your netherlips as she guides her shaft right where she wants it. "Now, lets see how you can really handle a sword" she says and then adds "Don't flinch, don't move." as a command as she thrusts into you, her shaft stretching you out as she plunges her length deep into your body. Her hips soon flush against your rear and her breasts smooshed against your back warmly as she penetrates you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="training1BA" text="*this, this is fine*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1BA">
	<text>
	"Keep your stance, a real soldier wouldn't let a little something like this spoil their poise." she says as she begins to thrust "Although, it IS a big something. Wouldn't you agree?" she asks as her hips move back and forth, slapping against your own as she pounds away at your sex, embracing you from behind and keeping one hand on your arm and the other on your hips as she fucks you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="training1CA" text="it's...big"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1CA">
	<text>
	Finally between her moans Varliss gives you permission "At ease, soldier" she tells you, and you untense, easing and relaxing into the fucking you're receiving. Leaning further forwards and planting your hands on your thighs as your moans join her own as you screw with all the more vigor now you can properly enjoy it.
	</text>
	<choice destination="training1DA" text="*almost..almost*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1DA">
	<text>
	Varliss's vigorous pace picks up, rocking you back and forth. She keeps both hands on your hips to steady you as her shaft pumps in and out of your nethers "Don't you dare fall" Varliss demands before letting out a lustful cry as her cock spasms, pumping hot seed deep into your womb as she bottoms out against your hips. Varliss waiting till she's shot her last spurt of cum deep into your snatch before pulling her cock out of you, smiling as she gives your rump a pat "You handle a sword well soldier. I enjoy training you, return should you need..a repeat lesson."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="training" value="2" />		
	<choice destination="end" text="I might very well, one never knows when ones swordswomanship might need checking"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="Perhap, or maybe I'll just stick to fighting monsters"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1A">
	<assertnot evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
	<text>
	You feel her tip prodding between your rumpcheeks as she guides her shaft right where she wants it. "Now, lets see how you can really handle a sword" she says and then adds "Don't flinch, don't move." as a command as she thrusts into you, her shaft stretching you out as she plunges her length deep into your body. Her hips soon flush against your rear and her breasts smooshed against your back warmly as she penetrates you.
	</text>
		<choice destination="training1BB" text="*this, this is fine*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1BB">
	<text>
	"Keep your stance, a real soldier wouldn't let a little something like this spoil their poise." she says as she begins to thrust "Although, it IS a big something. Wouldn't you agree?" she asks as her hips move back and forth, slapping against your own as she pounds away at your rear end, embracing you from behind and keeping one hand on your arm and the other on your hips as she ploughs your back passsage.	
	</text>
	<choice destination="training1CB" text="it's...big"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1CB">
	<text>
	Finally between her moans Varliss gives you permission "At ease, soldier" she tells you, and you untense, easing and relaxing into ass reaming you're in the process of receiving. Leaning further forwards and planting your hands on your thighs as your moans join her own as rock your hips back to meet her thrusts. Getting more into the buttfucking now you can properly enjoy it.
	</text>
		<choice destination="training1DB" text="*almost..almost*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training1DB">
	<text>
	Varliss's vigorous pace picks up, rocking you back and forth. She keeps both hands on your hips to steady you as she ploughs your rear end. "Don't you dare fall" Varliss demands before letting out a lustful cry as her cock spasms, pumping hot seed deep into your bowels as she bottoms out against your asscheeks. Varliss waiting till she's shot her last spurt of cum deep into your rear before pulling her cock out of you, smiling as she gives your rump a pat "You handle a sword well soldier. I enjoy training you, return should you need..a repeat lesson."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="training" value="2" />		
	<choice destination="end" text="I might very well, one never knows when ones swordswomanship might need checking"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="Perhap, or maybe I'll just stick to fighting monsters"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training0">
	<text>
	"Excellent, when you're ready we can begin" she says and smiles. <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />"Though of course, a soldier has no other identity, you'll need to take off your clothes for your training" she says and waits for you to undress before they could get started.
			</conditional>
	"Now, a soldier must bring even their breathing into obedience. Sit down..close your eyes, and focus." she says, you hear her moving to stand in front of you as you obey. "now, breath in, breath out...slow deep breaths." she continues, letting you focus on the exercise for about a minute before adding "now, breath in, then open wide as you breath out."
	</text>
		
	<choice destination="training0A" text="*open wide*"/>
	<choice destination="training0Refuse" text="*disobey*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="training0A">
	<text>
	You open wide as instructed, exhaling only to find something abruptly filling your mouth as she continues quickly "A soldier must accept the unexpected, and in all things keep in mind what will please her superiors" says Varliss, as she slides more of her thick length past your lips and reaches a hand down to stroke through your hair. Your training taking a not unexpected lewd turn as your tongue is flooded with the musky taste of her shaft.
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="trainingKnown" value="1" />	
	<choice destination="training0B" text="*suck her off like a good soldier*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training0B">
	<text>
	Varliss seems to enjoy your obedience, or maybe just your tongue action, as a full throated moan emanates from deep within her and she rocks her hips, thrusting her length in and out of your mouth "Yes, I can see you understand the importance of serving to the..best of your abilities.." she says and then shivers a little and smirks "you really are quite good at this, or maybe you're just eager" she says as she grabs ahold of the back of your head and ploughs your throat.
	</text>
	<choice destination="training0C" text="*mhmmph!*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training0C">
	<text>
	Varliss thrusts into your mouth firmly, vigorously using your lips and holding your head in place as she does so. Her hefty sack bumping up against your chin with each thrust she takes as her moans become louder and more delighted. As she feels her balls clench she speaks up again "A soldier must accept her reward readily when her superiors deem it fitting." she says, a warning of what's cumming soon.
	</text>
	<choice destination="training0D" text="narrator has terrible puns"/>
	</page>
	<page ID="training0D">
	<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="training" value="0" />			
	<text>
	Forwarned you swallow as you feel her length pulse and pump the first thick wad of seed into your throat. Varliss groaning as she continues thrusting, spasming her hips and then finally stopping and just holding her dick deep in your mouth as she pumps out her seed. Only when she's pumped out her last spurt of seed does she pull out and smile "mhmm, obedient..I'll make a 'soldier' out of you yet." she says and helps you up "Training is over soldier, but come back again any time."
	</text>
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="training" value="1" />		
	<choice destination="end" text="Mhmm, well that was much more enjoyable than expected, I might do that"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="Ah yes, i'll come back if i need..training, again"/>
	</page>
		
	<page ID="training0D">
	<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="training" value="1" />			
	<text>
	Forwarned you swallow as you feel her length pulse and pump the first thick wad of seed into your throat. Varliss groaning as she continues thrusting, spasming her hips and then finally stopping and just holding her dick deep in your mouth as she pumps out her seed. Only when she's pumped out her last spurt of seed does she pull out and smile "mhmm, obedient..I'll make a 'soldier' out of you yet." she says and helps you up "Training is over soldier, but come back again any time."	
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="I'll do that mistress"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="I'll do that Varliss"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="training0Refuse">
	<text>
	Varliss tut tuts, but doesn't bring it up directly. she continues the breathing exercises for a time and then simply calls an end to it and as you get up smiles and chidingly taps you on the nose "Remember, a soldier, is obedient. No matter what" she says and then shoo's you off.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="huh."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job2">
	<text>
	"You hunger for further challenge? or perhaps for further tutelage. Good. Prove yourself. There are fearsome beasts in the mountains north of here, their muscles are like rock and their teeth are like iron. If you have the mettle then go and defeat these tyrant lizards. Three should prove an apt task for you, face them without fear."
	</text>
	<choice destination="job2Accept" text="Sure, I can do that"/>
	<choice destination="job2Refuse" text="These things sound scary, I'd rather not"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job2Accept">
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="1" />			
	<text>
	"Excellent, return triumphant and perhaps I will continue your training if you are ready." she says with a smile.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Training, and a reward."/>
	</page> 
	
	<page ID="job2Refuse">
	<text>
	"Perhaps I misjudged you. Many others fear to travel into the mountains as you do. There is no shame in the unexceptional. But perhaps if you wish to prove yourself apart, come to me and we will see whether you have the heart for it."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="You have a strange philosophy, but if i change my mind I'll come back"/>
	</page>	
	
<page ID="job3">
	<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="4" />	
	<text>
	"Come now. You cannot return without wisdom. All things have a purpose, and though the death of the lizards will help my people the challenge is in itself a lesson for you." 
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="A lesson, well I suppose I should get on with it"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="job3">
	<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="4" />	
	<text>
	"Ah, you have returned eager for more training? Or perhaps you simply want the gold for your service to the people of Dammath." she smiles and looks you over "You have bested the lizards?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job3Reward" text="Yes, they proved less fearsome than their appearance suggested"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job3Reward">
	<text>
	"And that is the lesson, surface is nothing but a mask. All things have hidden depths, to probe, to explore, to understand. Inside everyone are facets of their personality that even they might not be aware of. Do not trust first impressions, seek the truth in all things. As I will should I train you further." she says and rewards you with gold your efforts, gold and a side order of philosophy.
	</text>
		<effect type="givegold" value="1000" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt1" value="5" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="Further training? well, i'm sure that will be interesting"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'm only interested in gold Varliss, gold and nothing else."/>
	</page>	
	
	<page ID="job1">
	<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="6" />	
	<text>
	"I can tell from your bearing, something about your stance. You haven't done it yet have you?" Varliss says with a soft hmm, looking you over and seeming to sense that you haven't yet slain that which is your task to slay.
	</text>
	<choice destination="bodylanguage" text="How on earth can you tell that from just how I stand?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="you're right, I'll come back when I'm done"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="bodylanguage">
	<text>
	"How does one know where the blade will fall if you cannot read the intent of the wielder? And a keen eye can serve even when no weapon is drawn."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="I see, I think. I'll come back when I'm done"/>	
	</page>

	<page ID="job1">
	<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="6" />	
	<text>
	"Ah, you have returned eager for training? or merely hungry for gold." she smiles and looks you over "You have killed the beasts?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="job1Reward" text="Yes, but you seem to already know that"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job1Reward">
	<text>
	"Of course, I know the air of victory when I see it. That confidence that's born of triumph in the face of adversity." she says and smiles "So here is your reward...and soldier, if you need training...ask. I'm sure I could find a way for you to better serve."
	</text>
		<effect type="givegold" value="500" />
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="7" />	
		<choice destination="end" text="The way you talk of this training intrigues me, i might very well take you up on that"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="It's just the gold I'm interested in, when we speak again it'll be on the subject of more work."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job0">
	<text>
	"So you have a desire to serve? Very good, very interesting. And very well, there are things I need to have done. We'll see how you fair, gators have strayed into the village of late. Thin their numbers to stop this happening. Kill five and I'll be satisfied." she says and then leans in "And of course, do this and there will be a reward...and perhaps i could train you to be a soldier?" she says suggestively.
	</text>
	<choice destination="job0Accept" text="Sure, I can do that"/>
	<choice destination="job0Refuse" text="Are you kidding? those things are bloody lethal"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="job0Accept">
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="Varless_monsterhunt0" value="1" />			
	<text>
	"Excellent, I look forward to an opportunity to train you. Return with word of your accomplishment, and soon." she says with a smile.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Of course. I'll try to hurry back."/>
	</page> 
	
	<page ID="job0Refuse">
	<text>
	"A soldier needs more than obedience, courage is also required. And were they not dangerous there would hardly be a reward, return should you change your mind."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="Yeah if I want to pick fights with more gators I'll come calling"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"
			flag="talked" />	
		<text>
		The warrior gives you a nod at your approach "Greetings <conditional>
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance" value="1" />
				ser knight
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance" value="0" />
				traveller
			</conditional> I am Varless, you may of course address me as mistress." she says and smiles a little "For I am master of arms here and commander of the queen's soldiers."
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />			
		<choice destination="greeting0" text="$it's good to meet you Varless"/>
		<choice destination="greeting1" text="$It's good to meet you mistress"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="greeting0">
	<text>
	Varless grins "Too soon? don't worry, I've dealt with that before." she says with a chuckle "But come, i doubt you came here purely for that reason."
	</text>
	<choice destination="job0" text="I was curious if you had any work for me?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="no, I merely wanted to make your acquaintance"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="greeting1">
	<text>
	Varless grins "Promising, I think I like you." she says and then leans back with a chuckle "But come, I doubt you came here purely for that reason."
	</text>
	<choice destination="job0" text="I was curious if you had any work for me?"/>	
	<choice destination="end" text="no, i merely wanted to make your acquaintance"/>	
	</page>
	
</Conversation>