<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
<page ID="start">
<preference fetish="cockvore"/>
<text>
The zetamorph looms over you, grinning as she reaches one of her arms down between her legs and caresses herself to hardness. That thick shaft rising to attention, those heavy balls swaying as she runs that clawed hand up and down it. a glop of precum oozing forth from her shaft and striking the floor next to you as the musky odour starts to get stronger and she seemingly thrills with anticipation of your fate at her hands.
</text>
<choice destination="prelude" text="at her mercy"/>
</page>
<page ID="prelude">
<text>
She keeps on stroking herself while reaching out with another hand to heft you up, hauling you by a firm grip on your head so you're face to face with the slightly agape cumslit of her cock, another glop of pre oozing as if her cock is...drooling, hungrily drooling...for you. and she grins a little more as she sees the realization on your face.
</text>
<choice destination="cockvore0" text="into the dick"/>
</page>
<page ID="cockvore0">
<text>
With the moment having been drawn out for comprehension she wastes no more time in thrusting you facefirst into her dick. That thick blue shaft stretching easily around your face and lubricating you with a gush of pre. You feel her arms descend to grasp your body and lift you up, handling you as she feeds you to her hungry cock. A needy buck of her hips causing your shoulders to squeeze in with a schlorp. A second thrust all it takes to claim your chest as well.
</text>
<choice destination="cockvore1" text="down the shaft"/>
</page>
<page ID="cockvore1">
<text> You can feel her cock stretching around your upper body, snugly pressing around you as she feeds you in. Grasping your legs and midsection as she thrusts her hips, forcing you deeper down her cock. Hot copious pre making the sensation of being cockfood even more debauched, her moans and the throb of her cock as loud in your ears as the squeelch of pre flowing past them. 
</text>
<choice destination="cockvore2" text="deeper!"/>
</page>
<page ID="cockvore2">
<text>
Only her hands on your legs are left now as she forces you in all the way to your hips. Her other pair of clawed hands felt running up and down the bulging blue cock, running along the outline of your body bulging out her shaft and jacking you down into her balls. As your legs start to vanish inside her shaft you feel a tight pressure around your head then abruptly you're pushing through into a rooomier and far more debauched space. Her balls welcoming you with the thick overpowering scent of hot cum, your legs sliding down her cock after you forcing you to dunk headfirst into her jizz and start to curl within her swelling sack. All four of her hands on her cock now as she lets out a hissing chirr of pleasure and feels your feet vanish into her tip.
</text>
<choice destination="balls" text="all the way in"/>
</page>
<page ID="balls">
<text>
You can hear her moaning and hissing in delight as your legs disappear from the inside of her cock and pile into her balls along with the rest of you. Two hands stroking her cock, still jerking off though more leisurely..savouring the feeling as her other pair slide down to caress and fondle her balls, possessively cataloguing the bulges of your curled up form within her loins. Her hot cum churning and soaking every inch of you and flooding your senses with her liquid lust.
</text>
<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="try and force your way out"/>
<choice destination="pleasurecheck" text="try to make her ejaculate you out"/>
<choice destination="submitdigest" text="submit to being her cum"/>
</page>

<check ID="strugglecheck">
<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="12"/>
<outcome destination="struggleescape"/>
<outcome destination="struggledigest"/>
</check>
<check ID="pleasurecheck">
<test what="PLEASURE" DC="10"/>
<outcome destination="pleasureescape"/>
<outcome destination="pleasuredigest"/>
</check>

<page ID="struggleescape">
<text>
Through sheer strength you manage to force your hands back up through the base of her cock. a gasping hiss from your assailant indicating just how much she finds this sensation distracting giving you the chance to brace your feet against the inside of her churning sack and push yourself upwards. Wriggling through her cock vigorously leaving her gasping as you worm your way out of her shaft, pulling free covered in her cum and pre from head to toe. She's dazed now, but it wont take her long to set about putting you back where she thinks you belong.
</text>
<effect type="heal" value="0.1"/>
<effect type="stunnpc" value="10"/>
<choice destination="end" text="get clear"/>
</page>

<page ID="struggledigest">
<text>You push at the sealed base of her cock trying to force your way out, your feet slipping on the sticky insides of her sack. You hear her moaning and hissing in pleasure as she jerks off and massages her sack, but for all your efforts your fingers yield before the seal of the cock does. Your hands and feet softening and turning weak before melting into her cum, despite the now doomed effort you continue to struggle. even as your limbs soften and slop away until finally your head and shoulders sinks into the rising level of her jizz. Your form succumbing to her balls <conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>melting you right out of your <readequipment slot="2"/></conditional> as you become one with her sloshing spunk.
</text>
<choice destination="struggleGO" text="burble"/>
</page>
<page ID="pleasureescape">
<text> Your only chance is to pleasure her into ejaculating prematurely before you're melted into spunk. With desperate hands you set to work rubbing the inside of her sack. You can hear her let out a drawn out hiss of delight, masturbating as her sack her jostles around with your squirms as you rub the inside of the sack and 'help her along' despite the bucking hips you pay attention to her responses, finding her sensitive spots amidst the slick cum coating the inside of her balls and finally as your skin starts to turn worryingly soft she cums. Your form rocketing up out of her shaft to land in a splatter of her seed before her, she seems slightly dazed by the climax..but that's probably momentary.
</text>
<effect type="heal" value="0.1"/>
<effect type="stunnpc" value="10"/>
<choice destination="end" text="get clear"/>
</page>

<page ID="pleasuredigest">
<text>
Your only chance is to pleasure her into ejaculating prematurely before you're melted into spunk. With desperate hands you set to work rubbing the inside of her sack. Your fingers searching out sensitive nerve clusters to pleasure while you listen to her responses. The churning of her eager balls starting to take effect as you soften, getting creamier...your fingers mashing and spreading out against the inside of her balls. Your form starting to deform as her sack clenches inwards and she jerks off all the faster from your stimulating rubs, your diminishing limbs less and less able to pleasure her as your squirms change to sloshes. <conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>her cum liquidating right out of your <readequipment slot="2"/> as your form spreads out into the cum. <readequipment slot="2"/> left floating in the thick slosh of spunk she's turned you into. </conditional>
</text>
<choice destination="pleasureGO" text="slosh"/>
</page>

<page ID="submitdigest">
<text>
You feel her balls roil softly around you, churning you.. she's going to turn you into cum. And you can accept that, it's not like you could resist being shoved back down if you tried to escape anyway. You rub at the inside of her sack, feeling her hands pressing possessively on the sack..letting out a moan as you feel her cum permeating your body, soaking into you as she jerks off. Hot tingles spreading through you as you bath in her cum, softening, getting creamier. Turning into the zetamorph's cum, your entire body being boiled down into nothing more than a way of giving her pleasure. Her balls starting to round out as your limbs liquefy, and slowly..you subside and sink into her rising cum. Your body now just nothing but a load of her jizz.
</text>
<choice destination="submitGO" text="time to be her orgasm"/>
</page>

<gameover ID="struggleGO">
<text> Her sack is smooth now, your body reduced to a smooth mixture of nutbatter that sloshes and sways as she jerks off. The Zeta's eyes half lidded as she lets out a hissing cry as she reaches orgasm, spurting out your remains onto the floor.
<conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>your <readequipment slot="2"/> blasting out of her cock to land in the oozing sticky mess that once was you and now is just the cummy testament to her satisfying climax. </conditional>
</text>
</gameover>
<gameover ID="pleasureGO">
<text> The zetamorph lets out a delighted cry, raised to the heights of pleasure by her cockfood's attempts to stimulate her from within she bucks her hips. cock spasming in her hands as she ejaculates massives of cum her debauched cockmeal has now been turned into. Your entire existence ending in a briefly memorable orgasm for this alien and a huge splatter of jizz on the floor. <conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>your cum soaked <readequipment slot="2"/> the only indication other than sheer volume as to the providence of her seed.</conditional>
</text>
</gameover>
<gameover ID="submitGO">
<text>
The zetamorph feels the last of you slosh away as she jerks off, a hand reaching down to fondle her balls..the undeniable sensation that you'd enjoyed being melted down making her feel a little thrill run through her and she half lids her eyes as she feels her pleasure building. The zeta gasping as her spasming cock paints the floor white with your remains, all of your body now just a stain on the steel as she cums you out. She spends a few moments to smirk and admire her handiwork as she wrings the last glob of thick cum you'd made for her out of her dick..then turns away, ultimately while the pleasure of being melted into spunk had been the capstone of your existence..you were just another orgasm to her.
</text>
</gameover>
</Conversation>