<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		<text>
			The drake flew close after you fell, landing to nudge you with its nose
			and make sure you weren't getting back up anytime soon. It seems
			satisfied by the groan you let out and while you're busy trying to
			recover your strength and your pride you lose track of what the
			reptile is doing for a short time. It really is indignified to be
			downed by a critter smaller than you. Speaking of indignities though
			the drake abruptly impugns back on your perceptions with a whiff of
			musk, you're not sure how you didn't notice that erection earlier but
			as you look at the drake again you see a formidably large shaft
			hanging under the beasty, it probably can't even walk when hard like
			this.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="what is it planning to do with that" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			Maybe it wants to violate your mouth to add insult to injury? nope. The
			drake waddles forwards in a lurching almost gator esque thrash and in
			doing so presses its tip against, and around your face. The little
			lizardling actually plans on trying to feed you to its cock, such a
			preposterous indignity to inflict on you. But apparently no one told
			the little dragon that it's impossible to cockvore someone bigger
			than it is. The critter shoving its cocktip around your head and then
			schlurping you in with the surprising strength of its rippling cock.
			Your shoulders no match for the hunger of the drake's remarkable
			member as it works you inside despite the size difference between you
			two.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="oh the humiliation" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			The shaft of the lizard squeezes tight around your body as it humps and
			spasms to work you further inside. You can only imagine how visible
			your contours must be bulging out the drake's cock, your face print
			stretching out that shaft as you plunge deeper and deeper towards a
			humiliating fate as cockfood for the inferior critter. You can hear
			it chirring loudly over the sound of pre flowing past your ears and
			the reptile's cock throbbing and pulsating around you as it takes you
			in down to your waist with torturous slowness. You can imagine the
			drake must be having trouble cramming your body inside itself. But
			apparently it doesn't know when to quit as it starts to cram you into
			its tight but stretchy sack. The bulge made by your upper body
			curling in its sack forces its legs well off the ground and you can
			feel its hindpaws rubbing at the top of the bulge you make as it
			starts on your legs now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="to be utterly confined" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The tight and sticky confines keep you from putting up any meaningful
			resistance beyond light squirms as the lizard sets about drawing your
			legs inside. That feasting phallus of the drake having such a good
			grip on you that the critter doesn't even need to tug at your legs in
			order to consume you. Not that the lizard doesn't grasp at your legs
			anyway as they pass under it and into its jutting cocktip. Soon
			though you disappear inside the lizard's loins utterly, squeezed and
			curled up in the tight confines of its now massively stretched out
			sack. The drake perching atop the contoured shape of its balls and
			rubbing its legs and tail against the shape you make with a chirr.
			The little critter did it, it succeeded in devouring the big stranger
			with its cock, it must feel very proud.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submit"
			text="it's too cute and worked too hard for this cockmeal, settle in and let it churn you" />
		<choice destination="struggle"
			text="I am not about to get cummed out by a pintsize flying newt, i'm getting out of here" />
	</page>

	<check ID="struggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest0" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggledigest0">
		<text>
			You squirm around to try and find the exit, the damnable little lizard
			rubbing and kneading at the shape you make in its massive sack as you
			try to find the way back out. Your fingers rub around the inside of
			the churning sack in search of the cumtube that leads back up the
			shaft. Eventually finding it but finding it damnably hard to squeeze
			your fingers into it, shoving them with difficulty up the cum tube as
			you push against the inside of the reptile's balls with both feet,
			the sheer tautness of how much the lizard's sack has been stretched
			to contain you should provide something good to push off of. The
			drake hissing as its shaft bulges anew around your arms, and tries to
			squeeze you back down with the swallowing motion of its dick.. that
			cum covering you seeming to soak in as you struggle.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggledigest1" text="must escape" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggledigest1">
		<text>
			You push against the sack walls again to try and force your arms further
			up the drake's cock, but something seems wrong...the push makes
			things yield as you realize you're softening, taking stock you find
			your arms all weak and partially melty as you pull them free, it's
			already too late. This doesn't stop you futilely protesting this
			churny fate though as you push and shove at the gurgling and sloshing
			confines of the sack that holds you. That hot cum soaking into you as
			you get creamier and creamier inside that increasingly roundish and
			sloshy drake sack, the lizard rubbing its limbs against your shape
			all the while as you soften.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleGO" text="liquidated" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleGO">
		<text>
			The drake seems indecently satisfied by the sensations as you succumb in
			its sack, the lil lizard resting atop its massive sack as the bulges
			you make go round and soft. The sounds of your squirms giving way to
			exquisite gurgles and sloshes of a truly indecent and preposterously
			large load of thick cum. The drake doing its level best to wrap
			foreclaws around its length and jerk off. The proud little predator
			feeling your remains yield and shift with each movement as it adjusts
			its weight atop you and chirrs loudly while locked in blissful self
			gratification. Finally it seems the lizard reaches climax, and with a
			snarl it releases you up and out. That lizard dick working hard to
			pump all your remains out into the open air, forming a massive puddle
			that continues to spread as the lil drake's sack steadily squeezes
			back down until its feet finally land on the ground under it once
			again. The cute critter taking a few moments to survey its handiwork
			afore fluttering back into the air, probably thinks its the best
			drake ever.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			You're not sticking around to get sloshed into a waterbed for this lizard
			and you start rooting around in search for the way you came in. You
			just need to squeeze back up that lizard dick. Luckily you find it.
			And it was more luck than anything else as you force your fingers
			into the tight tunnel of that drake cumtube, pushing off against the
			stretched taut flesh of its sack with your feet. The drake letting
			out a disgruntled meep as it's shaft is stretched and you push
			yourself up against the ripples of its cock until you hook your slick
			fingers against the cumslit of the reptile. From there despite the
			little critter's best efforts you manage to pull and wriggle your way
			back out into the open air. The drake left whimpering and whining
			behind you. The critter licking at its loosened sack and sore shaft,
			it probably wont be going after you anytime soon.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			The lizard really is kinda cute, you feel it rubbing over the bed of its
			own balls that it's resting on and you can't help but settle in. It
			earned this load you're going to make. The chirring critter's
			stretched sack starting to steadily churn and burble around you as
			you let it have you. The drake's hot cum soaking into your body and
			making you slowly soften within the reptile's loins, melting away
			ever so slowly and the contours of the sack starting to soften and
			round out. Your sensation of relaxation increasing as you churn until
			you find you've spread out and softened too much to move even if you
			wanted to. Nothing to do but sink into the cum it's made of your body
			now...
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitGO" text="burble" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitGO">
		<text>
			The drake pushes one foreleg against its sack with a chirr, feeling it
			fluidly yield but push back with the pressure of all that tightly
			contained seed. The lil lizard lets out a little mip and wraps its
			foreclaws around its shaft now. The lizard knowing that everything in
			its sack has been rendered down into thick and goopy nutbutter that
			needs to be released, at the very least so that said little lizard
			can actually move around again. The reptile setting about fapping
			away with chirrs and mips of delight, jerking off while resting atop
			the massive inflated pillow of its own cumfilled sack until with a
			blissful hiss it reaches climax. The lizard's cock erupting,
			splattering your remnants out in thick high pressure strands of jizz
			to form a naughty mess in front of itself. Those strands joining
			together into a puddle that deepens and spreads as the reptile
			finally starts to get its sack smaller and more manageable and
			finally down to the point where it can walk again as its orgasm
			tapers off. Several dozen gallons of jizz now forming a huge steaming
			puddle and a testament to the little lizard's big accomplishment.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>