<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="demis" />	
		<preference fetish="herms" />
	<text>
	The victorious icetreader lets out a pleased rumbling purr as she pins you down, kneading at your body menacingly with her forepaws as she looks down at you. She grins and you find any hope of mercy draining from your being, and then she's grabbing you up from the snows with her powerful arms <conditional><assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />and tearing your clothing with a forepaw to expose you 
			</conditional>. You feel her shift about as she presses you against her breasts, then the air turns musky as she settles down onto her haunches, and you feel something hot and broad pressing against your asscheeks.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck0" text="ohfuc-"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck0">
	<text>
	You don't even get to finish your thought before she shoves you down and rocks her hips up. Your pucker stretching and yielding before her massive shaft as she forces her length into your bowels in one brutal eye watering thrust. You hear her growling in delight as she shifts and grasps one of your legs with a forepaw and then places both hands on your shoulders and despite your pleading looks she pushes you down onto her dick further. You feel your insides stretching and pressing out around her throbbing shaft, your belly distending with the shape of her cock afore she flings you down onto your back beneath her and pins your arms so she can start using your ass properly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck1" text="*used*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck1">
	<text>
	Pinned down you can do naught but look up with desperate pleading as she starts to rut your rear end. But she can't even see your expression past her own impressive bust as she shoves her cock repeatedly into your violated rump. Each time she thrusts you feel her cock pressing up into your belly, its contours bulging your gut as she uses your ass as a cocksleeve. Her immense shaft ramming deep inside, jostling you back and forth under you each time she finishes a thrust. Not even using her full length to fuck you as she picks up her pace to an even more intolerably vigorous excess, your pucker's never gonna be the same.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck2A" text="*deeper?!*(all the way through warning)"/>
	<choice destination="fuck2B" text="*finish*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck2A">
	<text>
	You feel her thrusts straightening out your insides, forcing you to conform to her cock as you realize, she's going deeper. But there's no way she can do that right? wrong, you feel her cocktip thrusting up through your chest, a little deeper with each thrust. It seems impossible, but as you feel her cocktip pressing up past your collarbone and stretching your neck out around its girth you realize that she will make her cock fit in you. You can taste her pre, her musk, welling up into your mouth as her thrusts work their way through you until her cocktip is stretching out your cheeks and butting against your lips from the inside.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck3" text="*impossible fucking*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck3">
	<text>
	The rumbler fucks you mercilessly, your body now shaped by the contours of her cock thrusting through your torso as she batters against your lips. Overcoming your resistance until with a final thrust and a grunt she shoves her cocktip out past your mouth, spearing you entirely on her cock from end to end and then growling in delight as she just revels in the sensation of cold air against her slick tip and your body sheathing her throbbing length. But your reprieve is short lived, as now she starts to thrust through you again..her cocktip sliding towards your lips then thrusting back away as her pleasure builds. You can already tell that it won't be long now.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck4" text="*let it end*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck4">
	<text>
	You hear her growl and grunt in pleasure over you. Her massive balls slapping against your thighs and asscheeks each time she hilts her cock through you, her pace vigorous. Your insides stretched and your rear end sore from the perverse and thorough use she put you through you would sigh in relief if able as you feel her cock throb and pulse finally. Her orgasm sending cum jetting first out of her tip, then from your lips as she starts to pull back and draw her cocktip through your abused innards. Her third massive spurt surges up your throat to spill through your mouth and nose and her following wads of seed are pumped deep into your belly as she draws out of you. Finally her cock pops free leaving you to gasp and whimper on the ground underneath her as she rumbles in pleasure and glances down at you laying there leaking her seed into the puddle that surrounds you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*and then she eats you*"/>
	<!-- <choice destination="cockvore0" text="*first you around it, then it around you*"/>	 -->
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck2B">
	<text>
	The thrusting motions of the taur soon reach a merciful crescendo, that throbbing cock pulsing and splattering your innards with hot seed. Each pulsing ripple of her length felt intimately through your over stretched innards until she's spent and pulls out of your gaping stretched rear end. Her cocktip oozing out a splat of goo onto the slurry of molten snow under your well fucked ass as you hear her purring in satisfaction and shifting her position over you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*and then she eats you*"/>
	<!-- <choice destination="cockvore0" text="*and then she puts you in it*"/> -->
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>	
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	Her warm presence disappears from above you, but the sore glow of the reaming easily keeps you from feeling the chill. Though that chill seems short lived as she lifts you up off the ground beneath her with both hands, licking her lips as she brings you face to face with her hungry grin. You can only squirm weakly as her tongue licks over your face, unmindful of the musky scents you're slathered in as she pulls you closer and mashes you against her breasts. Before her jaws stretch wide to encompass your head and everything goes dark.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*post rutting snack*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The icetreader is rough and perfunctory with you as she swallows. Her powerful throat dragging you on down as her grasp shifts down to your hips and lifts them up. Your body sliding into hers even as you still leak out her seed from your rear end, unable to put up a significant struggle as she swallows up your upper body. Her midriff furless midriff on her upper body stretching out around your head, shoulders and then showing the contours of more of you as she gobbles down into the depths of her tauric belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*taur food*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	You feel the last trace of cold air against your lips vanish as she seals her jaws shut behind your toes and swallows. Your form entirely plunging into the stiflingly hot depths of her belly. The taur gut hanging low with your weight, large enough for you to occupy her stomach without curling but eagerly pressing around you on all sides nonetheless. It's clear from the sticky fluids that you'll soon be naught but a meal, the use of your body completed by her primal need for food just as it was by her primal need for a fucktoy.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralStruggleCheck" text="*resist*"/>
	</page>


	<check ID="oralStruggleCheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="17" />
		<outcome destination="oralStruggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralStruggleDigest" />
	</check>	
	
	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleEscape">
	<text>
	Not wanting to end up a meal you set about struggling to escape her gut. The fur of her belly shifting with the wobbling motions of her gut as you shove around inside her. Becoming a most disagreeable morsel to her in short order it seems as she growls and shifts and tries to suppress your motions by sitting down to squish you in her belly. But instead she seems to give you somewhere to push off against, and despite the reaming having left you a bit weak in the knees you seem to still have a desperate strength with which to shove yourself back out of her. The rumbler's tolerance finally being exceeded helps take you the rest of the way as she horks you up out into the snow, looking distinctly put out and nauseous from your internal pummeling you might have a chance to run away before she comes after you again.
	</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleDigest">
	<text>
	Not wanting to end up a meal you set about struggling to escape her gut. The fur of her belly shifting with the wobbling motions of her gut as you shove around inside her. Becoming a most disagreeable morsel to her in short order it seems as she growls and shifts and tries to suppress your motions by sitting down to squish you in her belly. Your form constrained by her hefty bulk pressing down over you, stilling your movements as the goopy fluids of her digestive processes start to soak your form. Every inch of your body soaked in hot enzymes as you try to push at her tightly squeezing innards and force her into horking you up, but to no avail. You can feel your flesh starting to melt down and digest under the onslaught of her innards.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreStruggleGo" text="*gurgle*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvoreStruggleGo">
	<text>
	Trapped in the sweltering darkness you feel your body succumbing. Melting into a goopy mass in her gut as she doesn't even try to pin her unwilling meal anymore. Striding along now  her gut sways and steadily softens and rounds out. Your form turning into a compact slurry as the rumbler claims your body as yet another meal. As she absorbs your form she is probably already forgetting the snack whose ass she'd ravaged, heading off into the snows. Only the diminishing bulge in her gut and the cooling splatter where you were rutted left as a testament of your doom.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	


</Conversation>