<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"
			flag="talked" />
		<!-- first time -->
		<text>
			"Hey star traveller. Can I ask like a huge favour of you?" the lizard
			smiles brightly, though as she continues to get it out her gaze
			lowers and she blushes "see I'm Suri and well, I'm not quite ready
			for breeding, but I kinda wanna feel what being a mom is like. Can I
			maybe...practice on you?"
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
		<choice destination="unbirthA0" text="sure, sounds fun">
			<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="not interested" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="talked" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="0"
			flag="times" />
		<!--refused -->
		<text>
			"Oh uh, hi star traveller..have you changed your mind? I can't ask
			anyone else, and I really wanna know how it feels to hold another
			inside me like that."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthA0" text="yeah i changed my mind">
			<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="no I havent" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="talked" />
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="greaterthan"
			value="0" flag="times" />
		<!--subsequent times -->
		<text>
			"ooh, hi again. What can I do for ya?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthBcheck" text="Do you want to practice some more?">
			<preference fetish="unbirth" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="no I havent" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthA0">
		<text>
			You follow Suri out of view
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				and undress as Suri giggles and blushes
			</conditional>
			"Almost can't believe I'm getting to do this." she says as she undoes
			the wrap around her hips. Her hairless snatch now revealed between
			the softness of her tanned inner thighs. Already moist she sets the
			wrap aside and then lays out on the ground, spreading her thighs "I
			think you should just like...crawl in?" she suggests with a blush and
			a chirr as she reaches down to stroke her sex, soaking her fingers
			then spreading her slit in invitation to you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthA1" text="get closer" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthA1">
		<text>
			Suri giggles a bit and twitches her tail under you as you settle onto
			your knees and then crawl fowards towards the open invitation of her
			nethers. That tail rubbing up between your own legs naughtily as you
			lean in to give her a lick. That lick making the tail twitch and
			flick underneath you as Suri chirrs "ah, mhmm...nice but i'm already
			wet enough for ya." she says and then giggles, using her free hand to
			mash your face lewdly against her netherlips. The naughty lil lizard
			moaning as you nuzzle into her, and then steadily part her folds
			around you. Your head disappearing inside her with a lewd schlorp,
			her thighs clenching around your upper body instinctively as her warm
			channel tugs you deeper inside her. Suri's silken soft warm welcoming
			your head as you push yourself deeper inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthA2" text="deeper" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthA2">
		<text>
			"oh, oh my this is...wonderful" suri exclaims with a gasp, sliding a hand
			up to tenderly rub the bulge made by your head and shoulders inside
			her. You can't help but agree, her warmth welcoming you as you push
			off against the ground with your feet. More of your body disappearing
			between her thighs as she chirrs and pants in delight, clenching
			rthythmically around your midriff, then hips until only your legs are
			left outside of her. Her middle now distended, bulged, massively
			pregnant with your upper body curled inside the cradle of her womb. A
			delightful embrace you cannot help but crave for the whole of your
			body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthA3" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthA3">
		<effect type="passtime" value="75" />
		<text>
			"almost there...thanks so much for...mhmm" Suri moans in delight and
			clenches, dragging your legs deeper inside. She can't see past the
			massive dome of her belly, now can she seem to keep her hands off of
			it as she draws you steadily the rest of the way inside of her womb.
			Her inexperienced sex seeming quite adept at tucking you away
			completely within her as your feet vanish between her thighs and she
			gasps in delight. "Ooh...ah, comfy in there? feels so good to have
			you. Hope you don't mind if I keep you in there for a while, I want
			to enjoy this."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthAend" text="fine with me Suri" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthAend">

		<special effect="marktime" />
		<text>
			The bulge in Suri's middle is treated good naturedly by the other
			villagers of Dammath as she hauls you around. Your form cradled
			snugly within her own for what's probably several hours as she enjoys
			doting on her taut tummy with strokes and pats now and then. It's
			during this period you find her warm softness luls you into sleep.
			Sometime later though you awaken to her clenching "ah, sorry. But I
			kinda wanna be slim again, hope you don't mind?" she says
			apologetically as she pushes you out exactly where you went in, your
			stuff still in the bushes nearby. Suri blushes as she rises to her
			feet and puts her skirt back on "It was fun though, I hope you
			enjoyed being womb filler for me." she says with a smile.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="1.00" />
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="times" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end"
			text="It was fun suri, maybe we can do it again sometime" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthBcheck">
		<condition evaluate="TIMEPASSED" operator="lessthan" value="3" />
		<text>
			"Eh, already? eager one aren't you. It's not that I didn't enjoy having
			you in there, it's just can we do it a bit later?" she smiles
			apologetically, blushing as she turns your offer down.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'll come back later" />
	</page>
	<page ID="unbirthBcheck">
		<condition evaluate="TIMEPASSED" operator="greaterthan"
			value="3" />
		<text>
			"...mhmm, eager to get all tucked away inside my womb again hmm? Sure. Though
			I think this practice is starting to be more for your benefit than
			mine" she teases with a blush.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthB0" text="whatever you say 'mom'." />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthB0">
		<text>
			Suri blushes deeply as you tease her right back "stoppit." she
			protests, but smiles. It's clear that it appeals to her maternal
			instincts even if it does make her embarassed. She slips back into
			the bushes, slipping off her skirt again
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				as you undress and get ready as well
			</conditional>
			. Suri laying out and assuming the position, thighs spread, one hand
			tracing down between her legs to invite you into her warmth again
			"Mhmm, well then, come inside your momma" she says with a giggle,
			blushing a bit deeper as she tosses the word back at you and you work
			first one hand, then both of them, into her hot nethers. The lizard
			starting to chirr in delight as you work your hands all the way into
			her up as far as her womb, sliding your head into the heat of her
			inner embrace.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthB1" text="back inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthB1">
		<text>
			Suri's nethers tug gently around your shoulders and chest, drawing you into
			her warmth inch by inch with more ease than the first time. The
			lizard gasping, chirring and running a hand over her middle in
			delight as you begin to nestle into her warm insides. Her tail
			curling up around you lovingly as she clenches and tugs inside your
			middle, her own midriff stretching wonderfully as your upper body
			gets situated. Her warmth, her snug embrace, all of that washing over
			you as you try to tug your legs past her netherlips faster, wanting
			to curl up entirely inside this caring young lizard.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthB2" text="all the way" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthB2">
		<effect type="passtime" value="75" />
		<text>
			"mhmm eager aren't we." remarks Suri and moans, eyes slipping closed as
			she arches her back and tugs your legs inside. Your feet sliding up
			between her thighs, and disappearing as she clenches her legs
			together forcing them up past her netherlips. The lizard's womb
			encompassing you entirely yet again as you curl once more in her
			wonderfully snug embrace. Suri laying there chirring in delight and
			tracing a hand over her middle as gradually you settle inside her,
			lulled by the warmth, softness and the steady rthythm of her body
			around you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthB3" text="nap" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthB3">

		<special effect="marktime" />
		<text>
			The sight of Suri playing with her new friend again garners little more
			than doting smiles. Not that you would notice, encompassed entirely
			within the darkness of her womb you are asleep within her warmth in
			minutes. Your last waking thought before pleasant dreams have their
			say how nice the lizard is to heft you around like this and keep you
			warm and safe inside her. Time passing with her curling up in her own
			bed, protectively wrapped snuggling around the bulge of your form as
			she sleeps.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="1.00" />
		<choice destination="unbirthBend" text="wake up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthBend">
		<!-- transformation phase 1, no scales, no tail -->
		<preference fetish="transformation" />
		<condition evaluate="SCRIPT"
			src="alpha_minoris_II/saurianSuri/suri_phase0" />

		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--herm -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="type" set="0" bodychange="add" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="5" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="0" />

		</special>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--female -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" negative="true" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="type" set="0" bodychange="add" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="3" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="0" />

		</special>
		<!--patchy scales -->
		<text>
			You awaken to the sensation of something different, but can't figure
			out quite what it is. Suri's attention is quickly garnered by your
			movements as you squirm around and try to feel over yourself to
			figure out the strange sensation. The lizard pausing what she's doing
			to glance down and rub a hand over her pregnant domed out middle
			"Mhmm, you're awfully restless, ready to be let out?" she asks and
			then takes your movements as assent and steps into the privacy of the
			bushes. The young yet motherly lizard squatting down and gasping as
			she tenses and squeezes you out steadily. Your form spilling out into
			the open air as she groans and lets out a chirr, and as you settle
			moistly onto the ground the change you felt earlier is revealed.
			<macro id="scale_colour_desc" />
			scales glistening on your limbs, dappling in scattered patches along
			your body. Suri's eyes widening in surprise "oh, ah, i didn't expect
			this to happen." she says and fidgets placing her fingers together
			"please tell me you're not mad?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="It's okay, I kind of like it" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Well this is an unwelcome surprise.." />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthBend">
		<!-- transformation phase 2, patchy scales -->
		<condition evaluate="SCRIPT"
			src="alpha_minoris_II/saurianSuri/suri_phase1" />
		<preference fetish="transformation" />
		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--herm -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" />

			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="5" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="2" />

		</special>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--female -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" negative="true" />

			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="3" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="2" />

		</special>
		<!-- limb scales -->
		<text>
			You awaken to realize that you must of absorbed more saurian DNA from
			Suri while you were sleeping. As you can feel the somewhat familiar
			sensation of a change having been worked upon you while you slept.
			Feeling over your arms and legs you can feel smooth scales now
			covering almost the entirety of your limbs, You prod at the inside of
			the womb to get Suri's attention. The saurian settling with a bit of
			trepidation behind some bushes to squeeze back out. Your
			<macro id="scale_colour_desc" />
			new scales gleaming wetly in the light as Suri gasps and leans back
			blushing as you looks down at you and you stretch slowly "Mhmm, you
			know. I think you look cuter with scales." she says and reaches down
			to help you up. Suri is rather unapologetic, but then, you went in
			again after last time, you must like having more saurian genes. And
			Suri seems willing to gradually transform you into one of her own
			kind.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="I'll have to think about whether I want to go the whole way" />
	</page>


	<page ID="unbirthBend">
		<!-- transformation phase 3, no tail -->
		<condition evaluate="SCRIPT"
			src="alpha_minoris_II/saurianSuri/suri_phase2" />
		<preference fetish="transformation" />
		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--herm -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" />

			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="5" />
			<mutation part="tail" variable="type" set="0" bodychange="add" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="3" />

		</special>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<!--female -->
			<criteriaAssertion part="penis" negative="true" />

			<mutation part="scales" variable="colour" set="3" />
			<mutation part="tail" variable="type" set="0" bodychange="add" />
			<mutation part="scales" variable="covering" set="3" />

		</special>
		<effect type="setfactionflag" flag="allegiance" value="1" />
		<effect type="manipulatefactionflag" faction="minyos" flag="allegiance"
			value="-1" />
		<effect type="manipulateDisposition" faction="minyos" value="-25" />
		<effect type="modfactiondisposition" value="25" />
		<!--all but face and back scales, also grows tail -->
		<text>
			You're familiar by now with the sensation of waking up to changes
			inside the adorable Suri. But this change is more drastic than
			others, sharing space with an ample fleshy mass that turns out to be
			a part of you and anchored to your ass. A long lizardy tail of your
			own. Suri feels you squirming around and then giggles, eager to see
			what's happened this time she sways her way into the bushes and
			squats down with a smile. She gasps and mhmms and then shudders in
			delight as you push out of her headfirst, slowly easing out until you
			slip free, your long tail last to emerge and ooloured
			<macro id="scale_colour_desc" />
			like the rest of your scales that now cover all but your face and the
			front of your torso. You've fully gone native now it seems. Suri
			smiles and leans in to give you a smooch "I guess I made you one of
			us now, this was better than I could of imagined." she says and then
			gives your still damp form a hug, sliding hands down to stroke your
			tail before disentangling. Though Suri's grin probably isn't going
			away any time soon.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="It's one way to make friends I suppose." />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthBend">
		<text>
			You awaken sometime later, from the angle you can tell Suri is up and
			about and push out to get her attention. You hear her giggle around
			you and make her apologies to whatever muffled individuals she was
			interacting with before walking back to the bushes where your stuff
			was stashed. The naughty lizard patting her middle and then squatting
			down, the familiar clench and release of her insides pressing around
			you as gradually you're eased out into the world. Emerging headfirst
			into the cool air once more as she gasps and groans above you,
			squeezing you out inch by inch until your feet finally pop free of
			her sex. Suri taking a few moments to lick over you with a smile
			"Mhmm, hope you enjoyed. But I think that's enough inside time for
			you don't you?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="for now yes, but perhaps later." />
	</page>

</Conversation>