<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="ferals" />
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			As you lie on your back, defeated, the Gator stomps over to you, hunger
			in it's eyes.
			It quickly seizes your feet in it's large jaws, taking a few quick
			gulps to swallow your calves. You try and drag yourself out of the
			Gator's hungry maw, but your hands
			find no purchase in the boggy ground. The Gator licks over you, enjoying
			your flavor, and it seems to stare straight into your eyes with a
			primal hunger. The lukewarm, slimy flesh of the Gator's
			maw can be easily felt, constricting your legs and feet.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="devoured" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The gator moves quickly, using it's bulk to force you down it's gullet
			as it walks forward. The walls of the esophagus are tight and slimy,
			forcing your legs together in the
			lukewarm tube. When the Gator reaches your hips, it tosses it's head back,
			causing you to slip in up to your breasts. The Gator licks over your
			flesh with it's long, reptilian tongue, letting out a hiss
			of satisfaction. You pound on the Gator's head in an attempt to make it
			let go, but as soon as it starts to bite down, you stop. You wimper
			as more and moe of your body is claimed by the Gator, and escape
			seems more and more hopeless.
			Most of your body is now trapped in the crushing tube, and it is nearly
			impossible to struggle. The Gator wastes no time in continuing it's
			meal, intent on sending you down into it's stomach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />

	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Your arms are forced above your head as the Gator starts to swallow your
			shoulders. You can feel your feet enter the Gator's stomach as you
			stare at the ridged roof of it's mouth.
			Your view of the outside is framed by rows of razor sharp teeth, with
			your hands grapsing uselessly at the air, trying to find purchase on
			something. One more swallow is all it takes to seal you inside
			completely, the teeth clacking shut.
			Another swallow and you are forced to curl up in the acrid chamber, a slimy
			liquid already pooling at your back. The walls start to churn and
			squish more digestive fluids on your skin,
			starting to break you don into nothing more than meat. You need to escape
			soon, while you can still breathe and the stomach acids are low.
			Otherwise, you may very well end up as the Gator's meal.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="struggle" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="submit" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submit">
		<text>
			You sit in the Gator's gut quietly, accepting your place in the food
			chain. The Gator was better than you, so it ate you; you are it's
			prey and nothing will change that.
			You adjust your position to try and live your last moments in relative
			comfort, as the muscular walls of the stomach squeeze around you,
			coating your body in digestive juices.
			It isn't long before the acids reach your chest, and your entire body
			burns. You take one last breath of the acrid, malodorous air and then
			breaht no more as your consciousness fades.
			After your body is nothing more than meat in it's gut, it swims over to a
			small patch of land and goes to sleep,
			caressing it's bulging gut with it's tail. In a few hours, all that's left of
			your body is a jumbled mess of bones and a meaty slurry, which is
			piped through the intestines where the Gator's
			body absorbs your nutrients. By the next morning, you will be entirely
			digested, giving the Gator strength to swim around and catch more
			prey.

		</text>
	</gameover>
	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			You thrash around as much as you are able, feeling your struggles press
			against the reptile's spine. The discomfort is enough to upset the
			Gator, and you force your hands into the esophagus. Pushing against
			the stomach walls
			with your feet, you manage to get your forearms past the sphincter.
			Feeling a squishing all around, you make another attempt to push
			yourslf out, and manage to get your head and shoulders past. You
			squirm and crawl out as best you can,
			trashing about to try and get the Gator to open it's mouth, evidently kicking
			a nerve.
			The Gator lets out a roar of pain and anger at it's meal escaping,
			allowing you to squirm out of the mouth and pull yourself free. As
			you struggle to stand, covered in slime, the Gator retreats into the
			brackish water to recover it's senses. Now would be a good time to
			escape.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggledigest">
		<text>
			The Gator swims lazily through the waters, enjoying the thrashing of
			it's prey. Inside, you can hear and feel the sloshing of water
			outside the Gator's stomach, making it even more frustrating to know
			that you are so close, yet so far, from the outside.
			The Gator rumbles deeply in satisfaction, having thoroughly enjoyed your
			desperate squims. But now it sensed you were at your end, soon to be
			nothing more than food. The Gator floats calmly, licking the last of
			your flavor from it's mouth.
			After your body is nothing more than meat in it's gut, it swims over to a
			small patch of land and goes to sleep,
			caressing it's bulging gut with it's tail. In a few hours, all that's left of
			your body is a jumbled mess of bones and a meaty slurry, which is
			piped through the intestines where the Gator's
			body absorbs your nutrients. By the next morning, you will be entirely
			digested, giving the Gator strength to swim around and catch more
			prey.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>