<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="ferals" />
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			That last blow flings you to the ground and the beast rumbles
			threateningly it's clear that it could crush you flat. But instead it
			proves itself less of a herbivore than you thought as it drops its
			scooplike jaws low and seizes your feet inside them. It's hot wet
			breath washing over your calves as it lumbers forwards and with a
			dreadful glucking gulping sound forces your feet into its throat
			proper. It's short fat neck shows little in the way of bulges as it
			eats you alive.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="treated as food" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The dumb creature continues swallowing you down, impersonal both
			in its
			dimwitted animal nature and its supposedly prey orientated eyes
			neither of which can orientate on you as it swallows your legs. Its
			steaming hot innards greeting your feet as it works you down into its
			belly, its gut starting to sag down between its legs as it eats you
			alive.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />

	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Unmindful of your weak struggles it forces you down, working up
			over your hips
			and then lifting its head and your upper body up off
			the ground. The
			arkosaur's jaws flex wide as it gulps, dragging part
			of your middle
			past its jaws as they wrap tight against around your
			torso. And then
			it repeats the procedure, chugging you down like the
			bothersome large
			morsel you are. Your efforts to grab its jaws and
			halt your descent
			no match for the power of its body epitomized in the
			throat rippling
			around you. Despite your struggles you find yourself
			consumed, the
			last you see of the outside world framed by your
			protruding arms and
			its roundtoothed jaws.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="consumed" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			You feel the beast move off again, lumbering with the low
			hanging weight
			of your curled up form in its gut brushing against the
			grasses but
			impeding the saurian herbivore very little. Your body ably
			contained
			behind stomach walls and reddish brown hide as it resumes
			its
			motions, adding to the vegetative detritus surrounding you as it
			grazes and its gut gurgles. That sweltering stomach gearing up to
			break down a far more protein rich meal. It might be best to try and
			force an escape lest you be smothered in pulped grass or ground down
			into slurry within this stomach, blandishments needless to say will
			serve you little to escape this primeval beast.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="struggle" />
	</page>


	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			The beast is clearly unaccustomed to a meal that struggles and
			moves
			around, letting out a series of grumbling bellows as you push
			around
			at its insides. It's stomach glorping hotly around you as you
			shove
			at the churning walls, back and forth making the arkosaur's
			belly
			sway and jostle against its legs. The upset finally too much it
			seems
			as the creature lets out a strangled bellow and shudders,
			horking you
			up in a deluge of plantmatter and ooze. It's unpleasant,
			but at least
			you're out safe. And if anything it was even more
			unpleasant for the
			arkosaur that slumps onto its belly with a
			distressed snort.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggledigest">
		<text>
			The beast is clearly unaccustomed to a meal that struggles and
			moves
			around, letting out a series of grumbling bellows as you push
			around
			at its insides. It's stomach glorping hotly around you as you
			shove
			at the churning walls, back and forth making the arkosaur's
			belly
			sway and jostle against its legs. The beast waddling forwards,
			and
			tearing up a thick mass of plants. Clearly the arkosaur's solution
			to
			a grumbling stomach, the damnedest thing is it works.. the mass
			pouring in atop you impedes your movements, cushions your shoves
			against the beasts insides. A few more masses and half smothered in
			plantmatter you're forced to abandon your attempts. The stomach
			enzymes forming a soup of dissolving plantmatter around you that will
			soon add your body to the mix as well.</text>
		<choice destination="struggleGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleGO">
		<text>
			The beast continued lumbering about, only eventually settling
			down to
			digest you. Settling on its belly it presses the glorping mass
			around
			you, making it even harder to escape even after having made it
			impossible. Gradually you fade away, the beast ruminating in an empty
			headed doze as within you employ the last of your energies in a vain
			attempt to stay above the gloop before succumbing. The beast's
			stomach is unused to dealing with meat, but your body is broken down
			just the same even if it is a long and slow process. Within two days
			nothing remains in its belly but the vegetation its constantly
			packing into its maw, all you amounted to was nothing but an extra
			layer of fat padding the beast's flanks. Truly the most ignoble of
			ends.
		</text>

	</gameover>

</Conversation>