<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			You have defeated the robot. Now disabled, it slumps into a heap of tangled
			robotic limbs and actuators.
		</text>
		<choice destination="extractComputer"
			text="Try to remove its computational components." />
		<choice destination="extractOptics" text="Try to remove something from its weapon system." />
		<choice destination="extractPower" text="Try to remove the power unit"/> 
		<choice destination="end" text="Do nothing." />
	</page>

	<check ID="extractComputer">
		<test what="TECH" DC="11" />
		<outcome destination="computerSuccess" />
		<outcome destination="computerFail" />
	</check>

	<page ID="computerFail">
		<text>
			You attempt to extract the computational parts of the robot intact but
			your lack of skill just leads to you breaking them in an inept attempt
			to rip them out. They're useless now, but at least you have a few
			wires and chunks of the robot's casing as a souvenir. Or maybe it'll serve can as a paperweight, or raw material for future use.
		</text>
		<effect type="giveitem" value="1" item="scrap metal" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Ah well, better luck next time." />
	</page>

	<page ID="computerSuccess">
		<text>
			You attempt to extract the delicate computation valves. The devices take
			a careful touch to extract from the surrounding systems but your steady
			your hands and manage to successfully extract a computation valve
			from the robot's brain, so to speak. To celebrate, you dismantle some of its
			wiring and casing for some additional raw material.
		</text>
		<effect type="giveitem" value="1" item="computation valve" />
		<effect type="giveitem" value="1" item="scrap metal" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Excellent!" />
	</page>

	<check ID="extractOptics">
		<test what="TECH" DC="13" />
		<outcome destination="opticsSuccess" />
		<outcome destination="opticsFail" />
	</check>

	<page ID="opticsFail">
		<text>
			You think you should try and extract the robot's weapon system, 'cause everything is
			better with lasers. Alas you're not as capable of that as you think you are
			and the robot's combination sensor and laser focusing optics is reduced
			to uselessness by your fumbling.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Damn it!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="opticsSuccess">
		<text>
			Looking at the robot's head, it's probably not possible to
			extract the laser system whole-cloth in any fashion that would be
			convenient or even possible to weild, but some elements may
			still be valuable. You set about dismounting the optical lenses and mirrors
			from inside the robot's otherwise empty head and soon enough, you have
			some relatively intact optical components for future use.
		</text>
		<effect type="giveitem" value="1" item="optics" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Well, at least these might come in handy." />
	</page>
	<check ID="extractPower">
		<test what="TECH" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="powerSuccess" />
		<outcome destination="powerFail" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="powerFail">
		<text>
			You set about attempting to extricate the power supply from deep inside the machine. Alas somewhere in trying to disengage it you must of done something wrong, there's a flash of arcing as something shorts out in a spectacular fashion. The device now emanates a sickly aroma of burnt plastics and fried electronics..yeah, you might of bungled this.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Damn it!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="powerSuccess">
		<text>
			You delicately remove the power supply from deep within the robot's innards. Having to disengage various damaged electrical circuits from it and unhook it from the chassis takes a good deal of skill but such you have in ample amounts. You've acquired a battery from the robot's guts, huzzah.
		</text>
		<effect type="giveitem" value="1" item="battery" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Excellent." />
	</page>
</Conversation>