<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="talked"
			value="1" />
		<!--subsequent meetings -->
		<text>
			"Greetings again star traveller."
		</text>
		<choice destination="history" text="$I would like to know your history" />
		<choice destination="statue0" text="$you misplaced something?">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="quest"
				value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="statue1" text="$about that statue">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="quest"
				value="1" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="friends"
			text="$I wish to be more than a stranger to your people">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="rockscleared"
				value="1" />
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance"
				value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="area" text="$can you tell me more about the surrounding area?"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="$farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<!--first meeting -->
		<text>
			The priestess seems to be frowning and searching around the room when
			you approach, but stops and her eyes alight upon you swiftly "Forgive
			me star traveller, I have misplaced something of mine. It is most
			distracting" she sketches out some form of ritualistic gesture "I am
			Shanna, keeper of histories, speaker for the spirits and priestess of
			this village."
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
		<choice destination="history" text="$I would like to know your history" />
		<choice destination="statue0" text="$you misplaced something?">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="quest"
				value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="area" text="$can you tell me more about the surrounding area?"/>
		<choice destination="end" text="$nice to meet you but farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="area">
	<text>
		"Very well, I suppose it is not unreasonable that you benefit from my wisdom rather than stray on your own and stumble into somewhere tight and digestive. I know much of the lands to the south and the west."
	</text>
	<choice destination="west" text="$What lies to the west?"/>
	<choice destination="south" text="$What lies to the south?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$On second thoughts I'll not take up more of your time"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="west">
	<text>
	"To the west lies a fertile yet perilous jungle. You can brave its winding paths if you wish, and many do to forage for fruits. But I should warn you the area is beset with voracious lamia, their coils are strong as the trees that surround them and should they entrap you your submission will be swift in coming. As will you ending up a melting bulge in their tail." she pauses a moment and then continues "If you should somehow survive the jungle though there are open lands beyond them. The creatures there are strong when roused to anger, so keep your distance."
	</text>
	<choice destination="south" text="$and what about the south?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$my thanks, that is all i require for now, farewell."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="south">
	<text>
	"To the south is a valley which is the only land upon which the tastey Deku nut tree will grow. Which is a shame as it is beset by raptors, these lizard folk cannot be bargained with and will devour you with a surety once they have laid you low with their claws. The only saving grace is they lack courage when alone. We think perhaps they make their nest in the ancient ruins. You should avoid the ruins if you can, they are dangerous as the last person to travel there did not return."
	</text>
	<choice destination="person" text="$Who was the last person to travel to those ruins?"/>
	<choice destination="west" text="$and what about the west?"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$my thanks, that is all i require for now, farewell."/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="person">
	<text>
	"Her name was Zhan, she was a scholar whose wisdom almost matched my own. She sought to re-connect us with our stolen past. She went to the ruins to search for answers in the relics of our foremothers. She was well armed, skilled and had friends of valour at her side, but none returned from her expedition. So I tell you now, avoid the ruins in the valley."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$an unfortunate fate, but perhaps there's something to discover, farewell"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="$thank you for the warning, i'll make sure to keep clear of the ruins"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="friends">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG"
			flag="friendship" value="1" />
		<text>
			"You have proven yourself stranger, your deeds are known. You have given
			of yourself to the village of minyos. So yes, if you truly wish I
			will declare to all the village that you are our friend and ally,
			ever to be welcomed and provided for by our people."
		</text>
		<choice destination="allegiance" text="yes, i am sure." />
		<choice destination="end" text="I need more time to think about it" />
	</page>

	<page ID="allegiance">
		<text>
			The priestess brings you before the village, ringing a bell to bring
			forth additional green elves to gather. And announces to them "You
			see before you the stranger from the stars, she came to us alone. She
			did not know us, yet she gave of herself to us. Now she has affirmed
			her desire for a deeper friendship. So it is time for us to give of
			ourselves to this stranger, you are alone no longer, we will comfort
			you, we will protect you, we will provide for you. and though your
			journey may take you far, know that we will always welcome you. Let
			all know that you are kin of the queendi, and rejoice." after the
			ceremony there is much cheering and celebration. You have sworn
			allegiance to the village of minyos.
		</text>
		<effect type="setfactionflag" flag="allegiance" value="1" />
		<effect type="manipulatefactionflag" faction="saurian" flag="allegiance"
			value="-1" />
		<effect type="manipulateDisposition" faction="saurian" value="-25" />
		<effect type="modfactiondisposition" value="25" />
		<choice destination="end" text="end" />
	</page>

	<page ID="friends">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="friendship"
			value="0" />
		<text>
			"Yes? you want us to call you friend? and what have you done for the
			Quendi?" the priestess asks with a sardonic eyebrow "Go, show that
			you are friend of quendi, then we will call you friend of quendi."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'll think about it" />
	</page>
	<page ID="history">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="friendship"
			value="1" />
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="rockscleared"
			value="0" />
		<text>
			"Normally I would not share such things. But you have proven a friend of our
			people. So I will tell you. For many generations we have lived upon
			this, our home. In peace we traded with star travellers such as
			yourselves who visited this world. All this ended when the ancient
			enemy came from the stars. They invaded seeking our land and our
			wealth. These reptilian monsters were relentless, we fought them and
			the struggle lasted many years. Their evil depredations caused us to
			lose many wonders we once knew. Finally we called upon the great
			spirits of the sky, who destroyed the ancient enemy. The way to what
			was once their lands forever cut off."
		</text>
		<choice destination="raptors"
			text="the lizards in the valley are still around" />
		<choice destination="end" text="My thanks, farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="history">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="friendship"
			value="1" />
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="rockscleared"
			value="1" />
		<text>
			"Normally I would not share such things. But you have proven a friend of our
			people. So I will tell you. For many generations we have lived upon
			this, our home. In peace we traded with star travellers such as
			yourselves who visited this world. All this ended when the ancient
			enemy who now plagues us once more originally came from the stars.
			They invaded seeking our land and our wealth. These reptilian
			monsters were relentless, we fought them and the struggle lasted many
			years. Their evil depredations caused us to lose many wonders we once
			knew. We thought they had been wiped from this world, but have seen
			them abroad upon our lands once more."
		</text>
		<choice destination="raptors"
			text="you don't mean the lizards in the valley do you?" />
		<choice destination="end" text="My thanks, farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="raptors">
		<text>
			"The lizards you speak of are a pale imitation of the evil of their
			progenitors. When we drove them forth the callous creatures did not
			seek to take with them their unborn young, several clutches survived
			and grew to be the ones of which you speak. But without the words and
			wisdoms of their foul ancestors they are but little threat, they're
			actually rather tastey and alone are no match for a Quendi."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="My thanks, farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="history">

		<text>
			"Our history is not to be shared with outsiders."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I meant no offence, farewell" />
	</page>
	<page ID="statue0">
		<!-- establish quest -->
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="quest" value="1" />
		<text>
			"Ah so good of you to ask traveller. I've misplaced a statue, it has
			ritual significance. But if it's not here it must be in the village
			somewhere. If you could do me the favour of fetching it for me I
			would be ever so grateful."
		</text>
		<choice destination="look" text="can't you find it yourself?" />
		<choice destination="end" text="I'll go look" />
	</page>

	<page ID="look">
		<text>
			"Yes but I am expecting a visitor soon. And I wouldn't want to leave this
			place unattended. Besides, you're a new visitor here and have an
			adventuresome look to you. You're probably going to search the entire
			village for hidden secrets or other such nonsense while bothering the
			residents so you may as well be useful to me while you do so."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I guess you have a point" />
	</page>

	<page ID="statue1">
		<!-- has item -->
		<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
			item="elf statue" />
		<text>
			"You found it. Here, it's not much. But I believe it's appropriate you
			have this gold for your assistance." she says taking the statue from
			you and handing you a small bag of gold for your troubles.
		</text>
		<effect type="setfactionflag" flag="friendship" value="1" />
		<effect type="removeitem" item="elf statue" value="1" />
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="quest" value="2" />
		<effect type="givegold" value="50" />
		<effect type="experience" value="25" />
		<choice destination="end" text="you're welcome" />
	</page>

	<page ID="statue1">
		<!-- does not have item -->
		<text>
			"I'm sure the statue is in the village somewhere. Have you looked
			everywhere yet?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I'll keep looking then" />
	</page>

</Conversation>