<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
		The wolfgirl's lost some pride and more importantly her bat after her defeat. She growls as you approach her, staggering to her feet with difficulty and swaying "Don't be looking at me like that, I ain't done yet." she says, despite evidence to the contrary and the way a gentle push could knock her over.
	</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="$Don't be looking at you like food? but you are food">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="$All I see is a worthless ballfodder in denial about where they're about to go">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="Put that doggy tongue of your to work and I won't report you to the wardens">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	"What? no! you can't just do that to me, I ain't gonna let you.." she says as you <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />free your beast and</conditional> stroke your member to a nice big and hungry state of arousal. You can see the ruffian mustering up her strength and ire as you prepare yourself "..you'll see, I'm gonna clobber ya but good if you try and lay a-glomp that thing on me." she says, her gaze drifting to that gaping drooling cumslit before she shook her head, reared back and took a swing at you. Her move was slowed by her weakness and nicely telegraphed though, which makes your response choreographed as you grabbed her plunging fist and guided it straight into your cocktip. The ruffian letting out a yelp as she sinks elbow deep in your cock in one unfortunate move.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="$See, you're nothing but a pitiful cocksnack"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	"I ain't, I ain't and I'll show you..you can't just..I won't just.." she whimpers as she tries to pull back against your hungry cock and it doesn't seem to be doing her much good. She's no match for the ravenous clenching tug of your shaft pulling her deeper in, her eyes widen as she's brought closer to that cocktip and your musk provides an overpowering scent for the wolfy. You further reinforce her inevitable fate though by shoving your hips forwards, the wolfy letting out a yelp as you engulf her head and dominate the ruffian with your dick. She's just cockfood, destined to be melted up good. And while she might struggle, that she's going to be your seed is not in doubt. The thought makes your cock throb and ripple hungrily around the girl and drag her deeper inside.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="$That's it, just accept it....you're just a walking refill"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	The wolfgirl's reply is muffled as your feisty cocksnack slides deeper and deeper inside of your shaft. Her squirms making your shaft bob and sway as you engulf her shoulders and chest and fill the halls with the sounds of your moans and lewdly schlurping cocktip. Your shaft bulging out even more as you cram her hips and especially her arse into your length. The muffled protests of her humiliating fate are now coming out more coherent and mixed in with splutters and gurgles as she begins to slide down into the place where she belongs, where all cockfood belongs, your ravenous balls.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="$mhmm, so good, get in me cumfuel"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	The wolfgirl protests "Not cumfuel! gonna get out of here, not giving up, going to whoop your ass once I--gah" she splutters loudly, defiant even as she's fed down into your sack. The ruffian putting on a brave and tough facade as you slurp up her legs and she vanishes into your loins entirely. The feisty toughgirl reduced to a jostling and bouncing set of bulges making your balls all satiated and saggy. Her protests and struggles bring a smile to your face and a throbbing insistent hardness to your well fed cock as she squirms and sloshes about in your seed.
	</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore4" text="$mhmm, really..but how are you going to do anything to me when you get out of there...you're going to be cum"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4">
	<text>
	"I'm not..I'm gonna...melting? i'm melting in here..let me out.." her tough facade breaks and yields up a pleading and desperate demeanour as your churning balls start to break her down. The loud glorps of cum around her toecurlingly exquisite for you and goopily panic inducing for her. Your cockfood puts up a nice struggle, but second by second and churn by churn you feel her weaken and fade away. Fade away until there's nothing but...cum.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="$mhmm, all gone, time to let you out and see if you can give me that..whooping..silly wolf"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	You make good on your indulgent promise with self indulgence. Feeling the wolfy rendered down entirely into sloshing cum inside of your sack you begin to stroke off. Your masturbation is leisurely at first, but then more vigorous as you feel the heady need to cum out all that seed become more insistent. Finally like a volcano of pure lust you erupt, sending her remains gushing out of your cock to splatter on the deck. The wolfy ruffian turned into a mere creamy splatter and puddle of your satisfaction. Her clothing resulted in brief spasming ripples of your cock as they interrupted the flow but are soon mired in the mess made of the rest of her. For all her fight, your cock made an easy meal of her.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />		
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"I ain't food! why you, I oughtta..come here so i can." she starts, and doesn't get to finish as indeed you do come here..but only to grab her arm, haul her forwards, grab her head and then guide the weakened wolfy headfirst into your mouth. Her protests nicely muffled as you stretch your lips around  her skull, matting her hair and ears against her noggin as you encompass her head entirely and take your first swallow. Her struggles are quite lively, but that yelp from in your throat as she slides through your neck makes it clear that even the rambunctious and confident wolf is realizing she's in hot water.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*soon to be hot enzymes, hue hue, keep swallowing*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The ruffian struggles against your voracious mouth and throat encompassing more and more of her body but to no avail. Your hungry swallows tugging her down into the depths of your belly as she yank her pants and boots off of her to make her go easier on your digestive process. For her life of crime this wolfy is about to get her just desserts as you swallow your way down to her rump and take in that ample ass of hers. Her kicking legs angling towards the ceiling above you as you prepare to cram her all the way down into your growing gut bulge.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*polish her off*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
		The wolfgirl growls as she's pushed against the bottom and front of your gut forming bulges in the shape of her hands and her face visible from outside. She's still putting up a commendable fight despite her predicament and the way her legs are disappearing past your lips. "When I get out of here I'm going to show you who's the boss." she threatens, even as you snap your jaws shut past her feet and condemn her entirely to your gut.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="$You're funny for someone who is about to get digested"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	"I am not about to get digested I'm getting out here" she retorts and then promptly yelps as your enzymes contradict her by spilling in from the fleshy walls. Your stomach starting to gurgle and churn around her as she struggles and squirms mightily to try and force her way back out. Unfortunately for the wolfy girl she's no match for your gut, and though your belly jostles, sways and bounces with her movements the end was never in doubt. Your stomach grinding her down until finally those growls turn to whimpers and those struggles turn to twitches and glorps..and then after that, nothing but smoothly liquid gurgles emanate from inside you as she breaks down. The wolfy turned into naught but a thick gooey mass inside you that your body all too readily and easily absorbs.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>		
	
	<page ID="unbirth0">
	<text> 
		“You… You can’t be serious?” the wounded wolf girl asked with incredulity. 
		“Dead serious.” You have to force yourself not to laugh at your “OH SO CLEVER” play on words.
		The Thug paused taking a brief look around, either looking for back up, or to be sure there were no onlookers to witness her disgrace. “Fuck it. I ain’t too good to fer this shit ‘f it means I ain’t gonna get put away.”

	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth1" text="You absolutely won’t be going to jail for this."/>
		</page>		
	
		<page ID="unbirth1">
	<text> 
	You wonder to yourself if this station even has a Jail, or if the criminal element just ends up on authoritarial elements asses. If what you are about to do is any indication, the latter would be correct. You lean back and spread your legs. “Sorry I don’t have any peanut butter for you doggy.” You joke at the brutish girl. “That is a Rasicks stereotype and a repent the asseration.” She retorted. As she dips down to begin her dirty deed, you ponder how she could have gotten such an inaccurate idea of what that sentence was supposed to be. You assume she must have only ever heard the phrase from a distance, through an exploding minefield, with water bubbles in her ears.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth2" text="That long tongue of yours is good for something outside of helping you say the dumbest shit I’ve ever heard."/>
		</page>		
	
		<page ID="unbirth2">
	<text> 
		“Thulk loo!” she muffles out having actually buried her face nose deep in your pink pussy. Her tongue is rough, long, flat, and best of all contours to your insides making this stage of your plan actually remarkably more pleasurable then you anticipated. If she keeps this up you won’t even need to force her into your quivering cunnie. You absolutely are going to no matter how good she does or how many times she makes you cum, the best part is turning someone’s life into a few moments of pleasure, and you aren’t about to pass that up.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth3" text="‘Huff’ Deeper Bitch!  ‘Huff’ or do you like the idea of one of those long eared half pints turning you to fat?"/>
		</page>		
	
		<page ID="unbirth3">
	<text> 
		The punk presses forward, popping her whole head into your horny pussy. She licks your inner walls, though now you find that she is having to work harder to keep your pumps primed, as she now has to turn her head to actually reach unattended and rapidly cooling areas of taco meat. “How shallow do you think my pussy is when I say deeper I mean DEEPER!” you clench your cunt tightly drawing in the poor and confused girl up to the waist.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth4" text="You’ve got 30 seconds to make me cum, or you are going all the way in, and aren’t coming out till your gallons for me to gush."/>
		</page>		
		
		<page ID="unbirth4">
	<text> 
		You hear a yipe originate from within your belly, as your captive begins frantically tonging everything with ravenous gluttony. She hungers to live, you think, you hunger to cum. 30……….. 29………… 28………. You feel the intensity of the ruffian increase with each passing count. The fingers on her left hand just barely free of your pussy work their way around and start polishing your pearl in the vain hope of progressing things more positively. Her fingers are actually a bit masterful and you realize she might just get you to cum before her deadline is up. 23…… 22…. 21.. 2019181716151413976321. You got really loosy goosy  there towards the end, in both saying the numbers fully, and saying them at all, and you actually started engulfing her on two, but who’s going to hold you accountable to the rules, a Warden?
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth5" text="Time’s up, you were really shit at this weren’t you."/>
		</page>		
		
		<page ID="unbirth5">
	<text> 
		“Fucking Cheating lying Bitch!” She screams from your gut. “Bitch? ‘Huff’ No that’s you Wuffy.” You gasp out, “But soon you won’t even be a worthless dog. You’ll just be a puddle I pay the whores upstairs 5 credits to lick out of me. Unlike you I’m sure they can accomplish that much. 5 credits is the most anyone would ever spend on someone as pathetic as you, so I hope you appreciate the sacrifice I’m making.” You cruelly taunt. “No No NO NOOO!!! Anyone but you. Please! PLEASE! WARDENS!!! POLICE!!! HELP ME PLEASE! PLEASE!!!”
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth6" text="Pipe down in there."/>
		</page>		
		
		<page ID="unbirth6">
	<text> 
		You slap your distended stomach right about where her face looks to be. “If you are going to shout in there you might as well try and find my G spot and yell into that. Pay me back at least a little for the 5 credits I’m about to waste on you.” The Ruffian probably would have responded, but her mouth fills with Roiling lady Juices. Your belly burbles with contentment. As the girl’s shape slowly softens, and juices languidly thicken. Your face reddens with pleasure, as the pressure in your belly grown, until you are ready to pop.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth7" text="Make a mess for that Idiot cleaner Warden to mop up."/>	
		</page>		
	
		<page ID="unbirth7">
	<text> 
		You decide to save yourself the 5 creds, you were really only saying it to be hurtful anyway. You blast your whole heaping load of Lady spoodge all over the hall, careful to get it on as many surfaces as possible, and in any cracks or crannies you can find. You must have been quite a sight, gut out to there, gushing thick waterfalls of spunk, running around spreading it about as much as possible, like you were marking your territory, all the while shrieking in ecstasy like a cat in heat. Much too soon for your liking your work is done. One fewer losers in the world, one more mess for other losers to clean up.
	</text>
			<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Fuck, one dumb bitch ain't enough, I need more." />
		</page>
			
	</Conversation>