<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
	<preference fetish="ferals" />
		<text>
			The wyvern darts in to finish you off with a tail lash, scoring your
			wobbly legs harshly and hastening your collapse to the ground. The
			Wyvern hissing and flicking his tongue out, stretching wings and
			crest in triumph and satisfaction. You make an attempt to maybe get
			away from it during its distraction revelling in its pride as a small
			predator having brought down someone your size. You move to try and
			push yourself to your feet only to let out a yelp, needly teeth
			digging into your hand as the wyvern snaps at you to exert dominance.
			It hisses and leaps forwards to exert its dominance...
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="landing atop you">
			<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="landing at your feet">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="gameover" text="a fate too terrible to contemplate">
			<notpreference fetish="cockvore" />
			<notpreference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			The creature lands in a flurry of wings over your feet, covering them
			with those broad leathery expanses. With them hidden from view you
			can't see what depraved dominance rituals its performing upon your
			feet, but you can feel the rubbing of warm flesh against your feet
			and calves. The creature clearly lost in animalistic lust as it rubs
			its firming and remarkably large shaft against your feet and presses
			the stretchy shape of its sack against your toes. But despite its
			foolish perversions the lizard reacts harshly when you attempt to
			squirm your legs out and away, snapping at your legs with its sharp
			teeth warningly..then seems to chirp as an idea occurs to it and it
			hops backwards, afore thrusting forwards. And now its depravity sinks
			to a deeper depth as its hot and musky prick engulfs your toes and
			slides up around your feet. This expression of dominance and lust
			seems to be taking a far stickier and worrysome path.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="damnable lizard" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			The little wyvern continues to exert its depravity and dominance over
			you. Its thrusting hips shoving its stretchy shaft up around your
			calves, tightly binding your legs together in the tightness of that
			throbbing musky tunnel. Your efforts to maybe pull back only
			resulting in further snapping, hissing and general all around
			disagreeable harshness from the wyvern. Despite the difference in
			size it seems to be having little trouble sliding more of your legs
			into its length and swelling its sack with the shape of your feet
			feeding on inside there. The hot cum squishing around your toes as
			your legs are steadily being consumed in this perverse fashion by the
			little wyvern.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2"
			text="why is it even things this small can eat me in lewd ways? groan" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The wyvern chirrs as it ignores your protests, shoving its perverse
			length steadily up over your body to claim your thighs and ass. The
			wyvern's hindquarters rising up off the ground as your legs are
			forced to curl packed away in the depths of its sack. The gooey cum
			oozing over your lower half as it stretches out that sack remarkably,
			the shape of your legs rather visible down there. Despite the lack of
			leverage the wyvern seems to not be having trouble, unable to
			scrabble forwards it chirrs and rubs its length with its stubby
			wingclaws. That shaft proving adept at schlorping in that immense
			cockmeal you seem to be now, slowly creeping up over your upper body
			towards your head and chest. More of you getting crammed inside that
			sack every few seconds.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="why is its cock so powerful" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			The wyvern topples backwards on the pivot point of its sack as your
			upper body steadily vanishes into its loins. Your arms and head the
			last to disappear into the reptile's cock with a schlurp. You can
			hear the lizard chirring over the sound of the squelching cum as
			you're packed away in its loins. That sack now stretched tight and
			form fitting around your curled up form, shadows of your shape
			visible through the taut skin of its scrotum as it chirrs blissfully
			and settles in proudly atop the mass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreStruggle" text="maybe if i pleasure it it'll let me go?" />
		<choice destination="cockvoreSubmit"
			text="it's so sticky and creamy in here, sticking around to get stickier and creamier sounds fun" />
	</page>

	<check ID="cockvoreStruggle">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="cockvoreStruggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="cockvoreStruggleDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="cockvoreStruggleEscape">
		<text>
			You set about rubbing the inside of the wyvern's stretched sack, doing
			the best you can in the tight confines to get the lizard off without
			it needing to turn you into nutbutter. Your efforts starting to take
			effect as the critter chirrs and kneads at the bulges of your shape
			under its feet. The wyvern's cum soaks every inch of you, tingling in
			a stimulating fashion as you arouse the reptile and feel it shift to
			stroke at its erection vigorously. It seems to be working as you hear
			the convulsive chirps of the lizard until finally...finally it cums,
			the wyvern shuddering in bliss and ejaculating. The lizard's sack
			snugging around you, in the aftermath it seems the wyvern is willing
			to let you out. It doesn't resist as you push up through its shaft
			out into the open air, sticky and being licked by the wyvern. Well
			that worked.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvoreStruggleDigest">
		<text>
			You set about rubbing the inside of the wyvern's stretched sack, doing
			the best you can in the tight confines to get the lizard off without
			it needing to turn you into nutbutter. Your efforts starting to take
			effect as the critter chirrs and kneads at the bulges of your shape
			under its feet. The wyvern's cum soaks every inch of you, tingling in
			a stimulating fashion that makes you shudder and moan. It feels
			pretty awesome and seemingly momentarily distracts you from your
			efforts inside the glorping and burbling sack of the wyvern. But you
			redouble your efforts after only a short spell of convulsive delight,
			feeling the wyvern stroking itself as you pleasure it from within..
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreStruggleDigestGO" text="wait how long have i been in here?" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoreStruggleDigestGO">
		<text>
			You stroke against the inside of the wyvern's sack, moving with the
			rthythmic pressures of the lizard's balls to further and further
			stimulate it. Won't be long now now, you can feel the wyvern's orgasm
			coming soon. You can feel it, a hot liquid pressure running through
			you. Any moment..now... the wyvern lets out a shuddering squeel of
			delight and thrashes around, its now roundened balls contracting and
			its cock spasming to splatter hot jizz across the ground. Your soft
			and sloshy form no match for the lizard's arousal, squished down into
			thick goo inside the naughty reptile's sack. In gushing pulses of
			reptilian seed you are ejaculated out all over the ground. The wyvern
			indeed was pleasured enough to let you back out, but you stayed in
			there a smidge too long it seems.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page Id="cockvoreSubmit">
		<text>
			You hear the wyvern chirring in triumph and satisfaction somewhere above
			you. Your tightly bound form stretching out the lizard's sack
			massively so that the wyvern's hindquarters are resting lifted high
			up off of the ground. The indignity is real, but..the confines are
			sensually sticky and warm and attempting to get back seems like an
			awful lot of work and the wyvern might bite you again..and in here
			it's hardly painful, far from painful.`You let the hot cum soak into
			your flesh as you stew inside the shapely sack and tensing pressure
			of the sack walls around you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreSubmitGO" text="time to melt" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoreSubmitGO">
		<text>
			The wyvern chirrs feeling its cockfood submit, stroking its shaft idly
			with its wingclaws and letting out little chirps when a particularly
			exquisite gurgle rocks through its sack. The shape in its balls
			starts off well defined, every contour and bulge and curve of your
			form visible in the tautly stretched sack skin. But as time passes so
			to does this state of affairs, your contours and outline softening,
			yielding, rounding out. The wyvern's blorping sack having to work
			over time to melt such a big and satisfying meal down into gallons of
			nutbutters. As you melt more and more the wyvern's decadent
			masturbation becomes more vigorous, then more vigorous still. The
			lizard jacking off and chirping and hissing with need as you become a
			heavy needy mass of cum inside its sack. The creature working
			desperately to reach the climax your insistent pressure urges it
			towards..until finally, release. The wyvern letting out blissful
			noises as it climaxes a continous stream of cum onto the ground
			beneath it. Your remnants forming a hot sticky puddle into which the
			dazed and satisfied wyvern collapses when its orgasm is spent.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<!-- eat hand first, not hands first, hand first -->
		<text>
			The reptile leapt atop you. The wyvern's claws digging into you
			uncomfortably as you shift to try and dislodge it off of you, your
			mistake was taking a swing at it with your other hand as it hissed at
			you. The critter's jaws snapping out to engulf your head to the
			wrist, curved inward teeth making the prospect of pulling your hand
			out a matter for careful consideration. Before you can work on
			extricating your hand though the bastard reptile is already gulping
			and chuggging your hand deeper into its slender neck, lashing out
			threateningly at your other hand. You wonder for a moment if the
			vicious winged lizard is serious, but as it works its jaws towards
			your head and your hand down into its belly you realize swiftly that
			the small predator has the audacity to try and eat you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="curse the lizard" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			You swear at the lizard vigorously, but it pays no attention to your
			vitriol. Besides that vitriol is soon muffled as it stretches its
			slender jaws around your head and shoulders, its ability to engulf a
			meal your size is quite impressive in a way. Though it'd be better to
			not be appreciating it while being the meal in question! You struggle
			only to yelp as its its teeth dig in. the critter starts writhing
			around to reposition itself off of you so it can make more headway on
			your chest.You have to be careful in your flailing due to the
			lizard's teeth, trying to worm your way back out the creature's mouth
			without suffering undue damage. But you make little progress before
			the creature has clambered off you and can start chugging down your
			upper body, squeezing your head and arm into the wyvern's belly. The
			wyvern being lifted up by its distending gut as it greedily swallows
			up your body down as far as your ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2"
			text="too cramped in here, but it's gonna get even more so" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			You can't believe your predicament as you're squeezed steadily into the
			wyvern's tight belly, the critter steadily becoming immobilized as it
			packs you away in its belly. But it probably isn't in a hurry to go
			anywhere, you on the other hand seem set to plunge entirely down the
			lizard's throat as the slender critter rocks its head back and forth
			and chugs down your legs. Your outline showing tightly defined in the
			stretched flesh of the lizard's gut, its scales and skin thinning
			enough to show shadows of your shape as you're squeezed and packed
			away inside until finally the lizard snaps its jaws shut past your
			feet. The lizard's hiss giving way to a delighted trill as the winged
			reptile rests atop the immobilizing beachball sized bulging mass you
			make in its gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreSubmit"
			text="i hate to think what it'd do to me if i tried to get out, being digested doesn't seem that bad" />
		<choice destination="oralvoreStruggle"
			text="like hell am i sticking around to let this impudent winged beasty gurgle me away" />
	</page>

	<check ID="oralvoreStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="15" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreStruggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreStruggleDigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleEscape">
		<text>
			You don't stick around to be savoured and digested by the lizard and
			start shoving your hands back up the creature's tight throat. The
			vicious lizard now in much distress as you force your way out of the
			squeezing slenderness of its flight adapted form. The wyvern
			thrashing and squirming around hissing as you force your hands up its
			neck and grasp its jaws. Your hands prying them back in a way that's
			painful for the wyvern but very useful for you not being lacerated by
			those vicious teeth. The wyvern letting out whimpering gagging noises
			now as you worm up and out, keeping its jaws clear until you wriggle
			entirely out of it. The wyvern looking profoundly sorry for itself
			behind you, sprawled and whimpering. All parts of the lizard hard
			used.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreStruggleDigest">
		<text>
			You don't plan to stick around to be savoured and digested by the lizard
			and start shoving your hands back up the creature's tight throat. The
			vicious lizard now in much distress as you force your way out of the
			squeezing slenderness of its flight adapted form. The wyvern
			thrashing and squirming around hissing as you force your hands up its
			neck and grasp its jaws.Those jaws snapping down harshly making you
			yelp and flinch as its teeth dig into your palms. The wyvern taking a
			swallow as you flinch your arms back from its teeth, your progress
			out of the creature's throat thwarted. You try several more times,
			but never make it as far as you did before. The wyvern becoming wise
			to your antics and your body tiring. Inevitably you are back where
			you were before you started trying to escape, curled up in the belly
			of the wyvern and feeling it prod angrily at its gut with its nose to
			try and chide you for being an unruly meal. There's no getting out
			now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreGO" text="no escape..." />
	</page>

	<page Id="oralvoreSubmit">
		<text>
			A good prey knows when they're beaten. and besides, there's no way you
			could get back out of this tight belly. It was hard enough for you to
			end up down here with the wyvern doing the work, you doubt from your
			current predicament you can make much headway. The wyvern chirrs
			triumphantly, resting immobilized atop the lumpy beanbag of sharply
			contoured bulges that is its gut. The creature's stomach starting to
			gurgle you away.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreGO" text="naught to do but digest now" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreGO">
		<text>
			The wyvern chirrs and chirps in delight as it settles atop its belly and
			your weakly squirming form begins to digest away. The enzymes and
			vigorous internal processes of the reptile working you over steadily
			despite your bulk in comparison to the size of the predator. The
			distinct bulges in that massively stretched and distended gut slowly
			fading away as you're gurgled into a softening indistinct mass. The
			lizard's gut round now, and slowly it diminishes and shrinks away as
			your fluid form is absorbed. That gut turning compact then finally
			vanishing away leaving naught but chirring satisfaction as you're
			utterly digested.
		</text>
	</gameover>


</Conversation>