<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The arachne tries to back away but stumbles, her abdomen crashing into the dirt as her legs aren't strong enough right now to support her. She raises her hands as you gaze roves over her ample breasts, a pleasing contrast to her earlier brazen displaying of those tits that speaks to her new found vulnerability in defeat.
		</text>
	
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="She'd make your belly nice and big, eat her up">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	The spider taur seems to sense your intentions and lets out an uneasy chitter, reaching up to shove you away all thought of modesty forgotten as she grapples with more important dangers. Namely the fact she's about to be eaten alive and digested by a victorious predator, namely you. Her protests and attempts to resist come to naught however as not to be deterred or slowed you grab her hands and guide them not to your chest where she'd be able to shove you back, but to your lips where she finds her hands shoved down your throat instead. The arachne lets out a dismayed cry as you swallow and drag her shapely upper body towards your mouth.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*who says spider ain't good eating, nom nom gulp her down*"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The hefty arachne squirms around as you enjoy your feast, gulping her in eagerly. Her ample assets and tauric frame will only add to your satisfaction rather than impede your progress. Her cries are muffled by your hungry mouth, her bountiful bust presses against your tongue and squeezes down your throat. Your hands roam down to grab ahold of her lower spider legs and use them as handles to cram her into yourself all the way down to her hips. The arachne's lower exoskeletal taur half is all that remains outside you and you can hardly wait to feel that part of her stretching and filling out your tummy.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*continue*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	You hear her muffledly protesting against the inside of your bulging belly and shoving at your innards. But the kneading she's giving your guts only loosens them up further to accept more of her. You cram her thrashing legs past your lips greedily, forcing her to squish up in your belly as you gobble her up entirely. Your middle now bloated and domed out massively, the shape of the arachne squirming inside clearly visible in your tummy contours. Truly she's a wonderful meal, now to squeeze and gurgle her until she's all gone.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="*oh yes, digest her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	Your gut gurgles and grinds, the soft curves and sturdy abdomen of the arachne now serving to please and feed you as your belly works her over. She doesn't go quietly, even apart from the noisy churns of your gut she lets out protesting cries and thrashes around powerfully in your bloated tummy. The spider taur making your rounded gut jostle and sway but her efforts to stop you breaking her down are as effective as they were at stopping you eating her in the first place. Her chitin softens, her curves round out and her squirms and protests weaken until only sloshing remains. And soon, as you soak up her nutrients and utterly absorb her, not even that remains. Your belly shrinking down steadily as all that was once her becomes fuel for your superior body.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>


</Conversation>