<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The strong and armoured insectoid hisses as you approach. But
			it's all she can do to keep herself upright with the help of a hand
			on the ground, kneeling as she tries to recover her strength and deal
			with the triumphant interloper before her. It looks like that might
			take a while and there's no sense wasting the opportunity right?
		</text>
		<choice destination="devour0"
			text="a big meal of bug girl would be a fitting reward for your victory">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>


	<page ID="devour0">
		<text>
			The big bug keeps on glaring as you come to a halt, she sees you lick
			your lips and chitterclaks in scoffing laughter. She seems
			disbelieving you could handle one such as her. Well, time to prove
			her wrong. You snag her antenna making her wince as you pull her
			forwards, keeping her from pulling away her head as you bring her to
			meet your lips. The armoured bug letting out a hiss of dismay as you
			start your attempt, engulfing her face with your lips. You waste no
			time from there in shifting your hands down to grab her arms and pull
			her forwards so you can swallow and start to devour more of her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="devour1" text="eat the armoured bug girl" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour1">
		<text>
			The chitinous armour of the lixi tastes interesting with unusual mixes
			of bitter and sweet from different segments as they cross your
			tongue. Though the bug girl's resilient form yields little to the
			pressure of her mouth and throat as you swallow up more of her,
			gulping over her shoulders and plated breasts. You can feel her
			powerful muscles working against you in futile resistance, pushing
			her armoured arms against the inside of your throat but unable to
			escape your hunger. That shapely chitin clad ass of hers gets closer
			and closer to your mouth now as you cram her form inside of yourself
			more and more. You can hear her hissing from within your gut as she's
			squeezed inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="devour2" text="swallow her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour2">
		<text>
			The big bug's armoured glutes flex as her tail thrashes around. But she
			can't escape you as you tip your head back and swallow up her kicking
			legs and writhing tail. The lixi worker letting out distressed
			hissing whine as she's squeezed and packed away in a tightly confined
			mass inside your belly. The insectoid's chitin clad limbs hardly able
			to move as you rub over the well defined bulges of your belly. Her
			chitin seems to protect her from the squeezing of your belly and
			might resist your acids for a time though right?
		</text>
		<choice destination="devour3"
			text="prove your belly is mightier than her shell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour3">
		<text>
			You get comfortable as best you can with the hard lumpy shape distending
			your belly. The bug is going to be tricky to digest, but it'll make
			her dissolution all the sweeter. She tries to struggle against your
			insides but can barely move as your belly gurgles around her,
			pressing tightly against her unyielding chitin as she hisses in
			protest. She can't get out now though, forced to bath in your stomach
			fluids that for the moment is kept at bay by her resilient chitin.
			but you can only imagine how her shell is softening as you soak her
			with your enzymes.
		</text>
		<choice destination="devour4" text="and soon, she will yield" />
	</page>

	<page ID="devour4">
		<text>
			The insectoid's squirms provide pleasing pressure pushing out against
			the relentless pressure of your belly. She seems to be trying to find
			a way of pushing back out thinking that you're unable to digest her
			and impatient to be let out. But then her armour began to crack, her
			weakening armour dissolving and splitting leaving her defenceless in
			a pool of frothing enzymes that break her down with furious vigour.
			Your innards seemingly in over drive from having to break her armour
			down her softer parts do not survive for very long, her despairing
			hiss swiftly fading to nothing and being replaced with vigorous
			gurgles and churns. The mighty insect warrior's shape soon turning
			soft and round within you, digesting away and diminishing. In time
			naught remains but your feeling of satisfaction and your belly at its
			normal proportions, armour, muscles and all she was no match your
			stomach.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

</Conversation>