<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="tailvore" />
		<preference fetish="demi" />
		<preference fetish="female" />
		<text>
			The worker glares down at you and lets out a threatening hiss afore
			hauling you easily up in front of her. Your feet dangle in the air as
			she hisses and scrutinizes you. Her antenna flicking forwards to
			brush against your head and shoulders as she completes her
			assessment. But she doesn't seem to have much trouble thinking of a
			way of dealing with this particular intruder into their tunnels. You
			feel something glomming around your feet and glance down to find that
			flexible tail of hers curled up beside her thigh, the tip parting
			into a segmented maw to wrap firmly around your ankles. It would seem
			that her tail is capable of gobbling you up, will wonders never
			cease.
		</text>
		<choice destination="tailvore0" text="being eaten by a tail" />
	</page>

	<page ID="tailvore1">
		<text>
			The big armoured bug girl follows your gaze and grin wickedly,
			chittering in clicking laughter a bit as you squirm and attempt to
			pull your feet out without success. You can see her tail flexing and
			working up towards your hips despite your efforts. Its segmented
			plates parting from eachother as your legs bulge and stretch it out.
			The mighty bug's tail seems strong enough to support you without any
			help as she gloms up your thighs and lets go of you. The lixi swaying
			you away ass deep in her tail before you can strike at her. Your
			hands trailing loosely back and forth across the dirty cavern floor
			as she sways her swelling tail around behind herself. The bug girl
			mmhmming and planting her hands on her legs as she leans forwards and
			feels you bulging more and more of her tail.
		</text>
		<choice destination="tailvore2"
			text="swallowed up the rest of the way by a hungry tail" />
	</page>

	<page ID="tailvore2">
		<text>
			In desperation to avoid being gobbled up by that flexing tail you grab
			ahold of the edge of her tailmaw and hold it down. The flexing tail
			powerfully sucks on your legs but can make no headway. But apparently
			your predator is untroubled and the insectoid worker just
			chitterclacks in amusement and starts waving her tail around rapidly,
			disorientating and discombobulating you until your grip loosens and
			her tail gobbles you up all the way to your armpits. You can't get a
			good grip now to stop her but despite it all you press your arms down
			against the rippling tug of her tail wrapped around your body. And
			this as well stops her for a time, the mighty bug girl looking at
			your stubborn resistance and angling her tail up over her head so she
			can look into your face upside down..then smirk as she reaches up and
			yanks your arms outwards with a powerful grip, it makes you wince but
			more importantly lets her tail get around your shoulders, your arms
			and head disappearing into her tailtip soon after this as she lets
			out a hissing moan of delight. Your form entirely incased in her
			tail, a series of nice bulges showing visibly in the stretched skin
			between her chitinous exoskeletal plates.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle"
			text="try to get out of here before you get pulled down into her belly" />
		<choice destination="submit"
			text="submit to the predatory insectoid and let her turn you into a belly bulge" />
	</page>

	<check ID="struggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleEscape" />
		<outcome destination="struggleBelly" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleEscape">
		<text>
			You won't have a chance to escape if you're tugged any deeper. The
			voracious tail rippling around you is massaging firmly against your
			flesh and working you further in even as you marshal your resolve.
			With no time to waste you begin furiously wriggling and pushing your
			way back up the tail, feeling the bug attempting to stop you by
			turning and bending her tail and thus you uncomfortably. But despite
			her efforts you manage to get a grip to pull yourself further up and
			then gradually out into the open air. Your hands emerging first to
			grab ahold of the tailmaw against its flexing and then gradually you
			use them to haul yourself entirely out into the open air. The bug
			girl looks down at you and her tail rears back in irritation, flexing
			its loosened jaws closed. It's clear this isn't over, maybe you
			should flee.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleBelly">
		<text>
			You won't have a chance to escape if you're tugged any deeper. The
			voracious tail rippling around you is massaging firmly against your
			flesh and working you further in even as you marshal your resolve.
			You start fighting against against the pulling rippling hunger of her
			tail. The lixi curling her tail tightly to constrain and constrict
			your movements as you try to make headway up her tail and towards her
			tailmaw and freedom. But your hand finds no grasp on the slick flesh
			of the tailthroat and in time you tire out, finding her tail dragging
			you down. The bulge of your form steadily slips lower down the tail
			until you start to squeeze feetfirst past her tailbase and into her
			belly. In mere minutes you are fed entirely into her middle, parting
			her chitin around the immense bulge of her belly as it stretches to
			contain you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleDigest" text="trapped inside her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggleDigest">
		<text>
			The bug hisses softly in pleasure as she reaches down to rub her hands
			over the bulge you make. You're trapped inside her now, squeezed and
			clenched behind her chitin and skin as she starts to gurgle you away.
			The lixi worker stretching and shifting before getting comfortable
			resting against the cavern walls and with both hands tracing between
			her bellyplates to feel your contours. The insect has you now, your
			intrusion into their caverns ending somewhat predictably as her belly
			works you over with ever increasing vigour.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggleGO" text="digested" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggleGO">
		<text>
			Within the bug you find yourself suffering a gurgling and gooey fate. The
			insectoid chittering and hissing in pleasure as you soften and melt
			away until you're utterly sloshed to soup within her, the bug's
			chitinous armour squeezing down your now liquid and compact form as
			they get closer and closer together as the bulge you make diminishes.
			Soon enough your remains are utterly gone, the bug looking down at
			her smooth armoured belly and feeling you coursing through her body.
			Your invasion of the lixi tunnels has ended with exploration of her
			circulatory system, as is to only be expected.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			The powerful bug has you contained entirely in her tail, and upon
			reflection on your chances you decide to simply relax and let her
			have you. Struggling against her seems futile and letting her pull
			you into her belly seems preferable and certainly sexier. The bug
			seems puzzled by your lack of resistance, but chitters and stretches,
			flexing her tail to schlorp you down into her belly inch by inch. The
			insect worker soon enough sporting a round belly that stretches her
			skin and parts her armour once you're packed away entirely within
			her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitGO" text="get digested" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitGO">
		<text>
			Within the bug you accept your gurgling and gooey fate. The insectoid
			chittering and hissing in pleasure as you soften and melt away until
			you're utterly sloshed to soup within her, the bug's chitinous armour
			squeezing down your soupy remains as they get closer and closer
			together as the bulge you make diminishes. Soon enough your remains
			are utterly gone, the bug looking down at her smooth armoured belly
			and feeling you coursing through her body. Your invasion of the lixi
			tunnels has ended with exploration of her circulatory system, as is
			to only be expected.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>