<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			The creature lungs towards you, its ire piqued by your impudent attacks.
			And you are too weak now to evade as its lashing tentacles grab ahold
			of you and haul you roughly off your feet. the impact of your head on
			the floor stunning you briefly afore you're yanked upside down into
			the air above the eldritch monster. Those tentacles having a firm
			grip despite the slime, their impossible strength grasping your legs
			roughly as you see an undulating circular maw flex open beneath you.
			It's clear it intends to break its long fast with your flesh, and
			there is nought you can do to resist it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="unwillingly sacrificed to the elder god" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The elder thing watches you with cruel and multitudinous eyes as you
			dangle and squirm above it, perhaps after so long starved taking a
			moment to enjoy the anticipation of things. But even that is short
			lived as it shoves you into its mouth, tentacles curling inwards then
			releasing leaving you hip deep in that voracious maw. The flexing
			undulating tunnel gripping around your thighs firmly and then hauling
			you inwards and down with a schlurp, your hands scrabbling for
			purchase against the sides of the creature's mouth but finding the
			lip slick and slimy.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="no escape" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Nonetheless for a moment it feels like you're momentarily able to make some
			purchase, gripping the rim of that rippling tube and holding yourself
			against its pull. But even that proves fleeting as a rippling tug
			yanks you down and you lose your grip, realizing the ancient monster
			is toying with you as you try to grasp the rim anew. That rim rising
			up around your chest, then over your shoulders despite your futile
			attempts to resist that deceptive and powerful throat, helplessly you
			find yourself drawn down inside where so many more had vanished
			before you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="devoured completely" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			The last glimpse you get out of the elder thing's maw is circled with
			curling tentacles that block off much of your view of that stone
			ceiling, and then you are pulled in entirely. Your body plunging down
			the ancient monster's throat and sealed into a clenching digestive
			sack, caustic fluids soaking your flesh as you attempt a misguidedly
			futile effort at escaping the eldritch deity even now.
		</text>
		<page ID="oralvoreGO" text="doomed" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralvoreGO" noReform="true">
		<text>
			You feel the creature in motion around you, no more attention paid to
			you as you struggle against the digestive fluids and gurgling
			confines of your imprisonment. The elder god seemingly already cast
			you from its mind, your service as a long overdue meal and releasing
			it from its imprisonment apparently already merits no further
			consideration. The caustic stomach breaking you down like so many
			others until naught but a stew of liquidated gloop dwells within and
			seeps into the monster's time ravaged form. You were no match for the
			might and will of the elder thing, and now you are no more.
		</text>
	</gameover>
</Conversation>