<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	The wyvern reacts to your approach with a dominance display. Trying to look tall and big and attempting to stare you down. It's really rather cute as even now he barely reaches your shoulders.
	</text>
	<choice destination="approach" text="get closer, see what he does"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="silly lizard"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="approach">
	<text>
	You half expect the silly wyvern to back down as you loom over him. So it's a surprise as he leapt up with a flap of his wings and digs his teeth lightly into the skin at the back of your neck, the audacious dominance makes you quiver lightly. The wyvern might honestly have expected to never get this far, but perched atop you he nonetheless presses down attempting to command a submissive crouch out of you despite your immense size.
	</text>
	<choice destination="submit" text="submit to him"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="submit">
	<text>
	The wyvern flares his wings out for balance as you lower yourself, a low submissive whine hinting at the genuineness of your acceptance of the tiny creature's dominance over you. It's clear it took him by surprise but it seems he rallies quickly. The wyvern letting out a delighted growl and giving you a few more dominant bites to make sure you know who's boss, then starts scrabbling along your resting form towards your hindquarters, you're tempted to look back but keep your head lowered as you feel something warm and fleshy and unfurred rubbing along your back and then hips in a way that makes your tail rise and your slit moisten...so bold..
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex0" text="give the lil guy access"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex0">
	<text>
	You feel the wyvern curling to rub his shaft against your hindquarters, remarkably well hung for his size and his sheer confidence and audacity lets him have his way with you. The wyvern thrusting his length up under your tail and into your sex, clutched tight around your hips as he buries his member balls deep in your accomodating nethers and lets out an eager growl.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex1" text="mhmm"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex1">
	<text>
	Your hindquarters raise slightly as you feel the wyvern going to work in fucking the unexpected bounty of submissive dragon he's lucked into. The wyvern letting out delighted growls as his length slides in and out of your nethers with the vigorous pace of his rutting. Though it's his confidence more than anything that excites you and lets your pleasure build as he uses a far larger being to slake his lusts.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex2" text="nearly there"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex2">
	<text>
	The growling vigorous humping from the wyvern starts to get the better of you still more, your murrs audible and loud but ignored by the wyvern. Lost in his own desires he pays no attention to how you're getting off on being used this way. So much so that you feel his length erupt, splattering your insides with his thick cum but sending you shuddering over the edge into your own spasming, clenching and snarling orgasm. In a haze of pleasure you feel his spurts trail off and his length pulling out of your nethers. You lose track of the wyvern as he clambers off the top of you but then you feel something against your tailtip...
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="feels wet"/>
	<choice destination="cockvore0" text="feels sticky"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	You feel a wet warmth around your tailtip, the scrape of teeth encroaching up the long length of your tail. Gradually that warmth encompasses more and more of your tail as you rouse yourself from your lethargy, then look behind yourself to see the audacious wyvern has started fearlessly turning you into a post fuck meal. The wyvern's jaws stretched wide around the thickening taper of your tail as he works his way towards your haunches and still sticky nethers.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="no end to his confidence"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	You feel your tail curling in his gut and wriggle, trying to pull away and uncurl your tail. But he's making far too much progress devouring your streamlined form by the time you've roused yourself fully to the threat, your hindlegs pinned up against your belly by his encroaching jaws as he gobbles you up. As his body rises up over his ever largening gut he continues swallowing you up eagerly, showing no signs of stopping or heck even slowing in his gluttonous devouring of your body.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="meep"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	The wyvern's understandably muffled, but you think he just growled in satisfaction as you meeped and tried to wriggle again afore realizing it's hopeless. There's really no way you can resist once a predator decides they want to have you, even if the predator is this tiny, adorable and yet disproportionately confident. Your body gradually slides past his lips as he curls his tail over the coiling bulges forming in his belly from your form packing away inside of him. The wyvern's fur spreading out immensely to reveal bared hide as you stretch his gut awesomely with your body and his jaws get closer and closer to your head. Soon you'll be engulfed entirely and won't be able to keep watch for spectators who might witness your humiliating ingestion by the little wyvern.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="probably for the best"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	The wyvern's mightily stretched jaws can be felt around your neck, sliding up around your head as he steadily gobbles you down until they snap shut past the tip of your snout. The wyvern taking a final swallow and tucking your head down his throat to join the rest of you curled up in immensely stretched and thoroughly satiated gut. The wyvern growling in delight as you wriggle around and meep within him, naught but a meal for the diminutive creature.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="fucked, devoured, now to be digested"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	You nudge out at the insides of the lusty wyvern, but all you get for your trouble is the gurgles and glorps of his gut working over you. The wyvern letting out a crooning whine of satisfaction as he starts breaking you down. Enzymes soaking your form as his long tail continues to curl and rub over the top side of his enormous belly. And gradually you find you're beginning to succumb,to soften and melt within the young wyvern.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore5" text="...glorp"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<text>
	The wyvern seems to be content to doze in satisfied torpor as you gurgle inside of him. Probably best as digesting a dragon multiple times his size takes the wyvern many an hour, your reduction to the insignificant role of meal seeming to last a small eternity. The wyvern's gut turning softer, rounder, squishier and then finally smaller and more compact.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreGO" text="gurgle"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvoreGO">
	<text>
	As time passes the wyvern begins to rouse, then burps and topples over in surprise as he's forced to full wakefulness. The wyvern looking down to find that where once he had a taut distended gut stretched around the contours of bulges of a large dragon now he sports only a rounded chubby gut. Your form is utterly digested and as the wyvern takes flight ponderously it's clear that soon the last compacted remnants of your form will be utterly absorbed by your predator.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>
	
	
</Conversation>