<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="demis" />
				<text>
		The saurian captain takes a moment to congratulate her fellows on their victory afore approaching you, passing off her crossbow "You fought well, for a filthy elf lover." she says as she looms over you "How does it feel to lose to us traveller?" she asks resting one booted foot victoriously upon you and looking down at you with a smirk.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*say nothing*">
				<preference fetish="oralvore" />	
				
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="$degrading">
				<preference fetish="cockvore" />	
			<preference fetish="herms" />	
		</choice>		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"Stoic type huh, i can respect that..but even the stoic digest just the same." she says and licks her lips afore stepping back and squatting down. The captain lifting your feet up to her lips and shoving them into her mouth, mhmming as she starts eating you alive. Her troops watching on avidly as she gobbles you up inch by inch. Your legs steadily vanishing down her throat despite your squirms. Not that struggling more than this would help you with her soldiers watching on and standing ready to help feed you in if you resist.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*victory meal*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	Faced with the futility of your resistance and her evident enjoyment you don't struggle or plead as she eats you alive. The captain's lips sliding up your thighs, over your hips and then onwards as she devours you alive. Her tunic riding up over the growing bulge in her belly as your legs are forced inside to bulge her out, you can already tell from the looks on their faces that her troops are gonna enjoy rubbing that belly once you're trapped inside. Little solace to give so many satisfaction though, as soon you will be only food.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*swallowed completely"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	The captain's lips slide up around your chest, her tongue roaming, and soon after that she gobbles you up completely. Those lips encroaching around your shoulders, then over your head and she takes a swallow. Her jaws snapping shut as the bulge of your head slips down her neck to join the rest of you in her belly "Mhmm, you were delicious..just the sort of enemy I like to enjoy after a victorious battle." she says and then mhmms "now soldiers, my belly requires..rubbing." she orders teasingly, leaning back and settling sprawled out so that her gut is on full display. Soon you feel multiple sets of hands rubbing over the shape of your curled up form, kneading at you as you're trapped inside her and setting your predator chirring in delight from it all.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="*no escape possible, digestion is inevitable*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	The rubbing hands and grinding pressure of her stomach walls help along the digestive process. Your squirms availing you nought against your inevitable processing into nourishment for the captain. Her reptilian subordinates seem quite happy to rub her belly all the way until you turn soft and mushy, your squirms fading away as you turn into an indistinguishable mass of nourishing glop within her. The captain only putting an end to this period of belly loving once you're evened out into a smooth consistency inside her, the saurian leading her soldiers on into battle once more..but now sporting a bit of a belly containing your digested remains as you're absorbed and soaked up by her innards. Your attempt to fight for the elves has led only to one of their enemies getting a satisfying meal.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	"Degrading..as if you're too good to lose to us?" the captain seems to take issue with that. But she leans down with a grin so she can conspiratorially say "Well in that case, feels like you should be taken down a peg or three...we'll see how superior you feel when you're churned into cum for me to share with my soldiers." she says, one hand going down to grab ahold of her crotch through her tunic afore she gets up off of you and turns to her soldiers "Hold her up..she's about to be cockfodder." the captain says and frees her length, stroking it as you're hoisted up by one of her subordinates. Brought into a position facing her hardening and enlargening cock.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="$No, no i'm not! no, please.."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	"Should of thought of that before you decided you could be an elf friend and better than us." the captain says, unsympathetic to your pleas as she brings her cocktip closer to your face. The broad head intruding on your senses with its thick musk as her cumslit gapes open in front of you. A bit of pre oozing from the tip like drool from a slathering maw as she prepares to shove you inside for a moment more and then sets about degrading you even more as she thrusts her cock forwards to engulf your head.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="*MMPH!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	Your protests at this humiliation are nicely muffled as her shaft stretches and schlurps around your head. Her length engulfing you rather easily even with you squirming against the hold of her subordinates to try and stop her making cockfood out of you. The captain letting out lusty moans as she works you deeper and deeper, closer to her balls. The hands holding you steady helping to lift up your ass and hoist your legs off the ground to help feed you into her voracious dick. The sticky tightness at the base of her shaft parts abruptly around your head as you push into her sack, getting dunked into her gooey cum..the fluid she intends to melt you down into more of.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="$I can't be cum, right..i can't be cum"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	The captain upends her cock, motioning to her soldiers that she's got this as she angles your legs skywards and steadily jacks and jerks you down into her balls. The officer's tanned balls swelling out and hanging low before her subordinates as you pile into them, the contours and outline of your shape bulging her sack out wonderfully as she finishes up cockvoring you "A much more fitting place for you..is she not much better here?" asks the captain almost rhetorically as she shows off her balls to the other lizards.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore4" text="$this can't really be happening"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4">
	<text>
	"Oh but it will cockfood, you're going to be slopping around in my nuts in no time at all now." the captain taunts in response to your muffled protest, then chirrs as you feel hands pressing on you from outside "That's it, help her melt...I'm going to share her after all." the captain said approvingly to her kneeling soldiers as they help knead and rub over your shape as her balls begin to burble and churn you up. Your struggles, squirms and protests all amounting to nothing as you find yourself softening and spreading out into the surrounding cum. Your awareness fading out as your form steadily loses all solidity. The lizardgirls kneading at their captain's balls gradually feeling your shape yield under their palms and your shape..rounds out.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="*burble"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	The soldiers rubbing at the captain's sack let out a delighted chir as they feel your form liquidate entirely and their loving attention to their superior's loins takes a different turn. One of the soldiers starting to jerk off that big well fed dick and licking and sucking on the tip while the other continues to knead, lick and suck on their captain's balls. Said worthy moaning in delight, closing her eyes. Her hands rubbing affectionately on the heads of her ministering soldiers one beneath each palm. Soon enough the cock pulses and throbs and the soldiers heed the warning, pulling back and into firing range as their captain pumps you back out of her shaft. The hot cumbath spilling over the pair, soaking their bared skin and scales and filling their mouths with your spunky remains as they do their best to catch their captain's seed. The trio are left a debauched, but happy mess in the wake of having shared you. The last glops of cum spilling out of the captain's dick onto the ground as she smiles at her sticky subordinates"And they say I don't know how to build camaraderie with my soldiers."
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
</Conversation>