<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="ferals" />	
		<text> 
		The dragomech bounds over and looms over you, pinning you beneath a heavy paw the armoured war synth looks down at you "Victory attained, hostile combatant detained. Now initiating prisoner processing." declares the dragomech as it looms over you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*dragomech licks lips*">
			<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="*something stirring between the synth's legs*">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="instakill" text="*fucking laser eyes*"/>
	</page>
		
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	The dragomech looks like its smirking as it looms over you, you wonder what it's doing..whether it's going to get to the processing...whether its glitched out in which case you might be able to escape. But the reason for that smirk becomes apparent, a hefty length of throbbing dickmeat extending from a port on the underside of the quadraped, draping down and firming up just ahead of hefty balls that you suddenly realize are to be your destination. The predatory synth lets out a chuckle "Yes, humiliation and liquidation." it declares, and shifts posture before shoving that girthy and drooling dick up against your feet.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="*fed into synth dick*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	The dragon thrusts forwards and your feet slide into that pulsating black rod with a squelch of hot lubricating fluids. That thick length bulging as the mighty war machine thrusts its length forwards again to engulf your calves, then yet again to engulf your thighs. A rumbling buzzing growl of what sounds very much like delight emanating from the dragonsynth above you as you sink into its voracious length. Your ass next to be consumed as the dragomech shifts and lifts that paw off you, content to squeeze you down into its cock. Your feet sliding into the synthbeast's sack now.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="all the way in"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>	
	"Hostile combatant, stimulating." the dragomech groans out as it clenches its shaft around your legs and slurps you deeper inside. Your upper body gradually vanishing under the dragon as you're crammed into its balls. Your shape making them swell and sag and hang low and heavy. With a final schlorp you vanish into its cocktip, your <macro id="hair_desc_short" /> hair the last anyone sees of you before that cumslit seals over the top of your head. The synth's voracious cock rippling as you're fed down entirely into the warmachine's balls.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="doomed to be fluid"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	The beastial synth begins to rub its cock against surfaces as a form of stimulation as those balls you're trapped in stir to life. The sticky goo churning around you as the dragon growls and groans in delight, gradually melting you down into a hot load. Those balls contracting, rounding out..your every trace rendered down into goopy fluids. Is it any wonder the wardragon is soon letting out a roar of pleasure, standing proud with legs spread and a bucking and gushing cock jetting cum from betwixt its limbs. Your sticky remnants arcing out to form a gooey splatter across the war torn ground in front of it "Hostile combatant, is now the optimal form of pleasure fluid."
	</text>
	
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"Defeated hostile combatant now defined as fuel." says the dragomech with a grin. And doesn't give you time to protest this before lunging forwards, jaws coming down around your head and shoulders. Hot lubricating fluid flowing over your skin and heat wafting out around you as the synth dragon's jaws clench tight around you. You can feel the weight of this armoured juggernaut shifting over you as its body bunches up, then mercifully that paw is lifted up off your body..but only so that the dragomech can grasp you bodily in its jaws and then fling its head back..your body carried with, upended by the hungry synth.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*fuel?!*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	You find yourself resting upside down in the flexible, and flexing, throat of the fuel starved war machine. The dragomech letting out a growl as its tongue licks, laps over and in general tastes your helpless body. The dragon deriving a very real satisfaction despite her synthetic nature. But the war dragon doesn't linger too long in savouring you before it resumes swallowing, gulping your body down into its throat to make a hefty bulge. Your legs gradually disappearing past the victorious dragon's jaws as they flex open and closed to ease you down with gravity's aid.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*swallowed*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Down down down you go with the sounds of the dragon's growls of delight and that rippling throat loud around you as you slip on into its belly. Your legs disappearing entirely out of view, the war dragon's jaws snapping shut behind your feet "Hostile combatant, consumed, processing..imminent, satisfaction, impending." the dragon says happily as you slide down to form a bulge weighing down the large and powerful predator's belly. The stomach of the synth as hot, wet and tight as any other stomach you could expect to find yourself in and your shape now makes that gut sag between the dragomech's legs "Processing..commencing." 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="*digested*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	You don't get any time to protest this, nor does the dragomech pay any attention. The stomach of the dragomech clenches and grinds about you relentlessly, processing fluids flooding in even as internal processes knead and press all about you. Against this powerful onslaught your body puts up as much of a resistance as you had been able to put up against the military might of the warmech before it had bested you. In hardly any time at all the dragomech's stomach is contracting and tightening up "hostile combatant processing complete, fuel reserves increased." the dragomech says and then smirks "Victory was delicious."
	</text>
	</gameover>

	
	<page ID="instakill">
	<text>
	The dragomech lowers its head towards your face "Prisoner elimination will now commence." says the dragomech..and those ocular lenses start to glow from within "And I shoot lasers out of my fucking eyes." the dragomech declares...
	</text>
	<choice destination="laserGO" text="uh oh"/>
	</page>

	<gameover ID="laserGO">
	<text>
	...Well at least that was..quick...
	</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>