<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<text>
	The drake glances your way as you approach, and lets out a questioning chirp cocking his lil head to the side. But he still seems unthreatened by your far greater size.
	</text>
	<choice destination="nuzzle" text="nuzzle him"/>
	<choice destination="lick0" text="lick him"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="walk away"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="nuzzle">
	<text>
	You gently nudge and nuzzle the lil lizard with your snout, getting a little bemused chirp as he stumbles then nuzzles back against your large head with a murr.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="nuzzle lil lizard lips"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="nose and then leave him"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	You continue to nuzzle the lizard and butt your snout against his cheek, the drake letting out a murf and flexing his jaws a moment in reaction. Seeing that gape though you take advantage of the opportunity and shove your head right between those jaws, the drake letting out a mhmmph and squirming as he unexpectedly finds an enormous dragon head sliding between his jaws. The drake is so surprised he isn't sure what to do about this unexpected development, but you do.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="feed yourself to the lil guy!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The drake squirms but can do naught against a larger dragon, especially a far more perverse one. So you thrust your head deeper into the poor confused reptile, his throat gulping and swallowing instinctively as your snout collides with the back of his mouth and slides down his neck and into his belly. The lizard soon sporting a remarkable bulge in the exact outline of your skull as you work your head entirely into that wonderfully accepting and stretchy belly he has, now all you've got to do is get the rest of your body into him.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="a tricky but alluring prospect"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	The drake isn't helping yet, so you push forwards to feed more of your flexible neck into his stretched agape jaws. The little lizard engulfing a bit more of you as you manage to squeeze more of your head neck into the inviting warmth of his tummy but seem to hit a snag, unable to shove further in. The drake confused to hear your whine from the bottom of his belly. But at last even if he's slow on the uptake his body knows what to do when something delicious and edible is stuffed into his mouth, and starts to slowly and inexorably swallow you up. It'll take a stupendous effort to swallow a dragon your size, but you're not struggling far from it and you're well worth it.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="feed the drake"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	The lil drake seems game to try despite the disparity in size. He keeps on swallowing, his overwhelmed and mightily stretched throat rippling to tug on your body. You tuck your forelimbs close as you start to make your way inside of him, his gut stretching out enormously with your head and neck as he engulfs more and more of your body. Pinned against your sides your forelegs slide down his throat and into his belly, and in your impatience you use them to help tug more of your smoothly schlurpable form past his jaws. The drake letting out strained but pleased noises mingled together as he gulps more and more of your body down. It seems to take an age for him to reach your hindquarters, your rear set of legs already helpfully tucked in alongside your form as all but your tail disappears inside of him.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="swallow me up completely"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	You wriggle your tail impatiently and you're unsure if it's your exhortation or that flailing flexible thick length of tail in front of the drake that stirs him on to finish the job. But he does, dragging your tail slowly past his lips to join the rest of you in the immense bulge underneath him. The drake perched atop the tightly packed shape of your curled up dragon body wrapped in his belly. He lets out a distressed squeek as you shift around, perhaps worried that you'll topple him over from within leading to him being smothered under the most amazing meal ever.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore5" text="not gonna be trouble, gonna be FOOD"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<text>
	You get comfortable, nuzzling the inside of the drake's taut tummy now and then as the digestion sets in. The enzymes slow to coat your body, the stomach walls so stretched they can barely squeeze on your firm body. But even without those rthythmic contractions the stomach walls provide a steady pressure and your movements rub the digestive fluids into your body. And slowly, slowly the drake began to digest and melt down your immense body. Enzymes softening and liquidating your form layer by layer as you stew in his belly and hear his steady breathing that indicates he's dozed off, digesting such a meal must of made the lil guy drowzy. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore6" text="gurgle"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore6">
	<text>
	You cannot say how long you stayed there being worked over by his digestive systems. But as time went on his belly rounded, your flesh softened and the rippling stomach walls pressed and squeezed over your more pliant and yielding form as your world and you shrunk, your form steadily being absorbed as the little reptile steadily digested and melted you down into soupyness. Mass and solidity steadily being taken away from you until finally the drake awakens to find a sloshy round and compact gut his own size to be all he sports as legacy of you, and by the time he awakens fully it's shrunk away that he can sort of walk on it. Got to hand it to the lil guy, its not every drake that gets to digest a dragon whose head alone is bigger than their entire body but he's a champ for managing it.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="lick0">
	<text>
	The drake mirps in surprise at the warm wet sensations as your tongue flicks out and across the side of his face, and wriggles a bit looking at you confusedly. So you give him a few more licks to get him used to your tongue and feel him nuzzle up against your jaws affectionately after the tongue washing.
	</text>
	<choice destination="lick1" text="lick him...lower"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="walk away"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="lick1">
	<text>
	The drake lets you groom and lick over him without being troubled as you nose and lick your way along his flanks, under his furled wing and then over his haunches. The drake chirrs and his tail sways out behind him as you coax his legs unconsciously higher...then dart your head in under his flank to lick over his loins. The drake letting out a startled mreep as he finds this large dragon licking over his shaft and making his length harden...
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore0" text="nose the tip, dragon wants in!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<text>
	Your tongue flicks and curls around his member one last time afore you decide he's ready, and more importantly that you don't have the patience to wait anymore, and nose in. The tip of your snout pressing against the tip of the far smaller lizard, feeling it moosh against your nose and then as you push in more insistently you feel the cumslit part and stretch around your face. The drake letting out a startled mreep and shuddering, the overwhelming sensations causing him to go weak in the knees and topple onto his flank, giving any hypothetical a good look at your head steadily sliding into the tiny young drake's cocktip. His length stretching out massively as a dragon many times his size thrusts herself into his maleness.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="deeper!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	The drake lets out a bewildered meep as you nose your way all the way down his length and into his balls. Your body from your neck down still extending out from his cocktip as you nuzzle against the inside of his balls and stretch them out larger than he is. The outline of your head clearly visible as the shape of his sack, splaying his lower legs out about the bulge as hot cum coats your face. It's clear the little guy is gonna be no help, guess you're gonna have to do the job of filling his balls with dragon all by yourself. You get a good grip digging your claws into the ground and thrust forwards, his blissed out chirrup and writhe barely notable to you as more of your body slides into the decadent sticky warmth of his shaft. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="so good, deeper!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	You continue feeding yourself to the lil drake's schlong, pushing off until your forelegs are pinned against your sides. The lusty warmth of his shaft stretching and throbbing around your sinous form as you writhe and wriggle deeper into his loins. The drake letting out a squeek amidst the blissed doped out confused chirring as his sack begins to stretch and bulge out massively. Already bigger than he is with just your head inside his balls swell with the tightly packed outline of your body worming into those hungry warm confines. Your lower legs sliding into his tip leaving only your tail swishing around not yet consumed, without any leverage outside his shaft you set about squirming and wriggling in his sack to tug your tail into his dick.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="all curled up now"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	The drake looks up from where he's still resting on his side and prods a forepaw against his incomprehensibly massive sack, feeling the firm shape of your flank under the sack skin and cum. He's clearly a bit stunned by what just happened, why did this huge dragon just willingly wriggle and worm her way all the way into his balls and....he lets out a chirr as his sack makes a pulsating churning noise attempting to contract around the dragon many times his own size. And abruptly the drake doesn't seem to care anymore WHY you're in there, as he knows what's going to happen to you now that you're in there...and so do you, it was the plan right?
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore4" text="yes...time to be nutbutter for the lil guy, gonna be such a big load!"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore4">
	<text>
	The massively stretched sack of the diminutive reptile ripples around you, soaking your hide with hot cum wonderfully as it secretes more digestive cream. Every detail of your form even down to the shape of your eyes is visible in how taut his balls have become in order to contain all of your immense form. But for all your immensity and might once in a sack you'll digest like any other cockfood, just might take a little longer. You can feel motion against your flank but barely hear his chirrs over the glorp of cum around your head as he jerks off..and gradually time becomes soft and pliant, impossible to define..much like you start to be...
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="melt...melt away"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	The sack of the drake starts to round out, losing definition slowly as you soften and melt inside his overly burdened balls. The drake occasionally kneading paws against his sackflesh and feeling your flank starting to yield and turn softer under the pressure of his comparatively tiny limbs. The taut sack now starting to contract and round out, compacting your form steadily as you're now more jizz than dragon. You're still just about holding together though as you're reduced from apex of creation to decadent fluids within the drake's balls but you know that won't last much longer. Your perception contracting in a sea of gurgling sloshing cream until in your last instant you feel a sloshy glorp ripple through your form and then...nothing, all that you were now rendered into hot spunk spreads out undifferentiated into an immense load within the drake's sack.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvoreGO" text="what is he going to do with me.."/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="cockvoreGO">
	<text>
	The drake looks at his looming sack and chirrs, he's still not clued in as to why a great big dragon would want to get churned down into his cum. But he's content with how things happened, he wraps both forepaws around his cock and kneads at his fluid sack with his hindpaws. The lizard starting to fap noisily as hot cum starts to leak from his tip. The former dragon in his balls is making him unbelievably pent up from all that high pressure jizz you'd turned into within him. The drake finding his relief at last as his pleasure reaches a peak and he cums, and cums..and cums, his cock firehosing thick splatters of jizz out onto the ground into a growing puddle and then LAKE of thick gooey ball batter. The drake can feel his balls shrinking, but he knows he's not even halfway..the lizard wriggling as the thick gooey mass piles up around him, easing his head up a bit further clear of the rising tide of jizz as his sack shrinks until finally it begans to taper off. The little lizard letting out a chirp of satisfaction as the last gush of ex-dragon splats forth..then sets about tiredly wading clear of the spreading lake of steaming jizz all around him.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
</Conversation>