<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The fawn whimpers looking up at you with literal doe eyes,
			helpless and unable to escape your might she's entirely at your mercy
			and knows it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="feeling hungry">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="maybe it'd be fun to force her up your ass">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="you feel your balls ache at the sight of her">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="capture" text="use capture device">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/fawn.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="fawn" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="feeling merciful" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
	<text>
	You've made your decision, this cute thing is going to go into you via the back way. She seems uneasy at the look in your eye as you 
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				pause to undress and then
			</conditional>
			place yourself over her, your bared rump placed over her head. The fawn blushing and trying to shrink back from your <macro ID="butt_size_desc"/> rear end. But you're easily able to keep her where you need her. But it's not where you need her, oh no...you start to squat down, one hand keeping the helpless fawn's head from pulling back as she lets out a muffled whimper...then you feel the exquisite sensations and hear the nice lewd schlorp as your sphincter parts around her face and you usher your prey into the heat of your back passage. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore1" text="ass food is the best use for someone as cute as this"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore1">
	<text>
	You can hear her muffled distress from deep in your bowels as she struggles. But she's in no position to stop you sitting down over her and thus sliding her steadily into your ass, the fawn's writhing torso steadily disappearing between the cheeks of your <macro ID="butt_size_desc"/> ass as you can't help but groan in decadent delight. Your middle bulging with the outline of her face as she's forced deeper and deeper inside of you. Your clenching rump starting to tug her in as you squat there with her legs protruding from your ass. She keeps on squirming, legs flailing as they're constrained by your tight sphincter, but she isn't even really slowing down the schlorping of your ravenous rear end.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore2" text="pull her in entirely"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore2">
	<text>
	You ease yourself into a more comfortable position as the cute fawn's feet get closer and closer to disappearing betwixt your ass cheeks. Her legs easily schlurped up, only able to twitch now as she sounds her distress muffledly from where she's clenched and curled deep inside of you. In a few more moments though you're feeling the wonderful satisfaction of those wriggly toes of hers disappearing past your sphincter. Her body now disappearing entirely into your squeezing derriere. You can feel her forcibly curled up within you, squirming and twitching around in your possessive and smothering heat. You get comfortable with both hands on your round and full belly, the fawn entirely under your control and within your power.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore3" text="digest her of course"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore3">
	<text>
	The fawn lets out a whimper as you let your insides start to gurgle her away, but she can hardly move let alone struggle and so her twitching only serves to please you. The fawn gradually fading into silence as your digestive processes take their toll and she softens then eventually melts and smoothes out into a nice nourishing soup within you. The fawn serving to fuel you as her body works back the way she came, seeping through your innards and being absorbed gradually yet efficiently into your being.
	</text>
	<effect type="feed" value="80" />
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="0" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text></text>

		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			you study the fawn extensively, observing and taking samples.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="fawn" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			She's truly a delectible little doe and you find your balls acheing
			hungrily in desire to have her inside. The fawn letting out a squeek
			as she sees your hand slide down to
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				stroke over your crotch afore you start to remove your pants and
				unveil your growing cock before
			</conditional>
				stroke over your hard and hungry length. That firming erection transfixing the fawn's gaze as she uneasily
			watches you work your hands up and down your cock. As you then squat
			down she looks confused as she looks down past herself at you and
			your cock, but all is swiftly revealed to her as you seize her feet
			and stuff them into your cocktip. The fawn letting out a helpless
			whimper and squirming, but unable to pull away from your grip as you
			feet more of her cute lil legs down your dick.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="feed her in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			The fawn tries to struggle, but she was no match for you even
			before
			this. her cute little body feels wonderful sliding into your
			dick
			though, nice and squirmy as she tries to wriggle around onto her
			front and grasp the ground beneath her. The fawn whimpering and
			squeeling as your cock steadily schlurp schlurp schlurps up her
			writhing legs. You can feel her slender form stretching out your cock
			as you engulf her thighs and work up to her waist, her cute nub of a
			doe-tail teasing at your cockslit before being engulfed as well. Her
			feet pushing into your balls, pressing and stretching them out and
			the sticky sensations of hot goo on her toes makes her squirm in a
			pleasingly and adorably helpless fashion.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="rest of the way" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The fawn must of already known it was hopeless, but she squirms
			even as
			you work up over her belly and petite chest. the fawn letting
			out a
			whimper as your cocktip slides up around her grasping arms and
			woe-stricken face. You feel her squirming form contained in your
			loins as those arms are sucked inside, stroking your cock to feel her
			being fed steadily into your balls. Her legs curling up, distending
			your sack with their shape afore her upper body plunges down to join
			the lower as fuel for your hungry sack. The fawn whimpering and
			squirming about in the hot cummy bath, making your sack jostle
			against your thighs as you stroke yourself.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="melt her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			Time to turn the lil fawn to nutbutter, oh yes. And the thought
			makes you
			stroke all the harder, running your hand up and down your
			shaft as
			you feel her squirm and whimper in your churning balls. The
			fawn
			pushing out weakly against the inside of those sagging nuts as
			they
			steadily do away with her. Her form gurgling and softening and
			then
			melting away into gallons of hot thick cream as your pace of
			stroking
			steadily increases. Your balls going still and contracting,
			rounding
			out as every solid mass is sloshed away and all that's left
			is a
			pleasing liquid weight. That needy pressure stirring you on to
			greater heights of stimulation, a groaning gasp heralding your climax
			as with a spasm of your hips you reach orgasm. A blast of hot cum
			rocketing up your shaft, splattering on the ground only to be
			followed by another hefty discharge of cum..and another, and another,
			as shot after shot you empty out your balls of much of the cum made
			of the fawn. that cute body now nothing more than fuel for your lust.
			By the time you're done you sigh and behold both your sticky and
			still dribbling tip and the immense gooey puddle of fawn you've
			created. She was adorable, but it's hard not to think she's better
			this way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="she was a wonderful load" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			Mercy? when she looks so delectible? how absurd. Besides,
			helpless morsel
			like her would of ended up eaten by someone sooner or
			later. And so
			it doesn't seem that bad to seize her hands and pull
			them to your
			lips, sliding them into your mouth, then your throat and
			enjoying her
			delicious flavour. Her eyes widen and with a whimper she
			attempts to
			pull her arms back, but the weak lil fawn is unable to
			resist your
			hunger. Her head being eased slowly closer to your lips
			even as she
			struggles.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="tastey fawn" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			She lets out a fearful squeel when you get past her head,
			sealing her
			into darkness as you wrap your lips around her shoulders.
			Her tail
			twitching cutely as she wriggles around and her legs scramble
			for
			purchase. It makes it all the more delicious as you work her down
			your throat, feel her plunging headfirst into your belly and starting
			to push it out from the inside. Truly someone so tastey and so unable
			to resist belongs in your belly and you take a series of eager
			swallows dragging her chest and middle past your lips, her form
			starting to curl as she's fed squirming into your now growing gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="finish her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			She's but a meal, her petite body easy to claim as you tip your
			head back
			and start swallowing her legs. She still squirms, but even
			the
			whimpering fawn has probably realized it was hopeless from the
			moment
			you set eyes on her and decided to make her your meal. Those
			delicious legs sliding past your lips, over your tongue and down your
			throat. As you claim your feet and send them on their way she lets
			out a whimper of resignation, curling up entirely as a bulge in your
			belly now as you polish her off. She was already in your power, the
			imprisonment inside your hungry belly is merely a formal codifying of
			the natural order.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="let her be one with her superior" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			She resists your digestive system as well as she resisted your
			other
			desires. The weak squirms overcome in record time with the
			gurgles
			and churns of your stomach breaking her down. The bulge of her
			cute
			body turning round and soft and then shrinking away as she takes
			her
			rightful place as your food. The fawn's nutrients flowing into you
			with ease.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="she was a delicious snack" />
	</page>

</Conversation>