<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The fawn whimpers up at you with literal doe eyes,
			helpless and unable to escape your might. She's entirely at your mercy
			and knows it.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="Craving venison...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="Maybe it'd be fun to fit her up your ass.">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0"
			text="Your balls ache at the sight of her.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unbirthing0"
			text="Your nethers tingle with voracious need">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use your capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="Study her.">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/fawn.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="fawn" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="Devour her.">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Feeling merciful." />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthing0">
	<text>
	As you look down at the little fawn, a tingle of excitement runs across your lower belly, letting you know exactly where you are going to stuff her. The thought of a squirming little doe plunging deep into your nethers is enough to nearly drive you crazy. The fawn watches in complete embarrassment as you slide your left hand down to your nether lips to let your tunnel know to prepare for her. Unable to wait any longer you grab her right arm and pull her forward then press your wet pussy over her face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthing1" text="oh yes"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthing1">
	<text>
	A delighted moan escapes your lips as you feel the stunned fawn squirm against your hungry pussy which was now spreading over her face. With a gentle press forward and down your nethers swallow up her head and tug in more of her soft little body. At this point, the bulge of her head formed a nice outline over your lower belly, which would grow into a nice heavy dome soon. Not waiting for any interruptions, you force more of her in. It was fortunate she was in a kneeling position as this made it nice and simple since she wasn't very strong in resisting and pushing would just speed her to her fate. As she is drawn in, your hands rest against the growing bulge of your womb, you gently played with the nubs of her horns and ears. Eventually, she was nearly claimed as her shoulders, arms and wrists sink into your hungry depths.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthing2" text="take her all the way"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthing2">
	<text>
	With just a little more to go, you slide more of her in until only her lower legs are sticking out and still kicking. You bring your hips forward and rest your body on the ground with legs spread and bent on either side of you. The last bit of the little fawn travels up your body and curls fully in your hungry womb, finally claiming its little treat. With the fawn curled up inside, you could not help but rub your engorged and squirming stomach. Each bulge shifted under your palms as the fawn both got comfortable as well as pressed for any way out. She would be lucid for quite a while, so you would have more than enough time to enjoy her movements. It was nice to just take a moment and enjoy the environment, with your active midsection.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthing3" text="and then the liquidation"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthing3">
	<text>
	While your wet and excited pussy still leaked you rested your back against a comfortable rock, and let your body do its magic. As time passed you played with yourself as the fawn was broken down into a wonderful gush of juice and warm liquid pleasure. Soon all bulges faded and left you with a smooth belly that reduced in size as what was left gushed out of your nethers. When you were done you got up ready to continue on with renewed energy.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
		You've made your decision, this cute thing is going up your rear end. She seems uneasy
		about the look in your eyes as you 
		<conditional>
			<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			first pause to undress and then
		</conditional>
		place yourself over her, bare rump looming over her head. The fawn blushes and tries to
		shrink away from your
		<macro ID="butt_size_desc"/>
		ass, but you're easily able to keep her where you need her. But it's not where you really,
		really need her, no ma'am... You squat down, one hand clutching the helpless fawn's head to
		prevent her from pulling back, leaving her unable to do anything about her situation but
		whimper, this time muffled by the posterior inches from her face. Then, pushing down, the
		exquisite sensations and the schlorp of a parting pucker around her face ring through your
		body and ears as you usher your prey into the heat of your backdoor. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="Ass-food is the best way to eat someone as cute as this girl."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
		You can hear her muffled distress from deep in your bowels as she struggles. But she's in
		no position to stop your descent on her, sliding steadily into your ass, her writhing torso
		steadily disappearing between the cheeks of your <macro ID="butt_size_desc"/> ass. And you
		can't help but groan in decadent delight while your abdomen bulges with the outline of her face
		forced deeper and deeper inside of you. Your clenching rump starts to tug her in faster than you
		can bear down as you squat there with her legs protruding from your ass, and faster the more her
		body tapers down. She keeps on squirming, legs flailing until they're locked together by your
		tightened sphincter. She, of course, had no hope of actually accomplishing anything to really
		slow down the schlorping of your ravenous rear.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2" text="Pull her in entirely."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
		You ease yourself into a more comfortable position as the cute fawn's feet get closer and closer to
		disappearing betwixt your ass-cheeks. Her legs easily schlurped up, only able to twitch now as she
		sounds her distress muffledly from where she's clenched and curled deep inside of you. In a few more
		moments though, you're feeling the wonderful satisfaction of those wriggly hoof-toes of hers disappearing
		past your back-entrance with a wet little pop. Her body hs now disappeared entirely into your derriere.
		You can feel her forcibly curled up within you, squirming and twitching around in your possessive and
		smothering heat. You get comfortable with both hands on your round and full belly, the fawn entirely under
		your control and within your power.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore3" text="Digest her, of course."/>
		<choice destination="analvore3Disposal" text="Absorb her directly into your ass..">
		<preference fetish="disposal" />		
	</choice>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore3">
		<text>
			After your intestines send her along on the conveyor belt to your stomach, the fawn lets out a whimper,
			realizing what you plan for her right before your insides start to gurgle her away, but she can hardly
			move, let alone struggle, and so her resistance only really serves to please you more. In time, the
			deer-girl's voice gradually fades into silence as your digestive processes take their toll, and soon
			her body softens then eventually melts and smoothens out into a nice, nourishing soup within you which
			shall fuel you as her body works back the way she came, seeping through your innards and being absorbed 
			gradually yet efficiently into your being.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore3Disposal">
		<text>
			With the fawn girl still wiggling and squirming inside of your intestines, you moan and clench them tighter and tighter, feeling her body getting softer and softer, squishing quite lewdly inside of you as her form began to lose shape and definition, instead starting to become more cylindrical and brown, her struggles slowing, then stopping, as you patted your belly a few times, grinning to yourself as you felt your ass successfully convert half of the cute doe into nutrients for your body, and the other half directly into a turd for you to squeeze out of your ass. After a few minutes, you squat down and grunt softly, starting to feel your pucker spread back open as the fawn's shitty remains slip back out, plopping into a steaming uniform pile on the ground.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified and unelaborated-on, yet surely satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="0" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			You study the fawn extensively, observing and taking samples before sending her back off, all frazzled and frightened.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="fawn" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Time to do some research." />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			She's truly a delectible little doe and you find your balls aching hungrily with desire to have her inside. She lets
			out a squeak when she sees you slide your hand down to
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				stroke over your crotch, before removing the obstruction so you can whip out and 
			</conditional>
			run it along your hard and hungry cock. Your firming erection transfixes the fawn's gaze as she anxiously follows the
			movement of your hands up and down its length. Then, as you squat down beside her feet, she puts forth a confused expression,
			nonverbally entreating you for an explanation. All is swiftly revealed to her, however, as you seize her feet
			and stuff them into your cocktip. The fawn helplessly whimpers and squirms but is unable to pull away from your grip as you
			feed more of her cute li'l legs down your dick.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="Push her in." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			The fawn tries to struggle, to free herself, but she was no match for you, even before all this. Her body slides wonderfully
			into your dick though, nice and squirmy as she tries to wriggle around onto her front and clutch onto the grass beneath her,
			whimpering and squealing all the way. Your schlong makes short work of her legs and easily stretches to fit her slender form,
			engulfing her thighs and working up to her waist, cute nub of a doe-tail teasing at your cockslit before slipping in as well.
			Meanwhile, her feet push into your balls, making hoof-shaped indents in your skin as the hot spunk and slack elasticity inside
			revitalizes her squirming magnificently.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="Take her the rest of the way." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The fawn surely must know it's hopeless by now, but still, she squirms, even as you work up over her belly and petite, A-cuppish
			chest. She whines as your cocktip slides up around her grasping arms and woe-stricken face, kicking and struggling but steadfastly
			contained your collective loins as her arms are bound and sucked inside. You feel her contours against your palms as you stroke your
			cock, no longer even needing to put the effort in to push her along; your body has that handled, steadily drawing her into your balls.
			Her legs are forced to curl up, already distending your sack with their shape before her upper body plunges down to join them as a new
			pendulum for your hungry sack. And yet her futile resistance does not cease even after she's reached the end of the line, thrashing and
			fussing as though it could possibly convince you to let her out. All she accomplishes is jostling her confines around while you sit back
			stroke yourself.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="Melt her up." />
	</page>

<!-- really let the line length get away from me. don't feel like fixing it though since it doesn't truly affect anything -->

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			Time to turn the li'l doe to pearls, yes ma'am. The thought of her transformation
			makes you jerk it that much harder while her pushing against the inside of those
			sagging nuts weakens, minute by minute, as they work their magic with her.
			Pretty soon, the gurgling softens and melts her away into gallons of thick, hot
			cream and your pace quickens with her expiry. Your balls go still and contract,
			rounding out as every hint of solid mass sloshes away and all that's left
			is a heavy, pleasant weight, itching for release. That needy pressure stirs you on to
			greater heights of stimulation before a moaning gasp and spasming hips herald your
			volcanic climax. A blast of hot cum rockets up your shaft and separates in the air,
			every droplet splattering sloppily on the ground, on the rocks and grass, on your limp,
			panting form; only to be followed by another hefty discharge and ensuing rain of cum, 
			and another, and another, and another, and another, shot after shot after shot. And so
			you soon empty your balls of the jizz you made of the fawn, that charming frame reduced
			to nothing more than the remains of your lust. By the time you recover from the afterglow,
			you sigh, beholding both your sticky and still-dribbling tip and the immense, slippery puddle
			of fawn you've created around you. She was adorable, but it's hard not to think she's better
			this way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="She was a wonderful load." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			Mercy? When she looks so delectible? The prospect is patently absurd. Besides,
			a helpless morsel like her would have ended up eaten by someone else sooner or
			later. Best that it's you. And so, without any ethical qualms, you seize her hands
			and guide them to your lips, sliding them into your mouth for your throat to swallow,
			enjoying her delicious, sweat-salted flavour all the way. Her eyes widen and,
			with an eep, she attempts to retract her arms, but the doe, already frail and
			weakened further by defear, is way unable to resist your hunger and iron grip.
			She yanks her head back, but as you pass her elbows, she resigns to bow it
			forward, between her upper arms, perhaps fearing a broken neck.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Succulent morsel." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Her fearful squaeling muffles once you get past her head and seal her
			eyes into darkness while your lips slink past her neck and over her
			shoulders. Her tail twitches before you quite adorably as she wriggles
			around in your grip, her legs scramble for purchase as you hoist
			her off the ground. Her fear makes her all the more delicious as you
			work her down your throat and feel her plunge headfirst into your belly,
			making just a faint outline. Truly, someone so tasty and so helpless
			to resist belongs in your belly. You take a series of eager
			swallows, dragging her chest and midsection past your lips, her form
			starting to curl and contort as she's fed squirming into your bulging gut.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Take one last gulp." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			She's doomed to mealhood, her petite body easy to claim the rest of
			as you tip your head back and gulp down her legs. Even after she settles
			into your stomach, she insists on squirming. She really should have realized
			escape was hopeless from the moment you set eyes on her. Eventually, though,
			you hear her groan her resignation, masked by the gurgling of your gut. Such
			is the natural order of things.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="Let her become one with her superior." />
		<choice destination="oralvore3Disposal" text="Let her become a dump for her superior.">
		<preference fetish="disposal" />		
	</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			She resists your digestive system about as well as she resisted your
			other plans for her. Pitiful fussing cedes to digestion in record time
			as your churning stomach breaks her down. The bulge of her darling
			form softens up and rounds out before shrinking away as she takes
			her rightful place as your food.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="What a delicious snack." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3Disposal">
		<text>
			She resists your digestive system about as well as she resisted your
			other plans for her. Pitiful fussing cedes to digestion in record time
			as your churning stomach breaks her down. The bulge of her darling
			form softens up and rounds out before shrinking away as she takes
			her rightful place as your food. After a bit longer, you find a good 
			grassy spot to let the fawn back out, thrusting your ass out as your ass 
			cheeks spread open and the fawn's remains slide out and plop on to the forest 
			floor, fertilizing it with your waste and ensuring more fawns will be able to eat 
			and grow up to be consumed by you, continuing the cycle.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="What a delicious snack." />
	</page>

</Conversation>