<?xml version="1.0"?>

<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
			<preference fetish="demis" />
		<preference fetish="females" />				
	<text>
	The Fawn seems to abruptly notice your tiny form near her. And for seemingly once in her life she finds a living creature she has no reason to fear. The loli ish girl squatting down to look closer at you and then experimentally picks you up off of the ground. Her innocent curiousity is sorta adorable, but for the fact you're helpless in the hands of the feral youngling. Her thumb stroking over your body as she brings you up to her face, then gives you a little sniff.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="*she likes what she smells*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	The fawn mhmms and then flicks her tongue out, sampling the flavour that goes along with that smell and then smiling. The lil one licking her lips and mulling over the flavour, her adorable head canting to the side as she thinks it over..and then opens wide and nomphs over your head and shoulders. Her hot wet mouth wrapped around the upper part of your body as she suckles and licks on you. Her tongue schlurping and playing around the top of you as she schlurps and savours you, well it's quite nice to be appreciated. But you can see that her throat is flexing in the gloom just past the top of your head, you're soon going to end up appreciated a lot more thoroughly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="*eaten by a cutie*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The fawn mhmphs as her throat flexes to engulf your head and shoulders. The cutie tipping her head back and running her tongue along your belly and legs as she lets go of you with her hand and tries to swallow up your tiny body. The fawn seeming to have a bit of trouble getting the bulge of your body past the entrance of her throat, but gradually she starts to squeeze you down her neck. Your legs flailing around and then disappearing past her lips as you become a meal for the youngling. The fawn's trim belly becoming your home as you finish plunging down her throat into the depths of her cute tummy.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="*food for cutie*"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	The fawn can be felt feeling up her belly as she feels you moving around in her. But you don't exactly make a bulge in the cutie. The lil fawn blushing at the feeling and licking your flavour off her lips innocently afore bounding off. She seemingly has forgotten about you or else is unmindful of you as she travels and you're jostled and bounced around. But gradually your bouncing turns to splashing as enzymes rise and fluids engulf you. And soon all your motions turn to sloshing as you diminish and dissolve into a nutritious broth inside her. The lil deer demi's body breaking you down into fuel, turning you into a meal for someone almost at the bottom of the food chain...almost, because she's eaten you.
	</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>