<?xml version="1.0"?>

<Conversation>

<!-- consider adding at a later date:

- ability to let fawn go in oral vore (choice of regurgitation or, if anal vore, expulsion that way)

- anal vore scene for seduced

- unbirth scene for both

-->
	<page ID="start">
		<text> The deer-girl blushes bright red, shyly, nervously watching you with a hand
			thrust between her legs, fingers delving into her furred snatch.
			You've charmed your way past her skittish nature and now, over-awed by your
			presence, she makes no move to retreat at your approach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal0" text="She looks tasty.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="preyslut0" text="I wonder if I could fit in that belly">
			<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="She'd make good cockfood.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use you capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="Study her.">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/fawn.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="fawn" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="Devour her.">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Let her fondle herself in peace." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="preyslut0">
	<text>
	The lil fawn is cute, but you can't help but imagine how cute she'd look with a belly. Though you might need to be the one to do most of the work on this one. <conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				She looks on curiously and with desire as you strip off your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				and expose your naked body before her. 
			</conditional>
			You bend forwards in front of the cutie and press your fingers at her lips. The fawn nuzzling at your hand affectionately and licking your fingers without realizing what you intend. Seems you're going to have to be a bit more pro active.
	</text>
	<choice destination="preyslut1" text="*shove your hands in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="preyslut1">
	<text>
	You force the issue, pushing your hands past her lips. Her eyes widening as her lips stretch and she gets your flavour more intensely. But she doesn't even have time to acclimatize to this before you're leaning forwards, feeding your arms down her throat as she lets out adorable muffled noises. That throat is tight as well, just the thought of how tight this must mean her lil belly is makes you shiver with anticipation. Your chosen pred hasn't gotten into her role just yet though, and so you duck your head down and continue to wriggle your way further into her as she squirms around.
	</text>
	<choice destination="preyslut2" text="she'll warm up to it"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="preyslut2">
	<text>
	The fawn reaches up to touch the sides of your naked body as you shove your head down past her lips and into her mouth. She seems to be taking her first attempt at swallowing, yielding to your desires and perhaps matching it with her own new found interest in putting you inside herself. Her cute belly going flat to bulging as your hands and then arms squeeze down inside her little body, you wriggle your hips and lean forwards as your descent begins to slow. The tightness of her stomach and the reluctance with which it yields works against the both of you. But her increasingly confident swallows are gradually taking charge of the process, and of you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="preyslut3" text="eat me you cute little thing"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="preyslut3">
	<text>
	You moan into the depths of her belly as she swallows her way down around your belly, then hips..working your rear end steadily past her jaws and then only having your legs to work in. Her hands are on the growing wondrous bulge in her middle now as she lays back and angles your legs up above her so they can be swallowed down. She's going to do it, she's really going to do it, you'd be so proud if you weren't also lunch about now. Your legs gradually disappearing out of view past her lips as she swallows you up entirely at long last.
	</text>
	<choice destination="preyslut4" text="finally eaten"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="preyslut4">
	<text>
	The fawn blushes and rubs her belly, the massive dome of her gut is such she can't get up or see past her bulging belly full of you. The lil cutie letting out an adorable mhmm and wriggling about a bit. Her stomach squeezing oh so wonderfully tight around you as her body awakens to the presences of an exceptional and unprecedented meal within her. The first gurgles and tensing ripples of her stretched out tummy walls around you hopefully a sign of what's to come.
	</text>
	<choice destination="preyslut5" text="you can digest me, i believe in you cutie"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="preyslut5">
	<text>
	You can hardly squirm in the tight confines of her belly, but do perhaps in impatience as her stomach proves slow in getting to work on you. But get to work on you it does, proving even the lowliest and least predatory can have you as a meal given enough encouragement. Her stomach starts to gurgle and glorp loudly, squeezing on you as enzymes soak your body. And gradually the fawn finds your shape softening and compacting..she still can't believe what just happened, why you drove her wild with desire only to feed yourself to her..but it feels, so very good..as the last of you dissolves and digests away within her and her gut shrinks down she can only reflect in wonderment on her experience as every trace of you is absorbed. And were you around to think about it, you'd probably agree that letting her explore her predatory side was totally worth it.
	</text>	
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified and unelaborated-on, yet surely satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>
	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			You study the fawn extensively, observing and taking samples before sending her back off, confused but happy to keep her life.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="fawn" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Time to do some research." />
	</page>

	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			Such a lusty and adorable girl. You think she'd make great cockfood. As you approach her,
			you
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				pull off the garments over your crotch, freeing your cock, and
			</conditional>
			stroke your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			schlong while towering over her, inducing her to blush even harder as her gaze shifts over
			to your trouser-snake, which grows larger and hungrier every pulsing second. You slide
			a hand down to caress her hair and wrap it around her head, bringing her face up and
			smooshing it against your throbbing girth. In response, she only thinks to give it a lick.
			"Oh, that's not quite what I'm after," you sultrily utter, before guiding her face down the
			underside and planting it betwixt your nads. You make sure she hears your balls burbling
			before informing her, "You're going inside there." She tenses up and makes a shocked sound
			as she puts two and two together, but she can't pull back, and part of her doesn't actually
			want to pull back. And as you rub her face into your scrotum and drown her nose with your musk,
			that part that wants to back out gets smaller and smaller until, with a shudder and a moan,
			she thrusts her hand back down into her crotch, overcome with adoring desire and compliance,
			even knowing all she'll be real soon is seed.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="Feed her to your cock." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You hold her in place a moment longer before moving on to the next and far more enjoyable part.
			Releasing her head, you angle yourself up to present your cockslit to her face before thrusting
			forward and sloppily "smooching" her mouth with it, a viscous strand of pre bridging the gap as
			you pull back. And the fawnish doe doesn't even think to squirm until you buck your hip forwards
			and slip her face through the lubricated slit, oozing even more pre-cum around her face and down
			her neck as it engulfs her head. She squeaks and writhes at the sensation, partially out of
			reflex and partially out of a desire to please. Your shaft ripples with desire to bring more of
			her into you, sucking in her shoulders, her collar, her flattish chest with lurching motions.
			And it feels delightful, not only to have her body stretch your shaft wider, but for that body
			to also playfully resist. It takes some of your will not to prematurely cum her back out before
			she's even in. You can only imagine she's enjoying the massage of your cock's constant throbbing,
			as well, judging by her delighted squeals and feverish fingering. She even seems to be trying to
			force herself deeper, though she's kinda not strong enough to be in a position to do that. You're
			more than happy to oblige, though, quickly pushing her in down to slender ass and twitchy tail.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="Now for the legs." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			Now that she's more than halfway down your cock, face making impressions in your balls, all you
			can think of is how good it will feel to have the rest of her inside. Her face is locked in
			a constant series of moans and gasps, bulging from your yearning gonads. Well, soon they'll
			have her. You squeeze the fawn's entrapped tush, coaxing a yelp from her and helping her even
			further along, despite the kicking of her legs. Soon, they can no longer even twitch, all wrapped
			up tight, just leaving gravity to finish the job of dropping her into your sack all curled up
			and cute. The final push elicits a gasp of delight from your mouth and a pleasurable shudder
			from your spine. And so she dangles there, continuing to fondle herself while waiting for
			what comes next.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="Melt her down." />
		<choice destination="cockvore3Endo" text="Hold her for a while." />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			"Safely" ensconced in your ballsack, the cutie suddenly moans loudly.
			Sounds like she just finished. Now it's time for your balls to do
			their thing and melt the relaxed, post-climax fawn right up. Though
			she's drained by her afterglow, she still manages to kick and squirm
			a little with the noisy burbling and churning of your balls' weird
			but sexy metabolic process. The lusty fluids, hot on her body, bathe and
			marinate her, inspiring her with a second wind and a delirious gasp to
			go at her peach. But she's already losing form. She probably won't finish
			this time. Soon, she ceases to resemble a humanoid, and even sooner,
			with a toe-curlingly magnificent sensation, condenses into a ball, just a
			hefty, liquid weight swinging from your loins, your nuts informing you
			with that triumphant and satisfying burble that your body has finished
			its work and resolved this solid doe-flesh into a very special kind of
			dew. It's music to your ears. With one hand on your shaft and the other
			fondling your bloated pair, it's getting time to expel all this sloshing
			cum. You quicken your pace, more than ready to move on to the final act
			of the fawn's existence. When your orgasm comes, the deer erupts from
			your cock as a hefty series of cummy splatters, each blast of thick,
			creamy jizz both deliciously satisfying and a fitting use for the fawn's
			charming little body. For a few moments more, as your orgasm subsides,
			you revel in afterglow, studying your handiwork: a goopy puddle of aromatic
			jizz in the grass. But you have more to do, and more cute things to coax
			into ending themselves inside your balls, so soon, it's time to move on
			and leave the fawn's sticky remains to cool and be absorbed by the soil.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

<page ID="cockvore3Endo">
		<text>
			Whether or not she understood what you were saying or even actually
			cares to argue the case, technically, all you promised was that
			she'd be going in there, and you made good on your word. You didn't
			really feel like actually melting her. Instead, you just want to
			kick back and relax in the soft grass, cool breeze, and quiet company.
			The doe, meanwhile, gets to play with herself to her heart's content,
			letting out with a moan to let you know she's enjoying herself every
			couple minutes. Eventually, though, she exhausts herself, and you remember
			you have things to do, so you tell her, "Time to let you out, now,"
			before taking your rod in hand and stroking it back to firmness.
			You follow up with, "Be a dear and help me out," giving her head a
			pat with your free hand. She seems to understand what you're after,
			and gets back to squirming for you. It feels just as great as when
			you got her in, and soon, you moan in delight as a stream of cum,
			followed by a doe, streaks through the wildgrass. Dazed and sliding
			a couple feet, she takes as long as you do to get up before beam
			at you and starting to scamper off, her stubby tail flicking faster
			than you've even seen them flick before.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="Wave goodbye." />
		<choice destination="capture" text="Capture her before she gets away.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="meal0">
		<text>
			The fawn lets out an adorable little gasp as you step up closer,
			pulling her up against your body and sliding an arm around her
			waist. She nuzzles up against you, murring, as you lean down,
			though the murr turns into a cunfused coo as you lick the top
			of her head, getting a taste for her hair, even sucking some into
			your hungry mouth. She glances up, curiosity and an uncharacteristic
			lack of fear written in her eyes as they meet your own. So, to test
			her trust, you take one of her hands with your own and guide it
			to your belly, letting her feel the hungry rumble that wordlessly
			conveys your intentions to her. First she whimpers, but then she
			blushes, so enamoured, so lost in her desire for you that even
			this intent she accepts as the price of getting close to you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal1" text="Eat her." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal1">
		<text>
			The look on her face makes you smile, but only for a moment. You
			have a fawn to devour, so you can't keep your mouth shut and smiling
			forever. Sliding your hands down to grip her petite little ass, you
			lift her up into the air. She doesn't weigh much. A yelp of surprise
			followed by a gasp of desire spill from her throat as your lips part
			over the top of her head. She makes no move to resist. You're going
			to devour her and she ain't stopping you. Her thighs rub together,
			the fur over her sex thoroughly soaked with her arousal as her head
			passes through. Your hot, wet throat easily parts around her face while
			your lips slide down her body, taking her in inch by inch. It's ever
			so easy to work her inside; soon you're at her waist her head in your
			belly. A confused and conflicted murmur rises up from from her as she
			enters the chamber that shall mark her end, then gives in to her desire,
			perfectly willing to be one with you, nuzzling submissively against the
			walls of your stomach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal2" text="Keep moving along." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal2">
		<text>
			She's your willing meal, murring and shivering inside you as
			you pause to lap your tongue over her furred sex, savoring its
			unique flavors while her feet twitch wildly in front of you.
			Her tail tickles the roof of your mouth as you ease her slim booty through your lips.
			Then suddenly, she peaks, shuddering like a vibrator inside your
			throat. With a loud cry, she floods your mouth with gamey fluids
			that run out your mouth and down your chin like watermelon juice.
			She pants and murrs within you as you kick back your head and let
			gravity slide her legs down to join the rest of her so she can
			curl up and continue to nuzzle agaisnt you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="meal3" text="Digest the cutie-pie." />
	</page>

	<page ID="meal3">
		<text>
			As you rub your distended gut, you feel her shifting and stirring 
			inside, tightly bound inside your abdomen. Soon, your acids begin
			to pour in, her gasps and murrs turning to little whimpers
			as your gut gurgles around her. But her face still nuzzles up
			through the skin of your tummy, against your rubbing hands.
			Conflicted as she may be, you've made her want this act of
			complete submission, her body given freely and totally unto
			you. After a short while, her nuzzling weakens and eventually
			stops, her movement soon after subsiding as your stomach gurgles
			louder. Her body steadily loses its shape now, as your belly turns
			soft and round. Then it begins to shrink as she sluices through your
			guts, the doe utterly digested. Soon you're back to normal, the fawn
			now no more than a meal, a nice memory, and, if you believe that stuff,
			something that will stay with you forever.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="80" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>
</Conversation>