<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		The catgirl pirate pouts and pants as she slumps in front of you, she seems to have lost her hat and her rogueish outfit is in disarray. "no fair" she utters, apparently having taken being thoroughly duffed over by you with poor sportsmanship. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="$should of thought of that before you found yourself about to be eaten">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />		
		</choice>
		<choice destination="fuck0" text="fair? what's fair, your ass is mine (fuck her)">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="darn"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="fuck0">
	<text>
	"what? no, nyah!" she protests trying to fend you off as you grab her legs and spread them, pulling her towards you. The kitty weakly shoving against your chest as you yank her skirt out of the way and stroke your shaft to hardness. The kitty unable to pull herself away as you shift your grip to her hip and press your tip against her nethers, grinding against her "You can't do this!" she protests further as you prepare to violate her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck1" text="quiet, fuckmeat doesn't get to talk"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck1">
	<text>
	The kitty's cheeks redden at that command, her further disobedient utterances though are interrupted as you thrust into her. The kitty letting out a gasp as she's stretched around your <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> shaft. You press over her, pinning her down, as you thrust the rest of the way into her. The neko's body forced to accept more and more of your shaft, filling her with as much of your cock as you can before pulling back for your first stroke. Stealing a kiss from her as you thrust back into her, forcing your lips against hers as she mewls underneath you and has no choice but to accept your desires.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck2" text="*keep fucking her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck2">
	<text>
	You find your rthythm, her hands weakly shoving or beating against your chest for a time but soon under your relentless thrusts she's forced to submit to your will. The cute kitty letting out mewls and whimpers underneath you as you drive yourself repeatedly deep inside of her and plunder the delights of this pirate. Your pace picking up with pleasure and vigor as you use her and prepare to pump her full of gooey cum.
	</text>
	<choice destination="fuck3" text="*fill her with your seed*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="fuck3">
	<text>
	The kitty sees the look in your eyes and yowls muffledly against your lips, clenching in anticipation as you near and then crest your peak. Your shaft erupting deep inside her, making her accept your seed as you pump spurt after spurt deep inside of her body. The neko shuddering and squirming and spasming under you as she's filled with every drop of your cream. She looks up at you sourly, face flushed, her spirit dour and humiliated as she feels your seed as a gooey warmth deep inside of her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF0" text="*own her completely, make her part of your dick">
	<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockmerging" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="fuck4" text="*pull out, you're done with her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF0">
	<text>
	You hold your shaft within her and feel her squirm underneath you as you refuse to pull out. It seems to confuse the kitty as she wonders what else you have in store for her after ravaging her. But as you groan and she feels hot tingling sensations threading out from your cock she myahs and her eyes widen, her hands snapping down to her hips to feel veiny flesh over encroaching over her "NO! no no i don't, i don't wanna be cock. stoppit" she pleads, trying to pull away from your hips but finding herself rooted to your crotch and still pinned underneath you as you change her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF1" text="$You're gonna be such a good addition to my dick, don't try and fight it"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF1">
	<text>
	"No no no!" she repeats hearing your words, but deep down she already knows she's doomed. She can feel your body claiming hers, your veins conquering her flesh as she's anchored thoroughly to your groin and finds herself being steadily re-made. Her legs writhe under you trying to scrabble for purchase, only for her feet to curl upwards towards your sack and her thighs stick to her calves. The kitty girl's body starting to diminish and regress into an addition to your shaft and sack "let me go" she begs, only to cough and then splutter up a stream of precum that drools from her lips.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF2" text="$no, a cock enhancement like you doesn't get to walk away"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF2">
	<text>
	She whimpers as you drive the point home, that all she is to you is a way to make your dick bigger. Her hands drum futilely against your body afore you pin them to her sides. Her arms sinking into her form as she diminishes under you, becoming tubular as her writhing motions are more and more diminished. Her bones, her muscles, all turning into throbbing dickmeat under your palm as you stroke over her and feel the final batch of changes beginning. 
	</text>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="penis" variable="length" modifier="6">
			<proportional ratio="0.05"/>
			</mutation>
		</special>
	<choice destination="CTF3" text="$soon, you'll be what you were always meant to be"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF3">
	<text>
	Your new member shrinks down under your stroking hand, her arms and curves subsuming into a turgid rod throbbing between your legs. Her pleas and protests silent now as she drools precum and her head turns into a sensitive glans, belling out into the tip of the shaft she will now be. The former pirate now truly a prized possession of yours as the last of her fades away, eyes, facial features, all turning into pink hot cocktip as you redouble your efforts to stroke along your now <measurement part="penis" variable="length" /> inch shaft. The kitty consummated in her new role as you spurt hot cum up through her body, having no choice but to serve you this way as your cock and indeed no choices at all now. You take a moment to wipe off the mess and admire your new size before continuing on your way, pleased to have a little extra heft between your legs now and perhaps more pleased to know her consciousness is still in there somewhere...helpless to do ought but experience her fate.
	</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="$she'll get used to it, or not, doesn't matter either way"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="fuck4">
	<text>
	You pull your cock out of the kitty and give her a swat on the thigh "I'm done with you meat" you tell her, and humiliated and violated she can muster nothing further and retreats. The kitty giving you an impotent glare afore she slips away to try and salve her wounded pride.
	</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"Nyah what that's not..." she starts to protest, silly really..were positions reversed she'd not hesitate, so you don't. Grabbing ahold of her and pulling her close before licking and slurping over her face, tasteing her and having her mewl and whine in distress at being sampled and treated as food. Still she can't muster the strength to thwart your desires as you yank her jacket off and then start eating her alive. One of your hands sliding up to grab ahold of the back of her head and then shoving her in.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="mhmm tastey kitty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	She lets out a muffled myah and half coherent pleas not to be eaten up as you slather her face with saliva and clutch her sexy squirming body against yourself. Her furred ears becoming soaked but still tickling the roof of your mouth as you savour her afore starting to gobble her up. Your throat bulging with the sweet shape of the catgirl's head as you work on turning the pirate into a tastey meal.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="pirates make good prey"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Her legs kick out and flail as her tail swishes around in agitation as her blouse soaks with your saliva and sticks to her chest. You continue undressing your meal as you gobble her up, hefty swallows rippling around her upper body as you swallow your squirmy meal a few inches at a time. Your belly starting to stretch out pleasingly with the contours of her head and hands pushing out your tummy as the catgirl mewls and protests "I dun wanna be food, you're the one who'se supposed ta get..."
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="silly kitty should of thought of what happens to unsuccessful pirates, it's an occupational hazard"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	No matter how much she protests being on the receiving end of predatory intentions she's filling you out just the same as you pack her away. Her upper body curling within you as you finish undressing her for consumption, her boots smacking to the floor discarded as your swallows work over her thighs and confine her fussy leg kicks to whiny twitches of her feet and flicks of her tail.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="swallow her completely"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	You teasingly rub your hands over her feet and then hear a suppressed giggle from your belly, teasing more with your fingers you hear her gigglefit. Ticklish kitty, ticklish, but really tastey...time to gobble her up entirely so she can be food for you. You swallow to tug her feet past your lips, licking over them one last time to hear her protest of "nyah stoppit!" and then close your eyes and swallow. A final gluck sending the entirety of her down into your belly, your gut stretched, bulgey and sagging low against your thighs with her curled up shape "nyah, stupid meanie, you were supposed to lose and get ate by me..warm belly though." she mumbles protestingly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore5" text="$heh, glad you like it. but I'm gonna digest you now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<text>
	"But I don't want to be digested I want to...nyah" she utters and shivers, pausing her squirms a moment as your gut gurgles around her and soaks her in hot enzymes. Sexy kitty girl is going to be one satisfying meal soon, your digestive processes starting to gurgle around her. The kitty squirming, mewling, but oddly seeming conflicted about her fate judging by the protests occasionally referring to 'sexy stomach' and other nonsense as you work her over in your belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore6" text="$Sexy stomach? is someone all hot and bothered about getting digested?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore6">
	<text>
	"nyah am not, i'm not enjoying it..it's mean to digest kitties like me...with your gurgling, hot juices all around me and..." she lets out a mrowl and seems to redouble her motions, but not squirming and more rthythmic inside you. Several gasping mewls and shudders emanating from within you until finally she turns still and soft within you...silly thing didn't know what she was meant for. Gradually your gut turns round and compact, shrinking down as the catgirl is utterly digested and absorbed by you.
	</text>
	<effect type="feed" value="120" />
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>	
	
</Conversation>