<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		The kitty pirate pants before you, her face flushed and her weapons scattered at her feet while her hands busily fondle herself. A murr emanating from her throat as she looks at you with a lustful desire and digs one hand under her skirt, busy with what by the occasional drip is a wet and aroused snatch "what are you going to do to me?" she asks needily.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="$I'm going to swallow you up..and digest you inside me, doesn't that sound sexy?">
		<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="facefuck0" text="$I'm gonna use your mouth, and you're gonna like it">
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/>	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="$Well, it starts with your legs spread and ends with you yowling for joy">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/>	
		</choice>
		
		<choice destination="CTF0" text="$I'm going to add your sexy body to my member, you're going to be extra inches on my dick">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockmerging" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>	
		<choice destination="end" text="darn"/>
	</page>

	<page ID="CTF0">
	<text>
	Her eyes widen, her tail twitches and a little shiver runs through her. She clearly didn't expect you to say THAT, she's simultaneously fearful...and aroused. Her gaze drifts down to your crotch almost of its own accord, and you're nice enough to show off what she's about to add to. Your hand stroking along your shaft as her eyes drink in the sight "You'd really, do that to me.." she asks, blushing hotly at the debasing thought you consider her a mere addition to your hermhood.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF1" text="$Yes, now..bend over"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF1">
	<text>
	The kitty flushes again at your command, and hesitates..part of her perhaps wanting to cling onto the silly notion she's anything but a few extra inches for you to add onto your dick. But in the end she's too horny for you to care and she presents herself, raising her skirt and her tail as she turns around and bends over to allow you to have your way with her. The kitty pirate about to be plundered and possessed and judging by the purr, she has no regrets. She lets out a mewl as you enter her, delighted at the feeling of your dick as you slide it into her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF2" text="$sluts like you are best put to good use as cockmeat"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF2">
	<text>
	She might be the sort to get off on debasing teasing like that as she lets out a mrowl as you tell her her purpose in life. But more likely it was just the feel as you thrust your shaft fully inside of her, filling out her nethers and stretching her to the core with your shaft that you'll soon make her a part of. You place your hands on her ass and dig your fingers into her petite derriere as you thrust in and out of her, teasing her with some regular fucking before you'll start to change her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF3" text="*and then, the transformation"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF3">
	<text>
	You thrust into her and let the change begin, the kitty letting out a gasping moan as she feels herself rooting to your hips. Her sex merging to your crotch, her body beginning to be overtaken and subsumed by your own "I can...feels so good, I'm gonna be your cock..." she exclaims lustily as her legs go limp and soft and her tail begins to recede. Her weight now resting on your hips as her cute ass conjoins smoothly to you and becomes a cylindrical cock base.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF4" text="$yes, and you're gonna be a good cock"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF4">
	<text>
	"Good...cooock" she manages to agree, spluttering up a glob of precum as her insides begin to simplify, organs converting into a simple tube surrounded by throbbing cockflesh. Her limbs are starting to fade away, her legs diminishing and sticking and flowing into your sack while her arms weaken. As veiny flesh overtakes her body she desperately strokes over her now more sensitive form only to have her hands and arms stick and sink into her flanks "STROKE MEEE!" she pleads as more and more of her is converted into your shaft.
	</text>
	<choice destination="CTF5" text="$you even sound like a cock"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF5">
	<text>
	"Stroke me!" is her only reply, reiterating insistently and then spluttering and gasping as her lungs devolve. But you oblige your needy dick, stroking your hands over her as she diminishes into a throbbing length between your thighs. Her head the only thing that's let of her former self now, and even that is losing definition. Her hair falling away and her ears receding as her head bulges out into a hot and pulsating glans, her lips drooling pre as they still and turn vertical..she's almost, gone...just a little more and she'll be nothing but your cock, you can feel yourself coming to the edge of orgasm at the mere thought of it.	
	</text>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="penis" variable="length" modifier="6">
			<proportional ratio="0.05"/>
			</mutation>
		</special>	
	<choice destination="CTF6" text="*cum through her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="CTF6">
	<text>
	You feel as the last parts of her change, her tongue fading away and her eyes sealing over leaving her throbbing and pulsing needily at your waist as nothing but a cock now. The kitty pirate now just extra meat on your shaft giving you a good 
	<measurement part="penis" variable="length" /> inches between your legs. The thought is enough to push you over the edge, hot cum spurting up through your newly enhanced member to splatter the floor in front of you. She was such a delightful kitty, but she makes an even better cock.
	</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on"/>	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA0">
	<!--oralvore after sex, feetfirst-->
	<text>
	She really is a delicious kitty. And she seems a bit out of it after the good hard screw you've given her. So while she purrs relaxedly in post coital relaxation you slip down to shuck off her boots, smiling as you expose her bare feet and see her toes twitch as you raise them to your lips.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA1" text="$Fucking you worked up an appetite kitty"/>
	</page>	

	<page ID="oralvoreA1">
	<text>
	"hungry what are you-" she starts to say but stops when she feels her feet engulfed by your mouth "you're eating me?" she asks, silly question with your mouth full and the answer evident to all to see. You lick over her soles a little and then she myahs flushing as she watches you take your first swallow. Your neck bulging out as her feet start to slide down your throat, your hands creeping up her legs to start undressing her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA2" text="*gobble her up"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA2">
	<text>
	"so you fucked me and now you're just gonna eat me?" asks the kitty, she seems oddly un distressed by the prospect. Maybe you're just that sexy, you nod and swallow your way up her smooth delicious calves. The kitty blushing as she realizes you're serious about this, her hand slipping between her legs to rub at her well fucked sex hornily as you steadily gobble her up. Your hands sliding up her legs until you're lifting up her ass as you continue to eat her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA3" text="*continue*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA3">
	<text>
	"just gonna...mraw" she gasps and bucks her hips as your lips encircle her ass. The kitty girl apparently climaxing as her legs slide down your throat and push into your belly, what a prey slut. You continue swallowing and working the kitty down into the hot warmth of your belly as she moans in a helpless kind of lust. Supporting her with one hand and yourself with the other you work your way up to her shoulders. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA4" text="*swallow her completely*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA4">
	<text>
	Won't be long now, "can't believe i'm just" the kitty manages to remark as her head slides steadily past your lips. Your jaws sliding shut past her cute kitty ears and you take a final gulp to swallow her down entirely. The catgirl curling up in your now rounded and bulging gut as she squirms around to get comfortable inside. She really was delicious.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA5" text="$you were delicious kitty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA5">
	<text>
	"Uh, thanks i guess." the pirate says as she gets comfortable in the snug depths of your belly as you trace over the shape of the kitty bulging your gut "Can't believe I just laid back and let you eat me." she says with a mrow as she feels you rubbing her through the walls of your belly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA6" text="$Guess you just really wanted to get digested by me"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreA6">
	<text>
	"Di-well...i suppose I'm your food now...ngh why are you so sexy.." she complains and squirms around a bit as she feels your stomach beginning to gurgle around her. The kitty dipping her fingers back between her legs to masturbate with a series of mrowls as you digest the pirate in earnest. Her form squirming, shuddering and letting out a few delighted cries before digestion begins to take its toll. And when that happens she turns instead soft, quiet, still and gradually fades away. Your belly turning round and shrinking back down as she's utterly digested and absorbed inside of you.
	</text>
	<effect type="feed" value="120" />
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore0">
	<!--cockvore after blowjob, "you emptied me out, now there's room for a catgirl to fill me back up again"-->
	<text>
	The kitty's eyes widen at your brazen declaration of your intentions and she lets out a little shocked whimper...shocked, but, turned on. You're clearly so sexy to her she'd even be willing to serve you as seed if you wished it. The thought brings a smile to your face as you stroke over your shaft and feel it grow, both larger and hungrier in preparation for the coming meal "you'd, really churn me?" she asks biting her lip as her gaze shifts to your length.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore1" text="$Absolutely, I'd churn a sexy kitty like you riight up"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore1">
	<text>
	The catgirl lets out a myah and blushes at the teasing "...o-okay.." she says and wriggles on the spot as she undoes her jacket and slips out of it, her blouse following it to the floor baring herself before you and your hungry dick. You drink in the sight, your eyes roaming possessively, she'll be a wonderful meal for your dick. She sees your gaze on her and lowers her eyes a little, shifting her attention back to your member.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore2" text="$mhmm enough stalling, time send you where you belong cockfood"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore2">
	<text>
	The kitty girl lets out a myah at that belittling moniker, but isn't able to reply as you take that moment to start your meal. Your hips thrusting forwards muffles and silences any further comment on her part as your cocktip smooshes and stretches around her face with a schlurp. Her head becoming a bulge in your cocktip as she mewls muffledly, seemingly overwhelmed with lust by the cum and musk flooding her senses as she starts to disappear into your dick.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore3" text="$feel good kitty, you'll feel better when you're all the way inside"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore3">
	<text>
	You can't tell if she heard you, but it doesn't matter as the horny kitty writhes and your member swallows more of her up. Her shoulders becoming a pleasing bulge in your member as she slips deeper inside and you thrust your tip down over her chest. Overpowering lust coursing through the kitty as she courses through your shaft inch by inch and steadily starts to slip into your sack, a muffled myah audible as her head slips into the cummy depths of your loins.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore5" text="*keep going*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore5">
	<text>
	Soon only her sexy legs and cute tail are left protruding from your member, waving and swaying around outside your hungry cocktip. The rest of her settling steadily into your sack and sliding down your length as you turn the kitty pirate into a thrilling meal for your dick. Her weight jostling around against your thighs as your sack swells and bulges and fills with her form. Her legs vanishing as you schlurp them down more and more.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore6" text="*finish her off*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore6">
	<text>
	The sensations are exquisite as you gradually polish off your cockfood, jerking the kitty down into your sack. Her feet slipping past your cocktip with a schlurp as you claim her as fodder for your loins entirely and she plunges entirely down into your sack. The kitty girl curling up and squirming as she gets comfortable with every inch of her bathed in sticky cum "soo gooey...smells good..."
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore7" text="$glad you like what you're gonna become kitty, you made great cockfood"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore7">
	<text>
	"I can't believe I'm saying this but..you're too sexy, churn me up..i wanna be cum." the kitty moans out, fully giving herself over to you and the hunger of your balls as they begin to churn around her. Her squirms are exquisite as she begins what sounds like a sensual change from sexy kitty to sloshing spunk inside there. The feeling of her movements stir you on as you stroke your shaft to how she's melting inside you. Won't be long now, won't be long until you're cumming her out...
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvore8" text="*melt her and pump her out*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvore8">
	<text>
	Her mrowls and moans last for a time emanating from your sack, but gradually they fade and the liquid churns and sloshes of your hot cum become more pronounced. The catgirl fading away akin to bliss until her form softens and spreads out into the surrounding cum. Kitty is now one with your cream and the sensation only adds to your building pleasure as you'd stroked off to her demise and sending you over the edge. Your cock erupting with your orgasm to splatter thick sticky seed across the floor in front of you, turning the kitty into naught but a gooey messy puddle in front of you. It takes you a minute or two but soon you've drained her back out of the balls she'd gone into whole so short a time ago.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex0">
	<text>
	"What do you-oooh" the kitty seemed unsure where you were going with this at first but catches on quickly as you shift your posture and her gaze drifts down to your crotch and the clear clues there-in that she's in for a ploughing. And judging by her expression and the way she starts to settle back and spread her legs she's more than okay with that.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex1" text="$Well someone's eager"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex1">
	<text>
	"You've gotten me all hot and bothered myah" the kitty replied with a blush as she settles onto her back and watches as you 
	<conditional>
	<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
			expose your length and 
	</conditional> stroke your hard <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> cock. The catgirl blushing as she admires your shaft, her hand sliding under her skirt to stroke her nethers even as you lower yourself over her. Her legs spreading and her skirt rising up and out of the way as you prepare to rut the horny catgirl. You feel her hand wrapping around your cock and guiding it to her sopping wet nethers as her other hand rests on your shoulder.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex2" text="$ready?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex2">
	<text>
	The kitty girl hears your question and responds emphatically without words. pulling you down to meet her lips in a lustful kiss, wrapping her arms around your shoulders while wrapping her legs around your hips. The catgirl spearing herself on your member with a mrowl, frenching you lustily for a few seconds before breaking from the kiss. Her nethers clenching around your thick shaft as she growls in pleasure "that answer your question?" she asks, smiling eagerly.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex3" text="*let your hips do the talking*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex3">
	<text>
	You put words past the both of you now as you begin to thrust into her. The kitty letting out mrowls and moans of pleasure as you work your <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> length in and out of her eager tight kitty sex. Your pirate fuckbuddy urging you on with tight gripping hands against your shoulders as you plough her most intimate innermost depths and steadily overwhelm her with a greatly needed screwing.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex4" text="*fuck her harder"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex4">
	<text>
	The kitty manages a breathless cry of "yes!" as you pick up the pace. Her legs urging you on in your vigorous thrusting as she scratches at your back in her fierce rutting frenzy. Your pleasures rising and intermingling as she accepts all you can give and more in the form of hard dickings.
	</text>
	<choice destination="sex5" text="*fill her up"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex5">
	<text>
	Your noisy sex with the kitty girl continued for a time, wet schlicks and delighted mrowls emanating from hips and lips of the pirate respectively. But all things must come to a blissful, delightful and sticky end. Your orgasm rocking through you, your cock erupting deep within her welcoming nethers and filling her with spurt after spurt of seed. The kitty girl letting out a yowl of pleasure and shuddering, her own climax clearly sending her to cloud nine right after your own orgasm was unleashed within her. You only pull out when the last spurt has been spent, looking down at the purring kitty with her cum leaking nethers. A well fucked mess of a catgirl looking up at you with an expression of dazed but intense satisfaction. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreA0" text="*she looks tastey that way, and you've worked up an appetite">
	<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="sex6A" text="*She's a good fuck, but you're done with her*"/>
	<choice destination="sex6B" text="*She's a good fuck, but you don't want to see her around no more*"/>
	</page>

	
	<page ID="sex6B">
	<text>
	"You're, done with me?" she blushes, but then seeing you already turning around she pouts. The dismissive attitude seems to get to her and she huffs a moment, probably taking a moment to pull a face at you behind your back afore slinking away. Well, it's not like it matters anyway.
	</text>
	<special effect="removenpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex6A">
	<text>
	"You're, done with me?" she blushes at the thought of being a quick lay, but seems forgiving of it. She leans up to give you a smooch and fondles your softening length a moment before seeing about cleaning herself off and dressing back up in her pirate outfit.
	</text>
	<special effect="nonhostile" />
	<special effect="healnpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="facefuck0">
	<text>
	She blushes and her gave lowers, a mrowl and faint shiver going through her at such a...demeaning submission you have planned for her. The kitty's gaze following your hands as you <conditional> free your shaft and <assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" /></conditional> stroke over that already hardening <macro ID="penis_size_desc" /> length of yours. But she doesn't shrink back when you step forwards and grab the back of her head firmly in hand, guiding her lips towards your tip "you-" she starts to say, but you're not interested in her talking and thrust into her mouth. The kitty girl letting out a mmph as you fill her mouth with your length and push her head down over your dick.
	</text>
	<choice destination="facefuck1" text="she's got a good mouth, use it well"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="facefuck1">
	<text>
	The kitty's tongue laps along the underside of your dick, servicing you even as you ram your cock balls deep into her lips and hold her head firmly in place. Your hips starting to rock back and force to use her mouth, the wonderful sensation as you use the submissive catgirls getting a moan out of you as you slam your cock repeatedly into her face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="facefuck2" text="keep on ploughing her mouth"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="facefuck2">
	<text>
	You thrust into her mouth forcefully and her hands rise up. The kitty making a distressed muffled sound around your dick and clutching your hips, you consider..then relent, easing up your grip on her head and your hip thrusts. The catgirl space pirate looking up at you in gratitude, but now starting to service you without additional coaxing as she bobs her head up and down over your crotch. Her eyes slipping closed as she wraps her mouth and throat around your length and slides back and forth along it wonderfully.
	</text>
	<choice destination="facefuck3" text="$good kitty, keep that up and i might..reward you"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="facefuck3">
	<text>
	You're not sure if the thought of a reward is what's motivating her or she just enjoys servicing your cock but she meets your hip thrusts with her bobbing head happily. Repeatedly she buries her nose in your crotch and engulfs your cock with her mouth as she moves to pleasure you. The hot wetness of her mouth rubbing back and forth as you feel your orgasm getting closer, closer..and finally, erupt. Your cock pulsing in her mouth as you hold her close over your dick and pump spurt after spurt of your cream down her throat. Draining your balls into the catgirl truly is satisfying and you let out a groan as your spurts begin to trail off.	
	</text>
	<choice destination="facefuck4" text="pull out"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="facefuck4">
	<text>
	You pull your shaft out of her lips and mhmm, giving her a bit of a smack on the cheek with it to raise that submissive blush on her cheeks and leave her face sticky. The kitty girl flushed and panting as she looks up at you, Then lowers her gaze, licking her lips and then wiping her cheek clean and licking the seed off the back of her hand afore her gaze drifts back up "reward?" she asks simply.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cream" text="$kitties love cream silly, you got to drink mine"/>
	<choice destination="kiss" text="*kiss her*"/>
	<choice destination="cockvore0" text="$you emptied me out, now there's room for a catgirl to fill me back up again">
	<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
	</choice>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cream">
	<text>
	The kitty blushes at that, but nyahs. she's maybe not entirely sold on this being the reward she was promised, but who cares you've had your fun. A quick nudge as you turn away from her is all she needs to know that you're pumped her belly full of jizz and you're done with her. You sense more than see her slink off after that.
	</text>
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />		
	</page>
	
	<page ID="kiss">
	<text>
	The kitty probably wasn't expecting that your reaction after that was to pull her up to her feet and into your embrace "nyah w-" she started and them mpphs as she meets your lips, she blushes..but mrowls and gropes you as you kiss her deeply. The kitty's mrowl settling into an uneven purr as you tongue wrestle for a few moments before pull back from her "mhmm oh..that sort of reward." the cute kitty manages to say as you leave her blushing in your wake with your smile and the taste of your lips lingering to keep her company.
	</text>
	<special effect="nonhostile" />
	<special effect="healnpc" />	
	<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>

	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	"That's not sexy that's..." she blushes deeply as she lets her gaze drift down, seems she might be against the idea on the surface..but deep down. She shivers and lets out a low mrowl as her gaze stays locked a short distance below your eyes.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="$It is, just think, soon you'll be inside me, masturbating as I churn you away. Comeon kitty, just give your body to me."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	The horny kitty lets out a shuddering gasp as you tease her so, her knees wavering and a small dribble of steaming hot catgirl love juice staining the floor underneath her "yes...mhmm.." she utters in semi coherent need and fumbles to undress, her outfit steadily joining her equipment in a discarded pile. The catgirl blushing as you admire her naked form, letting your gaze rove over her teasingly until seemingly she can't hold herself back from your sexyness anymore and throws herself at you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="$my you're an impatient meal aren't you?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	"yes...no...yes.." she seems to baulk at being called a meal at least initially, but then...she nuzzles at your lips submissively letting making you smile and lick over her face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore3" text="$I want you to say it"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore3">
	<text>
	"say..." she fidgets and blushes, squirming on the spot..then meets your gaze "I'm your meal" she admits in a small voice, blushing at expressing her submission so. But it's what you wanted to hear, and so you start your meal. The kitty letting out a mrah as your lips stretch around her head, her ears tucking against the top of her head as you begin to swallow her up. Your hands sliding down to grope her rear and ease her upwards and inwards. Her tail curling and swaying as she purrs and slides into the hot warmth of your throat.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore4" text="mhmm, delicious kitty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore4">
	<text>
	She's a delicious and obedient meal, your tongue roams across her bared breasts following the path your gaze had traced across her front. Her wonderful flavours soaking your tongue as her mrowls rumble from your throat. The sexy kitty slipping deeper as you continue to swallow her up, lifting up her hips and watching her legs playfully kick around as you gulp your way to her waist. Only for her legs to straighten out obligingly as she sinks into your belly and prepares for you to devour her lower half "sooo warm" she exclaims, blushing heavily as she sinks inside.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore5" text="swallow her up entirely"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore5">
	<text>
	Gradually the flavours of her thighs and calves soak your tongue afore those parts of her slide down your throat. Your hungry swallows tugging her ever deeper as she mewls and twitches her feet, her tail curling against one leg in submissive lust as she's gobbled up by a sexy and alluring predator in the form of your seductive self. Finally though at long last you snap your jaws shut past her toes and swallow her down. Your meal settling completely in your belly and purring as she's surrounded on all sides by your warm belly snugly holding her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore6" text="$you were delicious kitty, i hope you're ready to digest"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore6">
	<text>
	The catgirl lets out a myah at that reminder, squirming around a bit at how she's about to engage in the ultimate form of submission and surrendering her entire being to you. The kitty hesitating a moment then pushing out with a hand "yes..." she says with a mewl, ready to feel the pleasure of your enzymes it seems. Cute kitty, so eager to submit.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore7" text="$good kitty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore7">
	<text>
	The kitty squirms around as you get to work digesting her. Hot stomach fluids soaking her as she writhes within you. Her mewls, moans and mrowls providing a lewd counterpoint to the wet sounds of your gurgling belly glorping around her. But though the sounds and movements peak and lul a few times the end was inevitable. Her movements slow, her shape softens and her sounds fade, the kitty gurgling away inside of you and turning all sloshy under your hand as you rub your belly. Delicious kitty, your middle begins to shrink down now. The kitty finishes her transition that had started as submissive and horny, entered gurgly and soupy and now becoming one with you.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>	
	
</Conversation>