<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
		The catgirl chuckles as she looms over you, planting a booted foot on your chest triumphantly and smirking "Well now. Looks like you're ripe for plundering now aren't ya." she says with a wicked gleam in her eyes afore she moistens her lips. Seems though that as her eyes rove over you and she rubs one thigh in against the other with a mrowl she has some naughty desires in mind.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="used for sex">
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="oralsex0" text="made to service her"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="sex0">
	<text>
	
	</text>
	
	</page>

	<page ID="oralsex0">
	<text>
	The piratical kitty looms over you and sees your expression "I'm not interested in what you have to say." she says at your open mouth and then reaches one hand down to twine her fingers into your hair "I am interested in what you can do with that tongue though." she says with a mhmm, her other hand straying down to hitch her skirts up and settles astride your shoulders, guiding your head up close between her thighs. Your face coming to rest nestled between those hot thighs and up against the pungent moistness of her netherlips, a scent so tantalizing you can't help but give it a taste..and hear her mrowl in delight "that's it, to the victor go the...nyah..spoils." she says, her voice hitching as you lick again at her pleasure dew'd snatch.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralsex1" text="pleasure the kitty girl"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex1">
	<text>
	You start to lap at her sex tastey sex, lost in the moment of servicing this eager and horny feline. You hear her mrowls and purrs as she grinds against your face. Her hand clutching tight to the back of your head holding you firmly in place as she stains your lips and chin with feline sexual fluids. The kitty rocking back and forth riding your face as you lick vigorously deep into her nethers and hear her mrowling atop you with every stimulating flick of your tongue between her folds.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralsex2" text="how many more licks to make this kitty cum?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex3">
	<text>
	Not too many more it seems. The kitty's mrowls and yowls of delight hitch into an incoherent blending sound of pleasure as she closes her eyes and spasms atop you. The kitty mashing your face against her nethers as she gushes her lustful juices over your face, coating your face entirely with her lust as she shudders and purrs atop you. Her afterglow settling in as she relaxes hotly and aroused still with her legs bestride your face.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth0" text="try to nuzzle into her">		
	<preference fetish="unbirthing" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="oralvore0" text="...just...rest a minute"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
	<text>
	Your focus wavers for a few moments, when your eyes open again you feel <conditional> the kitty undressing you as she makes her way down your body. The kitty pirate settling at your feet, lifting them up before you feel
	</conditional> her tongue and warm mouth around your feet. The kitty wanting a post pleasure snack of you as she swallows and tugs your feet into her mouth. The neko's tail swaying in delight as she murrs and swallows her way up your calves, padding forwards as she gobbles you up and plunges more and more of your body down her throat. You feel your thighs start to disappear and your feet push through into her voracious belly, she can't tease you with her mouth full but to lick over your bared skin. But you can only imagine how she would as you try to squirm free but cannot stop her lips encroaching on your waistline.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore1" text="kitty food"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore1">
	<text>
	You can feel her purring around your thighs then rear end as she eats you alive. The neko pirate enjoying herself clearly as she squeezes your legs inside her stretching belly and runs her hands up along your bared flanks. Your predator sampling the softer parts afore her lips will reach them as she swallows more and more of you down. She's a sweet kitty but you can't help but attempt to spoil her enjoyment, shoving at her face with both hands to stop her lips encroaching further up over your ass. You manage to get a frustrated muffled feline sound from her as her hands go from enjoying your frame to thwarting your resistance. The kitty shoving your arms up and away from where they're halting her progress into you as she takes a mighty swallow to drag your midriff past her lips. Like it or not she's eating you, you don't have the angles to keep her from doing so now.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvore2" text="swallowed completely"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2">
	<text>
	Gradually sensations of the outside world are cut off as she swallows up past your shoulders and encompasses your head. Your arms forced over your head, you see them briefly above you as your vision is framed by her jaws and then you slide down her throat. The kitty schlurping your arms down and licking her lips with an indecent satisfying series of smacks once she's dislodged your final defiant fingers from her jaws and swallowed you down entirely "Delicious, best bit of the job is getting to swallow and digest prey things like you" she says as you're entirely packed away in her belly, her fingers drumming on her taut and distended belly. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreStruggle" text="I'm no prey thing! I'm getting out of here"/>
	<choice destination="oralvoreSubmit" text="Maybe she's right, maybe a prey thing is all I am"/>	
	</page>
	
	<check ID="oralvoreStruggle">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreEscape" />
		<outcome destination="oralvoreDigest" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreEscape">
	<text>
	You reject the labelling as prey despite your current predicament and set about attempting to get out of here. She's a catgirl you're sure you've bested stronger predators than this and start jostling and shoving around to try and force your way back up her throat. The kitty letting out a displeased mrowl as her gut starts bouncing around and delivering a thump to her belly "quiet down in there, digest like good prey thing!" she protests, though winces at having punched herself in the gut. Her wince turns into a distressed expression and a hurk as she finds your arms shoving their way back up her throat and out into the open air. All she can os flail around impotently as you force yourself back out of her, leaving her in a distressed whimpering and panting heap. You glance back at her then attempt to get your bearings, her stomach juices drying on your skin.
	</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreDigest">
	<text>
	You reject the labelling as prey despite your current predicament and set about attempting to get out of here. She's a catgirl you're sure you've bested stronger predators than this and start jostling and shoving around to try and force your way back up her throat. The kitty letting out a displeased mrowl as her gut starts bouncing around and delivering a thump to her belly "quiet down in there, digest like good prey thing!" she protests, though winces at having punched herself in the gut. The blow seems to disorientate you though as despite your efforts you can't find your way back up out of her throat. Your jostling movements availing you naught but tiring you out as the kitty giggles and snugs her stomach realizing she's bested you "Silly prey thing, you can't get out of me, all you're gonna be is digested." she says and grins, murring as her stomach gurgles around you.		
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreDigestGO" text="get digested"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvoreDigestGO">
	<text>
	You can't escape from her, maybe she was right after all. In time your struggles fade away to be replaced by fluid gurgles as you soften and digest away. The kitty's belly turning nice and soft and round as you're reduced down to a nutritious slurry within her. The kitty giving her belly a pat and straightening up as her middle compacts and shrinks slowly away. You put up a good fight but were no match for her belly and she does her jacket back up over the bulge of your remnants with a satisfied smile.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="oralvoreSubmit">
	<text>
	You feel her purring in satisfaction as her belly presses around you from all around. Her flesh squeezing against you and oozing enzymes into your body as it treats you as the food you are. And that's what you are, her food...the thought makes you shiver but not shrink back as you accept your role as nourishment for the triumphant kitty pirate. Her hands rubbing over her belly as she realizes you're being awfully calm and relaxed about this as she's starting to digest you "I guess I'm just too cute to resist huh?" she says and giggles as she gives her gut a pat and then gets back to purring. The sounds of her enjoyment becoming harder to hear over the increasingly loud gurgles of her stomach.
	</text>
	<choice destination="oralvoreSubmitGO" text="gurgle away"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="oralvoreSubmitGO">
	<text>
	The kitty girl's fingers keep on tracing around the shape of your curled up form in her belly as your digestion takes its toll. That shape turning soft, mushy and then nice and round as you gurgle away inside her. The kitty's purring never changing as you melt until you're utterly digested into sloshy fluid within her and ripe for the absorption that happens immediately afterwards. In time her belly has shrunk enough to let her do her jacket back up over the compact paunchy bulge in her middle and mhmms "I love my job nya, i get to digest so many tastey people."
	</text>
	</gameover>
		
	
	<page ID="unbirth0">
	<text>
	You nuzzle against her sex lips as they relax and find them gratifyingly accomodating to yourface as you start to slide up between them into her sweltering warmth. The kitty pirate letting out a gasp and then a mrowl "ooh, have a thing for being turned into a gush do you? well then." she says and giggles as she firms up her grasp on the back of your head and eases herself forwards. Your head disappearing entirely into her nethers as she rocks forwards and clenches to start squeezing in your shoulders with a deep and lusty mrowl.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth1" text="wrong decision? gonna be womb fodder now"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth1">
	<text>
	The kitty's skirts tickle against your flanks as she settles onto all fours and clenches again and again, rocking her hips backwards in between to work more of you into her voracious snatch. The pirate claiming ever more of your body as she does so and imprisoning more of your body in the sweltering depths of her womb, bulging out her middle with increasing gravidity as she works you in all the way down to your hips "mhmm...you're gonna be an amazing orgasm, even better than the one you gave me." she says teasingly, starting to draw your legs into her hungry sex inch by delicious inch.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirth2" text="a prisoner in a cutie kitty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirth2"> 
	<text>
	You feel your soft and snug confines shifting around you as she stands up, slurping your feet into her nethers as she does so and entirely confining your body within her womb. The kitty purring as she feels you moving around in there and runs her hand over her rounded tum where it spills out from within her jacket, bared and gravid and clearly something supremely satisfying for her "Mmhmm, gonna feel amazing to gush ya....i'm told its..pretty..mraw, good for the gushee as well." she says and giggles as you feel her till now cosy if soaking wet womb squeeze around you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthPleasure" text="try to get her off afore she can melt you"/>
	<choice destination="unbirthSubmit" text="she's right, gushing'll feel amazing, let it happen"/>
	</page>
	
	<check ID="unbirthPleasure">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="14" />
		<outcome destination="unbirthEscape" />
		<outcome destination="unbirthDigest0" />
	</check>
	
	<page ID="unbirthEscape">
	<text>
	All you got to do is get off a libidinous feline before you melt to a slush of lustjuices inside her. Couldn't be simpler, you ply your fingers along her inner flesh and rub your feet and hips against the inside of her womb. Your tongue darting out to flick over her inner flesh and seek out the most mrowlsome parts of her insides "nyah, what are you...oooh, are you try- don't care, keep on doing it...mrah..." the kitty pirate shudders in an increasingly incoherent mess, panting and mewling and weak in the knees as you stimulate her to orgasm from within...the kitty stumbling and landing on her knees and then yowling out as she crashes onto all fours and climaxes. The second climax so soon after the first seems to have left her pretty much half conscious, you take advantage to start worming your way out of her womb. Your hands pushing out of her sex and into the open air followed by the rest of you as you drag yourself free and clear...probably best to back up afore she recovers her wits though.
	</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthDigest0">
	<text>
	All you got to do is get off a libidinous feline before you melt to a slush of lustjuices inside her. Couldn't be simpler, you ply your fingers along her inner flesh and rub your feet and hips against the inside of her womb. Your tongue darting out to flick over her inner flesh and seek out the most mrowlsome parts of her insides "nyah, what are you...oooh, you think that'll get you out...nya... don't care, keep on doing it..." she utters as you caress her sweltering insides, her hot sexual juices soaking into you as you work her towards her pleasurable release. The kitty going weak kneed and mewly as you rub at her insides, her climax approaching as she drops to her knees and vigorously masturbates to the sensations coming from within her. Her pleasure finally reaching a fever pitch as she yowls, her womb clenching down and her fluids gushing out anew onto her still sticky thighs. the kitty panting in afterglow and delight you try to make your escape, only to find her channel clenching and trapping inside...	
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthDigest1" text="not good enough to escape"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="unbirthDigest1">
	<text>
	"Not going anywhere myah..you're gonna be a puddle." the kitty says, her fingers languidly stroking over her clenching nethers as you try without success to escape her womb. But she's too aware to let you out and you can't work against the muscles of her birth canal, though you do try and that seems to please her. Or maybe that's just the afterglow of her orgasm that's making her purr..either way there's naught to do but be helplessly melted down into sloppy fluids inside her...
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthDigestGO" text="sploosh"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="unbirthDigestGO">
	<text>
	The kitty masturbates, thighs splayed and resting on her own calves as she fingers herself with steadily increasing vigor. Inside her intimate depths you can do nothing to stop her as she uses your form to fuel her pleasure, her womb squeezing over your softened form until the sensations and pressure get the better of you and you're squished into juices in a last moment of exctasy followed by extinquishment. The kitty letting out a mrowl as she follows up your liquidation with her own orgasm, that final moment of bliss on your part followed by her own delight as she climaxes you messily out over the floor. Your remains forming a sticky spreading puddle beneath the purring kitty when her orgasm is spent and every ounce of you has been used up to give her pleasure.
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
	<page ID="unbirthSubmit">
	<text>
	You shiver at her words and the tantalizing sensations of her juices exquisitely marinading your body and can't help but agree..this is going to feel amazing. You make no effort to escape your most intimate prison as you hear her purring in delight and sliding one hand down between her legs to delve into her nethers repeatedly, her drooling snatch spilling fluids down her legs from hips to boots as she frig herself to the sensation of your form softening blissfully within her. The kitty's womb squeezing repeatedly around you as you get sloshier and more liquid, steadily mashing away into delightful goo.
	</text>
	<choice destination="unbirthSubmitGO" text="...sploosh"/>
	</page>
	
	<gameover ID="unbirthSubmitGO">
	<text>
	Your moans fade away yet the pirate's remain constant as she sloshes you away, your last breathless cry within her doesn't even register as you liquidate entirely within her wom and her pleasure roils ever more intensely through her. The kitty masturbating vigorously as you slop away into a mass of fluids, with all of you mooshed inside her it seems to take only a little more effort for the kitty to push herself over the edge. The catgirl letting out a yowling cry of bliss as she orgasms out your remains, creating a splattering mess underneath her 			
	<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				containing naught but your 
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				as a sticky legacy of the one who served to give her this satisfying orgasm.
	</conditional>
	<conditional>
	<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
	, a formless puddle of femmecum with not a trace of you left other than her satisfying orgasm.			
	</conditional>
	</text>
	</gameover>
	
</Conversation>