<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!--written by tirat -->
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="absorption" />
		<text>
			The batgirl grins as you flop on your butt in front of her. Seems like
			she just won the battle and got you for… fun? The girl winks and
			moves closer, wrapping her large wings around you and enveloping you
			in the feeling of private warmth and her body all around. Maybe she
			only wants to give you a big hug? And also show off her naked
			boobies.
		</text>
		<choice destination="absorb0" text="hugs arent dangerous" />
	</page>

	<page ID="absorb0">
		<text>
			You chuckle and lean closer as well, cuddling the batgirl as much as her
			wings allow you. She coos and hugs you in return, this time really
			enveloping your form. Maybe only your feet are still visible
			underneath? Her body warmth feels so good! And the batgirl even
			grinds into your front, playfully squeezing you and gently rubbing
			with her soft wings. The closeness feels good! So very private,
			thanks to the wings ‘curtain’
		</text>
		 <choice destination="sex0" text="may as well screw her"> <assertion 
			evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/> </choice>
		<choice destination="willcheck" text="maybe not so safe" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			In the cosy privacy of her wings you feel her warm body against you
			and decide that screwing her is probably the best idea you've ever
			had. You
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				pull it out and then
			</conditional>
			stroke your cock to hardness while smooching along the batgirl's jaw,
			the bat letting out a little giggle and coo as she helps you line
			yourself up with her cleft. The batgirl grinding herself against you,
			her softness only helping you get hard and coaxing you on until you
			spear her on your length. The batty letting out a gasp and smiling,
			wrapping her wings around you in approval of your idea for a lovely
			bit of foreplay.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="boning" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			You're a bit weak from being bested by the batgirl but faced with her soft
			warm nethers and her willing cooperation you find your vigor
			returning rapidly. Your hips thrusting as you fuck her in the embrace
			of her wings but no one would be fooled that you're just engaged in
			vigorous cuddling, the batty's moans, the lewd slurps and your ass
			contours pushing out the leathery wings between thrusts make it oh so
			obvious that you're fucking the batgirl with wild abandon.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="fuck and finish" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			The batgirl's pleasured sounds mingle with your gasps and pants as you
			thrust in and out of her, fucking her with all the vigor your current
			state allows you. Fortuitously your stamina proves enough, the
			batgirl letting out a squeel of delight as with your waning energy
			you buck your hips and cum up into her. Your cock spurting hot jizz
			up into the batgirl who'd defeated and seized you. She murrs as you
			finish your little romp with her, though after a few moments you
			realize that you can't actually pull out of her..and the batgirl
			gives you a smooch, snuggling you close and smiling.
		</text>
		<choice destination="absorbAlt0" text="uh oh" />
		<choice destination="cocker0" text="*smile back*">
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockmerging" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="absorbAlt0">
		<text>
			The batgirl keeps on smiling and snuggling you close as you realize your
			cock is merged into her sex, your body starting to sink into her as
			she murrs. The batgirl squeezing you against her chest with her
			wings, smooshing you against the softness of her belly and breasts
			until your skin stucks to hers and you start to sink in. Your
			exhausted form is helplessly starting to add to the soft
			curvaceousness of her own as she holds you close. the wings doing
			much to hide your disappearing act though as your legs stick to her
			own even her wings cannot hide your fate.
		</text>
		<choice destination="absorbGO" text="sink in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cocker0">
		<text>
		The batgirl snuggles close to you and looks puzzled at how you smile back at her. Your cock merging into her sex, your bodies joining together as one is destined to become part of the other. It feels wonderful, the batgirl crooning triumphantly and stroking her wing arms around you possessively. She doesn't even seem to mind as you stroke over her legs, and she doesn't notice as they start to sensitive, soft and round.
		</text>
	<choice destination="cocker1" text="turnabout"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cocker1">
	<text>
	The batgirl lets out a confused chirp as she tries to wriggle her legs, and finds she cannot. It's then she realizes that her plan to absorb you has gone wrong and her squirms to get a look back down at what has become of her legs makes you smile all the broader. Your hands continuing to massage your new sack as it gradually loses the outlines and contours of the batgirl's knees and feet, the last shapes of her lower half converting into roundness now. The batgirl gives you a look of comical betrayal as you turn the tables on her as to who is absorbing who and starts trying to push herself away and wriggle free. But to no avail, she's firmly rooted to your crotch now.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cocker2" text="pin those arms"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cocker2">
	<text>
	You distract the batgirl from her plight with a kiss, tasting pre on her lips as her insides simplify and you shove her arms down at her sides. The batgirl letting out a whine as she finds she can't move them back away, looking into your face with a look of dismay. She still doesn't seem happy that you're making her your cock and she isn't making you her curves. Her arms and wings merging into her flanks steadily.
	</text>
	<choice destination="cocker3" text="change her mind"/>
	</page>
	
	<page Id="cocker3">
	<text>
	The changes are mostly done but you still see a look of disapproval on her pre cum oozing face as she becomes increasingly veiny. Perhaps she just needs to learn to appreciate the possibilities of being your cock. With that in mind you place both hands firmly on her veiny and sensitive body and start to jerk off, letting out a groan of delight as you masturbate with your new cock. The batgirl writhing as if to protest this at first, but then uttering breathless gasps and hums of delight as her oh so sensitive body becomes awash with pleasure. Her lust visible in her eyes as you stimulate your new cock and feel her arms sinking and merging away entirely. Your last look at her face before her eyes seal over lets you see her lost in pleasure, all restraint and regret gone as her face bells out gushing precum. It's enough to push you the rest of the way over it really is.
	</text>
	<special effect="mutation">
		<mutation part="penis" variable="length" modifier="3">
		</mutation>
	</special>
	<choice destination="cocker4" text="cum through her"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cocker4">
	<text>
	Your shaft erupts, the last traces of the batgirl it once was fading away as you climax away her individuality and splatter the cavern floor with jizz. Your newly enhanced cock pumping your load and shrinking down, softening and settling nicely against your sack as you revel in afterglow. Well that was certainly a fun way of being 'defeated' by one of these bat femmes, you reach down to fondle your shaft and feel it twitch in response. Perhaps she doesn't mind your turnabout either...either way you're now packing a good <measurement part="penis" variable="length" /> inches of dick between your legs with the addition of the batgirl.
	</text>
	<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
	<special effect="removenpc" />
	<choice destination="end" text="wonderfully delicious turnabout, but i should carry on"/>
	</page>

	<check ID="willcheck">
		<test what="WILLPOWER" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="escape" />
		<outcome destination="absorb1" />
	</check>

	<page ID="escape">
		<text>
			You relax for a moment, giving the batgirl a chance to share her body
			warmth and softness with you. But as the hug becomes really intimate,
			you find enough will to squirm and pull back realizing that this will
			probably end badly for you as nice as it is. Suddenly slipping free
			from the soft wings and shoving her away easily in her surprise. And
			with the hug broken, the batgirl frowns at you and even shows her
			tongue, then going to jump and disappear in the darkness above.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="hopefully a good choice." />
	</page>

	<page ID="absorb1">
		<text>
			This hug feels so very relaxing, you can probably just stay here and
			enjoy the batgirl’s company. But strangely your body starts feeling
			even warmer and softer, fuzzier. Needs fade away slowly as the
			batgirl pets you here and there. You notice how her flesh seems to
			welcome your own, fusing like molten wax. You find it hard to be
			alarmed by the wonderful sensation of flowing into her soft warmth.
		</text>
		<choice destination="absorb2" text="sink in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="absorb2">
		<text>
			More and more as she churrs and snuggles you close with her wings you
			feel yourself diminishing. Your arms sinking into her, absorbing into
			her flanks as you seem to shrink down, head now level with that
			impressive cleavage. You find yourself letting out a moan as her
			breasts part around your face, and then you turn silent, merging into
			her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="absorbGO" text="absorbed" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="absorbGO">
		<text>
			The batgirl remains in one place for several minutes as you fade away,
			not moving much as the process continues. Your outlines slowly shrink
			and disappear beneath the curtain of her wings. Eventually leaving no
			visible bulges. Not long ago she'd drawn you behind that shroud. But
			minutes later those wings move apart and only revealing only a few
			tatters and remnants of your equipment and clothes. But what's
			perhaps a better indicator of her thorough snuggling skills are her
			nicely enlarged breasts, curvier rump and more padded middle. beyond
			these things not a trace of you remains, that was an impressive
			disappearing act.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>