<?xml version="1.0"?>
<NPC>
	<sprite value="mushroommother.png" />

	<name>mushroom mother</name>
	<description>

		Just like the smaller mushroom girls, this being is of humanoid figure,
		with a slightly darker, medium grey skin and a bright, red mushroom
		cap instead of hair.
		But that is where the similarities end.
		Where so far encountered mushroom girls were cute and pretty, slender in
		build and bashful in behaviour, this creature looks more like a full
		grown, mature relative of them.
		LBREAK
		Broad hips and a sizeable rump are stacked upon meaty thighs, and a layer
		of pudge cushions her belly.
		Much taller than the other mushroom folk, a deep shadow cast by her hood
		hides her eyes and a cloud of pheromones wafts around her like a thin,
		greyish mist.
		Her most noticeable feature though are her breasts.
		Big, full and heavy the orbs rest on her chest, tempting you with their
		obvious softness.
		Each of the thick globes is crowned by a big, broad nipple, sitting
		proudly in the middle of a dark aureola.
		LBREAK
		Heaving one of the large tits up with a hand, the creature gives it a firm
		squeeze.
		Grey fingers sink into the malleable flesh, spilling it over them, hiding
		the digits within the soft mound as a creamy liquid spills from the
		nipple, squirting onto the ground in thick stream.
		When the pressure subsides, the other hand is brought up to gather some of
		the last, milky droplets running down the full curve of the breast,
		and heave them up to her plump lips.
		LBREAK
		You cannot see her eyes below the large mushroom cap, but you can feel
		their burning desire on your skin as a dark, grey tongue sneaks out to
		flick over her lips, and a curving finger beckons you closer.
		LBREAK
		You have stumbled upon the Mushroom Mother.

	</description>


	<rpg>
		<experiencevalue value="25" />
		<ability ability="STRENGTH" value="5" />
		<ability ability="AGILITY" value="5" />
		<ability ability="DEXTERITY" value="5" />
		<ability ability="ENDURANCE" value="5" />
		<ability ability="CHARM" value="5" />
		<ability ability="INTELLIGENCE" value="5" />
		<stat stat="HEALTH" value="35" />
		<stat stat="RESOLVE" value="35" />
		<attribute attribute="DODGE" value="-2" />
		<attribute attribute="PARRY" value="-2" />
		<combatMove name="seduce" pattern="RANGED" bonusAttribute="SEDUCTION"
			timeCost="2">
			<effectDamage type="PHEREMONE" minValue="1" maxValue="6"
				modifier="NONE" />
			<missText count="1">
				<text>the mushroommother's pheremones fail to aroused TARGET</text>
			</missText>
			<hitText count="1">
				<text>the mushroommother's pheremones weakens TARGET's resolve by
					VALUE points</text>
			</hitText>
		</combatMove>
	</rpg>

	<respawn delay="2000" />

	<disposition value="25" />
	<defeated conversation="alpha_minoris_IIA/mushroommother/mushroommotherdefeat" />
	<seduced conversation="alpha_minoris_IIA/mushroommother/seduced" />
	<victory conversation="alpha_minoris_IIA/mushroommother/mushroommothervictory" />
	<seducer conversation="alpha_minoris_IIA/mushroommother/mushroommothervictory" />
	<controller AI="mushroommother" />
	<faction value="monster" />
</NPC>