<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="1" operator="equals"
			flag="first" />
		<text> "Greetings again visitor. Come to keep me company again?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="I want to be inside you" />
		<choice destination="friends" text="Can you make your sisters not attack me?">
			<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="0" operator="equals"
				flag="friends" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unlock0" text="I want to be able to do what you do">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="brightfeatherquest1" text="So I met a group of talking harpies on a world far from here, i told them about you and they want me to invite you to live with them">
					<condition evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" value="1" operator="equals"
				flag="BRIGHTFEATHER_QUEST" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="why" text="Why did the harpy carry me up here?" />
		<choice destination="different" text="you seem different from the others" />
		<choice destination="end" text="not right now" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="brightfeatherquest1">
	<text>
	Brightfeather's eyes widen "oh? OH! oh oh that's wonderful. I could talk to other harpies? have other harpies to talk to i mean.. i mean." she blinkblinks and ruffles herself a bit afore calming down "That's wonderful news." she says and then seems to consider "but...could i take my friends from here with me as well?" she asks "I know they can't talk? but I'm awful fond of them. They're like family?" she says looking awkward as she makes that suggestion.
	</text>
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="BRIGHTFEATHER_QUEST" value="2" />		
	<choice destination="brightfeatherquest1A" text="Tell you what I'll go see what they say"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="brightfeatherquest1A">
	<text>
	"Really? really you would.. ooh i hope they say yes, I'm sorry to be such a bother but. I really can't imagine leaving them behind." she says with an apologetic shrug "I hope to hear back what they said soon."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="I'll come back with news"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="AMIIA_BRIGHTFEATHER" value="1" />
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="first" value="1" />
		<text> "Hello, what have we here? you must of made someone happy to
			have ended up here" The harpy cocks her head to the side and examines
			you then smiles "I am called BrightFeather. I'm sure you will be
			enjoyable company."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="I want to be inside you" />
		<choice destination="friends" text="Can you make your sisters not attack me?">
			<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="0" operator="equals"
				flag="friends" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unlock0" text="I want to be able to do what you do">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="why" text="Why did the harpy carry me up here?" />
		<choice destination="different" text="you seem different from the others" />
		<choice destination="end" text="actually not just now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="hub">
		<text>
			"Of course, I so seldom get to enjoy conversation. Ask your
			questions."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="I want to be inside you" />
		<choice destination="friends" text="Can you make your sisters not attack me?">
			<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="0" operator="equals"
				flag="friends" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unlock0" text="I want to be able to do what you do">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="why" text="Why did the harpy carry me up here?" />
		<choice destination="different" text="you seem different from the others" />
		<choice destination="end" text="actually not just now" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			"oho, want to have the same kind of fun with me you've been having
			with my sisters? I accept of course." she smiles in delight and
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				waiting for you to undress so that she can begin.
			</conditional>
			She prepares herself by running her feathery wing against her sex,
			moistening up though harpies probably suffer for their lack of
			fingers here. Still you can certainly help out, and her delighted coo
			as you delve between her thighs with your tongue indicates she's
			certainly appreciative.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="start on in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			"my, you're eager" Brightfeather moaned out as you pressed
			facefirst into
			her sex. The harpy shivering in delight and cooing as
			she clenches
			and suckles on your face using her welcoming snatch.
			Bright doesn't
			tug you in though, even as being a harpy her nethers
			are easily
			strong enough to do so, letting you take your time and only
			gradually
			ease your shoulders and chest past her netherlips. Your
			breasts
			disappearing between her thighs, into the wonderfully snug
			warmth of
			her lustful passage.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
		<text>
			Brightfeather's moans and coos as you willingly work your way
			into her are quite
			nice to listen to. Though muffled by the hot and
			wet flesh of her
			womb around your ears and drowned out partially by
			the rthyhmic
			pulsing of her biology "I can really see why they thought
			i'd enjoy
			meeting you." Bright exclaims as your hips pass her
			netherlips, your
			form starting to curl up inside her. Your legs brush
			ineffectually
			against the ground a few moments before she takes over,
			easily
			tugging your legs in. Soon Bright feather is sealing you inside
			as
			you utterly disappear between her legs, taking your place within
			the
			gravid dome of her pregnant middle as you curl within her womb.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth3" text="get settled in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth3">
		<text>
			Her womb is delightfully comfortable, hot and moist. Her body
			snugly
			containing your naked form. The harpy runs a wing over the dome
			in
			her middle and shifts to get comfortable on the ground with you
			within her "mhmm, comfortable my friend?" she asks with a smile,
			looking at the bulge of your curled up form.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirthendo" text="yes, can i rest here a while?" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirthendo">
		<text>
			"Of course friend, enjoy your nap. I will enjoy your company
			even as you
			slumber." Brightfeather remarks and stretching before
			furling her
			wings about herself snugly and closing her eyes. Resting
			with you as
			you doze off into slumber in the warmth of her womb. The
			sounds of
			her body around you lulling you into sleep. It's many hours
			before
			you awaken anew. Ready to be let out, Brightfeather gently
			easing you
			out on the ground and giving you a few grooming licks and a
			smile
			before you bid your leave after that enjoyable experience.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="1.00" />
		<choice destination="end" text="*thank bright and leave*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="friends">
		<text>
			"Mhmm tiring of their attentions? Well I suppose they are a bit
			rough. I
			will tell them, but this will only last so long as you also
			play nice
			you understand. Should you hurt them they will assume you're
			errant
			womb fodder again."
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="friends" value="1" />
		<effect type="modFactionDisposition" value="55" />
		<choice destination="hub" text="I'd like to ask something else" />
		<choice destination="end" text="I need to go Brightfeather" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock0">
		<text>
			"You mean like how you got here?" Brightfeather giggles "I can
			change
			you, grant you the ability to feed people to your womb...melt
			them
			for your pleasure if you wish." she pauses and then adds "but to
			do
			that, you'd need to trust me, and go inside of me." she says
			gliding
			a wing down between her legs to rub at her blondefurred mound.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unlock1" text="I trust you Brightfeather" />
		<choice destination="unlockcancel" text="I'm not ready to go that far" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock1">
		<text>
			"well now. I'll do my best not to betray such trust." Brightfeather
			says and waits for you to be ready
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, watching in curiousity as you undress.
			</conditional>
			Once you are she settles herself down in a seated position, leaning
			back and spreading her thighs in invitation.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unlock2" text="crawl into her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock2">
		<text>
			"just crawl in, don't be scared." says Brightfeather, perhaps a
			little
			teasingly with her grinning and spreading her wings on the
			ground
			behind her for support as she watches your approach, first with
			nervousness and then with resolve as you remind yourself this is a
			way of gaining the means to do this to others. Brightfeather letting
			out a gasping moan as you work your hands inside her "mhmm, hope this
			feels different for you like it does for me." she says as her moist
			heated harpy nethers clench around your hands, then relax, then
			clench again as you slowly begin to ease your arms deeper inside of
			her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unlock3" text="It's different with Bright" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock3">
		<text>
			"I'm glad you agree." Bright murmurs and half lids her eyes as
			she curls
			a wing forwards to urge your head down between your arms.
			The last
			you see her smile and then darkness as you plunge into the
			welcoming
			heat of her moist tunnel. The harpy moaning and clenching
			around you,
			gently drawing in your upper body in cooperation with your
			crawling
			motions. Though once she reaches your waist you can do little
			to help
			her enwomb you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unlock4" text="let her take you inside" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock4">
		<text>
			Bright moaned, coo'd and gradually, slowly, almost
			leisurely..drew you up
			inside herself. Her middle swelling out with
			your curled up form as
			your legs disappear inside you. Bright running
			a wing over the
			pregnant dome and smiling "you might want to take a
			nap, this'll take
			some time my friend."
		</text>
		<choice destination="unlock5" text="nap time" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unlock5">
		<text>
			In the warm comforting heat it's easy to take her advice,
			falling
			asleep in the warm embrace of her womb. You don't feel her
			start to
			change you, her essence flowing in to course through you and
			leave
			you subtly changed to be more like her kind. When you eventually
			rouse and shift around you hear her giggle "ready to be let out
			then?" she asks and at hearing your assent starts to clench and push
			you out. Allowing you to stretch muscles that are starting to cramp
			as you emerge into the open air again. When fully released you delve
			fingers down, finding yourself newly more pliant you realize she's
			done what she said "mhmm, use it wisely..a womb is a powerful thing."
			she says playfully as she gets to her feet.
		</text>
		<special effect="giveperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		<choice destination="end" text="thank you bright" />
	</page>


	<page ID="unlockcancel">
		<text>
			"Quite alright, I am perfectly happy for you to keep me company
			out here.
			But I can't change you without taking you into my womb."
		</text>
		<choice destination="hub" text="I'd like to ask something else" />
		<choice destination="end" text="I need to go Brightfeather" />
	</page>

	<page ID="why">
		<text>
			"My sisters know I crave company. and not just their own, you
			must of
			convinced one of them that you'd be good company for me, and
			so they
			brought you to me."
		</text>
		<choice destination="hub" text="I'd like to ask something else" />
		<choice destination="end" text="That's interesting, I must take my leave" />
	</page>

	<page ID="different">
		<text>
			"less driven by base desires? more talkative?" she chuckles "I
			know. While
			I admit I am partial to the recreations of my simpler
			sisters. I am
			more curious about more regarding you than how you'd
			feel staining
			the inside of my thighs."
		</text>
		<choice destination="stupid" text="so you're smarter than your sisters?" />
	</page>

	<page ID="stupid">
		<text>
			"Perhaps you would see it that way. I believe it's more that
			they are,
			satisfied with a simpler life?" she says consideringly "yes,
			that's
			how I would view it. Untroubled by greater concerns they live a
			life
			of simple pleasures. While I am dissatisfied, my curiousity
			drives me
			to seek out different things."
		</text>
		<choice destination="hub" text="I'd like to ask something else" />
		<choice destination="end" text="That's interesting, I must take my leave" />
	</page>



</Conversation>