<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text> You have overcome the gold raptor, she's at your mercy. What do
			you wish to do?
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF0" text="put that cock of hers to work">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="do nothing" />
	</page>
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="100" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF0">
		<text>
			Standing over her your eyes can't help but to wander over her
			curves, after
			managing to overpower such an alluring creature you
			can't help
			yourself – adrenaline and excitement, perhaps a dash of
			fear still
			running through your system, but you want more, and its
			clear how she
			can give it to you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF1" text="leap atop her!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF1">
		<text>
			With a shrill cry the raptor-girl shifts, trying to dislodge
			you, yet
			already your chest is smushing down against her own,
			shamelessly
			rubbing your crotch against the hardening shaft. The
			golden raptor
			can't help but note the lust in your eyes, unable to
			resist as it was
			cowed by your stubborn insistance – it lets out a
			guttural whine,
			pushing you down onto its thick shaft with a lustful
			moan. With
			wicked glee you so eager pin down the golden raptors limbs,
			bucking
			against your hips needily and greedily as you take inch after
			inch of
			the member, your muscles already clenching down upon the
			steadily
			hardening shaft.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF2" text="enjoy yourself" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF2">
		<text>
			After a few moments she surrenders to your growing lusts,
			thrusting
			herself into you deeply, the hard shaft properly lubricated
			by your
			growing desire. Lust overrides reason as your lips latch onto
			its
			neck, suckling and kissing against the cool scales, bucking and
			thrusting, it takes no time at all for you both to get so excited,
			the sounds of your moans and its guttural squeals echoing into the
			air. Unable to help yourself you let out a desperate cry as you are
			pushed to your peak – the golden raptor shifts, grasping at your arms
			with clawed hands digging into the tender skin – she thrusts firmly
			again and again, such noises escaping from its jaws until a flood of
			its seed spills out inside of you, leaving you a panting, twitching
			mess.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sexF3" text="turnabout!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sexF3">
		<text>
			As you try to dismount yourself the raptor-girl seems to smirk
			up as
			you, even from your dominant position she is already bucking her
			hips
			back into you, elicting another whine from your lips – still warm
			from your first peak the raptor-girl doesn't seem like she is done
			with you yet, despite how the tables were in your favour. With each
			buck and thrust she groans, and you feel compelled to ride them,
			shivering as that hard shaft buries itself deeper and deeper inside
			of you, crying out with such wanton lust! Without waiting, the
			raptor-girl is on top of you, working its shaft fully inside of you,
			losing itself to its own carnal needs, again and again pounding your
			needy folds until another screech, and a spray of raptor nectar fills
			your fuckhole. Satified, the golden raptor takes barely a moment to
			steady herself, already its quick reflexes allowed it to regain its
			footing – not hesitating to slink away into the darkness, feeling
			very satisfied with itself despite losing the fight for dominance.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

</Conversation>