<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			Filled with lust you find yourself approaching the naughty raptor as
			she strokes her cock to hardness. Moistening her lips and grinning at
			the sight of you, those lips and that dick both drawing your eyes as
			you gaze upon her.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Your
				<readequipment slot="2" />
				seems too constraining for the needs burning within you and even as
				you approach you undress, leaving your garments scattered by the
				time you're standing in front of the raptor.
			</conditional>
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvorestart" text="kiss her">
			<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="kneel before her">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvorestart">
		<text>
			The raptor chirrs as you kiss and slip into her embrace. Her
			arms
			slipping around you, her erect cock pressing up against your
			thigh.
			The lusty lizard returning your kiss, that long forked tongue
			invading your mouth and her amber eyes half lidding. She pulls back
			from the kiss to lavish your face with a few licks, tasteing, leaving
			your face covered in saliva, her belly letting out a hungry growl
			before she goes back to kissing you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoresplit" text="mhmmm" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoresplit">
		<preference fetish="sex" />
		<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		<assertnot evaluate="haspart" part="cock" />
		<text>
			Her licks indicates she has a need you'll sate for her. But as
			she
			grinds her erection against you and feels it brush up between your
			legs against your snatch her grin widens and she slides a hand down
			to make it clear she has another need that she wants to sate. Those
			fingers first plying over your sex and then sliding to cup your thigh
			and hitch your leg up as she leans back, lining her cock up with your
			netherlips.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="hardly an unwelcome proposition" />

	</page>


	<page ID="oralvoresplit">
		<text>
			Make outs with a lusty lizard are quite pleasing, though as she
			keeps on
			kissing her belly growls again more insistently. The raptor
			chirring
			as she pulls back, running her over long forked tongue over
			her lips
			afore stretching them wide to engulf your face. Her desire
			for you as
			a meal taking precedence over other needs as she sets about
			swallowing you down, cramming your head into her throat. Her neck
			bulging as she claimed your shoulders and a hearty GLUCKing sound
			drowns out her pleased chirs as you slip deeper inside her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvorealt0" text="raptor food" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvorealt0">
		<text>
			You can feel her member brushing against you as she eats you
			alive. But
			beyond prodding warmly at your thighs as she lifts you up
			she does
			nothing more with her erection while using both hands to cram
			you
			inside. Your feet lifted up off the floor as she lifts and feeds
			you
			past her lips, chirring loudly as you slide into her belly
			headfirst
			and she engulfs your waist swiftly enough. Only your legs
			outside as
			your body fills out her belly pressing it down atop her
			erection.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvorealt1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvorealt1">
		<text>
			The raptor's dusky yellow belly stretches steadily around you as
			you
			pile in. One of her hands slipping down to her erection down
			beneath
			you to stroke off and grind her cock against her swollen belly
			as she
			devours your legs. It doesn't take her much longer to polish
			you off
			entirely and pack you away, sealed in that now massively
			distended
			gut as she masturbates and bucks her hips to grind her cock
			against
			your shifting form within her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="altoralstrugglecheck" text="try to force your way out" />
	</page>

	<check ID="altoralstrugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="altoralstruggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="altoralstruggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="altoralstrugglescape">
		<text>
			You're not about to simply rest here contently. You might have
			been
			beguiled into this belly but you're not going to stay beguiled
			into
			padding her thighs and so you start jostling and pushing around
			at
			her insides. The crafty raptor issuing a distressed series of
			noises
			as she finds herself subject to an unruly meal disturbing her
			post
			devourment masturbation session. Soon enough it turns out to be
			too
			much for her, and with a suddenly strangled cry she rolls over
			onto
			her front to messily hork you up, the poor lizard looking most
			put
			upon as the last of you trails free of her. Her erection still
			untended to and her belly undistended, you should probably back up a
			tad afore she tries to lure you in again.

		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="5" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="altoralstruggledigest">
		<text>
			You're not about to simply rest here contently. You might have
			been
			beguiled into this belly but you're not going to stay beguiled
			into
			padding her thighs and so you start jostling and pushing around
			at
			her insides. The crafty raptor issuing a distressed series of
			noises
			as she finds herself subject to an unruly meal disturbing her
			post
			devourment masturbation session. But as you shove at her insides
			she
			rolls over onto her front, pinning you between her body and the
			dirt
			so that your struggles only succeed in rubbing against her
			erection
			where it butts up against the bottom of her belly. Judging by
			the
			moans she 's uttering now you're doing less well, her gurgling gut
			working you over as you expend your strength against her insides.
		</text>
		<choice destination="altoraldigest" text="digest" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="altoraldigest">
		<text>
			It's no use, you hear her gasping as you diminish inside her.
			Your
			struggles weakening forcing her to reach down past her softening
			belly and take over stimulating herself. In not too much longer you
			fade away, her chirrs and gasps the last you hear before she
			liquidates you entirely. Her gut rounding out as she cries out and
			climaxes, tailwhipping as she stains the ground beneath her with her
			seed and feels your remains compact with a glorp. All that's left as
			she rolls over onto her front is for her greedy guts to absorb your
			gloopy remains, that belly shrinking and flattening out as she chirs
			contently. Soon enough there is not a trace of you that remains.
		</text>

	</gameover>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			Seeing your expression she wastes no more time, one hand sliding
			down to
			clutch your derriere as she lowers you down onto her cock. The
			raptor
			letting out a delighted chirr as her thickness slides up inside
			of
			you. Her lips pressed back against your own in a kiss as your hips
			come down against her crotch, hilting and spearing you through with
			lust impeccably. Her thrusting hips starting their work as she
			adjusts her supportive grasp on your leg and ass, easily able it
			seems to fuck you standing up like this.

		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="a capable lover" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			You feel her hips rocking up and down beneath you as you hold
			onto her
			shoulders. The raptor vigorously fucking you, perhaps using
			her tail
			for balance as she remains leaned back and bouncing you upon
			her
			cock. Through it all her lips remain locked to yours, the kiss
			passionate, that long forked tongue invasive and lewd as it probes
			your mouth, truly none french like a reptile.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="nearly there" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			You feel your own pleasure building and you can tell from the
			rumbling
			chirring delight of your lover that her own is equally is
			equally
			close to boiling over. Her hip thrusts becoming faster,
			pistoning up
			with hip slapping lust as she breaks her kiss with you.
			Looking into
			your eyes, chirring, and then licking her lips. When the
			dam breaks
			its with a cry from the both of you as she orgasms and
			sends spurts
			of her seed up inside you. Cries that are swiftly
			muffled, with you
			by the mouth encompassing your face and with her by
			the faceful of
			lover now in her mouth as she sets about eating you
			alive.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="from lover to food" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			You feel her cock still spurting within you even as she sets
			about
			eating you alive. Her body starting to curl forwards as she
			swallows
			your head down her throat, licking over your chest as it and
			your
			shoulders are encompassed by her mouth. The predatory raptor only
			pulling her shaft free as she reaches the bottom of your ribs. Cum
			dribbling out between your legs as her cock slips free slickly and
			she straightens up, hands still supporting your rear and feeding you
			down her throat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="continue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Your middle slowly disappears as the raptor girl swallows you
			up,
			cramming you inside of herself. The lizard's middle stretching
			out,
			yellow skin bulging as your head, then shoulders and chest pile
			into
			her belly. Your hips and cum leaking snatch slipping past her
			lips
			next. Her hands slipping from your ass to rest one on her gut and
			cock to rub them both as she works to make your legs disappear the
			same way the rest of you has. Your body curling up as she runs her
			tongue and lips along your thighs, then calves, then feet.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="eaten completely" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			With a final chugging swallow you disappear entirely within her.
			A most
			filling post sex meal as the bulges you make settle into her
			belly,
			your form curling up as she shifts to get comfortable seated on
			the
			ground. One hand still busily jerking off to the sensation of you
			moving about in that distended dome of a gut the raptor is sporting
			now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralstrugglecheck" text="sex isn't worth this (Struggle)" />
		<choice destination="oralsubmit" text="let her digest you" />
	</page>

	<check ID="oralstrugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="oralstruggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="oralstruggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="oralstruggleescape">
		<text>
			With your lust starting to fade you come to your senses. Even a
			good
			screw isn't worth getting digested for. The raptor's chirring
			skips a
			beat as your squirms taken on a distinctly more vigorous
			aspect.
			Vigorously pushing at the now gurgling innards of the raptor
			you feel
			her shift and glurk as you make your attempt. the lizard
			rolling onto
			all fours with a hiss of dismay she tries to settle atop
			her belly
			and squeeze you into submission with her own weight. But to
			no avail,
			with a final hurgh she loses her lunch, body convulsing as
			she
			disgorges the meal that had disagreed with her. She looks dazed
			and
			slumps into a heap gasping as the last of you exits her lips. You
			get
			a little time to salvage your clothes and put them back on but
			soon
			after that the raptor will be back to trying to beguile you.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="5" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralstruggledigest">
		<text>
			With your lust starting to fade you come to your senses. Even a
			good
			screw isn't worth getting digested for. The raptor's chirring
			skips a
			beat as your squirms taken on a distinctly more vigorous
			aspect. You
			vigorously shove at her insides, and you feel her place a
			hand
			against the bulge you make in her as her gut gurgles and churns
			around you. But for all your efforts her stomach seems more resilient
			than you are, her other hand working her slick cock as she feels her
			gut squeezing and pressing over you. The grinding process steadily
			overcoming your resistance, making your struggles more squirms and
			only pleasant for her. You hear her gasp, unable to see her cock
			spasm and stain her belly with cum as she sprawls backwards in
			delight..and settles in to absorb your body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralstruggleGO" text="digest" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralstruggleGO">
		<text>
			Your body succumbs steadily to the digestive process. The lewd
			raptor's
			belly turning round and softening, shrinking. Your form
			reduced to a
			mushy soup of nourishment, in very little time her belly
			is as flat
			as before though maybe a little softer. All that you were
			now reduced
			to a pleasing fuck and satisfying meal.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="oralsubmit">
		<text>
			Well it was a good fuck. The tingles of pleasure and
			satisfaction from
			your nethers testify to her lustful talents. Maybe
			she deserves her
			meal, as you hear her chirring and jerking off you
			get comfortable.
			Letting her stomach take you as it gurgles and
			churns, pressing in
			from all sides and working you over. Your only
			movements to grind
			down playfully, hearing a gratified chirp of
			delight from the raptor
			as you press the bulge of her belly down on
			her cock. Soon after you
			hear her gasp, climaxing and staining her
			belly with cum, it's good
			she's enjoying digesting you as much as
			earlier. But you're not in
			much of a state to do more now, not much
			more than be food for her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralsubmitGO" text="digest" />

	</page>

	<gameover ID="oralsubmitGO">
		<text>
			The digestive process is easy and satisfying for all involved.
			The
			raptor chirring and licking your flavour off her lips as her belly
			works you over and then works you down. The bulges you make rounding
			out and softening until she's left with a fluid dome of a belly. A
			belly that shrinks down as she sprawls there, utterly absorbing your
			form into her own and giving her a slightly more alluring ensemble of
			T and A.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You kneel and she chuckles, rubbing her cocktip against your
			face..smearing you with pre as you reach up to stroke and caress that
			long, thick...hungry, cock of hers. She reaches a hand down and uses
			two clawtips to part her cumslit in front of you, letting you know
			her desire before she sets about satisfying it. The raptor wants you
			in her balls, as her cum. She wastes no more time. The raptor
			shifting her posture and fondling herself to place her cocktip
			against your forehead, then thrusting forwards with a moan of
			pleasure. Her cock engulfing the crown of your head before stretching
			down over your face. That voracious cumslit soon resting against your
			shoulders.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="raptor cockfood" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			you feel her thrusting her hips leisurely, slowly driving her
			cock down
			inch by inch over your shoulders and chest. Possibly putting
			on a
			show with how drawn out she's making your consumption. Or maybe
			it's
			for your benefit, letting you feel the slick cummy insides of her
			cock sliding against your naked body as she pulls more and more of
			you in. Working towards your hips, the pull of her rippling cock now
			more working to draw you in rather than her earlier hip movements.
			Her bulging cock lewdly slurping as she passes your waist and starts
			on your legs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="into her balls" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			Only now do you feel her tracing the bulges in her cock that you
			make.
			The raptor leaning back as you begin to slide into her balls,
			piling
			into their cummy confines and stretching them, bulging and
			swelling
			them out with the meal that will sate them if the raptor has
			her way.
			Your own legs easily schlurped in now, that powerful cock
			rippling
			and pulling your legs up and in. Soon enough your feet
			disappear into
			her tip and course down her length, making you slow
			motion tumble and
			curl up as the last of you piles into her sack, the
			hot cummy walls
			stretchy yet snug around you. The raptor fondling her
			cock and no
			doubt having some fun plans for you, at least once you're
			her seed.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockpleasurecheck" text="try to change her mind" />
		<choice destination="cocksubmit" text="let her spunk you" />
	</page>

	<check ID="cockpleasurecheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="cockescape" />
		<outcome destination="cockdigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="cockescape">
		<text>
			As much as the trip down was fun, you're not onboard with the
			next part
			of her plan. and the only way out is to coerce her into
			cumming you
			out unmelted. Your hands dexterously rub at the insides of
			the sack,
			the slick cumsoaked fleshy embrace yielding to your digits
			as you
			hear her gasp. The Raptor now stroking herself and chirring in
			delight as you caress her from within her sensitive loins. Her plans
			derailed as she cannot help but give in to lust, jerking off as you
			writhe within her. Your efforts continuing until with a cry and gooey
			eruption you emerge victorious. Victorious and very sticky, landing
			in a splatter of cum in front of her after sliding up her cock, her
			shaft spurting other blasts of seed to land atop you. Probably best
			grab your clothes and do your best to get clear of the thwarted but
			perhaps satisfied lizard.
		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="get clear" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockdigest">
		<text>
			As much as you enjoyed slipping inside that cock you're not on
			board
			with being melted down into seed. Only way out is to pleasure
			her
			into spurting you out, as you stroke and caress the inside of her
			sack you hear her chirr and moan in delight at the sensations. The
			churning sack around you getting stimulated by your dexterous
			fingers, you hear her giggle and then feel a shifting around. Wait,
			was that even her voice giggling? As you feel a pressure from above
			and hear stereo gasps you realize what's happening, your devourer has
			found a playmate. A playmate who currently has the cock that ate you
			balls deep in her nethers, you can feel the pressure of her butt
			against the top of the sack containing you lift up, then lower down
			again.
		</text>
		<choice destination="raptorsexstruggle" text="be the fuel of lust" />
	</page>

	<page ID="raptorsexstruggle">
		<text>
			Thwarted. Escape now would only lead you up into the womb of the
			raptor who is
			riding that cock above you. You continue pushing around
			for a time,
			blushing at the sound of the two going at it. the raptor
			bouncing up
			and down above you, helped by the hands of her playmate on
			her ass.
			The two making an uninhibited racket with their moans, chirs,
			chirps
			and gasps as they fuck with abandon. And as they do you can
			feel
			yourself getting softer, the sack around you stirred by their
			lust to
			melt you down faster.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoreGO" text="orgasmic ending" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoreGO">
		<text>
			You hear them going at it, but gradually that sound fades,
			drowned out
			by the goopy churn of oozing cum around you. And steadily
			you become
			one with it, the two raptors getting closer and closer as
			steadily
			you melt down into the orgasm that's about to happen. The
			last of you
			desolidifying in a burbling clench as the sack squeezes
			around you
			and the raptor orgasms, sending gallons and gallons of hot
			seed up
			into her playmate. The brown femme moaning as she's distended
			and
			bulged out with all the cum, inevitably leaking a hefty amount as
			the
			golden raptor licks her face affectionately before easing her up
			and
			off. A sploosh of your remains splattering out as that cock pops
			free, all that you were now amounting into giving these two a really
			good time..and maybe some baby raptors somewhere along the line.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="cocksubmit">
		<text>
			You shudder in delight, blushing as you settle in her balls. She
			must
			have plans, plans that require you to churn into a load of cum
			for
			her to use...plans you're either too perverse or too lusty to
			object
			to. You feel her fondling herself, murring and rubbing her sack
			with
			a free hand and chuckling at hearing you moan. And then as you
			resolve to be good cockfood in her burbling balls she gets to her
			feet, you can feel her walking, your form swaying against her thighs
			and knees with every step.
		</text>
		<choice destination="raptorsexsubmit" text="wonder where she's taking me" />
	</page>

	<page ID="raptorsexsubmit">
		<text>
			You feel her balls sway to a stop as she comes to a halt, feel
			another
			pair of thighs against the sagging bulge you make in her
			balls. Hear
			sloppy kisses, chirrs, another giggle..then a long gasping
			moan. The
			raptor who cockvored you has found a playmate, the other
			looking back
			past her raised tail at the gold as she sticks it in
			eliciting that
			pleasured moan. The gold raptor groping that rear a
			moment before
			falling into motion, thrusting into the femme raptor's
			nethers and
			making the sack you're inside sway back and forth with
			each thrust,
			rocking against one set of thighs then the other as that
			dick is
			pumped in and out above you. And through it all you feel
			yourself
			diminishing with a smile on your face, a part of their
			lovemaking as
			you steady churn down. That sack growing rounder and
			sloshier as you
			relax into your role in their play.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoresubmitGO" text="orgasmic ending" />
	</page>


	<gameover ID="cockvoresubmitGO">
		<text>
			The last thing you hear is their lustful fun as you're boiled
			down into
			cum. Your form sloshing apart entirely in the swaying balls
			of the
			raptor as she fucks her playmate, pressing in close to bite her
			chin
			and gasp out a moaning orgasm as she reaches climax soon after
			the
			last bits of you slosh away. The two moaning and writhing as blast
			after blast of hot cum are sent rocketing into the femme raptor's
			nethers, filling her womb, distending her middle and towards the end
			resulting in splatters of cum leaking out around that thick dick to
			stain the ground beneath them. The two slumping into a cuddling heap
			as they finish, and by and large that's where your story ended.
			Though the three raptor children the femmy raptor had a few months
			later might count as a continuation of a sorts, maybe one or two had
			your eyes?
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>