<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance"
			value="1" />
		<text>
			Laurisse watches you approach with a friendly smile "You don't need to kneel
			my knight. Though you can if you want to." she remarks as you cross
			the point where customarily you'd pay your respects.
		</text>
		<choice destination="talk" text="don't kneel" />
		<choice destination="respect0" text="kneel anyway" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			Laurisse watches you approach with a small self confident smile. Once you
			stand before her regal presence she glances down meaningfully at the
			stone floor in front of her throne of pillows as if expecting
			something of you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="respect0" text="kneel" />
		<choice destination="disrespect0" text="don't kneel" />
	</page>

	<page ID="talk">
		<text>
			Her majesty smiles "Now, tell me, why do you seek an audience with me?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="valley0" text="$I would like to talk to you about something I found in a valley far to the north">
						<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley" value="1" />	
		</choice>
				<choice destination="crashRecovery0" text="$I would like to talk to you about digging up the ship">
						<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="valley"
				value="1" />	
						<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley"
				value="5" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="crashRecovery1" text="$I would like to talk about how the excavation is going">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="valley"
				value="1" />	
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley" value="6" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="history0" text="Can you tell me your people's history" />
		<choice destination="knights" text="If you are a queen do you have knights?">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="knights"
				value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="friendship" text="can i become a knight your majesty?">
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="LOCALFLAG" flag="knights"
				value="1" />
			<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="allegiance"
				value="0" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="I actually don't know" />
	</page>

	<page ID="valley0">
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="valley" value="1"/>
	<text>
	"Oh and it is so significant you bring it to my attention? we know only a little of those lands and that only from long ago when they belonged to our people." the saurian queen leans forwards "So tell me please, what is it you found far to the north?"
	</text>
	<choice destination="valley1" text="I found a spaceship, it's crashed and partially buried but looks like it could be recovered."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="valley1">
	<text>
	"Recovered you say? now i am intrigued. Sadly my people have lost knowledge of how to operate space vessels, it's of no use to use. But I am great appreciative of this news. Though if the vessel is buried then surely it cannot fly." she observes.	
	</text>
	<choice destination="valley2" text="I was hoping that I could have the help of the noble people of dammath to dig it out as it happens"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="valley2">
	<text>
	"And we could certainly do so, though my people. It would be wrong to ask them to work for free. Lets see it should take.." Laurisse looks thoughtful and glances off to mentally check into her calculation space "1000 gold to pay for sufficient laborers to excavate the ship." she says coming back with what she obviously feels is a fair price for her people's efforts.
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I will come back when I have the gold to pay for your laborers your majesty"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="crashRecovery0">
	<text>
	"Do you have the gold required now traveller? my terms remain fair and unmoving. My people will not labour for free, but if you have the gold, well, we can begin."
	</text>
	<choice destination="crashRecoveryStarted" text="$I have the gold to pay the diggers">
	<condition evaluate="GOLD" operator="greaterthan" value="1000" />
	<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley" value="4" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I can't afford that much gold">
	<condition evaluate="GOLD" operator="lessthan" value="1000" />
			<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley" value="4" />	
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$It's actually not safe for you to start digging while there's still robots there">
				<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="hauntedValley" value="4" />
	</choice>
	<choice destination="end" text="$actually nevermind"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="crashRecoveryStarted">
	<effect type="givegold" value="-1000" />
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="hauntedValley" value="5"/>
	<special effect="marktime" />
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="hauntedValley" value="6"/>
	<text>
	"Excellent, our people will begin digging shortly. It has been a pleasure to come to a satisfying agreement on this matter." she says and has a guard receive the gold from you on her behalf.
	</text>	
	<choice destination="end" text=" "/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="crashRecovery1">
	<condition evaluate="TIMEPASSED" operator="lessthan" value="10" />
	<text>
	"My representative at the digging site last reported that while they are making good progress the work is not yet complete. We'll need more time."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="$I see, I will check back later then."/>
	</page>

	<page ID="crashRecovery1">
	<condition evaluate="TIMEPASSED" operator="greaterthan" value="10" />
	<text>
	Laurisse smiles "I have received reports that the digging has completed, your ship has been unearthed."
	</text>
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="hauntedValley" value="7"/>	
	<special effect="worldScript" script="restoreShip"/>
	<choice destination="end" text="Thankyou your majesty, I think I'll go admire their work now."/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="friendship">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG"
			flag="friendship" value="1" />
		<text>
			"Your deeds are known to me. Surely you are worthy now of this honour I
			bestow. Are you sure this is your wish? that I proclaim you a knight
			of Dammath?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="allegiance" text="yes, i swear myself to you your majesty" />
		<choice destination="end" text="I need to think about this" />
	</page>

	<page ID="friendship">
		<condition operator="equals" evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" flag="friendship"
			value="0" />
		<text>
			"I don't think I should hand out a knight hood to just anyone do you?"
			asks the queen rhetorically and gestures dismissively "Go show me
			you're worthy then come back."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="farewell then your majesty" />
	</page>

	<page ID="allegiance">
		<text>
			Her majesty queen laurisse calls for a sword and her chronicler, rising
			from her cushions at last to stand before you "kneel" she commands,
			and as you do so she unsheathes the blade "Let it be witnessed and
			proclaimed that the stranger who has come before me is stranger to
			our people no longer." she says and places the blade on your shoulder
			"I dub you a knight of Dammath, loyal to the crown, defender of my
			people, may your actions bring you honour for all of your days." she
			says and then removes the sword "rise ser, and know you will be
			forever welcome in dammath."
		</text>
		<effect type="setfactionflag" flag="allegiance" value="1" />
		<effect type="manipulatefactionflag" faction="minyos" flag="allegiance"
			value="-1" />
		<effect type="manipulateDisposition" faction="minyos" value="-25" />
		<effect type="modfactiondisposition" value="25" />
		<choice destination="end" text="i am yours your majesty" />
	</page>


	<page ID="knights">
		<text>
			"Knights. hmm. and these are my favoured warriors you say? loyal and dutiful
			and capable?" the queen seems to find this idea very appealing "I
			will have to see if our lore contains any mention of such things. But
			regardless whether they will or wont, I think I will have
			knights..but I must think some more on this subject, go, I need some
			time."
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="knights" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="very well, farewell" />
	</page>

	<page ID="history0">
		<text>
			"The tale of our people is a tale of determination and resolve in the
			face of malice, deceit and coveteousness. For many generations we
			called this world our home. Here we tilled the fertile field and
			raised the fatted beast, but we were not a simple people. We traded
			with the people of other worlds, and we had the secrets of Technology
			and Industry. And then the green ones came, with ears as pointy as
			knives and hearts as black as sin. We trusted them at first, fools
			that we had become in our complacency from peace and plenty. It was
			world enough for both our peoples we thought, and while I confess
			being first to make it our home the choicest parts were ours we did
			not see the greed that festered in their hearts. They lured our
			greatest to a feast celebrating their arrival, and there began with
			treachery and daggers the war that would see us driven to this harsh
			and unforgiving corner of our world. We have lost so much of what we
			once had, our Industry and Technology were lost, left behind when we
			were forced to flee. And no doubt you have seen how little our
			enemies have made of them. They are not a people who can build, only
			take and destroy."
		</text>
		<choice destination="history1" text="what will you do now?" />
		<choice destination="end" text="that was all i wanted to know" />
	</page>

	<page ID="history1">
		<text>
			"We will take what is ours. Our enemies will bend or they will break but
			we will make them yield and take our place that we had so long ago. I
			confess I did not believe this war would come upon us so soon, so
			much of our former Technology and Industry are still beyond our
			reckoning. When we were ready and able we would of blasted asunder
			the stone barrier and swept upon the greenskins like an inexorable
			tide."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="thankyou for sharing this with me" />
	</page>

	<page ID="respect0">
		<text>
			You kneel before her. And hear her shift softly on the pillows, a glance
			up sees her smiling in soft approval. It's clear she gets off on
			submission like this, perhaps now she'll be willing to talk. Or maybe
			kneeling before her majesty has further potential.
		</text>
		<choice destination="talk" text="*stand*" />
		<choice destination="respect1" text="*eye her bulge*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="respect1">
		<text>
			Laurisse off on a pretty girl kneeling submissively to her turns out to be
			not that much of a metaphor but rather more literal. That robe of
			hers is bulging down between her legs, where her hermaphrodite
			arousal is stirring slightly. It must be a hefty tool to be visible
			in her loose robes while only slightly hard. But is it any wonder
			that her majesty would have a rod that befits the prominence of her
			office?
		</text>
		<choice destination="respect2" text="*get closer*" />
		<choice destination="talk" text="*a look is enough, stand*" />
	</page>

	<page ID="respect2">
		<text>
			Laurisse smirks at where your gaze is resting, and as you approach she slides
			a hand down to undo the front of her robe "well now, if you wish to
			show me further honour, who am I to deny your excess of virtue." she
			says. That one free hand now taking the hem of her robe and parting
			it, revealing the smooth majesty of her belly and the inner curves of
			her breasts but also and perhaps more importantly the mostly flaccid
			girth of her royal cock. On your knees before her you reach out and,
			as she sips from her winebowl and mhmms to encourage you, take her
			cock in your hands. Stroking her to hardness as she drinks, only a
			soft throaty mhmm from her lips and the engorging of her cock work to
			show that your efforts are pleasing her majesty. Soon enough though
			you have her at full erection, and that queenly rod is truly
			magnificent to behold. you find yourself drinking in the sight of it
			for a moment, from broad glans to weighty balls. But it seems to be
			up to you what you should do now faced with such a magnificent organ.
		</text>
		<choice destination="blowjob0" text="worship it" />
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="feed it">
			<preference fetish="cockvore" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			Her cock is so magnificent, you find yourself wanting to give
			yourself to her royal cock.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Laurisse quirks an eyebrow but doesn't do more than glance your way
				as she sips her wine and you undress, not wanting to trouble her
				cock with your clothes.
			</conditional>
			You stroke her cock with one hand while raising the up the other, a
			bit of a smile quirking her her majesty's lips as your fingers ply at
			her cocktip. You press on, wondering if her cock with accept you, if
			she will accept the offering of her body. With a chir from her lips
			and schlurp from her tip you find the answer is an emphatic yes, her
			cock stretching and schlurping around your hand. Her shaft sucking
			you in up to your wrist "oh, now this is. Few people are willing to
			go THIS far." remarks Laurisse with a mhmm, then glances your way and
			smiles "but by all means, do continue." she says at your expression,
			and with that you insert your other hand. The queen is willing for
			you to be a sacrifice to her cock, and such a thought fills you with
			warm and pleasant tingles as you start to slide your arms into her
			shaft.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1" text="feed yourself to her cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			As you plunge your arms inside Laurisse's welcoming cock you hear a
			gasp from her majesty, one of the guards having to take the bowl of
			wine from her lest it spill during her loss of composure. Your last
			sight of the outside world her pleasantly shocked expression afore
			you plunge your head down between your arms and into that stretched
			out cocktip. The queen's member rippling around you, starting to take
			charge of your body and pull you deeper inside. That dominant organ
			tugging on your shoulders, claiming your chest even as it snugly and
			muskily presses around every inch of you that has so far been
			offered. Her gasping moans of pleasure music to your ears, muffled as
			they are by pre and cockflesh, driving home her enjoyment of the
			sheer depraved depths of your deference to her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2" text="give yourself entirely" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			Deeper and deeper you slide into her cock. You're no longer really able to
			push yourself in as the power of her royal member lifts your feet up
			off the floor. Laurisse's hungry cock angling up a few degrees with
			each lewd schlurp that draws you deeper inside, your ass and thighs
			sliding out of view into that yellow orange member, your body piling
			into her sack as your legs are consumed. You feel the softness of the
			pillows beneath you and the warm pressure of her thighs to either
			side as you start to curl but perhaps what is most important is the
			warm stickyness engulfing you as her cock finishes its meal. Her
			cocktip sealing shut behind your feet as the last of you is schlurped
			inside and slips down to become a massive bulge in her balls "mhmm,
			oh if all my subjects were as devoted as you. But then I suppose I'd
			run out." Laurisse says chirring and reaching down to fondle herself
			"now, what to do with you I wonder?"
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoredigest0" text="I wish to be your seed your majesty" />
		<choice destination="cockvoreEndo0" text="may I please you from within your majesty?"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvoreEndo0">
	<text>
	"Mhmm, well if you want to honour me from within. But make it good." she commands with a smile as she settles with her sipping bowl of wine and waits to be impressed. As comfortable as her sack is though you have a queen to honour, and set to work, running your hands and feet along her hot cum soaked flesh. Your limbs making well defined lumpy prints pushing out the flesh of her sack as you do your best to pleasure the reptile queen. There's a submissive thrill from stimulating her from inside her sack this way, now you can only hope you can do a good job of pleasing her here. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvoreEndo1" text="I can do this"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvoreEndo1">
	<text>
	Laurisse had been scandalously unimpressed initially, sipping from her bowl of wine as you rub at her insides. But as you warm up to your job inside of her you feel her mood almost heat "mhmm ah..." she manages afore a deft guard catches the bowl lest it spill "that's better..." she murmurs and reaches down, stroking one hand then another along her cock as you pleasure her from within her balls. The experience turning out to be steadily more stimulating for the saurian queen as she feels you push around and rub against her inner thighs so wonderfully. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="cockvoreEndo2" text="make her cum"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="cockvoreEndo2">
	<text>
	"Mhmm yes you...are really quite good at this" Laurisse exclaims as she jerks off to the sensations now. Your skillful rubbing of her inner flesh driving the queen to delightful distraction as you work her pleasure higher and then higher still. "Keep...ah, YES!" she declares in a shuddering spasming gasp as her climax rocks through her and her balls contract anew to squeeze you back out. Your form landing with a splat amidst her orgasm, gooey but whole and able to savour the blissed out and langourous smile of the queen you'd so ably honoured with your naughty internal rubbings. It takes her a few moments to collect something even resembling her composure and queenly comportment but once she does "well?" she asks as if you're not coated in her cummy juices.
	</text>
		<choice destination="talk" text="time to talk" />	
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvoredigest0">
		<text>
			"Well who am I to deny such a request. Besides, it does seem like it would
			be a rather a bother to have to squirt you back out whole." Laurisse
			says with an amused smile and takes her wine bowl back from the
			guard, sipping as inside her balls you get your wish. Her sack
			churning and burbling softly around your form, slowly softening and
			melting your body as she chirrs and fondles herself with her free
			hand. The royal reptile languidly luxuriating as her balls churn you
			blissfully away. It takes what feels like a small eternity as your
			body spreads out, marinating in her cum and steadily merging into it
			until you're an indistinguishable mass of royal spunk sloshing around
			in her majesty's balls.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvoredigest1" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="cockvoredigest1">
		<text>
			Laurisse smiles a little at feeling you slosh away, her self gratifying
			fondling becoming a bit more vigorous as you form a hefty needy
			weight bloating out her sack. The lizard queen starting to moan in
			delight as she jacks off and hears the insistent burble and glorp of
			all the cum in her sack that you have now become. Her cry of
			delightful bliss heralds the return of your steaming remains to the
			outside world as she climaxes. Your gooey remains erupting out of
			your cock in a series of mighty spurts, splattering against the cool
			stone floor to puddle and cool there in front of Laurisse's cushion
			throne. Her majesty's orgasm trailing off gradually leaving only a
			languid and wonderful sensation permeating the royal reptilie as she
			surveys her handiwork with a smile "Do have someone clean up our
			guest won't you?" she remarks to one of the warriors, who though
			slightly flushed at the debauched display hurries to obey without
			outward signs of grumbling.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="blowjob0">
		<text>
			You lean in closer, laurisse mhmming a little as your warm breath washes
			over the tip of her cock before letting out a delighted chir as you
			wrap your lips around it. "Mhmm yes, serve your majesty." she says
			pausing to refill her winebowl, presumptive confidence oozing out
			with every word along with a steady murr of pleasure. Your desire to
			serve drawing your attention down from her face back down to her cock
			where it belongs. Her majesty's eyes half lidding slightly as you
			work your lips further down her cock, easing that magnificent
			thickness into your throat and coaxing a well earned and well
			received gasp of delight from her lips.
		</text>
		<choice destination="blowjob1" text="suck harder" />
	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob1">
		<text>
			As you start to bob your head up and down upon her lusty royal rod
			queen Laurisse finds it a bit difficult to keep up her affectation of
			nonchalance. Chirring in delight she sets the bowl down to one side
			and spreads her thighs as her attention slides fully onto you. Her
			lust and pleasure visible in her eyes as she watches you lavish her
			cock with the most eager attentions you can muster. Her hands
			steadily clenching into claws grabbing handfuls of pillows as you
			hear her gasp in bliss and feel her shiver, cock twitching and balls
			tensing as she nears orgasm.
		</text>
		<choice destination="blowjob2" text="receive your reward" />
	</page>

	<page ID="blowjob2">
		<text>
			"that's...it..." she manages, her only warning before her orgasm makes her lose poise
			entirely. Her hand coming down to grab your head and hold you down as
			she climaxes. Her cock spurting wad after wad of hot royal lizardcum
			down your throat as she pants and chirrs in pleasure. Her climax
			tapers off only gradually and with it her grip on your head loosens,
			until she lets you up. Panting and chirring she smiles and tucks her
			softening cock back into her robes as you wipe her cum off your lips.
			She seems quite contented by your show of deference now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="talk" text="time to talk" />
	</page>

	<page ID="disrespect0">
		<text>
			You're not about to kneel to this so called queen. As she regards you her
			gaze turns ice at your inaction, then with a hmmph she dismisses you
			from her attention. Ignoring you pointedly as she drinks more from
			her bowl.
		</text>
		<choice destination="disrespect1" text="try to talk to her" />
		<choice destination="end"
			text="maybe i'll try being more respectful next time" />

	</page>

	<page ID="disrespect1">
		<text>
			You attempt to talk but her majesty ignores your attempts to get her
			attention for several seconds before an irritated eyebrow quirks. at
			that point she gestures and her guards draw their weapons and step
			forwards.
		</text>
		<choice destination="disrespect2" text="no she will not ignore me!" />
		<choice destination="end" text="backoff" />
	</page>

	<page ID="disrespect2">
		<text>
			Her majesty glances up from her distraction "slay her" she commands. And
			with that it seems you have angered the ruler of the lizards to the
			point of pique, you'll be lucky to escape the village of Dammath with
			your life.
		</text>
		<effect type="manipulateDisposition" faction="saurian" value="-25" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well crap" />
	</page>

</Conversation>