<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The elf meets your approach eagerly with her own. Her arms twining about
			you as her lips lock to yours in a lusty kiss for a good twenty
			seconds afore coming up for air to talk "mhmm, you like me..dont
			me..especially." she guides your hands down her sides to rest on the
			curves of her ample ass. She smiles as you rub your hands along those
			soft cheeks and dig your fingers in with a mhmm of agreement "Well
			then, I think you should appreciate it properly don't you?" she says
			playfully and places her hands on your shoulders, guiding you
			downwards afore turning around tantalizing to present her ass towards
			you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="ass0" text="$mhmm it's so sexy, it's an amazing ass" />
	</page>

	<page ID="ass0">
		<text>
			"Of course it is." she says with a small laugh as you knead at her
			bountiful ass curves and part them so as to lick between at her
			tantalizing pucker. The green elf letting out a little gasp and mhmm
			as you do so. Your tonguing bountiful ass worship makes her moan and
			lean forwards, glancing over her shoulder back at you coyly
			"compliment my ass more."
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="$you have an ass to die for">
			<preference fetish="analvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="ass1"
			text="$you have the most perfect ass I've ever seen" />
	</page>

	<page ID="ass1">
		<text>
			"Mhmm, yes...keep going" she mumbles and encourages you as you probe her
			ass with your tongue. The deft intrusions further stimulating her as
			you have your fill of her rump, fingers digging into the ample curves
			as you feel her shudder and smell her moistening. Won't be long now
			afore your expert ass ministrations push her over the edge. The elf
			asking for but a few compliments to accompany the lavished attentions
			upon her derriere to be pushed over into shuddering climax. She
			straightens up flushed and panting, reaching one hand down between
			her legs to negligently clean off afore turning around towards you
			and smiling "..thanks, you know how to show my butt proper respect."
			she says and chuckles.
		</text>
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="$I'd molest that ass of yours anytime" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
		<text>
			"to die for? well then..do it...do it..slide yourself into my ass." she
			demands lustfully, chuckling as she reaches her hand back to grasp
			your head and urge you between her rumpcheeks. Though the angle is
			enough she can't quite push you in, but the hot flesh of her derriere
			tantalizes your face as they press against your cheeks. It feels so
			inviting, the urge to dive into her rear end rising up within you as
			you nuzzle at her pucker.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="$yes, let me in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			"that's the spirit" the elf exclaims and mhmms, shifting her hands out in
			front to grab ahold of something to support herself as you prepare to
			work yourself into her ass. The elf letting out a gasp as you slide
			your hands up her soft emerald rump cheeks and then press your
			fingers against her pucker.Her tight bowels clenching, then relaxing
			to let you ease your hands into the heat of her ass. You feel the elf
			letting out a gasping moan and her sphincter clench anew sucking your
			hands deeper in "oh...yes." you hear her exclaim, and find you cannot
			help but agree as you begin to be dragged inside of her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2"
			text="$is your backside always this hungry cause...mhmm" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
			"Yes..but I seldom get someone so willing to slide inside of me." she replied
			with a delighted mhmm. The elf's derriere clenching and relaxing
			alternately to slide your arms deeper and deeper into her ass. Your
			ability to trade vorish banter with her cut short now as you have to
			duck your head down and plunge into her rear end. Her moans becoming
			all the more eager as her middle begins to bulge out with the shape
			of the parts of you already deep inside her as your shoulders and
			chest slide into her ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore3" text="cant talk, wriggle into her butt" />
	</page>

	<page Id="analvore3">
		<text>
			"ah, you're...very willing" the elf says with a delighted chuckle as you
			work yourself inside. Pushing off on the ground until your waist
			schlorps between her rear cheeks and your feet end up dangling
			twitching and waving around in the air. You'll have to rely on the
			hunger of her ass to polish you off the rest of the way and you doubt
			that'll be a problem. The elf leaning forwards and letting out little
			moans and gasps as she clenches and tugs your legs into her. Your
			body more and more contained tightly in the heat of her innards as
			she does so.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore4" text="all the way in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore4">
		<text>
			"mhmmm perfect buttfood" she says as she finally finishes pulling your legs
			in. Her ass sealing over your toes with a schlorp. The elf
			straightening up and running her hands over her middle as it's
			stretched out now around your shape, confining you as a tightly
			curled form in her belly as the last of you feed up through her
			innards to join you entrapped within her "You feel wonderful in me."
			she says as she keeps on rubbing and squeezing her belly around you,
			humming softly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore5"
			text="$And it feels wonderful in here, your hungry ass was so good, I want you to digest me" />
		<choice destination="analvore5Endo"
			text="$And it feels wonderful in here, you don't digest right?" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore5">
		<text>
			"Well that was the plan." she says with a giggle and gets comfortable
			sprawled out comfortably, hands resting on her belly. "besides,
			you'll add nicely to my ass" she teases as she begins to digest you.
			Her gurgling belly pressing tight all around you to rub enzymes into
			your flesh as you get to experience her body making you a part of
			hers. As time passes you soften and gurgle inside her belly and she
			dotes on you and occasionally murmurs some unheard tease to you as
			you're broken down and digested.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvoreGO" text="gurgle" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="analvoreGO">
		<text>
			The elf continues to dote on you even as the bulge you make in her turns
			soft and round. Her delighted cooing as she kneads her fingers into
			the pliant fluid shape of her belly would of been a wonderful sign of
			her appreciation for you had you been around in any meaningful sense
			to hear it. And the way her already wonderfully curvaceous and
			rounded ass becomes somehow yet more perfect as it plumpens with your
			fat as her belly trims is a lasting testament to just how good an
			assmeal you were for her.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="analvore5Endo">
		<text>
			"Well, I was planning to. But you've been so good to me. I suppose I could
			hold ya for a while and push ya back out again." She says and
			giggles, getting comfortable sat and sprawled out comfortably. You
			get yourself comfortable to bask in her heat and the softness of her
			flesh for a while as she rests a hand on the bulge of your form. Time
			passing as you relax squeezed in the warmth of her body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore6Endo" text="comfortable" />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore6Endo">
		<text>
			You get to stay enjoyably nestled in the lazy elf for a while but
			eventually its time to exit back out the butt. The elf getting up and
			giggling "I think that's enough alone time, I got things to do and
			you'd be a bother to heft around." she says and then squats down to
			start clenching and working you back out her ass. Your confines
			contort and press around you, squeezing you slowly down and out as
			she gasps and groans. You gradually emerge into the open air,
			headfirst them worming your hands free to cushion your fall as you're
			disgorged out into the open air. Your feet plopping free of her
			bountiful butt at last as she straightens up and looks down at you
			with a smirk then leans in and experimentally sniffs and snickers
			"You smell like ass dear, you might want to clean up"
		</text>
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<choice destination="end"
			text="$That was fun, we should do it again sometime" />
	</page>

</Conversation>