<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="FACTIONFLAG" value="1" operator="equals"
			flag="allegiance" />
		<text>
			The pointy-eared humanoid is similar in most regards to humans
			but for
			her pale, green skin. She stands around five feet tall and
			more than
			fills out her form, especially viewed from behind. She wears
			a skirt
			that does little to hide her wondrous, shapely ass-- in fact,
			it
			seems to highlight it-- and no top, her breasts swaying free on her
			chest, small and pert. "Greetings and well-met, friend," she says at
			your approach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="seduction" text="Attempt to seduce." />
		<choice destination="info" text="Ask some questions." />
		<choice destination="earth"
			text="-Can you, by any chance, give me directions to Earth?-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Well, bye.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="start">
		<condition evaluate="LIKENESS" operator="greaterthan"
			likeness="saurian" value="2" />
		<text>
			The pointy-eared humanoid is similar in most regards to humans
			but for
			her pale, green skin. She stands around five feet tall and
			more than
			fills out her form, especially viewed from behind. She wears
			a skirt
			that does little to hide her wondrous, shapely ass-- in fact,
			it
			seems to highlight it-- and no top, her breasts swaying free on her
			chest, small and pert. She eyes you distrustfully as you approach,
			something about your appearance engendering distrust "speak your
			piece stranger."
		</text>
		<choice destination="seduction" text="Attempt to seduce." />
		<choice destination="info" text="Ask some questions." />
		<choice destination="earth"
			text="-Can you, by any chance, give me directions to Earth?-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Well, bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The pointy-eared humanoid is similar in most regards to humans
			but for
			her pale, green skin. She stands around five feet tall and
			more than
			fills out her form, especially viewed from behind. She wears
			a skirt
			that does little to hide her wondrous, shapely ass-- in fact,
			it
			seems to highlight it-- and no top, her breasts swaying free on her
			chest, small and pert. "Greetings, stranger from the stars," she says
			at your approach.
		</text>
		<choice destination="seduction" text="Attempt to seduce." />
		<choice destination="info" text="Ask some questions." />
		<choice destination="earth"
			text="-Can you, by any chance, give me directions to Earth?-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Well, bye.-" />
	</page>


	<!--written by serenity, edited by Slayerhero90 -->
	<page ID="seduction">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="0" operator="equals"
			flag="attempt" />
		<text>
			Gears turn slowly in your head and you realize just how
			appealing this
			alien villager looks. Sashaying your hips and
			fluttering your eyes at
			the comely villager, you put on your best
			impression of a female
			equivalent to the legendary Captain Kirk,
			always having freaky sex
			with every alien life-form you meet. This is
			the best idea you've
			ever had.
		</text>
		<choice destination="seductioncheck" text="-To boldly go...~-" />
	</page>


	<check ID="seductioncheck">
		<test what="SEDUCTION" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="seductionwin" />
		<outcome destination="seductionloss" />
	</check>


	<page ID="seduction">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="1" operator="equals"
			flag="attempt" />
		<text>
			The seduction attempt seems to be becoming less effective with
			time as
			she frowns "Why do you keep doing this...? I'm not going to
			change my
			mind just 'cause you stand funny."
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="attempt" value="2" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Slink off." />
	</page>


	<page ID="seduction">
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" value="2" operator="equals"
			flag="attempt" />
		<text>
			Her scowl deepens as you attempt another come-on. “Is this some
			strange
			habit of your people? An inability to accept no as an answer?
			It's a
			wonder you haven't died off long ago. You would think that
			evolution
			would have just turned your species directly into butt-fat
			by this
			point of time.”
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="attempt" value="3" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Dejectedly leave." />
	</page>


	<page ID="seduction">
			<preference fetish="females" />
			<preference fetish="demis" />	
		<text>
			“Still? Still? You know what, fine, I am tired of having to deal
			with you.
			But you need to prove that you're quite skilled at using
			that tongue
			of yours for something other than bothering people.” With
			this, she
			lifts up her strange space-skirt, revealing her delectible,
			green-framed cleft. She motions for you to kneel in front of her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="seductionfail0" text="Get on your knees." />
	</page>

	<page ID="seduction">
	<text>
	“Still? Still? go away. I'm not interested."
	</text>
	<choice destination="end" text="*leave*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="seductionfail0">
		<text>
			You take your cue, kneeling down on both knees and leaning in to
			lap
			gently at her exposed slit. She casually drapes one leg over top
			of
			your shoulder and reaches down to spread her labia with her
			fingers.
			Deciding that she must be pleased with your abilities, you
			dive in,
			lapping and licking and swirling your tongue around.
			Unfortunately,
			it quickly becomes apparent that she isn't too happy
			with you at all.
			Her fingers move away as her free hand presses
			against the back of
			your head and shoves you into her snatch. Before
			you even get the
			chance to flail, she begins to work her way down your
			body.
		</text>
		<choice destination="seductionfail1" text="-Ah, crap.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="seductionfail1">
		<text>
			Unphased by your cries of protest, she moans in delight, her
			snatch eagerly
			devouring your body. You feel your shoulders and chest
			slide into the
			dripping folds as your head journeys deeper inside.
			From there she
			squats lower and lower until she gets to your hips and
			then uses her
			hands to straighten your legs into a more manageable
			position.
			Gripping your feet, she pushes you up further still until
			you are
			completely tucked away in her hot womb.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasurecheck" text="Last chance to prove her wrong." />
		<choice destination="seductionfail2" text="Too late for regrets." />
	</page>


	<check ID="pleasurecheck">
		<test DC="10" what="PLEASURE" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureescape" />
		<outcome destination="seductionfail2" />
	</check>


	<page ID="pleasureescape">
		<text>
			Okay, okay, you can fix this. You can show her she was wrong
			about you and
			continue to live your life still shaped like you.
			Summoning your
			reserve of untapped strength, will, and agility, you
			play by ear. The
			louder she moans, the sweeter the rise of her voice,
			the more you
			know you need to minister to that part of her womb. And
			like a
			space-DJ at her turntables, you run your hands and elbows (and
			to
			break from the simile, your knees and feet) against the walls
			confining you. Before long, her voice reaches fever-pitch, just about
			screaming into the heavens, and these sweltering, dark, fleshy walls
			around you suddenly quiver and quake, building pressure until it
			peaks and shoots you back through her cervix. You skid a little ways
			across the ground, thanking the lubrication of her juices as you come
			to a stop. Looking up at the Quendi, you see her blushing, panting
			face stabilize and her eyes return to lucidity. Noticing you staring
			up at her, she smirks, waves at you, and tries to walk away before
			you can needle her again, muttering something like, "If she tries
			again, I swear..."
		</text>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="Get up and live that life you wrenched back from the jaws of death." />
	</page>


	<gameover ID="seductionfail2">
		<text>
			Her body clenches around you, almost completely locking your
			body up.
			"Hmm, I knew you would make a terrible mate. Your entire body
			and
			still it seems you're hard-pressed to satisfy me. Plus, you've
			ruined
			my skirt. Well, at least you can still make me gush." A
			tingling
			sensation creeps up and down your body and you feel your
			senses
			slowly turning numb. You lift your hand up to try and work some
			feeling back into it, only to find that it has liquidated. You would
			be quite surprised by this odd turn of events, except it seems the
			rest of you has been converted into femcum as well. As you can no
			longer really think for yourself, you decide to just go with the
			flow. And the flow is out. On to the ground. As an orgasm. Maybe this
			counts as seduction?
		</text>

	</gameover>


	<page ID="seductionloss">
		<text>
			She looks at you with confusion. Maybe alien mating rituals are
			different than yours? As you attempt to lay it on a bit thicker,
			understanding dawns across her face. "O-oh! No, I'm not interested in
			girls like you. I am, um, flattered that you'd ask though?" Well
			shoot, it seems that that didn't work.
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="attempt" value="1" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Apologize." />
	</page>


	<page ID="seductionwin">
		<text>
			Fluttering your eyes and sashaying your hips, you whisper sweet
			nothings into
			her comically-large ear. Soon she is putty in your
			hands; hot, green
			putty. Your hands move to her bare breasts, groping
			and squeezing as
			you nibble at her ear. She is quite responsive to
			your ear nibbles,
			much more so than you'd expect. You make a note that
			these aliens'
			ears may be an erogenous zone. You move on from ear
			nibbles to
			kissing her and groping the ample curves of her ass, making
			out with
			her as a prelude to something more.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralsex0" text="Urge her down." />
		<choice destination="sex0" text="Bend her over.">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<!-- <choice destination="oralvore0" text="-I wonder how she'd taste...-"> 
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore"/> </choice> -->
	</page>


	<!-- <page ID="oralvore0"> <text> </text> </page> -->


	<!--edited by Slayerhero90, vore & cockmerge sections written by Slayerhero90 -->

	<page ID="oralsex0">
		<text>
			You place your hands on her shoulders and push gently, firmly guiding
			her down in front of you. She seems to have at least some idea of
			what you have in mind and as she lowers herself quickly
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, pulling your garments out of her way as she goes
			</conditional>
			.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralsex1" text="Enjoy alien tongue.">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="blowjob0" text="Plug up her mouth.">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="Feed your hungry snake.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="Invite her into your flower.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="butt wait there's more">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="butt" />	
		</choice>
<choice destination="breast1" text="here comes the breast part">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="breastvore" />
				
		</choice>

	</page>

	<page ID="analvore0">
	<!--analvore content by serenity-->
	<text>
	She bends down and gives your crotch a few sniffs. Her nose wrinkles at the smell and for few a moments you’re worried that you might have to go unsatisfied. Then, though, she turns around to your backside and her whole expression changes. Seems like she’s got a thing for butts as she dives straight to it, licking and squeezing and fondling yours. You let out a low moan and bend over as she spreads your cheeks and circles around your backdoor with her tongue. That tongue flickers inside of you a moment later, causing you to gasp. You feel more pressure against your pucker and before you have a chance to ask what’s going on, the elf is pushing her whole head into your rectum! You stumble for balance but she continues onward. With a wet schlurping sound her head is stuffed neatly into your anus, your sphincter wrapped around her neck. You stumble some more and fall backwards, landing on her. Her neck and shoulders slide into your back door and you look down to see her masturbating rather furiously. 
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore1" text="continue"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore1">
	<text>
	From here gravity is running the show, and you pant as her chest is squeezed into your intestines. Your stomach bulges out as more and more of her fills your colon, your ass sliding down her torso. As her hips slip in you fall forward, landing on your hands and knees. More wet schlurping sounds fill the air as you anus begins pulling her in of its own accord, her legs disappearing inside of you. Finally with a pop her feet are pulled in, leaving you gasping and panting. As she travels backwards through your intestines you sheepishly look around to see if anyone saw what just happened. To your embarrassment a guard is standing not two feet from you, and she looks as though she saw the whole thing. You start to mumble some sort of explanation but she simply walks over and gives you a pat on the butt and walks off.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore2" text="continue"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore2">
	<text>
	You get to your feet as the elf is pulled into your stomach, the gut already gurgling and groaning around her and try to figure out what just happened. You recall seeing a few of the elves around the village with engorged stomachs, you had assumed that they were pregnant but maybe this is just something they do from time to time. As you get your clothes back on your stomach churns around your playmate. Well at least you won’t have to use any rations for a little while.	
	</text>
		<effect value="95" type="feed" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Well that was unexpected" />	
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralsex1">
		<text>
			She gives your crotch a few sniffs and you suddenly realise you
			aren't sure if these aliens have the same idea of sex as you do.
			Before you're able to worry too much about possible silly sex
			rituals, though, she buries her face in your snatch. She is terribly
			enthusiastic about it, and you begin to worry that you did too good
			of a job with your seduction. Your legs wobble and threaten to give
			out as she applies her oral ministrations, tongue swirling about
			within you. She cups your buttocks carefully to steady you as your
			body shudders of its own accord. You soon find yourself cumming all
			over the alien's face, though she doesn't seem to mind. She licks her
			face clean and ruffles your hair playfully
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, and, once you've recovered your breath, she helps you back into
				your attire
			</conditional>
			. She certainly is a helpful alien.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Oh yes...-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="blowjob0">
		<text>
			She gives your crotch a few sniffs and you suddenly realise you
			aren't sure if these aliens have the same idea of sex as you do.
			Before you're able to worry too much about possible silly sex
			rituals, though, she takes your shaft in one hand, stroking it and
			leaning in to lick your hardening length before her mouth engulfs it.
			The alien elf "mhmm"s appreciatively at the flavour as she slides
			your shaft into her mouth, all the way to the hilt, nuzzling into
			your crotch as her throat ripples and tugs around your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft. The Quendi starts to bob up and down, facefucking herself
			vigorously as possible. You shudder and moan, weak in the knees as
			she supports yourself with a grip on your hips. The elf keeps you
			steady until, with a cry, you're pushed over the edge, pouring your
			creamy jizz down her throat. She "mhmms" for a while, swallows, and
			pulls off slowly, wiping her lips clean and smiling up at you.
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Once you've recovered your breath she helps you back into your
				attire.
			</conditional>
			She certainly is a helpful alien.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Oh yes...-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			She gives your crotch a few sniffs and you suddenly realise you
			aren't sure if these aliens have the same idea of sex as you do.
			Before you're able to worry too much about possible silly sex
			rituals, though, she takes your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft in one hand, stroking it and leaning in to lick your hardening
			length. Before she can cram it in her mouth, though, you buck your
			hips forward with a hand behind her head, claiming her entire face
			with your swelling cockmeat. She doesn't struggle, though. No,
			instead, she shifts on her knees to push up off the ground and down
			the length of your cockhole.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1"
			text="Looks like she's more than happy to participate." />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			She drops her arms to her sides and tucks her shoulders in as
			your snake
			advances past her neck, streamlining her form for
			ingestion. The
			warmth of her skin on your cockhole is delightful and
			the friction
			between the slight roughness of her skin and the rubbery
			smoothness
			of your flesh feels phenomenal. With her help, you quickly
			work your
			way down her body, her legs unfolding as your cock lifts her
			off the
			ground. Passersby gawk at her exposed ass, just barely
			sticking out
			of both her skirt and your glans. You give her plush
			posterior a
			solid smack, sending her legs a-flailing, and push it
			through with
			the rest. The widest, most shapely aspect of the
			space-elf out of the
			way, it's nothing but easy-navigating from there.
			Her legs slip in
			like the diver she is and a spurt of pre splashes out
			in their wake.
			There she is, rocking in your balls, surrounded by your
			spunk.
		</text>
		<choice destination="jizzoutwhole0"
			text="Relax a while and let her out. You've had your fun." />
		<choice destination="cummify0" text="Melt her." />
	</page>


	<page ID="jizzoutwhole0">
		<text>
			Content to just sit back and savor the new weight hanging from
			your loins,
			you recline on the ground and allow your sack to stretch
			out. You
			take a moment to check your gear and count your money, making
			use of
			your free-time. After a couple moments, the Quendi asks, "What
			now?,"
			to which you reply, "Just relax. I'll let you out in a few,
			don't
			worry. It's not often I get to do this with someone who wasn't
			trying
			to kill me only moments ago." And the both of you sit there a
			while,
			maybe fifteen minutes at most, making small talk and enjoying
			yourselves, before she asks to be let out. An honest woman, you hold
			up your end of the deal, aiming your cock away from your face and
			pumping it like only you know how to. It really doesn't take long at
			all for your gonads to seize up in tightened ecstasy and shoot her
			back through the tubes. She flies out, the impact softened by the
			volume of jizz coating her. Getting up, she smiles and gives you a
			gesture which you're pretty sure is a Quendi thumbs-up before walking
			off.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Seeya.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cummify0">
		<text>
			Kicking back, feeling oh-so-satisfied, you rest your head on a
			shored-up
			pile of things. After a couple moments, the Quendi asks,
			"What now?"
			You answer, "Well, seeing as you were so eager to climb on
			in, I was
			thinking about churning up a creamy batch of alien-butter
			with you."
			To that, she replies, "I don't know, I still got stuff to
			do."
		</text>
		<choice destination="cummifycheck"
			text="-Come on, it'll be the best thing you ever feel.-" />
	</page>


	<check ID="cummifycheck">
		<test what="SEDUCTION" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="cummifywin" />
		<outcome destination="cummifyloss" />
	</check>


	<page ID="cummifywin">
		<text>
			"...I didn't really want to do any of those chores anyways. The
			others can
			pick up the slack. Go ahead, turn me into cum!" You chuckle
			and kick
			back while your body's natural processes swing into gear.
			Before her
			body breaks down and loses form, she reaches down between
			her thighs
			and fits in one last schlicking, gushing a bit of her own
			juice into
			the slurry with a moan. Not very long after that, your nads
			begin to
			round out, settling into a person-sized beanbag of seed. You
			purr a
			little, yourself, and climb back to your feet, taking a seat on
			your
			jewels and finishing what the space-elf started. When all is said
			and
			done, there's a neat little alabaster puddle of villager soaking
			into
			the earth, with a primitive skirt that so doesn't fit you
			floating on
			top.
		</text>
		<effect value="95" type="feed" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Someone else can clean that up.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cummifyloss">
		<text>
			"Well then why haven't you gotten turned to cum yet? I'm out of
			here."
			Before you can protest, she forces her hands up your shaft,
			shooting
			signals of pleasure up your spine. Finding anchors along its
			interior
			until she breaches your glans, she pulls her shapely self
			out,
			flopping to the ground, walking off, and leaving a
			derious-with-pleasure you lying dumb on your ass.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="Well, you tried." />
	</page>


	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			She gives your crotch a few sniffs and you suddenly realise you
			aren't
			sure if these aliens have the same idea of sex as you do.
			Before
			you're able to worry too much about possible silly sex rituals,
			though, she buries her face in your snatch. She is terribly
			enthusiastic about it, and you begin to worry that you did too good
			of a job with your seduction. If so, then you know just what to do
			towards that end. A gentle tap on the back of her head is all you
			need to give to for her to know you want her deeper.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="Give her room to work." />
	</page>


	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			The Quendi pulls back, licking her lips, and thrusts her warm,
			green
			hands into your spread nether-lips. Her palms are rub up just
			roughly
			enough against your flesh that, between this and her prior
			ministrations, it takes just a little bit of resolve not to cum right
			then and there. But you're stronger than that. Pretty soon, her
			fingertips breach your cervix and she bows forwards, both
			straightening herself out and giving you plenty of room to lift your
			leg over her head and bring yourself down. Neck, shoulders, tiny
			tits, belly, hips-- your snatch stretches to fit them all. It's that
			ass you're worried about. She's got so much junk in the trunk it
			genuinely crosses your mind that, though she probably won't split you
			in half, the effort of getting it in may just force you to gush her
			back out. Taking a deep breath in, you square your stance and grip
			her by the ass-cheeks. Gently but forcefully, you wiggle that beast
			through the gate, whereupon suction practically-instantly slurps her
			legs through with it. Thrown back a little, you take a seat against
			the nearest thing you can lean against and get to rubbing your belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="catchandrelease0" text="Just womb-cuddle a while." />
		<choice destination="gush0" text="Gush her." />
	</page>


	<page ID="catchandrelease0">
		<text>
			After a little while, exhausted by the efforts you just put
			forth and
			hearing your little guest snoring, you check that your
			things are
			secured and doze off yourself, slumped over your bulging
			midsection.
			Near as you can tell, maybe thirty minutes have passed by
			the time
			you wake up and the space-elf's still snoring. You at least
			need to
			stretch your legs, so you tap near her head and wake her up.
		</text>
		<choice destination="catchandrelease1" text="Wake her up and let her out." />
		<choice destination="unbirthjoke0" text="Perfect opportunity for a goof." />
	</page>



	<page ID="catchandrelease1">
		<text>
			"Morning," you say to her, giving her some time to wake back up.
			"It's time to
			let you out." She asks in response, "Really? So soon?"
			and you tell
			her you're getting a leg cramp. "Well, thank you for your
			time all
			the same. I just wish I could shirk my responsibilities just
			a bit
			longer." Spreading your legs, you seize control of your
			abdomen's
			muscles and push against the Quendi, who slides on out very
			easily,
			coated in your cum. Fixing her skirt and hair, she gets back
			up
			strolls away, dripping-wet and energized by her nap.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Seeya.-" />
	</page>



	<page ID="unbirthjoke0">
		<text>
			"Morning, sleepyhead," you say to her, trying not to giggle.
			"You've been
			asleep in there for days. I didn't want to disturb you,
			so I just
			brought you along with me on a trip to your moon. You ever
			been?" She
			"eep"s in surprise and asks, just a little bit frantically,
			"What?
			We're on the moon?! I have to get home! Please take me back!"
			She
			fidgets a little bit before you pat your belly, stand up, and
			assure
			her you're joking. Sounding more than a little bit flustered,
			she
			asks you to let her out. Hands underneath your pussy to keep her
			from
			clonking her head against the ground, because that's how she's
			oriented herself in there, you muster up your control over your womb
			and push. Lubricated by your juices, she slides out nice and easily,
			taking your hands for support as you set her down. A nearby guard
			leans against a tree, snorting as she watches the villager climb to
			her feet, fix her skirt, and slink away.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Seeya.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="gush0">
		<text>
			Before the pleasure of getting the space-elf up in your womb can
			fade, you
			take the opportunity to slip your hand around your womb and
			finish
			yourself off, confident your cervix will keep her in. Hearing
			you
			voice your satisfaction as a stream of cum trickles out of you,
			she
			asks, "What do you want to do now?" You answer, simply, that you
			had
			plans on gushing her. Not sounding too enthused by your designs on
			her, she says, "I've still got things to do."
		</text>
		<choice destination="gushcheck" text="-You'll love it, trust me.-" />
	</page>


	<check ID="gushcheck">
		<test what="SEDUCTION" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="gushwin" />
		<outcome destination="gushloss" />
	</check>


	<page ID="gushwin">
		<text>
			"...Well, I did climb inside to avoid work. And this will keep
			me from ever
			having to do work again, so… Sure, do it. Gush me."
			Chuckling to
			yourself, you tell her, "Alright. Don't forget to please
			yourself one
			last time while you still can." And she does just that
			whilst your
			womb contracts around her. Warm as she was before, her
			body
			effervescing into cum fills your insides with wonderful heat.
			Were it
			not for her little moan, you genuinely wouldn't be able to
			tell if
			she hit climax or not. Then, before you know it, your belly
			sloshes
			with ex-Quendi, waiting to be released. You're more than happy
			to
			oblige (and to no longer need to work around your belly to get at
			her
			pussy), spilling buckets of villager-juice onto the ground. That
			felt
			too good.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Hope you enjoy your new form.-" />
		<effect value="95" type="feed" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>



	<page ID="gushloss">
		<text>
			"I think I should trust a puddle of juice before trusting
			someone who
			turns others into juice. I'm out; I've got work to do."
			And before
			you open your mouth to speak, she's prying at the gate and
			stunning
			you with circles of pleasure. Soon she induces an orgams in
			you,
			shooting her out feet-first and across the ground. She tidies
			herself
			up before storming off.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end"
			text="Well, you can still try with someone else." />
	</page>


	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			The space-elf grabs onto the nearest rock for support and
			presents her
			rump to you with a giggle and a gentle sway.
		</text>
		<choice destination="anal0" text="Ream her brains out." />
		<!-- <choice destination="sex1" text="Fuck her right in the pussy."> -->
	</page>


	<page ID="anal0">
		<text>
			You set your sights on her cute little green pucker, cock
			stiffening
			between you. Planting your hands on that juicy posterior,
			you line
			yourself up and thrust. Their asses, as you've been able to
			discern
			thus far, are very well-acquainted with receiving large loads.
			Burying yourself up to hilt comes easy and it doesn't take long for
			you to build up a steady, rhythmic pace slamming your hips against
			that magnificent cushion until your skin's bright red. As for the
			interior? Despite how easily she let you inside, her rectum clenches
			so very tightly around your girth and her colon feels velvety-smooth.
			It would take you ages to get sick of this and, before very long at
			all, you're faced with the pressing need to climax.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockmerge0"
			text="You want something to remember her by. What about a couple more inches?">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockmerging" />
			<preference fetish="cocktransformation" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="anal1" text="Cum." />
	</page>


	<page ID="anal1">
		<text>
			Your fingers grip her ass like a vice as your entire body seizes up
			in the ecstasy of orgasm. You paint the space-elf's colon white with
			your seed and take a moment to catch your breath before stepping back
			to admire your work. A dribble barely escapes the Quendi's asshole
			before she pushes herself back up,
			<conditional>
				<condition evaluate="BODYVALUE" value="24" partvalue="length"
					bodypart="penis" operator="lessthan" />
				tells you she's taken bigger, and walks off.
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<condition evaluate="BODYVALUE" value="24" partvalue="length"
					bodypart="penis" operator="greaterthan" />
				tells you to hit her up again, and walks off.
			</conditional>
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="-Seeya.-" />
		<!-- <choice destination="end" text="-...Rude. Seeya?-"> <assertion evaluate="BODYVALUE" 
			value="24" partvalue="length" bodypart="penis" operator="lessthan"/> </choice> 
			<choice destination="end" text="-...Will do. Seeya.-"> <assertion evaluate="BODYVALUE" 
			value="24" partvalue="length" bodypart="penis" operator="greaterthan"/> </choice> -->
	</page>


	<page ID="cockmerge0">
		<text>
			Your fingers grip her ass like a vice as your entire body seizes
			up in
			the ecstasy of orgasm. You paint the space-elf's colon white
			with
			your seed and take a moment to catch your breath. The villager
			tries
			to pull off, but you come with, firmly affixed to her posterior.
			She
			stares at you in utter confusion until it clicks in her head. She
			looks in the direction of the apothecary for a moment, seeming to
			think that's how you're able to do this, before looking at you and
			smirking. "Oh, I see," she says. "You want to take me with you, don't
			you, space-traveller? I accept your invitation." With that, she
			settles down and takes a moment to get herself off before her arms
			are gone.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockmerge1" text="-Figured you wouldn't mind.-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockmerge1">
		<text>
			Inch by inch,
			<macro id="skin_colour_desc" />
			skin overtakes the elf's plush, green rump, only getting faster and
			faster the more it claims. The juices raining down from the
			villager's cooch suddenly cease as her pussy seals shut. She starts
			to say something else to you but before she can get a word out, she
			hiccups a spurt of pre which dribbles from the side of her mouth. By
			the time she's cleaned it off her face, her legs have already
			disappeared and her belly's grown the outdent of a urethra. Even
			though you just came, you can't help but get to stroking again while
			everything's (which includes the villager's entire body) so
			hyper-sensitive. She feels fantastic.
		</text>
		<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="penis" modifier="3" variable="length">
			<proportional ratio="0.05"/>
			</mutation>
		</special>
		<choice destination="cockmerge2"
			text="-Any last words while you've still got a mouth?-" />
	</page>


	<page ID="cockmerge2">
		<text>
			"It's a pleasure to join your crew.” She says that right as your
			pigments override those of her lips, leaving her skin pure
			<macro id="skin_colour_desc" />
			. Her arms vanish and her ribs soften into erectile tissue. Then go
			her breasts and then her hair and eyes and ears and nose. Finally,
			her lips thin to the point of nonexistence, go vertical on what used
			to be her face, and her skull changes into a glans just in time for a
			second load of jizz to gush from your balls to the tip of your
			swollen shaft. It quickly falls limp, but you saw you had at least
			<result/> more inches on it since last time you looked. That brings you
			to
			<measurement part="penis" variable="length" />
			inches. You do not regret stopping by that derelict at all.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Let's go.-" />
	</page>

<!--breast vore content written by ConnTheElite -->


<page ID="breast1">
		<text> 
			You look down and notice the elf staring intently at your breasts. This comes as somewhat of a surprise from
			a girl raised by a culture that seems to value butts above anything else. "Go on, you may suckle them if you wish."
			You tell her with a grin across your face. The green-skinned girl gladly acts on this statement and pops your left nipple
			into her mouth. She uses her tongue to stimulate your nipple as she increases the intensity of her sucking. Suddenly,
			she removes her mouth from her nipple and looks up at you. "Is there something wrong?" You ask. "N-no." she anwsers with a
			blush on her face. "I was just thinking of my friend who also enjoys this sort of thing."
				
				
				
		</text>
		<choice destination="breast2" text="Double the girls means double the fun." />
	</page>

<page ID="breast2">
		<text> 
			"She's welcome to join. My right breast could do with the attention." You respond with a smile. The elf nods a looks around before
			waving towards a very similar-looking girl. The second elf quickly runs over to you and exchanges greetings with her friend. She then
			promptly sticks your right nipple into her mouth and begins mimicking her friend. Not to be outdone, the first elf resumes her task
			of pleasuring your left breast. Having two girls dedicate themselves to the task of pleasruing you through breast play alone is a new
			and exhilarating experience.

<conditional><assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="Lactation"/>

The combined efforts of the elf girls cause you to orgasm. Milk from your breasts fills their waiting mouths. The elves seem surprised by this turn of events
but continue to suckle your mammaries until they get their fill. The elves eventually detach their mouths from your breasts. "That was the most delicious thing I have
ever tasted." The first elf compliments you with lust her voice. "Yes! Yes! Please! We want more!" The second elf adds. Apparently, you've not only inherited the mushroom mother's
ability to produce milk on demand, you've also inherited the ability to make your milk addictive and intoxicating! Enough to make other creatures into boob sluts! The two elves
eye you with expecting stares. They are now completley at your mercy.

</conditional>	

<conditional><assertnot evaluate="hasperk" perk="Lactation"/>

The combined efforts of the elf girls cause you to orgasm. Your cum leaks out onto the ground below you. The elves detach their mouths from your breasts. 
"Your breasts are the best I've ever tasted." The first elf compliments you. "I must agree." The second elf adds. "We have to get back to work, but if you happen
to be in our village again, we can do this again." With a slightly dissapointed sigh, you nod as the elves begin to walk off. Apparently they are not in love with your
breasts to the point where they would want to become one with them.

</conditional>	
				
				
		</text>
		<choice destination="breast3" text="Give them what they want.">
<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="Lactation" />
</choice>

<choice destination="end" text="I better get going." />
	</page>



<page ID="breast3">
		<text>
			
		You grin and confidently shake your <macro ID="breast_size_desc" /> breasts at the elves. "Don't keep my girls waiting." You command them with a hand cupped underneath
each tit. The egar elves resume their breast suckling, but this time your nipples suck back. With one big pull, your breasts swallow the heads of both elves. It is now only a matter of time
before they are taken in completley. You look at your surroundings and see that you're threesome has gathered a bit of an audience. Several elf villagers and guard watch the torsos of your
willing prey disappear into your mammaries. None of them raise a finger to stop you. "I guess this really is a girl-eat-girl planet." You think to yourself. "Those who willingly
give themselves up as food, will be treated as such." When you looks back to your chest, you see that your breasts have worked their way to the elves' rear ends. You would love to give
those fine asses one last slap for the road, but your breasts have swollen up such a massive size that reaching around them is nearly impossible. You place your hand on the ground and
angle your chest upwards to let gravity do its thing. You moan as your hungry tiddies quickly eat up the butts and legs of the green-skinned pair. An outline of an elf assuming the fetal position can been
seen in both of your breasts. Muffled cries of delight can be heard from inside. It is time for them to become one with you.

		</text>
		<choice destination="breastend1" text="I wonder what elf milk is like?" />
		<choice destination="breastend2" text="You two will make fine additions to my girls.">
<condition operator="lessthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE" bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="14" />
</choice>
<choice destination="breastend3" text="You two will make fine additions to my girls">
	<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE" bodypart="breasts" partvalue="size" value="14" />
</choice>

	</page>


<page ID="breastend1">
		<text>

		They loved your milk, why not use their bodies to make more? You place one hand on top of your left breast as your body begins the process of turing your
		prey into milk. The heavy weight of your elf-filled breasts begins to lighten as their bodies are broken down into liquid. You use your hands to massage your shrinking
		breasts. Within the hour, the green elves have become nothing but milk inside your mammaries, fuel that you will use to continue your own adventures. You lick your lips
		as you position your left nipple near your mouth. You then being you suck the white creamy liquid out of your left breast. "mmm. sweet but also a bit thick. just like
		like their rear ends." You empty the milk supply in your left breast before giving the right one the same treatment. Your breasts have shruken back down to their usual size
		and you now have a bit of a beer belly full of soon-to-be digested elf milk. You give your belly a pat before standing back up to resume your adventure.
			
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

<page ID="breastend2">
<text>

	You decide to break the elves down into nutrients and tit fat. Who knows, maybe more people will willingly give themselves up to you if your assets are larger?
	With this devious thought in mind, you lie down on the earthy soil and let your body do its work. Your breasts quickly wear down the bodies the of the elves, their
	figures can no longer been seen from outside. As your breasts begin to shrink, you watch them intently. Surely absorbing TWO girls will increase your cup size.
	Several minutes pass and your breasts stop shrinking. To your delight, they've increased by one cup size each! You you sit up and pat your right breast with one hand. "I know you
	two can't hear me anymore, but thank you. You've made fine additions to my body." 
			

</text>
<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
<special effect="mutation">
			<mutation part="breasts" modifier="1" variable="size"> </mutation>
		</special>
<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
</page>

<page ID="breastend3">
<text>


	You decide to break the elves down into nutrients and tit fat. Who knows, maybe more people will willingly give themselves up to you if your assets are larger?
	With this devious thought in mind, you lie down on the earthy soil and let your body do its work. Your breasts quickly wear down the bodies the of the elves, their
	figures can no longer been seen from outside. As your breasts begin to shrink, you watch them intently. Surely absorbing TWO girls will increase your cup size.
	Several minutes pass and your breasts stop shrinking. To your dissapointment, your breasts have returned to the their usual, non-girl-filled size. You sit up with
	a dissapointed grunt. "At least their nutrients will satisfy the rest of my body... for now."
		
		
	</text>
<effect type="feed" value="150" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />


		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
</page>


	<page ID="info">
		<text>
			"Ask and I will answer, traveller."
		</text>
		<choice destination="danger" text="-What dangers are there nearby?-" />
		<choice destination="pad0" text="-What's with the stone platform?-" />
		<choice destination="supplies" text="-Where can I get supplies?-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Actually, I've changed my mind. Bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="danger">
		<text>
			"There is plenty to look out for beyond the safety of our
			community,
			between the lamia huntresses to the west, prowling the
			underbrush for
			live prey, and the raptors to the south. There is very
			little more
			terrifying than a pack of those raptor-girls chasing you
			back to the
			safety of our humble village."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="-I would like to ask another question.-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Thanks, bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pad0">
		<text>
			"Isn't it true that these landing pads are used by star-craft
			bearing cargo
			to perch upon the surface of worlds? we have built this
			pad of stone,
			that vessels from the stars will come to our village
			bearing cargo."
		</text>
		<choice destination="pad1"
			text="-I'm fairly sure that's not how it usually works but... I guess it worked on me.-" />
		<choice destination="info" text="-I would like to ask another question.-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Thanks, bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pad1">
		<text>
			"And we have long waited for your arrival. But with it, you have
			surely
			proved the merits of our work. I have no doubt that now many
			vessels
			will come to our village bearing cargo in future. Yours is but
			the
			first."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="-I would like to ask another question.-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Thanks, bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="supplies">
		<text>
			"Ask for the storekeeper. She is eager to trade with
			star-travellers for
			any cargo they might have and will certainly show
			you what we can
			offer you."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="-I would like to ask another question.-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Thanks, bye.-" />
	</page>

	<page ID="earth">
		<text>
			"I have no idea what or where that is."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="-I would like to ask another question.-" />
		<choice destination="end" text="-Thanks, bye.-" />
	</page>

</Conversation>