<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>This ventilation hatch is sealed for good!
			using brute force would be too dangerous here, some kind of
			tool might be able to help.
		</text>
		<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"
			flag="FIRST" />
		<choice destination="plasmacut" text="use the multitool">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="multitool" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="plasmacut">
		<text>
			You muster the metal plating in front of you, there are no visible screws you could remove.
			You turn the multitool and press the plasma cutters end at the seal. After activating the tool you
			melt the metal like butter while tracing the edges of the seal. Suddenly the entire room 
			around you shifts, it seems like something large is grabbing the air vent with crushing force. The
			metal around you creaks as it gets slowly squished like a tin can.
			In a moment of shock, you drop the multitool. As it hits the bottom of the air vent, all you can do is 
			watch the device bounce around in the shifting metal, cutting a small hole and vanishing out of sight.
			Once again, you feel the metal around you shaking again. In an act of desperation you try to crawl backwards as the 
			air vent bends forward and shifts downward.
		</text>
		<effect type="removeitem" item="multitool" value="1" />
		<special effect="destroywidget" />
		<choice destination="out1" text="brace yourself!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="out1">
		<text>You brace yourself as gravity forces you to slide uncontrollable towards the damaged 
			containment seal. There is nothing you can do as you hit it face first. A dull pain fills your body 
			as you hit the abused metal, providing the required force to finally crack the seal.
			You shift uncomfortable as your surroundings screak and hit the ground catapulting you out of your
			entrapment.
		</text>
		<special effect="transition" x="21" y="4" destination="debrisF2" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Recover" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="start">
		<text>A ventilation hatch is blocking your way.
			You can see the other side of the spaceship through the metal bars.
			Some kind of science room with strange tubes filled with strange green goo
		</text>
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="FIRST" value="1" />

		<choice destination="rem1" text="try removing it" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="rem1">
		<text>You try pushing the ventilation hatch... With no avail
		</text>
		<choice destination="rem2" text="try punching it!" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="rem2">
		<text>Annoyed by the stubborn contraption, you swing your fist and punch it with brute force... 
		Your hand hurts, but something has budged.
		</text>
		<choice destination="rem3" text="try kicking it" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="rem3">
		<text>You shift around in the tight air vent and kick the hatch with both legs. 
		The metal creaks as the hatch flies off, success! You try to slip out of the 
		air vent as a sudden rumble seals it again. You just triggered the emergency containment seal...
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="damn" />
	</page>
</Conversation>