<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			RSV LYSSA RESEARCH TERMINAL 01
			Welcome USER: Dr. Miller
			PLEASE REMBER TO LOGG OFF AFTER
			EVERY SESSION TO PREVENT ACCOUNT
			ABUSE
		</text>
		<choice destination="log1" text="Miller; research log 43" />
		<choice destination="log2" text="Miller; research log 45" />
		<choice destination="log3" text="Miller; research log 46" />
		<choice destination="log4" text="Miller; research log 47" />
		<choice destination="darkl1" text="Access C01 eventlog" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="log1">
		<text>
			*static* "ahem, Dr. Emanuel Miller genetic engineering
			Supervision research log 43... Today, we've received another
			remarkable specimen. Its structure is comparable to basic amoeba
			but with a far more defined carapace. Like most of the prior specimen.
			This one is completely feral. Scans indicated it certainly never was intelligent.
			I see potential in this one, I think this one will be my favorite."
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="log2">
		<text>
			Dr. Emanuel Miller, log 45. This is astounding! This amoeba is nothing we've ever
			Seen before. It appears perfectly able to mimic simple objects by changing its shape.
			Yet it is also able to manipulate its surface density to switch from semi-fluid to rock solid.
			Ethology division has run test on it and we can manipulate its neural core to let it perform simple tasks. 
			Arms officer Richard has suggested to weaponize its potential, while one C2 supervisor suggested to 
			turn it into a shape shifting sextoy. I think I have my own idea.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="log3">
		<text>
			Miller, log 46. I have erased my previous logs, nothing should distract me from this
			subject. We have genetically uplifted its intelligence to make it more receptive for commands.
			It worked better as we ever expected, the amoeba has developed the ability to perform complex
			tasks. I have also discovered something spectacular, thanks to my assistant Ryan. *you can clearly 
			hear muffled screams in the background as Miller pauses* Unlike normal amoeba, this one is able to
			ingest prey and hold it captive until it requires the nutrition. It's also able to bypass the containment
			lock and free itself, we need to give it some defined shape to prevent this from happening again.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="log4">
		<text>
			Miller here, we held a vote in the cantina about the defined shape of the amoeba,
			Some suggested to turn it into a grumpy blob version of Admiral Lewins and while
			I must agree, that I found this idea amusing, I'm glad this one won the poll.
			G2 is calling it goo dragon, It's almost perfect. I will have to run some tests on the clones.
			It seems to enjoy eating everything edible it can find, I'll have fix this later, also might reduce the size.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="darkl1">
		<text>
			PLEASE ENTER PASSWORD
		</text>
			<choice destination="darklog2" text="$Enter archive password">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="DARKLOG" value="2" />
			</choice>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
			<page ID="darklog2">
		<text>
			You enter the password and access the emergency live broadcast.
			You can see the white, terror fueled, scaly face of a very humanoid looking person, wearing glasses while staring into the 
			terminal camera, sweat is running down his cheeks as he speaks. "This is Dr. Miller *ugh* something
			is attacking the ship, readings show half of the ship is damaged, reformers are offline, if they get me, 
			I'm done for." An audible crash fills the room as the sound of warning sirens springs into live. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="darklog3" text="keep wathing" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
		</page>
		
			<page ID="darklog3">
		<text>
			You see Dr. Miller turn around in panik, as something approaches him. "NO NONONO STAY PUT YOU 
			STUPID CREATURE!". You can see an orange, gooey creature leap from the side as Miller gets tackled 
			to the ground. "NO YOU CAN'T DO THIS I'VE CREATED YOU IM YOUR MMPPFF"" You watch the 
			creature move in front of the camera, head down and clearly busy with the scientist. You can't see 
			every detail since most of the creature is blocking the view. But you notice a bulge wandering 
			the creatures' neck and descending into its belly, clearly filling it out in the process. Suddenly the 
			creature arches up, staring straight into the camera. You see the former scientist feet vanish into 
			its gullet, as the goo dragon approaches the terminal... The next 2 minutes of the recording, mainly 
			consists of footage of the goo dragon gingerly licking the camera, until the screen goes dark.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was something - exit" />
	</page>

</Conversation>