<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			This terminal seems badly damaged. Judging by the marks it appears that something has repentantly tried to bite it 
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="Work directive R01" />
		<choice destination="info2" text="TO ALL EMPLOYEES!!" />
		<choice destination="info3" text="Access research log" />
		<choice destination="darkl1" text="Access R01 eventlog" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="darkl1">
		<text>
			PLEASE ENTER PASSWORD
		</text>
			<choice destination="darklog2" text="$Enter archive password">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="DARKLOG" value="2" />
			</choice>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
			<page ID="darklog2">
		<text>
			You enter the password and access the emergency live broadcast.
			The screen springs to live and you see what appears to be grey, furred wolf like creatures lying all around the room. As the camera focuses you notice each of the wolves being bloated with what appears to be the staff that worked here before. You can still see the outline of some of the unlucky victims that ended as wolf fodder. The picture suddenly shifts as the camera moves to focus another part of the room, you see two pairs of clawed feet desperately dangling out of the wolf's bulged blue hued cocktip, while slowly sinking inwards, much to the wolf's enjoyment. The camera suddenly rattles, as something seems to malfunction drawing attention of the remaining wolves, who quickly dismantle the camera.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="uh, time to go back.." />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="info">
		<text>
			RESEARCH FACILITY 01 DIRECTIVE
			Long term observation and research of all category V specimen
			DO NOT ENTER THE HABITAT AREA WITHOUT
			SPECIMEN CONTROLL UNIT
			DO NOT INTERACT WITH THE SUBJECTS
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info2">
		<text>
			Research supervision wants to inform you, that any kind of specimen interaction
			outside the normal research routine is STRICTLY FORBIDDEN!
			We can't afford to run reform-bay in overdrive because you can't contain
			yourself! Remember YOU ARE STILL DEALING WITH FERAL CREATURES, and the AI habitat
			surveillance AI makes sure that they are ALL well fed! YOU ARE PROFESSIONALS,
			so, act like professionals! – Lyssa Operative
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info3">
		<text>
		You try to access the research log files. While the system indicates over 1400 available logs, it seems like the terminal damage has clearly rendered most of them useless. The system however, offers an option to only display the functional files.
		</text>
		<choice destination="log1" text="Research log 1002" />
		<choice destination="log2" text="Research log 1100" />
		<choice destination="log3" text="Research log 1337" />
		<choice destination="log4" text="Research log 1338" />
		<choice destination="log5" text="Research log 1343" />
		<choice destination="log6" text="Research log 1413" />
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log1">
		<text>
		log 1002- You see two very lizard like humanoids in tight jump suits standing in fair distance to the camera. The female looking one nibbles on what looks like beef jerky while the other, smaller, male looking seems to patch wires behind an open wall panel. Both seem unaware that the camera started recording them mid-talk.
		"I'm not sure about this, whole thing, genetics is very... sensitive about the entire artificial virus topic, what if we are not here to reverse, but to replicate it... I mean... Mikal? Are you even listening?"
		"Rose please, ugh, for the love of, just stop, you should really stop digging around in this, I mean, why would they risk another plague? Just to repel Zenturion? We both know that Ashar would obliterate them if they came anywhere close our sector, just let the eggheads do their jobs and let us do our, after all we are here for precision engineering and not this bio humbug... *he suddenly bends upwards* Ah fixed, this should stop the observation recorder from malfunctioning" 
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log2">
		<text>
		log 1100- You see two slightly scaled male looking humanoids in lab coats in a hefty debate, both arms swinging and clearly angry. One seemed to have triggered recordings mid debate.
		"You see this, you see this... thing there behind the glass." The scientist points angry in a room outside the camera view. "This thing has eaten 11 of my man and you insist on keeping it! I can't believe you are this stupid. What is your team thinking?! Ohhh, we found a walking glutton, let's call it gulper and weaponize it so it can beat our enemies by eating them. This is straight up absurd!" You see the second scientist interfere "But mission control has approved this project you moron!" only to be cut again by the first "YEAH! I don't care about mission control, if it eats just another of my man, I will personally ensure you a trip to the reformer!"
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log3">
		<text>
		log 1337- This video recording pops in grey but slowly regains its colors, you can see the outline of another lizard persons upper head underneath the camera and what appears to be the robot janitor you have met before, standing in the background, holding a multitool. "alright Bob, what is your assessment?" The lizard shifts as he appears to be working on the terminals electronics. "THIS UNIT HATES HIS JOB" the lizard chuckles. "I feel you buddy, no I mean the, political assessment" you see the robot shifting "WAR OUTCOME ASSESMENT, UNPREDICTABLE, ZENTURON CAN NOT BE EVALUATED, ASHAR RESPONSE 80% CHANCE OF BEING TACTICAL PROPAGANDA, CONTINUE TO DE-CYPHER COMMUNICATION LINK" The screen suddenly goes dark and you can see a scaly hand moving in front of the camera. "shhh buddy, I think the camera just went online, please be so kind and pass me my multitool"
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log4">
		<text>
		log 1338- You see a young looking humanoid woman with light green scaly face and a lab coat jumping around like an exited dog as you activate the log replay. 
		"Hey operation Miranda here, here! R1 observation deck! You remember the black quadruped fluffy creatures you have send us? Yeah, the one you told us that they were a lost cause.
		You would not believe what happened! Cedrick from genetics has managed to make them smarteeer, like a lot! They now seem to like him. I mean, every time he sits in the observation room
		they just come up and lick the glass. That's so cute! The others at gen bay also seem exited! That's all byyeee."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log5">
		<text>
		log 1343- You see a well build humanoid lizard in uniform standing 5 feet tall in respective distance to the camera.
		"Arms officer Richard Volborn second command area 4 RSV Lyssa, reporting facility R 01 according to protocol. Genetics has successfully uplifted and modified genotype 137, codename Gulper, we are now running field test." You hear a sudden crash and incoherent screaming in the background. "All according to plan, expecting final modification and cloning in about 6 days, Volborn out"
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log6">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="clevergirl" value="1" />
		<text>
		log 1413- The screen flickers, you can see what looks like an anthropomorphic, fully scaled lizard person in a re-enforced lab coat, casually leaning in a small chair. His emerald green scaled arm is covered with tiny syringe filled holster. He leans his head sideward, as he somewhat annoyed addresses someone outside the camera view. "do I really have to do this? I really have better things to do right now". You hear the other person reply, "It's your turn reporting this time Cedrick, you know the rules". The lizards sights as he shifts back, once again facing the camera. "Fine! Alright, G2 genetics grunt here, nothing special to report for today, stabilized the neuro serum. The intelligence uplift should make them about 24% smarter now. Dan from R1 got exited about the taurs, took one of them for testing, called it his clever girl, we found him later, feet sticking out of her snatch... They both deserve each other, that's all Ced out."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

</Conversation>