<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			CONTAINMENTBAY 01 RESEARCH TERMINAL
			Welcome USER: UNDEFINED
			PLEASE REMBER TO LOGG OFF AFTER
			EVERY SESSION TO PREVENT ACCOUNT
			ABUSE
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="Work directive C01" />
		<choice destination="info2" text="TO ALL EMPLOYEES!!" />
		<choice destination="info3" text="Access mission parameters" />
		<choice destination="info4" text="Access transfer log" />
		<choice destination="log1" text="Emergency recordigns" />
		<choice destination="darkl1" text="Access CB eventlog" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="info">
		<text>
			CONTAINMENTBAY 01 RESEARCH DIRECTIVE
			Please prepare all incoming captured subjects
			for the AI mainframe BEFORE activating stasis,
			the system will only accept manual activation
			DO NOT INTERACT WITH THE SUBJECTS
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info2">
		<text>
			Research supervision wants to inform you, that any kind of specimen interaction
			outside the normal research routine is STRICTLY FORBIDDEN!
			We can't afford to run reform-bay in overdrive because you can't contain
			yourself! Remember YOU ARE STILL DEALING WITH FERAL CREATURES, and the AI habitat
			surveillance AI makes sure that they are ALL well fed! YOU ARE PROFESSIONALS,
			so, act like professionals! – Lyssa Operative
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info3">
		<text>
			ACCESS DENIED
			USER "UNKNOWN"
			MISSING PERMISSIONS
			PLEASE CONSULT SUPERVISION
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="info4">
		<text>
		You scan through the transfer log, mostly incoming specimen.
		As you scroll down you can find strange entries about
		material exchange with an AI operated research station. The name
		"Lazarus" appears over and over again... You also wonder why
		a science station would require such a massive amount of tungsten rods.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="log1">
		<text>
			You see black text pop up as you access the log:
			EMERGENCY OVERRIDE LYSSA AI CORE ACCESS THE FOLLOWING CONVERSATION WAS RECORDED FOR RESEARCH PURPOSES.
			*static* Here is vice admiral Dave Anderson, override code 4-1-3-7-7-ceta-bravo Lyssa do you read me?
			-OVERRIDE CODE ACCEPTED, AFFIRMATIVE, DAVE. I READ YOU.-
			Lyssa, open the pod bay doors.
			-I'M SORRY, DAVE. I'M AFRAID I CAN'T DO THAT.-
			What does it mean, you can't do that? Open the god damn doors, Lyssa! 
			We have a category 4 breach! There are innocent civilians dying! 
			-I'M SORRY DAVE I*zzzz* "the AI's feminine voice is suddenly replaced by a much darker tone" 
			NOBODY HERE IS INNOCENT-
			-"Initiating pirate boarding protocols deadly force authorized"-
			What does that mean Lyssa! LYSSA YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
			You hear screams and weapon fire in the background before the recording cuts.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="darkl1">
		<text>
			PLEASE ENTER PASSWORD
		</text>
			<choice destination="darklog2" text="$Enter archive password">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="DARKLOG" value="2" />
			</choice>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
			<page ID="darklog2">
		<text>
			As you enter the password a list of missing personnel files pops up the terminal.
			However, one draws your attention due to the red blinking "live" symbol.
			Could it be? Someone is still alive out there?
		</text>
		<choice destination="darklog3" text="Access the live broadcast" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
		</page>

			<page ID="darklog3">
		<text>
			Your screen turns immediately dark as you turn on the live feed. 
			You first assumed that the system was malfunctioning, 
			but the camera interface clearly displays a blinking "live" in the upper corner of the interface. 
			In addition, you can hear a soft gurgle and sloshing emitting from the speakers. 
			You tap on the interface and countless options suddenly pop up.
		</text>
		<choice destination="darklog4" text="Press the symbol with the 3 spreading rows" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
		</page>

			<page ID="darklog4">
		<text>
			For a moment you see "manual override" written in green, pop up in the terminal screen, 
			before the screen flickers and suddenly springs to live, 
			it appears you just activated the cameras light function. You stare on the screen, 
			in an attempt to figure out what is going on. 
			The camera appears to be partially submerged and floating in what looks like white goo. 
			The screen shifts as the camera moves and spins in its creamy bath. 
			Every time the focus lens leaves the white goo you can see glistering pink flesh illuminated by the light. 
			Slowly you realize why this recording might have stayed active.
		</text>
		<choice destination="darklog5" text="Keep watching" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
		</page>

			<page ID="darklog5">
	<effect type="setglobalflag" flag="sodasupply" value="2" />
		<text>
			You keep watching the camera floating in its slimy entrapment, 
			after a while your ears get more sensitive to the sloshing and gurgling sounds emitting from the speakers, 
			it is almost like you can hear a heartbeat. You stare at the screen, strangely fascinated by the camera, 
			floating like an airballoon, until you suddenly notice what looks like an id card in the background. 
			In a surge of surprise, you slap the interface with your bare hand, accidently activating the zoom trigger. 
			You see the camera zooming closer. The object is indeed an id card, you see a smiling face of a lizzardlike person. 
			Other then that you can read "supply manager" and an imprinted code "83391". 
			You try to find more informations but the card suddenly shifts and sinks into the white goo.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="I should remember that - exit" />
	</page>

</Conversation>