<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
	<condition evaluate="LOCALFLAG" operator="equals" value="1"	flag="talked" />
		<text>
			GENETIC BAY 03 RESEARCH TERMINAL
			Welcome Dr. Halbei
			PLEASE REMBER TO LOGG OFF AFTER
			EACH SESSION TO PREVENT ACCOUNT
			ABUSE
		</text>
		<choice destination="info" text="Work directive G03" />
		<choice destination="info2" text="TO ALL EMPLOYEES!!" />
		<choice destination="info3" text="Access research log" />
		<choice destination="darkl1" text="Access G03 eventlog" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="darkl1">
		<text>
			PLEASE ENTER PASSWORD
		</text>
			<choice destination="darklog2" text="$Enter archive password">
				<condition operator="equals" evaluate="GLOBALFLAG" flag="DARKLOG" value="2" />
			</choice>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

			<page ID="darklog2">
		<text>
			You enter the password and access the emergency live broadcast.
			The screen springs to live and you see what appears to be Dr. Halbei, cowering in the corner of the room, as emergency sirens ring in the background. Suddenly the room is filled with an audible crack, as one of the ships ceiling tiles pop open, crashing to the ground with a loud clonk! Dr. Halbei screams in terror, as a pair of thick, blue tentacles appear from the hole in the ceiling, slowly descending towards the panicking scientist. "NO! Leave me alone! I never wanted this! I did not know! Please! AhHH!" You hear the scientist plead, before one of the tentacle wraps around his legs, swooping the scientist into the air, while the other tentacle positions underneath his head. Halbeis screams are quickly muffled, as the second tentacle parts, revealing a purple glowing mouth, quickly engulfing his head. The unknow beasts wastes no time, fully shoving the struggling scientist into its depths, gulping him down like a snake. You can see the squirming bulge of the former scientist slide up the tentacle, as it retracts back into the ceiling.
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="time to go back.." />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

		<page ID="info">
		<text>
			GENETIC BAY 03 DIRECTIVE
			CLASSIFIED DATA:
			AUTOMATIC REMOVAL
			SUCCESSFUL 
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info2">
		<text>
			Research supervision wants to inform you, that any kind of specimen interaction
			outside the normal research routine is STRICTLY FORBIDDEN!
			We can't afford to run reform-bay in overdrive because you can't contain
			yourself! Remember YOU ARE STILL DEALING WITH FERAL CREATURES, and the AI habitat
			surveillance AI makes sure that they are ALL well fed! YOU ARE PROFESSIONALS,
			so, act like professionals! – Lyssa Operative
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="info3">
		<text>
		There are countless entries in this terminal. However, one folder labeled "Important" draws your attention
		</text>
		<choice destination="log1" text="R 3004" />
		<choice destination="log2" text="R 3401" />
		<choice destination="log3" text="R 5221" />
		<choice destination="log4" text="R 5899" />
		<choice destination="log5" text="R 6001" />
		<choice destination="log6" text="R 6007" />
		<choice destination="start" text="back" />
	</page>

	<page ID="log1">
		<text>
		The recordings spring into life, a light scaled humanoid wearing glasses and a hazmat suit appear on screen. "Dr. Halbei, genetics, research log 3004, we managed to isolate traces of the plague, NATs test and Nano mapping have revealed that it was indeed artificial. T05 is working on a serum to re-create components. Most parts of the original formula appear to be lost, we will have to fill the gaps our self. That's all for the moment."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log2">
		<text>
		You see a scaled humanoid with glasses and a very dirty hazmat suit appear on screen, the background appears to be splattered with some kind of green goo. "Dr. Halbei, genetics, research log 3401, we are still working on T05s serum. Stabilizing it appeared to be... very challenging. Genotype 52, 54 and 55 developed a rather" He pauses for a moment and check the goo dripping walls. "...extreme reaction, to the new formula, we might run out of subjects if we continue in this pace. I will have to ask C02 for resupply, Halbei out." 
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log3">
		<text>
		A scaled humanoid with glasses wearing a lab coat appear on screen. "Dr. Halbei, genetics, research log 5221, T05s serum successfully stabilized, who would have thought that this imbecile from G02 knew the solution all along. The current form can be used to make ferals more receptive and intelligent enough to follow commands, we will continue to monitor the first uplifts and report accordingly, operation will now take over and complete the sequence. Halbei out"
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log4">
		<text>
		A scaled humanoid with glasses in a clean white lab coat appear on screen. "Dr. Halbei, genetics, research log 5899, uplifts are going according to plan genotype 137 and 155 appear to be very promising. Genotype 189... what did they called it again? Goo dragon? Anyway, Genotype 189 is still promising but even after neuro conditioning and gen therapy still appears to have a mind of its own. We work on bypassing this issue. That's all for now, Halbei out"
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log5">
		<text>
		You see a scaled humanoid in a lab coat setting up the recording before sitting back into his armchair.
		"Dr. Halbei genetics research log 6001 I.." You hear a ship door swooshing in the background as Halbei turns around to face the intruder. "what are you this classifie.." He can not finish the sentence before a scaly hand balled to a fist hits his face, shortly after, you can see the attacker following. A figure in a re-enforced lab coat quickly swipes trough the cameras view, tackling the doctor out of his armchair. You hear a fight breaking loose, followed by angry screams from the rooms corner. "YOU TRAITOR! YOU NEVER PLANNED TO CREATE A CURE YOU FOOLED US ALL!" undefined grunts fill the room as you hear the doctor speak up "Cedrick! Stop this right now, ugh, we, STOP, SECURITY!" The screen goes dark, as armed forces enter the room.
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="log6">
		<text>
		You see a scaled humanoid in a lab coat, his cheeks appear to be swollen and blisters cover his scaly face. "Dr. Halbei, genetics research log 6007, Lazarus has isolated what appears to be an egg in an unmapped sector. Scans indicate, that this egg might serve as some kind of containment field, as we can pick up traces of antimatter radiating from the inside, we will continue to monitor, Dr. Halbei out."
		</text>
		<choice destination="info3" text="back" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>
	
		<page ID="start">
	<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="talked" value="1" />
		<text>
			You turn on the terminal, an input prompt forces you to type in a password
		</text>
		<choice destination="search" text="search for a clue" />
	</page>

	<page ID="search">
		<text>
			You look around the terminal to find any kind of clue. After a few minutes you manage to find some dirty notes, on them a sticky note spelling PASSWORD in large letters
		</text>
		<choice destination="search2" text="type in PASSWORD" />
	</page>

	<page ID="search2">
		<text>
			ACCESS GRANTED
		</text>
		<choice destination="search3" text="No way..." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="search3">
		<text>
		You resist to face-palm on the spot as you resume with your prior plan
		</text>
		<choice destination="start" text="press Home" />
		<choice destination="end" text="exit" />
	</page>

</Conversation>