<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>The lamia is slumped in defeat, a heap of muscular coils and a
			dazed and panting feminine upper half lying before you. She watches
			your approach uncertainly, but certainly cannot resist if you were to
			take advantage of her in this state.</text>
		<choice destination="tailsex0" text="stick that tailtip somewhere">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="vagina" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="cockvore0" text="cockvore her">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore0" text="shove her up your ass">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />	
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="not interested right now" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore0">
	<text>
	The desire is naughty and yet thrilling as you consider how it'd feel to have all of this snakey woman sliding up your rear. The look on your face makes the lamia shrink back and hiss warningly as she seems to intuit what you're about to do. 		<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				She feels no reassurance as you expose your ass to her and approach.
			</conditional> The lamia lets out a threatening hiss as you grab her by her shoulder and head and squat over her. But the warning comes across as more amusing to you than anything else as you press your <macro ID="butt_size_desc" /> rear end into her face. Your ass muffling her protesting noises and humiliating her judging by the warmth of her cheeks. Her hands come up to shove at your hips and end this demeaning experience, but you're having none of that and indeed you've barely started on her..your hand curls round the back of her scalp and, shoves.... the lamia's head sliding into your rear with a schlurp and a redoubling of her squirming underneath you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore1" text="*take her...in*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore1">
	<text>
	You clench, and feel her shudder and thrash as you drag her head deeper into you. Her shoulders vanishing into your stretched pucker and her arms constrained by your hungry behind. She can grab your rear still, but no longer apply any force and soon she won't even be able to do that much as you drag her into your rear with muscular contractions alone. The lamia continuing to struggle around as she finds you dominating her with naught but your ass. Her breasts providing a pleasing bit of extra stretching to you as they slide on inside. Her tail is now thrashing and curling back and forth now, her writhing scaled shape spasming around energetically but without managing to stop you shoving the entirety of her feminine half into your ass. Soon that tail will join the rest of her inside of you.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore2" text="*all the way*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore2">
	<text>
	Your gut swells out steadily as you cram her inside. Her upper body squished deep within you and her hands pushing out at the inside of your belly forming bulges that cannot help but make you moan. Her powerful tail no match for your hungers as you continue dragging her in with rippling clenches, squeezing her body underneath the coils of her tail as your gut begins to bulge out massively with her compacted form. The last few feet of her tail twitching around and sliding up your rear end as you finish her off, her last few inches of tail pleasingly flicking back and forth against your rumpcheeks before it vanishes inside you. Every inch of her impressive form now squeezed and compacted within your belly. Her struggles and writhing coils making you groan in delight at being so stretched and filled by her.
	</text>
	<choice destination="analvore3" text="*and then you digested her*"/>
	</page>
	
	<page ID="analvore3">
	<text>
	Your gut knows just what to do with your ass meal. The serpent femme squirming around furiously as your insides gurgle and grind, taut stomach walls pressing hard over her body. Gradually you make headway, her struggles tiring and her form starting to soften and wear down. She lets out a whimper as the contours of her body in your belly start to lose their tight definition. And after that her digestion is comparatively rapid, her body suffused with enzymes she breaks down and starts to yield more and more to the pressure of your belly. Your gut rounding out and compacting, her noises silenced and overcome by your belly's hearty gurgles as she's mooshed down and absorbed. The lamia soon naught but a pleasant memory and even more pleasant sensation of strength and nourishment coursing through your veins.
	</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />	
	</page>

	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured your prey in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore0">
		<text>
			You can't help but think that long snakey tail would feel good
			sliding into a particularly...intimate, part of you. And so you
			approach her
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				, baring yourself from the waist down as you do so
			</conditional>
			and fondling that special part of yours. The lamia watching your
			stroking hand and the
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			length it holds with curiousity, unsure of your plans.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore1"
			text="time for your dick to taste her, tailfirst" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore1">
		<text>
			You bend forwards to scoop up her tailtip and feel her shift and
			coil
			uneasily. Then it's a simple matter to stick that tailtip in and
			the
			lamia's eyes widen and she writhes in resistance, but you seize
			firm
			her muscular tail a few feet above the tip and stop her from
			pulling
			away. Your shaft rippling and schlurping its way up the taper
			of her
			tail as you groan and look into her fearful gaze with a smirk.
			Your
			grip on her tail only helps to pull her deeper into you, working
			your
			hands up over her tail length and then pulling her deeper in with
			the
			help of your ravenous shaft.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore2"
			text="her struggles are for naught, show her her place" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore2">
		<text>
			The lamia struggles against your ravenous shaft, uncoiling to
			try and
			knock you off your feet but alas for her you see the move
			coming in
			time to step over those muscular coils. Your response of
			sucking in a
			few inches of her tail with no hands to show your
			superiority over
			her doesn't cow her though does get a hissing whine
			out of her as you
			feel her tail starting to pile and coil in your
			balls wonderfully.
			You can feel more and more of her wriggling
			serpentine body sliding
			down your shaft and as it does so the lamia's
			forced to straighten,
			having less tail to work with in her futile
			attempts to stop you she
			grabs ahold of the ground in desperation.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore3" text="conquer her with your cock" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore3">
		<text>
			But to no avail as you lean back and with a moan on your lips
			and
			squeelches from your tip you draw her in. Your rippling cock
			working
			up towards where her girlsome part begins, all of her tail
			writhing
			now in your balls and length as you draw her in. Your nuts
			sagging
			low and shifting with the movements of her tail even as she
			glances
			back at your expression and redoubles her effort to pull away,
			pulling chunks of plant detritus in her hands she lets out a
			despairing cry and feels her breasts and shoulders are pulled into
			your tip. The lamia unable to reach behind herself for purchase on
			your shaft and soon unable to reach the ground either as your mighty
			cock lifts her up and pulls her in. Her hands twitching and flailing
			about uselessly as soon they're all thats left outside of the snake
			lady.
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore4" text="finish her!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore4">
		<text>
			You look down at those flailing fingers and clench, pulling them
			inside.
			Your shaft bulging for only a little longer with her arms as
			they
			slither down to join the rest of her underneath the stroking of
			your
			hands. Your sack is massive now, hanging low past your knees and
			bloated with the mass of roiling lamia hissing and whining as she
			seeks to try and escape the cummy confines to which you have banished
			her. But there's no escape, not whole anyway, is there?
		</text>
		<choice destination="cockvore5" text="melt her!" />
	</page>

	<page ID="cockvore5">
		<text>
			There isn't, and you set about making that so. As you stroke
			your cock you
			feel your sack churn and hear the lamia squirm and hiss
			anew as she
			realizes what you're doing to her, turning all of that
			tail length
			and indeed the rest of her into a heaping load. The
			lamia's hands
			shoving out and her tail trying to uncoil and stretch
			your sack makes
			you groan but does nothing to help her escape. Instead
			the churning
			burbles of your balls only grow more pronounced as her
			struggles
			weaken and she begins to soften and succum. Her hissing
			whimpers
			overwhelmed by your gurgling balls now you feel her slow to
			stop and
			her motions taken over by the slosh of cum as she loses
			definition,
			spreading out into an immense load of jizz and giving you
			an
			incredible desire to let her loose. The lamia's form dissipating
			completely as you redouble your stroking and feel the pleasures and
			desires building...and then, unleashing.. the sensation of cumming
			out this load shuddering through you, going on and on as that mass of
			lamia turned cum erupts from your shaft to splatter on the ground.
			You can feel yourself starting to become faint as the orgasm roils
			through you, extended by each rocketing eruption of cum out of your
			shaft as your balls deflate steadily from their massive cum filled
			swollenness. The lamia forming an immense pool of jizz on the jungle
			floor as your climax prolongs yet longer before finally trailing off
			leaving you barely able to stand. You somehow manage to avoid
			faceplanting into the massive lamia puddle soaking into the
			leaflitter and take time to recover, and with that you should compose
			yourself and carry on leaving the reeking spunk pool to cool under
			the canopy.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

	<!--written by mac tavish -->
	<page ID="tailsex0">
		<text>
			With a haughty smirk,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				you undo your belt and drop trow,
			</conditional>
			then clamber atop the scaley pile, grabbing the end of her tail along
			the way, until you’re face-to-face with her. Your free hand goes to
			her chin, covering it with your palm as your fingers squeeze her
			cheeks and force her gaze downward, forcing her to watch as you
			thread her tail between your legs from behind and start grinding on
			it. This also serves, after a moment, to hide the silly expression on
			your face and your hunched neck and shoulders as you finagle the
			still-protesting appendage between your slickened labia.

		</text>
		<choice destination="tailsex1" text="ride the snake" />
		<choice destination="unbirth0" text="you want more than just the tip inside">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="tailsex1">
		<text>
			Once you’ve fed a good, sturdy amount of that smooth-scaled tail
			into
			your sopping sex, both of your hands are free to grab her by the
			shoulders, and you press your weight into her, making a rape-bed of
			her coils. Once some of the latter few inches are pinned under your
			crossed ankles behind you, you make sure you’re straddling her hips,
			then start moving yours, riding that length of squirming tail like so
			much cock.
		</text>
		<choice destination="tailsex2" text="proceed" />
	</page>

	<page ID="tailsex2">
		<text>
			Once you’re comfortable with the rhythm and certain of her
			submission,
			those tits of hers start looking like much more pleasant
			handholds,
			and your fingertips deeply dimple the supple flesh as you
			squeeze one
			roughly, her nipple grinding against your palm. The other
			hand moves
			between your legs to stimulate your clit, her own sex left
			ungraced
			by friction aside from the occasional brush of her own tail.
			When
			your orgasm finally comes, hers is still rising and, as cruelly
			as
			she surely would have treated you, had the tables been turned, you
			don’t even grant her that much, slipping up and off of her to re-gird
			your loins, leaving her desperate and mewling.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="who cares, you've had your fun" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth0">
		<text>
			After a few moments of enjoying the lamia’s wriggling struggles,
			the
			thought crosses your mind that you’d like a bit more than a few
			paltry inches of tail inside of you and, after eyeing the massive
			length of the girleater, you decide that there would be some poetic
			justice in indulging your perverse impulse. Rising slightly, you turn
			around and lie down on your victim’s body, a hand at the back of her
			head keeping it by yours so that she can stare down your body as you
			begin to draw hers in. Your vaginal walls pulse and ripple around her
			tail, which stretches them out the further up its taper you travel.
			Her eyes widen in horror, and her weak squirms under and in you only
			serve to stimulate you, drawing out moans from deep within your chest
			as you get your feet involved, gripping the tail between them and
			dragging it in, to feed the ever-growing, undulating bulge.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth1" text="suck her in" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth1">
		<text>
			Eventually, you run out of tail, and must lean forward.
			Thankfully, at this
			point, her upper body is close enough that you can
			hook your insteps
			over her shoulders. In that time, however, she
			manages to twist
			around onto her belly, the motion subsequently
			rolling the rest of
			her muscular coils around inside your loins as she
			starts clawing at
			the ground in a last-ditch effort to escape. But
			it’s too late, and
			there’s too much of her already trapped, at the
			mercy of your reverse
			contractions, and your folds are soon hugging at
			her waist, then her
			shoulders.
		</text>
		<choice destination="unbirth2" text="snake makes the best pussy food" />
	</page>

	<page ID="unbirth2">
		<text>
			The last the world ever properly sees of her, as the light
			shrinks in
			her sight, are her weakly-scrabbling fingers. After that,
			you’re free
			to nap where you are, folding your arms under your chin to
			elevate it
			above your bulging bed of flesh, which begins to squirm
			less and less
			as its occupant slowly loses oxygen. Then, stillness and
			quiet, as
			the walls of your womb squeeze mercilessly at the massive
			form,
			compacting it down and juicing it into sweet, feminine fluids.
			The
			final disappearance of the bump is preceded by your busy fingers
			finally being able to easily reach down there to get to work and is
			accompanied by your shrill cry and a clear, sticky spray that would
			make most firehoses jealous of its intensity.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="done making a mess of a snake" />
		<effect type="feed" value="120" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
	</page>

</Conversation>