<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<!--written by andrea_crawford -->
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>

			Entranced you stumble towards the shroom girl, who puts a hand
			against her
			mouth to hide a giggle at your clearly pheremone addled
			state.
			She seems so downright adorable as she looks up at you and
			licks her
			lips, parting them slowly to allow you a first glance
			inside.
			Her flesh is of a darker hue than her pale, grey skin, and
			moisture
			glistens on her tongue as you peer over it, towards the end
			of her
			mouth and the opening of her throat.
			You cannot help it, cannot
			resist the luring temptation an dip your
			fingers inside, feeling her
			lick over your hand - and your desire
			grows.
			You have to get inside.

		</text>
		<choice destination="down the hatch" text="So inviting..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="down the hatch">
		<text>

			The next giggle from the mushroom girl is a tad muffled, as your
			arms
			are wriggling their way down her throat, your fingers pushing
			aside
			the soft, wet flesh to make way for you.
			Gracefully her hands
			reach up to grasp your arms and aid you, to ease you down
			into her
			lithe, little body.
			Her throat stretches easily as you push deeper,
			squeezing first your
			head, then shoulders into it to follow the lead
			of your arms.
			LBREAK
			Even your breasts are no obstacle for the petite
			girl, as they are
			quickly compressed against your chest, sliding over
			her tongue and
			into her gullet in one quick move.
			Your feet leave the
			ground just as your hips are devoured, your butt
			bulging out the small
			cheeks of the mushroom girl for a moment,
			before a quite notable bulge
			trails down her neck to sink deeper into
			her body.
			While you want to
			keep your legs still to make it easier for the short
			female to devour
			you, your arousal-ridden mind has you squirm and
			twist inside her.
			But
			despite your accidental resistant, the young creature seems to be
			easily capable of handling a prey your side, and not long after you
			find yourself curled up inside her belly.
			LBREAK
			With a happy giggle
			and a stiffled hiccup from outside, you can feel her
			hands caressing
			you through the stretched skin.

		</text>
		<choice destination="swallowed" text="Finally inside..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="swallowed">
		<text>

			The mushroom girl continues her treatment, rubbing her hands
			over her
			massive gut, following your curves with her fingers as you
			press
			yourself against her gentle touch with need.
			Kneaded around by
			surprisingly strong stomach muscles, squished into the
			slippery
			surface of the grey, fleshy walls, you cannot help but moan.
			You can
			hear her giggling happily upon that, but when her gleeful
			noises get
			washed out by gurgling sounds around you, your head
			finally starts to
			clear.
			LBREAK
			Inside the mushroom girl's belly, you are out of reach
			for her pheromones
			and their effect wears off just in time.
			Taking in
			your surroundings with blinking, still lust-heavy eyes, you
			wonder
			what to make of this situation.
			Sure, you could try to fight back,
			struggle and squirm for all that it is
			worth - but is it really worth
			it?
			It is so cosy and warm in here, you are hugged to tight by the
			cutie's
			short, little form, and she seems so happy about you being
			there.
			Surely you do not want to disrupt this by selfish, rebellious
			behaviour?

		</text>
		<choice destination="digest" text="So comfy in here..." />
		<choice destination="struggle" text="Not this time!" />
	</page>


	<page ID="struggle">
		<text>

			Fun or not, you decide that your time in this belly is up.
			With
			her lithe, light-built frame, the young girl will hardly be able to
			put up any notable resistance on your way out, and you begin to flex
			your muscles.
			Well, when you do so.
			LBREAK
			In just a minute.
			LBREAK
			Any
			moment now.
			LBREAK
			Right after you fought off this amazingly cozy
			feeling of being inside
			her...
			LBREAK
			Blinking, you clear your head and
			redouble your efforts, weakly pushing
			against her dark flesh,
			stretching yourself.
			But then you slump back into the old position
			with another groan, as her
			stomach squelches and kneads around you.
			Turns out not her strength is what you will have to fight to get out
			of
			this, but instead the lustful feelings burning inside you,
			assaulting
			your pheromone-weakened mind.

		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="Must resist!" />
	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="WILLPOWER" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="escape" />
		<outcome destination="succumb" />
	</check>


	<page ID="escape">
		<text>

			The mushroom girl urks and lets out a whimper as you begin to
			push
			against her belly, almost causing you to cease your resistance.
			The poor girl.
			But no! You must not be considerate of her right now,
			or you will never
			escape.
			Steeling yourself, you push upwards, against
			the tiny opening at the top,
			where the entrance of her throat is
			located.
			LBREAK
			Moments later, you find yourself laying on the rocky
			cavern floor in a pool
			of mixed juices and body fluids, catching your
			breath.
			In the end, getting out of your predator was quite easy.
			After
			you had overcome your mental blockade, you were able to push up and
			out of her without much of a trouble.
			LBREAK
			Turning your head towards
			the mushroom girl, you take a look at your recent
			hostess.
			The petite
			girl is down on her knees, obviously much more exhausted from
			the
			ordeal than you.
			She still coughs and sputters on occasion,
			whimpering, pleading with her
			eyes for you to get back into her now
			empty belly.
			you feel a little bad for her, but not bad enough to go
			back to being
			mushroom food.

		</text>
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunNPC" value="10" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Get back to your feet, quick!" />
	</page>


	<page ID="succumb">
		<text>

			You shake your head and try to clear it, but with the soothing
			gurgles
			of the stomach around you, and the remainders the the
			pheromones
			still lingering in your system, it is hard to focus.
			The
			mushroom girl giggles and patpats her full belly, as your half
			hearted kicks and shoves make her middle jostle and sway - but to no
			avail.
			Your hands and feet slide off the slippery surface of the
			churning
			stomach walls, causing you to lose your weak grip every time,
			and
			your will to fight vanishes.
			Try as you might, you are unable to
			clear your mind from the tempting
			ideas to give in, and soon enough
			you stop your struggles and allow
			yourself to sink deeper into the
			fluids surrounding you.

		</text>
		<choice destination="food" text="Gurgle..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="digest">
		<text>

			You yawn and settle in, the mushroom girl murring as she rubs
			her belly
			and feels you doze within the cosyness of her gut.
			Her
			stomach gurgles softly around you, and you can feel its gentle
			embrace squeezing you over and over, working its digestive enzymes
			into your skin.
			But you do not mind.
			In the end, it is for a good cause
			- and she really is a cutie.

		</text>
		<choice destination="food" text="Gurgle..." />
	</page>


	<gameover ID="food">
		<text>

			Over what feels like a few hours, your whole form is squeezed
			and churned
			about, squelched into the juices sloshing around in the
			short girl's
			enlarget gut.
			You have long passed out when your
			previously clearly visible outlines
			begin to soften, and her noisily
			gurgling stomach adopts the form of
			a large and soft, round sphere.
			The mushroom girl giggles and stretches, her sloshy belly now
			gradually
			shrinking as your digested form is absorbed to feed her cute
			body.

		</text>
	</gameover>
</Conversation>