<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			You have defeated the mushroom girl, her frail body sprawled
			out on the floor before you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="You could use a snack.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="analvore1" text="She's shaped like a plug (AV).">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="study" text="Study her.">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/mushroomfolk.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="mushroomfolk" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="Devour her.">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Do nothing." />
	</page>
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified and unelaborated-on, yet
			surely satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<!--written by chardos, edited by Slayerhero90 -->

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			Smiling, you approach the defeated mushroom-girl, your growling
			stomach signalling its intent. Battered and momentarily unconscious,
			she is completely unaware of your approach. You lick your lips
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				as you disrobe,
			</conditional>
			before taking her petite feet in both hands, wiping the dirt off
			her soles, and gingerly placing them in your mouth for an
			experimental taste. It takes only a moment for her flavor to begin
			seeping onto your tongue, like a rich, nutty, earthy broth permeating
			your mouth, strengthening with every second you hold her there. While
			it is tempting to simply savor the moment, an insistent growl from your
			stomach reminds you that you have only just begun. So you push forward,
			the fungirl's savory legs effortlessly sliding down your throat while
			you blissfully run your tongue along her calves and thighs. You hardly
			even have to put any muscle into swallowing, slender as her legs are,
			and every gulp briefly lifts her prone figure off the ground a little
			more, until soon, she doesn't even touch the ground anymore. You also
			start to notice a weary frown occasionally crossing her face and while
			her legs begin to twitch in your throat. She must be waking up. For you,
			however, such movement only serves to spread her intense flavor across
			your tongue, the nuttiness getting a little stronger as you near her
			groin. You smile and continue forward, sealing the mushroom girl's fate
			without her even knowing.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Delicious." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			As you make your way closer to her breasts, you grab her hands and
			cram them in your mouth as well. Now, even if she fully awakens,
			you may continue to enjoy her without worry of physical resistance.
			Those spores might still be a problem, though, but you'll cross that
			bridge if you even get to it. Arms and legs now secured and her pucker
			inches from your mouth, you grin (as best you can) and grab her by her
			firm tush, lifting her whole body up in the air without breaking a
			sweat, all waiting to slide down your eager tongue. A strand of saliva
			escapes your maw as the shroom-girl's flavor takes on a sweeter
			note, perhaps like nectar. Then your eyes widen as a trickle of familiar,
			feminine fluid graces your tongue. Nectar could describe it, sure,
			as nectar comes from a flower, but in terms of flavor prifoles and
			euphemisms for that which seeps from a snatch, you'd sooner call
			this honey, dripping from a honeypot. With nothing but devious intent,
			you forcefully swallow another couple inches down to bring her
			within reach and twist her unconscious torso around until her front
			touches your tongue. Now that she's in position, you lick your
			tongue across her folds and plunge it into this unexpected
			treat, just as her feet finally plunge into your stomach.
			The mushroom girl awakens with a startled cry, confusedly moaning
			as she struggles to look around. Between your sly face around her
			crotch and your gleeful probing of her box, she's caught between
			fear and hesitant pleasure, and both are telling her to squirm
			helplessly in your mouth, limbs all locked in place and body
			still battered from your fight with her. Well, now that she's
			awake, it'd be in your best interest to hurrry this along, so,
			kicking your head back, you get back to swallowing her down,
			taking large swathes of her slender waist with every contraction
			of your muscles. The rest of her draws near.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreend" text="Going down." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreend">
		<text>
			Still enjoying yourself, you press your teeth into her pert breasts
			just a little bit as they enter your mouth, eliciting more
			confused moans from the mushroom-girl. Despite her initial reaction,
			she seems to be almost enjoying this. Or, at the very least, she
			understands she's not getting out of it. Now, with only her head and
			cap outside your mouth, you reach up and run a hand across her flushed
			cheek, momentarily calming her confused whimpers and moans. Fortunately,
			she doesn't seem too keen on blasting you with pheromones as you had
			initially surmised she might. Instead, slightly teary eyed, she locks
			eyes with you, silently pleading. Though, difficult as it may be to be
			certain, she seems to be begging you to keep going. You try your best
			to smile at her before grabbing her mushroom-cap with both hands and
			closing it over her head like an umbrella. Then, after a few forceful
			swallows, you finally send her on her way to your stomach. However,
			en route to your belly, her cap tries to flare out in your throat,
			almost causing you to choke, and definitely forcing you to lay your
			hands on the lump and push it down manually. Eventually, though, you
			manage to slowly slide it down and, at last, the girl curls up in your
			stomach. You give a contented sigh as your snack squirms inside you,
			still not fully ready to accept her place within your stomach as much as
			your stomach is more than ready to accept of her. You smile and rub your
			belly as its gurgles and groans begin to overpower her weak squirms and
			struggles, the shapes and bulges in your belly softening out and forming a
			single curve, before even that gradually shrinks away. Eventually, you
			can barely taste her in your burps anymore, so you lick your lips one last time,
			in a final attempt to savor the last of the mushroom-girl's flavors
			before continuing on your journey.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			You study the shroom-girl extensively, your scans collecting a large
			amount of data. Once you're done probing her, you mercifully give her
			the opportunity to scurry off.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="mushroomfolk" group="liforms0" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>

	<!--anal vore scene written by Slayerhero90 -->

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			You step forward and prop the shroom-gal butt-first and belly-up
			against a nearby stalagmite, still utterly conked-out. Then,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>
				after stripping out of your get-up, away, and kneeling down,
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>
				turning away and kneeling down,
			</conditional>
			you slip your feet beneath her back so you
			your heels keep her shoulderblades off the ground. All that remains
			for this peculiar system to be set up is for you to plant your hands
			firm on the ground, sidle your knees back, and lift your feet (and
			therefore the fungus-girl) just a bit higher, like orienting a missile
			to the heavens. Except this girl isn't aimed anywhere but your
			<macro ID="butt_size_desc"/>
			back-end.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2" text="Pop it in." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
			Chuckling to yourself to ease the thick suspense, you steel yourself
			and press your posterior dead-center against the mush-girl's
			amanita-esque cap. Of course, it's just a touch too big and wide to
			simply pop right through your pucker just like that. But you knew that.
			That's why you set her up against the rocky outcrop like this. And
			there's more fun to this way of eating than just the having-her-in-there
			part. You take one hand off the cavern floor to pull aside an ass-cheek
			while grinding your star against her crown, all slickened with
			cave-moisture. And then, suddenly, your backdoor parts with a
			resounding pop which almost successfully masks your gasp of surprise
			and pleasure and the clap of your ass against her shoulders. And, to
			make matters more complicated, a startled yelp sounds out from within
			your belly, so it looks like your buttplug's up. And it would seem
			her first reaction is to swing and flail her arms around. We can't have
			any of that, now, can we?
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore3" text="Push back." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore3">
		<text>
			Fortunately for you, her shoulders aren't nearly as broad as her
			cap. It's the arms that are gonna be a little tricky. You may
			have been willing to get violent to take this cutie-pie down,
			but that doesn't mean you wanna dislocate her shoulders and have
			her spend the rest of her life crying about it. So, taking your hands
			off the ground and your ass, you wait until the time is right to
			snatch her arms by the wrist before working your grip closer to her
			body, quickly binding her arms to the side. All that's left is to
			scoot back until your
			<macro ID="butt_size_desc"/>
			tush touches the stalagmite and you can let go, stand up, clench
			your asshole, and slurp the last of her dainty, kicking legs up.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvoreend" text="She's on her way now." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvoreend">
		<text>
			Your stomach's more than ready for her by the time she finishes her
			voyage through your guts, rumbling while it waited like an impatient
			child at a fancy restaurant. It doesn't take long at all for the
			shroom-girl to dissolve into soup and course through your innards,
			absorbed into fuel for your body.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

</Conversation>