<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!--written by andrea_crawford, edited by Slayerhero90 -->
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The mushroom girl is unable to fight anymore, propping herself
			up against the rocky cavern wall with her arm. You can tell she'd
			just collapse if she didn't something to lean on. Her narrow chest
			rises and falls with her horny panting, slender thighs rubbing against
			each other in a desperate attempt to satisfy her
			lust. The other arm stretches out in your direction, the enthralled
			fungirl pleading at you with her eyes to do something with her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Just a little taste...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="analvore1" text="Let her in through the backdoor.">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="Study her.">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/mushroomfolk.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="mushroomfolk" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="Devour her.">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="Do nothing." />

	</page>
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified and unelaborated-on, yet
			surely satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			You study the shroom-girl extensively, your scans collecting a
			large amount of data. Once you're done probing her, you benignly
			give her the opportunity to scurry off.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="mushroomfolk" group="liforms0" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Time to do some research." />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			In just a few steps, you stand at her side. If it's pleasure she
			wants, you have just the right thing for this cavern beauty.
			Pressing yourself against her, you pin her ash-skinned body against the
			wall, soaking in the faint heat radiating from her lithe, little body.
			Your lips inch closer to hers and she lowers her eyes, bottom lip
			trembling with anticipation. You can smell her arousal, her need.
			LBREAK
			But you do not kiss her. Instead, you stop just an inch before
			you'd touch her, wrapping an arm around her slender waist to pull
			her even closer against your body, and in turn, she raises one of
			her shapely legs to rub its calf against you. "I'm going to eat you."
			you whisper to the underside of her cap, tasting a hint her spores as
			you speak, and she nods in response. There is no denial in her eyes,
			just lust and eager desperation, as she raises her slender hands to your lips.
			At this point, she does not care anymore how you satisfy her lust.
			If you are to devour her, she shall be more than willing to go
			along with that.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Let's not keep her waiting." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			Smooth and quick, her slim, gray-green digits slide past your lips,
			over your tongue, and into your throat. She very, very eager to
			get herself into your body. Still shifting from one foot onto the
			other to try and get some pleasure out of the friction of her thighs,
			the shroom-girl raises onto the tips of her cute, little toes and she
			bows her vermilion-capped head between her arms. You sample her
			earthy flavor as you hold her by the hips and stretch your mouth
			over her skinny arms and broad hood; a light, earthy aroma with a
			note of nut. Hoisting her off the ground to take her in further,
			the fungirl gasps and kicks her feet back in surprise,
			but the gentle gasp soon turns into a breathed moan as you
			cup her rump in your hands and squeeze, providing you the
			anchor you need to pop her cap through your lips and into your
			mouth. With such a large protrusion on her head, the beginning
			of the process is a bit more difficult than usual, but nothing you
			can't handle. Quickly and without gagging, you shove the girl's cap
			down your throat, where your esophageal muscles can swallow just fine,
			and soon, trembling with need in your grip, ease the rest of her
			arms im, past the shoulders. Next up: breasts.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="Perky and firm." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>
			As her B-cups squeeze past your lips, flattened against her chest,
			you take a moment to close your eyes and moan, vibrating your
			around the mushroom girl. Though far from anything you'd call big,
			they're so firm and ridiculously full of flavour. It feels as though
			her nipples leave a trail of delightfully ruptured taste-buds in
			their wake, over your tongue, towards your throat. You lap
			your tongue against them as best you can with a mouth full of
			her, eager to get the most out of this experience. She writhes
			in your arms at the sensation, moaning deeply in your throat,
			and you are sure that she at least by now regrets that she presented
			her hands first. Unable to reach the flower between her legs, she
			squirms and kicks harder, trying to bring it closer to your
			tongue, or at the very least try and do something about her nether
			itch. It's charming enough to bring the best attempt you can at a
			smile onto your body-plugged lips, as you watch rivulets of her juice
			and your saliva tail down her legs.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4" text="Time for the juicy part." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore4">
		<text>
			Her hips pose no obstacle whatsoever and you suck them into
			your mouth like mushroom soup from a spoon. Unfortunately, it is
			at this point you must let go of her firm ass and hold her up by the
			knees instead. And on entering your mouth, she immediately begins to
			grind her meaty crotch against your tongue, and you nearly choke on
			a chuckle as you hear her cry out with lust deep inside you.
			The sweet taste of her nectar mingles with its heavenly aroma, and for a
			brief moment you consider coughing her up so you can give her box
			a proper licking. But you are much too eager to get her inside you now,
			and your growling stomach reminds you who's calling the shots here.
			LBREAK
			Eh. You can afford to take a few more minutes to sample her femcum,
			jumping between digging the tip of your tongue as deep into her pussy
			as it can go and scraping the muscle over her labia. But that's enough;
			you're hungry. A desperate cry of frustration is heard from below when you
			finally swallow, sending the young woman's hips down your throat as a
			very lively, squirming bulge.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore5" text="Devour her completely." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore5">
		<text>
			With her slim hips and cute little rump gone, only the slender legs
			of the mushroom girl remain un-gobbled up. But now she squirms much
			more actively, struggling and kicking in your grasp, trying anything
			to speed up her descent into your waiting gut. Luckily for her, you
	`		do not intend to keep her waiting. Tilting your head back, you swallow
			her legs with only a couple quick, short gulps. Within moments, her
			thighs vanish behind your lips, soon followed by her knees and shapely
			calves. Even her feet, studded by those adorably wiggling toes, do not
			linger in front of your hungry lips for more than a couple seconds,
			snapping them up with ease. One last swallow sends the girl finally
			down into your distended gut, and you breathe a deep sigh of relief.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreend" text="Make her a part of you." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvoreend">
		<text>
			Leaning against the cavern wall, you wipe your forehead with the
			back of your arm, panting heavily as the mushroom-girl settles in
			your belly. You can feel her shift and turn wildly in there, trying
			her best to get herself off, now that her hands have access to all
			of her body again. The girl has a few moments to busy herself
			before the gurgling and churning noises that indicate the start of
			digestion roar up. It doesn't seem to bother your prey at all, however,
			and she keeps up her activities as you rub your bloated belly,
			moaning quietly at the pleasant feelings. After a while, she
			finally quiets down within you, and the outlines of your
			stretched-out gut begin to soften. It takes the good part of an hour
			before you can comfortly move again, picking up your belongings
			and continue through the caves. That sure was a delicious encounter.
			Hopefully, all encounters with these shroomfolk end as
			pleasantly as this.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

	
	<!-- anal vore section completely written by Slayerhero90 -->

	<page ID="analvore1">
		<text>
			You smile at the thought as you saunter over to the
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>
				mushroom-girl, pausing to shed your clothing. The delay
				evokes a whine of desperate need from her mouth, until you suddenly
			</conditional>
			<conditional>
				<assertnot evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2"/>
				mushroom-girl. Then, suddenly, you
			</conditional>
			bob forward and plant a kiss on her charcoal-lipped mouth.
			She practically melts on the spot, collapsing squarely onto her tush,
			just as you were about to help her down yourself. Then, pulling back
			from the kiss, you turn around, slip your fingers into the brim of her
			cap to hold her in place, and take gingerly take a seat. You can't see
			her face to gauge how she feels about this, but if the fact she hasn't
			made a fuss about it yet means anything, then she seems to be down with
			it as much as you are. Which is good, because you don't plan on standing
			back up until this girl's all the way inside your derriere.	
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore2" text="Shift your weight around." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore2">
		<text>
			The moment your squat turns into a sit atop the pliant cap, it's like a meaty,
			two-foot-wide cock just pressing against your pucker, provoking a gasp of sudden
			delight from you and a soft whimper from the girl below. You hope you're not too
			heavy for her. You're pretty
			<macro ID="body_weight_desc"/>,
			after all. It's not long before she starts squirming under your weight, and,
			moistened by the natural moisture of these caves, the cap starts pressing deeper
			into your
			<macro ID="butt_size_desc"/>
			posterior. Looks like you're getting her in there sooner rather than later.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore3" text="Help her out." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore3">
		<text>
			Your reply to her antsiness is to clutch your ass-cheeks and spread them as
			wide as you can. And soon, with a great, loud, wet pop, her whole head bursts
			through your back-door. The shroom-girl yelps in surprise and as you briefly
			lose your footing and tilt your body forward, you can't help but moan at the
			delightful feeling of
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis"/>
				her cap prodding at your walnut and
			</conditional>
			her cool skin rubbing up against your warm guts. Now you sit upon her shoulders,
			but, between their narrowness and the lubrication your intestinal juices
			provide, that lasts for little more than a second, and you slip all the way
			down to her spread thighs, her head protruding from your abdomen.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore4" text="Just a little bit more..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="analvore4">
		<text>
			You pat her on the head for her cooperation before leaning onto your side,
			propped up by your elbow, and working the muscles that govern your rectum
			to tug the rest of her in. It takes a couple squeezes on her ashy thighs,
			each engulfing only a few inches, before you hit the tapering in her legs
			just before thighs become knees and all the matters of physics line up just
			perfectly in order to slurp up the entire remaining span of her body-- calves,
			feet, and curled-up toes-- all in one go. Your starfish seals back shut, locking
			the girl in.
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvore5" text="One way road." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvore5">
		<text>
			Sitting back up, you give your bulging belly a hug before resting your head
			against the cavern wall and letting your body do the rest. Constrained by the
			coils of your intestines, there's simply no way for her to properly pleasure herself
			until she finishes her journey to your stomach, and so you get several minutes to
			your own relaxation before your belly starts shifting anew, the shroom-gal finding
			a comfy position and launching into her fun. From her confines, you hear her bring
			herself to moaning again and again until soon, the gurgling of your stomach drowns
			her cooing out. 
		</text>
		<choice destination="analvoreend" text="We know how this ends." />
	</page>

	<page ID="analvoreend">
		<text>
			Burping every now and then, your belly and the girl inside start to round out
			and soften up, her contours vanishing more every minute. And once she's finished
			melting into a ball, once you've made her into mushroom soup, your stomach takes
			to shrinking as the slurry trickles back the way it came, this time getting absorbed
			by your villi instead of allowed safe passage. When all's said and done, your burps
			smell like mushroom soup and you feel so much more sated.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>

</Conversation>