<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!--written by andrea_crawford -->
	<page ID="start">
		<text>

			The mushroom girl is unable to fight anymore, leaned against the rocky
			cavern wall with a hand.
			Her little chest raises and falls with her panting, her slender thighs
			rubbing against each other in a desperate attempt to satisfy her
			lust.
			The other arm stretched out in your direction, the enthralled, young
			little thing pleades to you with your eyes.

		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="Do nothing." />
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Just a little taste...">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/mushroomfolk.xml" />	
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="mushroomfolk" />
		</choice>
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			you study the mushroom extensively, your scans collecting a large amount
			of data. You benignly give the mushroom girl a chance to scurry off
			now you're done probing her.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="mushroomfolk" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>

			With just a few steps, you are at her side.
			If it is pleasure she wants, you have just the right thing for this
			cavern beauty.
			Pressing yourself against her, pinning the grey skinned girl against the
			wall, you can feel the heat radiating from her lithe, little body.
			Your lips inch closer to hers and she lowers her eyes, the female's
			bottom lip trembling with anticipation.
			You can smell her arousal, her need.
			LBREAK
			But you do not kiss her.
			Instead, you stop just an inch before you would touch her, wrapping an arm
			around her slender waist to pull her even closer against your body
			and she raises one of her shapely legs to rub its calf against you.
			"I am going to eat you." you whisper - and she nods in return.
			There is no denial in her eyes, just lust and eager desperation, as she
			raises her slender hands to your lips.
			At this point, she does not care anymore how you satisfy her lust.
			If you are going to devour her, she seems to be more than willing to go
			along with that.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="Let's not keep her waiting..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>

			Smooth and quick her slim, grey digits slide past your lips, over your
			tongue and into your throat.
			She seems eager, very eager to get herself into your body.
			Still shifting from one foot onto the other to try and get some pleasure
			out of the friction of her thighs, the mushroom girl raises onto the
			tips of her cute, little toes as she bends her head with the bright
			red cap between her arms.
			You sample her flavour as you hold her by the hips and stretch your
			mouth over her arms and the large hood, experiencing a light, earthy
			aroma with a nuttily note.
			LBREAK
			Hoisting her off the ground to take her in further, the short female gasps
			and kicks her feet back in surprise, but the gentle gasp soon turns
			into a breathed moan as you squeeze her rump into your hands - and
			then her head into your mouth.
			With the large hood on top, the beginning is a bit more difficult than
			usual. But nothing you cannot handle.
			Shoving the girl further in, trembling in your hands with need, you envelop
			the rest of her arms, then the shoulders.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore3" text="Perky and firm..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore3">
		<text>

			When her small breasts are squeezed past your lips alongside her chest,
			you close your eyes and moan, causing your throat to vibrate around
			the mushroom girl.
			They are far from big, but so firm and full of flavour.
			It feels as if her nipples leave a trail of exploded taste buds in
			their wake over your tongue on the way to your throat, and you press
			the fleshy muscle against them, eager to get the most out of this
			experience.
			LBREAK
			The girl writhes in your grasp in response, moaning deeply in your
			throat, and you are sure that she at least by now regrets to have
			started with her hands.
			Unable to reach the sweet-smelling spot between her legs, the young female
			squirms and kicks her legs, eager to get it closer towards your
			tongue.
			You smile around her midriff at her reaction, watching small rivulets of
			her juices trailing down her legs.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore4" text="Time for the juicy part..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore4">
		<text>

			Her hips to not pose much of an obstacle, and you suck them into your
			mouth with ease, holding up her slightly spread legs by the knees.
			The grey skinned girl immediatedly begins to grind her crotch against
			your tongue, and you nearly choke on the chuckle as you hear her cry
			out with lust deep inside you.
			The sweet taste of her nectar mingles with its heavenly aroma, and for a
			brief moment you consider coughing her up so you can give this little
			box a proper licking.
			But you are too eager to get her inside you now, and your growling
			stomach reminds you of who is calling the shots here.
			LBREAK
			Still, you allow yourself a few more minutes to sample her delicious
			femcum, digging the tip of your tongue as deep into her pussy as it
			will go, before switching back to rubbing over her labia with your
			slippery muscle.
			A desperate cry of frustration is heard from below when you finally
			swallow, sending the young woman's hips down your throat as a very
			lively, squirming bulge.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore5" text="Devour her completely..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore5">
		<text>

			With her hips and the cute, little rump now gone, only the slender legs
			of the mushroom girl remain to be gobbled up.
			But now she is squirming more actively, struggling and kicking in your
			grasp, trying anything to speed up her descent into your waiting gut.
			Luckily for her, you do not intend to keep her waiting.
			LBREAK
			Tilting your head back, you begin to swallow her legs with quick, short
			gulps.
			Within moments her thighs vanish behind your lips, soon followed by her
			knees and well-curved calves.
			Even her feet with those cute, wiggling toes do not linger in front of
			your hungry lips for long, and you snap them up with ease.
			One last swallow sends the girl finally down into your distended gut,
			and you breathe a deep sigh of relief.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreend" text="Make her a part of you..." />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvoreend">
		<text>

			Leaning against the cavern wall, you wipe your forehead with the back of
			your arm, panting heavily as the mushroom girl settles inside your
			belly.
			Well, that was a delicious encounter for sure.
			You can feel the short female move around in there, most likely trying
			her best to get herself off - now, where her hands have access to all
			of her body again.
			LBREAK
			You give the girl a few moments to busy herself, before gurgling and
			churning noises indicate the start of digestion.
			It does not seem to bother your prey at all however, and she keeps up
			her activities even as you rub your hands over your bloated belly,
			moaning quietly at the pleasant feelings.
			LBREAK
			After a while she finally quiets down within you, and the outlines of your
			stretched gut begin to soften.
			It takes the good part of an hour before you can comfortly move again,
			and you pick up your belongings to continue your journey.
			Hopefully, all encounters with the mushroom folk will end as pleasant as this.

		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="100" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>
</Conversation>