<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>

	<page ID="start">
		<text>You have defeated the mushroom girl, her little body slumped
			before you</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="You could use a snack">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>

		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/mushroomfolk.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="mushroomfolk" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="do nothing" />
	</page>
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>


	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<!--written by chardos -->
		<text>

			Smiling, you approach the defeated mushroom girl, your growling
			stomach
			signalling its intent. Battered and momentarily unconscious,
			the petite mushroom
			girl is completely unaware of you
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				licking your lips while disrobing, before
			</conditional>
			taking her feet in both hands and gently placing them in your mouth
			for an experimental taste.
			A moment of confusion passes as you try to
			detect her flavor before it slowly begins seeping into
			your mouth and
			across your tongue. A contented moan escapes from you as her earthy
			richness
			begins to permeate your mouth, strengthening the longer you
			hold her there. While it is tempting
			to simply savor the moment, a
			more insistent growl from your stomach reminds you that you have
			only
			begun.
			LBREAK
			The mushrooms girl's legs begin effortlessly sliding down
			your throat as you blissfully push forward, hardly
			having to swallow
			as her prone figure is briefly lifted from the ground before
			descending down your throat. You realize
			she must be waking up as you
			barely notice a weary frown cross her face and her legs begin to
			twitch
			in your throat. Such movement serves only to spread her
			gradually intensifying flavor across your tongue and
			you begin to
			notice a nutty aftertaste as you work closer to her waist. You smile
			to yourself as you
			continue forward, sealing the mushroom girl's fate
			without her even knowing.

		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="delicious" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>

			You grab her hands and put them in your mouth as well, now even
			if she awakens you can enjoy her
			with no worry. Her arms and legs now
			secured, you grin as you clutch her firm butt, lifting her waist
			towards your eager tongue. A strand of saliva escape your maw as the
			mushroom girl's flavor takes on a sweeter
			note...perhaps like nectar?
			Your eyes widen as a trickle of feminine fluid touches your tongue.
			No,
			not nectar...you've come upon a honeypot. Grinning devilishly, you
			forcefully swallow to bring this new flavor
			within reach, you give a
			firm lick across it and plunge your tongue into this unexpected
			treat...just as
			her feet finally plunge into your stomach.
			LBREAK
			The
			mushroom girl awakens with a startled cry, confusedly moaning as she
			struggles to look around. Seeing
			your grinning face around her waist
			and gleefully probing her sparks an expression of fear, but she can
			do
			nothing but helplessly squirm with both legs and arms locked in
			your mouth and still battered as she is
			from your battle. Any sense of
			stealth lost at this point you stand up, lifting her torso with you,
			and
			resume swallowing, easily sending her hips and slender waist down
			as the rest of her drawn near.


		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvoreend" text="going down" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvoreend">
		<text>
			Still enjoying yourself, you chomp on her pert breasts a bit as
			they enter your mouth, eliciting more
			confused moans from the mushroom
			girl. Despite her initial reaction, she seems to be almost enjoying
			this.
			Or at the very least she understands she's not getting out of
			it. With now only her head and mushroom
			cap outside your mouth, You
			reach up to her and run a hand across a flushed cheek, momentarily
			calming her
			confused whimpers and moans. Slightly teary eyed, she
			gazes at you as you try your best to smile at her,
			before grabbing her
			mushroom cap with both hands and closing it over her head like an
			umbrella. You forcefully
			swallow a few more times and finally send her
			on her way to your stomach.
			LBREAK
			Her mushroom cap flares out in your
			throat, almost causing you to choke, and definitely forcing you to
			take a few large gulps. It proves no problem though, eventually it
			slowly slides down and the mushroom
			girl is forced to curl up in your
			stomach. You give a contented sigh as your snack squirms inside you,
			still not fully ready to accept her place within your stomach, though
			your stomach is fully accepting of her.
			You smile and rub your belly
			as the gurgles and groans begin to overpower the squirms and
			struggles. The
			shapes and bulges in your belly soften out and form a
			single curve before even that gradually shrinks away.
			You lick your
			lips in a final attempt to get the last of the mushroom girl's flavor
			before continuing on your
			journey.

		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="110" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			you study the mushroom extensively, your scans collecting a
			large amount
			of data. You benignly give the mushroom girl a chance to
			scurry off
			now you're done probing her.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="10" data="mushroomfolk" group="liforms0" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>

</Conversation>