<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<page ID="start">
		<text>
			The raptor girl chirrs at lustfully at your approach, rubbing
			her thighs
			together. It's clear from the sweet nectar of her loins
			you've
			enthralled her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="study" text="study her">
			<assertnot evaluate="hasEntry" entry="lifeforms/raptor.xml" />
			<assertnot evaluate="hasResearch" research="raptor" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="sex0" text="have sex with her">
			<assertion evaluate="haspart" part="penis" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="she looks tasty">
			<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="capture" text="Use you capture device.">
			<condition evaluate="HASITEM" operator="greaterthan" value="1"
				item="capture device" />
		</choice>		
		<choice destination="devour" text="devour her">
			<assertion evaluate="operatorOr">
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="oralvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="cockvore" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="unbirthing" />
				<assertion evaluate="hasperk" perk="analvore" />
			</assertion>
		</choice>
		<choice destination="end" text="leave her be" />
	</page>

	<page ID="study">
		<text>
			You study and probe the raptor in a thorough and probably rather
			disagreeable way, the data you've collected should be very valuable.
		</text>
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<special effect="research" DC="12" data="raptor" />
		<choice destination="end" text="time to do some research" />
	</page>		
	
	<page ID="devour">
		<text>
			You have devoured her in some unspecified, unelaborated on yet
			satisfying way.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="carry on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="capture">
		<effect type="setlocalflag" flag="seduced" value="1" />
		<special effect="captureNPC" />
		<text>Yoink. The device worked.</text>

		<choice destination="end" text="Carry on." />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			The raptor girl watches you approach with hazy, lustful eyes. You open
			your mouth and point to it, making your intentions clear, and to your
			surprise, this elicits a moan from the aroused young raptor woman.
			She leans forward and presses her face right onto your tongue. Your
			mouth explodes with her delectable flavor. Her scales are slick and
			smooth and they taste divine as she eagerly rubs her cheek on your
			tongue. She doesn’t protest as you bring your jaws all around her
			head and your lips press around her neck. You hear soft, pleasured
			cooing sounds coming from inside your mouth as she willingly lets
			herself be devoured.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="Swallow her" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			You take her shoulders in your hands and lift. Her head tilts directly
			into your throat. You begin to gulp her down, aided by gravity. The
			raptor girl seems to realize what’s happening. You feel some
			half-hearted squirms from within your throat. She wriggles her arms,
			pinned to her sides by your mouth, and her legs kick a bit, tail
			swishing this way and that, but as your tongue reaches her mound she
			moans out loud. Her body quakes, then relaxes, giving in to you
			entirely. You slurp her legs and tail together like one big noodle
			and gulp them down. She settles in your stomach. You soon begin to
			feel some shifting inside. A few muffled moans from within confirm
			that she’s pleasuring herself inside you.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="digest her" />
		<choice destination="oralvore2disposal" text="waste her">
		<preference fetish="disposal" />
		</choice>
		<choice destination="oralvore2Endo" text="let her finish, then let her out" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			You sit back and begin to work her down. The moans only get louder as
			your stomach fills with deadly digestive acids. She kicks and writhes
			and cries out in ecstasy. You see bulges form on your stomach where
			her legs and elbows push out. Her moans reach a peak as the acids
			begin to eat away at her scales. Soon, she’s no longer moving inside
			you. You churn and grind her body until your bulgy stomach begins to
			smooth and round out, your prey liquefying until she’s nothing but
			digestive mush, her body used up to fuel yours.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="delicious, moving on" />
	</page>
	
	<page ID="oralvore2disposal">
		<text>
			You sit back and begin to work her down. The moans only get louder as
			your stomach fills with deadly digestive acids. She kicks and writhes
			and cries out in ecstasy. You see bulges form on your stomach where
			her legs and elbows push out. Her moans reach a peak as the acids
			begin to eat away at her scales. Soon, she’s no longer moving inside
			you. You churn and grind her body until your bulgy stomach begins to
			smooth and round out, your prey liquefying into a mushy soup of nutrients
			that slid down through your bowels, nourishing and fueling your body, helping
			expand your curves in all the right ways, before finally reaching the end of her
			journey through your gut, collecting in your ass as a pressing need to poop.
			With a sigh, you squat down next to a nearby bush, your ass cheeks spreading apart
			as you started squeezing out several logs of brown muck, the thick turds laced with 
			bits of the raptor girl's scales and bones, soon to be washed away and used to fertilize
			the lands.
		</text>
		<effect type="feed" value="95" />
		<special effect="removenpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="delicious, moving on" />
	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2Endo">
		<text>
			You sit back, allowing her to continue her blissful pleasure. You can
			feel wriggling and bucking within you, and every so often you’ll hear
			a high pitched moan of ecstasy. You begin to rub at your stomach,
			helping her along, and her moans in response let you know this is
			exactly what she wants. You continue to rub and knead at her, feeding
			her pleasure, until her moans begin to rise in pitch, turning into
			all out cries. She’s reaching her summit. You wrap your arms around
			your stomach and squeeze her. In moments she reaches her climax and
			an explosion of femcum erupts into your stomach. She cries out loud,
			then heaves for breath, slumping within you. She lovingly rubs your
			inner walls as her orgasm slowly fades. You then bend forward and
			begin to cough her up. Soon, the raptor girl splats onto the ground
			in front of you, slick with your inner juices. She beams up at you in
			wordless thanks.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<choice destination="end" text="well that was fun" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex0">
		<text>
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				Pausing only to undress before getting down to business
			</conditional>
			you present your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft to the raptor, stroking it to hardness and looking at her and
			it suggestively. There's no way to convey your desire to her with
			words, but it so matches her own desires, dropping down onto all
			fours she looks over her shoulder at you and raises her tail. An
			invitation you'd be a fool not to take up, grasping her tail with one
			hand and your length with the other as you settle in behind her.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex1" text="give the needy slut what she wants" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<condition operator="greaterthan" evaluate="BODYVALUE"
			bodypart="penis" partvalue="length" value="18" />
		<text>
			You tease for only a bit of time before working your ample
			endowment
			into her, the raptor letting out a gasping chirr as she's
			stretched
			out but rocking her hips back to meet yours even if you're
			stretching
			her so much your dick can be seen on her belly like a coke
			can under
			a blanket. Her tail curls around your waist as you set your
			hands on
			her hips, then start to thrust urged on by her movements and
			delighted chirrings. Soon you're falling into a rthythm of mutual
			pleasure, rutting her vigorously as she animalisticly coaxes you to
			ever greater feats of penetration.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="fill her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex1">
		<text>
			You tease for only a bit of time before working your hard cock
			into her,
			the raptor letting out a gasping chirr as she's you fit
			snugly within
			her and rocking her hips back to meet yours, clenching
			around your
			cock eagerly with her nethers. Her tail curls around your
			waist as
			you set your hands on her hips, then start to thrust urged on
			by her
			movements and delighted chirrings. Soon you're falling into a
			rthythm
			of mutual pleasure, rutting her vigorously as she
			animalisticly
			coaxes you to ever greater feats of penetration.
		</text>
		<choice destination="sex2" text="fill her up" />
	</page>

	<page ID="sex2">
		<text>
			It's too much, the lusty reptile pushing you over the edge as you
			feel her gasping and squeezing down on your cock in climax. Your
			<macro ID="penis_size_desc" />
			shaft erupting inside her nethers, filling her with the hot cum she
			craved so deeply. The reptile gasping and murring as you pump her
			full of cum and she clenches, milking you until you're done and pull
			out of her. The raptor mhmming, flush with afterglow as she slides a
			hand down between her legs then brings it up to her lips to taste
			your seed. She seems remarkably well pleased with your prowess.
		</text>
		<special effect="nonhostile" />
		<special effect="healnpc" />
		<choice destination="end" text="it's the best way to make friends" />
	</page>

</Conversation>