<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Conversation>
	<!-- <page ID="start"> <preference fetish="analvore"/> <condition operator="lessthan" 
		evaluate="DICEROLL" value="10"/> </page> -->
	<page ID="start">
		<preference fetish="oralvore" />
		<text>
			The raptor girl looms over you, cocking her head to the side and
			licking her lips as she regards your prone form. Her movements are
			flighty and she hisses darting forwards as you move, but upon
			realizing the fight has truly been taken out of you she smiles. The
			raptor girl bounding forwards to land in a squat,
			<conditional>
				<assertion evaluate="slothasitem" slot="2" />
				yanking off your foot coverings
			</conditional>
			and lifting both feet to her lips. That long reptilian tongue lapping
			over your toes teasingly and she makes an exaggerated chirring sound
			as if teasing, tightening her grasp on your ankles when you try to
			pull away.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore0" text="raptor food" />

	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore0">
		<text>
			Your feet go in and this time the chirring isn't feigned as the raptor
			savours your feet. She half closes her eyes with her lips wrapped
			around your ankles, but her eyes snap open again as you try to pull
			back and her hands snap forwards to grasp your legs and pull you
			towards her. Your reptilian predator starting to take hearty eager
			gulps, cramming your feet down her throat and working her way up your
			legs. That lean body clearly hungry for the coming meal as you feel
			her belly growl just beneath your feet before they're plunged inside.
			Her hands alternating up towards your waist as your legs disappear
			past her lips and down her throat, starting to swell out her middle
			with the bulges of your feet visibly pressing out her belly.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore1" text="rest of the way" />

	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore1">
		<text>
			It doesn't take her long to take in your thighs, lips around your waist
			she straightens up leaving your upper body at an angle. Her tail
			swaying in delight and her belly bulging with the curled up shape of
			your legs. From here it's a simple matter to eat the rest of you
			despite your struggles and protests, her hands hoisting you up and
			feeding you in. That greedy gullet claiming your middle and chest
			before forcing your arms above your head, in desperation you splay
			them against the hungry tug of her throat, but know it will buy you
			but a little time with your vision framed by the red encompassing
			mouth of the femme lizard. Her swallows are thwarted, dragging around
			your saliva soaked upper body but making no headway, a reprieve of
			but a few moments.
		</text>
		<choice destination="oralvore2" text="swallowed completely" />

	</page>

	<page ID="oralvore2">
		<text>
			You see through the gap of her jaws her hands reach up, forcing your
			arms together and dislodging them as she takes a final swallow. The
			raptor girl letting out a long drawn out chirr of pleasure that
			sounds in your ears along with her gulps as your head slides down her
			throat. Your hands the last of you to go being schlurped up past her
			lips and forming a bulge that disappears past her neck swiftly as
			you're utterly devoured. As this happens your predator sits down
			comfortably and rests both hands on her now massively distended and
			domed out orange belly. Your form made to curl up helplessly within
			her gut as it gurgles softly in welcome around you, that chirr of
			delight from feeling so full not letting up as it comes from the
			raptor who ate you. You could try taking advantage of that, or maybe
			struggling free.
		</text>
		<choice destination="struggle" text="struggle" />
		<choice destination="pleasure" text="pleasure" />
		<choice destination="submit" text="submit" />
	</page>

	<page ID="struggle">
		<text>
			You can feel her chirring triumphantly, but you're not beaten yet. You
			start kicking up a fuss within her, trying to unsettle that gurgling
			gut and force her to disgorge your struggling form. The muscular
			flesh pressing around you yielding slightly as you thrust your hands,
			elbows and feet against her insides. The Raptor letting out a
			startled urp and yelp as she clutches her jostling belly as it
			gurgles and wobbles around with you inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="strugglecheck" text="try to make her spit you out" />

	</page>

	<check ID="strugglecheck">
		<test what="STRUGGLE" DC="10" />
		<outcome destination="struggleescape" />
		<outcome destination="struggledigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="struggleescape">
		<text>
			The raptor starts to look more and more distressed as you shove at her
			insides, unsettling her until finally she can take it no more.
			Doubling over on all fours as she noisily disgorges you back out of
			her belly, you land in a heap somewhat wetter than when you went in.
			The raptor girl looks dizzy and disorientated and nauseous after
			horking you back up, she shouldn't be an immediate threat.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="struggledigest">
		<text>
			The raptor starts to look more and more distressed as you shove at her
			insides, but while you're hard at work so is her belly. And soon
			you're in no fit state to struggle out of her, the gurgles and churns
			and glorps of her belly starting to replace the sound of your
			struggles and the yelps and hisses of her distress are replaced with
			the resumption of that pleased chirring. You've lost your final
			struggle, your body getting increasingly broken down by her gurgling
			gut. In time you can't even twitch, being digested down entirely as
			her gut rounds out into a smooth massive dome full of soupified
			remnants. The raptor girl chirring in delight and running her hands
			over the mass as her belly starts to compact and shrink down again,
			absorbing your nourishment and letting it course through her body.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="pleasure">
		<text>
			She's chirring, enjoying herself..maybe if she lost herself in the moment
			you could escape. You set about moving around in there, but not
			struggling more..rubbing, especially focusing your attention down
			below you. You hear her make a startled mip of delight as your
			rubbing begins to bear fruit, but mere pleasure won't be enough. It's
			time to see if your fingers are magic enough to bring her to orgasm
			from the inside.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasurecheck" text="magic hands, go" />
	</page>

	<check ID="pleasurecheck">
		<test what="PLEASURE" DC="12" />
		<outcome destination="pleasureescape" />
		<outcome destination="pleasuredigest" />
	</check>

	<page ID="pleasureescape">
		<text>
			The chirring moaning sounds are music to your ears, louder than the
			sound of her belly around you as one hand delves down past the bulge
			of her belly and into her naughtyness. The raptor sprawled out on her
			back as you rub her inside, her gut swaying back and forth
			rthythmically as you please her and she masturbates to the sensation.
			As things are getting increasingly hot inside her you reach your
			triumph, the raptor letting out a delighted cry and arching her back,
			thrusting her hips skywards and staining her own tail with femmecum.
			The opportunity as she bucks and shudders and slumps into afterglow
			too good to ignore, and the raptor acks and glucks as you force your
			way out of her during the relaxing post masturbatory slump. Leaving
			her flushed and sour on the ground, it'll take her a bit to
			recover..but she's not likely to treat you kindly for escaping her
			belly and spoiling her afterglow.
		</text>
		<choice destination="end" text="back away" />
		<effect type="heal" value="0.1" />
		<effect type="stunnpc" value="10" />
	</page>

	<page ID="pleasuredigest">
		<text>
			The chirring moaning sounds are music to your ears, louder than the
			sound of her belly around you as one hand delves down past the bulge
			of her belly and into her naughtyness. The raptor sprawled on her
			back, eyes closed and fingers busily working in bliss as you work to
			please her and her gut works on you. The glorping, moaning, gurgling
			and chirring all combining into a symphony of predatory bliss around
			you. As things get hot and you work with diminishing strength you
			reach your triumph, her pleasure rocking through her as the raptor
			girl arches her back and cries.. her tail staining with juices. Her
			full body spasm of delight pressing down on you as her belly
			contracts, squeezing you and forcing your semi digested form to give
			way. She slumps back in afterglow, but there'll be no escape for you.
			You've been here too long and the clench of her muscular stomach
			walls has left you unable to escape, you're in for the long haul now.
		</text>
		<choice destination="pleasureGO" text="get digested" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="pleasureGO">
		<text>
			You tried. You failed. But at least you gave the raptor demi a pleasing
			orgasm to remember you by as you succumb inside her. The raptor girl
			closing her eyes, resting her hands on the bulge of your diminishing
			form. Your shape steadily breaking down, gurgling away into soup
			inside her as she relaxes in afterglow. The raptor able to cherish
			the drawn out pleasurable sensations of her afterglow and the
			pleasure of digesting you as she lays there. Your form soon entirely
			liquid, compacting her belly under her fingers as you're absorbed
			into her. Her belly making little gurgles and burbles quietly as it
			trims back down, until you're utterly digested and not a trace of you
			remains, not even a bit of pudge on her middle that's as slim as it
			was before. All that will be left to remember you by is a saucy
			memory and a tingle of past pleasure for the raptor girl who'd
			claimed you.
		</text>
	</gameover>

	<page ID="submit">
		<text>
			As you settle in comfortably you realize the truth of your desire. To
			let this powerful, cunning and sexy predator claim you. The raptor
			chirrs and prods her belly curiously as you relax in its gurgling
			confines, puzzled perhaps by your lack of resistance. But after the
			effort of overcoming you she's not going to question a nice easy time
			digesting you too hard. You feel it as she rubs her belly, with each
			gurgle and glorp of her stomach around you you succumb a little more
			to her innards..yield a little more to her hands, weaken a little
			more such that even if you wanted to put up a fight it's too late
			now. You can feel yourself becoming one with her, starting to ease
			apart layer by layer.
		</text>
		<choice destination="submitGO" text="get digested" />
	</page>

	<gameover ID="submitGO">
		<text>
			The raptor girl remained seated and stroking, both of you losing track
			of time. Probably she can't put a finger on when you transitioned
			from digesting prey to nourishing soup within her but it happens all
			the same as your relaxed form breaks down and sloshes about. Her gut
			gradually turning round and smooth instead of bulgy and contoured and
			it shrinks back down. Your body given to her utterly, nothing more
			than fuel to nourish and sustain the predatory femme lizard. It's not
			perhaps the end that you could of foreseen, but it's the end you
			chose in the end.
		</text>
	</gameover>

</Conversation>